<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-12-24T06:22:07.251Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rashan Gary terrifies Lisa Salters by crashing postgame interview with Jordan Love]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686785</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/packers-rashan-gary-jump-scare-lisa-salters-interview.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T05:50:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lisa Salters has been a mainstay on Monday Night Football as a sideline reporter for over a decade. But on Monday, Salters was genuinely shaken in a way that you rarely see Salters shaken thanks to a very energetic Rashan Gary following the Packers’ win over the Saints. Viewers at home weren’t all that entertained Read more...
The post Rashan Gary terrifies Lisa Salters by crashing postgame interview with Jordan Love appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troy Aikman, Joe Buck call out CFP critics on ESPN]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686782</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/troy-aikman-joe-buck-cfp-critics.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T05:07:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Green Bay Packers were winding down a 34-0 win on Monday Night Football against the New Orleans Saints, ESPN announcers Joe Buck and Troy Aikman took some time to talk about the lopsided games that took place in the first round of the College Football Playoff. On the field, this season’s first four Read more...
The post Troy Aikman, Joe Buck call out CFP critics on ESPN appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NBA ref during strange sequence: ‘I f***** up’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686753</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/76ers-andre-drummond-ejection-jenna-schroeder-referee.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T04:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those who watched Monday night’s game between the San Antonio Spurs and Philadelphia 76ers saw an unusual sequence. Philadelphia’s Andre Drummond was ejected from the game and then quickly reinstated after the review. So, what happened? The referee who ejected Drummond messed up — something she acknowledged in slightly more colorful language. The ejection came Read more...
The post NBA ref during strange sequence: ‘I f***** up’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effectively Wild Episode 2261: Rickey Broke Records, and the Mold]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453419</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/effectively-wild-episode-2261-rickey-broke-records-and-the-mold/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T04:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Lindbergh and Meg Rowley discuss the career and life of Rickey Henderson, focusing on changes in public perceptions of his play and personality, how underrated he was (even though he was highly rated!), and his impact on the modern game and media, then (41:52) catch up on a flurry of transactions, including a run […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Lindbergh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Kelce, Scott Van Pelt, and Stanford Steve spread Christmas spirit on ‘Monday Night Countdown’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686723</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/jason-kelce-santa-week-16-monday-night-countdown.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T03:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Kelce has always played the part of a jolly individual since joining the ESPN Monday Night Countdown cast, frequently spending time at tailgates around the NFL this season. But on the Week 16 edition of Monday Night Countdown, which aired ahead of the Monday Night Football game between the New Orleans Saints and Green Bay Packers, Read more...
The post Jason Kelce, Scott Van Pelt, and Stanford Steve spread Christmas spirit on ‘Monday Night Countdown’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joel Klatt: ‘I remain incredibly frustrated and disappointed in the commentary regarding the CFP’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686693</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/fox-joel-klatt-cfp-commentary-frustrated-disappointed.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T02:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you went into the first round of the College Football Playoff expecting close games, then you were no doubt disappointed by the opening weekend. But if you went into the first round of the College Football Playoff expecting close games, Joel Klatt isn’t sure why. Klatt, Fox’s lead college football analyst, has heard the Read more...
The post Joel Klatt: ‘I remain incredibly frustrated and disappointed in the commentary regarding the CFP’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fox color analyst Jonathan Vilma calls for Aaron Rodgers to retire: ‘I want to remember the greatness of that guy’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686632</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/jonathan-vilma-calls-for-aaron-rodgers-retirement.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T01:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fox NFL color analyst Jonathan Vilma understands as well as anyone what it takes to perform at the highest level in the NFL. And unfortunately, Vilma seems to believe that it would be best for the legacy of New York Jets quarterback Aaron Rodgers to call it a career before his skills diminish even further. Read more...
The post Fox color analyst Jonathan Vilma calls for Aaron Rodgers to retire: ‘I want to remember the greatness of that guy’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Wall is reportedly experimenting as a broadcaster]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686662</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/john-wall-makes-broadcast-debut-g-league-winter-showcase.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When athletes are in the twilight of their career, it’s sometimes difficult to know exactly when to hang it up. And for five-time NBA All-Star John Wall, that moment has come a bit full circle. This time last year, Wall was playing in the G League Winter Showcase hoping to find his way back onto Read more...
The post John Wall is reportedly experimenting as a broadcaster appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN cannot stop calling Fresno State the ‘Bulldongs’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686626</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/cannot-stop-calling-fresno-state-bulldongs.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T00:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bowl season is well underway, and the Famous Idaho Potato Bowl was Monday’s main event. Northern Illinois and Fresno State faced off on Boise State’s iconic blue turf field. And those watching the game were in for an unfortunate, if not fairly humorous error from the ESPN graphics department. The full Fresno State Bulldongs experience Read more...
The post ESPN cannot stop calling Fresno State the ‘Bulldongs’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lamar Jackson plans to watch Beyoncé at halftime Christmas Day: ‘Sorry, Harbaugh’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686603</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/lamar-jackson-beyonce-halftime-christmas-day.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T00:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever big halftime speech John Harbaugh might be planning for Christmas Day, Lamar Jackson doesn’t want to hear it. Netflix has a star-studded cast of teams and announcers for its first ever NFL broadcast on Christmas Day. And even though Jackson will be playing in one of those games Wednesday afternoon, the Ravens quarterback is Read more...
The post Lamar Jackson plans to watch Beyoncé at halftime Christmas Day: ‘Sorry, Harbaugh’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[College Football Playoff viewership strong for ESPN, mediocre for TNT]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686639</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/first-round-playoff-viewership-strong-espn-mediocre-tnt.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T23:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preliminary viewership figures are in for the inaugural first round of the College Football Playoff. And as expected, ESPN’s games performed quite well while TNT’s fell victim to some stiff competition from the NFL. According to Nielsen’s fast national measurements, as reported by ESPN, Saturday night’s Tennessee-Ohio State first round College Football Playoff matchup averaged Read more...
The post College Football Playoff viewership strong for ESPN, mediocre for TNT appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers wonders if Adam Schefter engages in ‘quid pro quo’ relationships for scoops]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686579</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/aaron-rodgers-adam-schefter-quid-pro-quo.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T23:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the New York Jets continue to leak like a sieve, Aaron Rodgers wonders if NFL insiders like Adam Schefter are in the business of making trades for information. It seems like there’s a new embarrassing story about the Jets almost on a weekly basis. During an atypical Monday afternoon appearance on The Pat McAfee Read more...
The post Aaron Rodgers wonders if Adam Schefter engages in ‘quid pro quo’ relationships for scoops appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Herbstreit defends ‘lunatic fringe’ comments, mentions Ryan Day needs 24/7 armed security]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686597</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/kirk-herbstreit-defends-lunatic-fringe-comments-mentions-ryan-day-hires-armed-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T22:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a week it has been for ESPN college football analyst Kirk Herbstreit. The longtime College GameDay panelist has faced a mountain of criticism in recent days surrounding comments he’s made about the Ohio State football fanbase, particularly in relation to head coach Ryan Day. During the Buckeyes’ convincing win over Tennessee on Saturday in Read more...
The post Kirk Herbstreit defends ‘lunatic fringe’ comments, mentions Ryan Day needs 24/7 armed security appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2025 Royals Free Agent Rankings]]></title>
        <id>https://farmtofountains.com/?p=6635</id>
        <link href="https://farmtofountains.com/2025-royals-free-agent-rankings/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=2025-royals-free-agent-rankings"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T22:09:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who are the remaining MLB Free Agents? Should the Royals have any interest? A list of the notable free agents and signings is included below for easy tracking! Check out notable free agent options our team has deemed a good option for Kansas City to consider this offseason. Top 30 Available Free Agents for the […]
The post 2025 Royals Free Agent Rankings appeared first on Farm to Fountains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Farr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Clark continues beef with Aaron Rodgers: ‘He has an issue with people talking about his play’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686552</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/ryan-clark-continues-beef-aaron-rodgers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T22:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers knew what he was doing when he went on The Pat McAfee Show in early December and knocked ESPN for its indulgence in personality-driven, athlete-hosted content over classics like SportsCenter. But so far, Ryan Clark has been the only ESPN talent with the stomach to stand up against the crotchety, washed-up quarterback. Perhaps that’s because Read more...
The post Ryan Clark continues beef with Aaron Rodgers: ‘He has an issue with people talking about his play’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen A. Smith expresses regret over voting for Democrats]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686551</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/politics/stephen-a-smith-voting-regrets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T21:45:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen A. Smith is moving the goalposts regarding his political affiliation(s) — again. The First Take star, who’s never been shy about his support for Kamala Harris and his disdain for Donald Trump, is now questioning whether he should’ve ever voted for Democrats in the first place. Smith, who labels himself as an Independent, walks Read more...
The post Stephen A. Smith expresses regret over voting for Democrats appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL flexes Cowboys out of national window in favor of Packers-Vikings]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686549</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/flex-cowboys-out-national-window-packers-vikings.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T21:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFL has made a schedule swap in the penultimate week of the regular season. According to ESPN NFL insider Adam Schefter, the league is flexing the Dallas Cowboys-Philadelphia Eagles game out of the 4:25 p.m. ET national window slot on Fox in favor of the Green Bay Packers-Minnesota Vikings game originally scheduled for the Read more...
The post NFL flexes Cowboys out of national window in favor of Packers-Vikings appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keith Hernandez shares secret behind Mets booth’s chemistry]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686527</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/keith-hernandez-sny-david-samson.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T20:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone seems to be trying to recreate the magic in the booth that the New York Mets and SNY have perfected, but no one can truly replicate it. David Samson, former president of the Miami Marlins and current Meadowlark Media personality, admitted as much to Keith Hernandez during a recent episode of his Nothing Personal Read more...
The post Keith Hernandez shares secret behind Mets booth’s chemistry appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Takes What He Can Get]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177133</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/elon-musk-takes-what-he-can-get"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T20:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday of last week, the richest person in the world seized control of the government of the United States. It's going to be helpful, over the next four years, to note down the events that happen, when they happen, before the next events come along.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Olsen feuds with Eagles fans after bashing offensive performance without Jalen Hurts]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686509</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/greg-olsen-feuds-philadelphia-eagles-fans-jalen-hurts-injury.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T20:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Olsen and Joe Davis had the Fox call of perhaps the most consequential Sunday game of NFL Week 16, as the Washington Commanders upset the Philadelphia Eagles at home and stayed alive in the NFC East. Beyond the result of the game, the NFC postseason picture was scrambled as Eagles star quarterback Jalen Hurts Read more...
The post Greg Olsen feuds with Eagles fans after bashing offensive performance without Jalen Hurts appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Racing With Mortality In Norman Maclean’s ‘Young Men And Fire’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177064</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/racing-with-mortality-in-norman-macleans-young-men-and-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T19:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rachelle Hampton: Can I just say I’m so honored to be taking part in my very first DRAB? This was one of the series I was most jealous of before I joined Defector because it seemed so fun. That maybe makes it even funnier that the very first book I suggested (and the one we ended up choosing) is the biggest bummer DRAB has ever seen.
I first came across Young Men And Fire in a McNally Jackson earlier this year; I remember my attention being caught by the promise of an in-depth look at the Smokejumpers, who I’d been sort of lowkey obsessed with since reading Nora Roberts’ Chasing Fire. I’d never heard of the Mann Gulch fire or Norman Maclean really, though I realized after we picked this book that he also wrote A River Runs Through It, which I’ve seen the movie adaptation of. All to say, I was pretty stoked when y’all agreed to read it. What piqued y’alls interest?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Cris Collinsworth stays off social media after games: ‘It hits you like a ton of bricks’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686495</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/cris-collinsworth-social-media-bricks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T19:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now, here’s a guy that doesn’t check social media… Even though Cris Collinsworth is one of the most beloved announcers in the NFL and is a content machine for us at Awful Announcing on Sunday nights — both good and bad — he doesn’t want to see how he’s being perceived. That’s why when it Read more...
The post Why Cris Collinsworth stays off social media after games: ‘It hits you like a ton of bricks’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPNers pay tribute to late colleague Zach Jones, dead at 41]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686476</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/zach-jones-stats-information-dead-41.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T19:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN shared some tragic news during Monday’s episode of SportsCenter. Just a few days before Christmas, the network announced that research manager Zach Jones, who joined ESPN in 2010, had died at the age of 41. Jones, who is survived by his wife, Amber, and his son, Silas, had been a Stats and Information team Read more...
The post ESPNers pay tribute to late colleague Zach Jones, dead at 41 appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen A. Smith on broken relationship with Skip Bayless: ‘We can’t vibe’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686428</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/podcasts/stephen-a-smith-relationship-skip-bayless.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T18:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the relationship between Stephen A. Smith and Skip Bayless is ever going to be repaired, Smith believes it’s on Bayless to make the next move. Bayless has mostly maintained a positive relationship with Smith since he parted ways with ESPN and First Take in 2016. But in recent years, that relationship has faltered, with Read more...
The post Stephen A. Smith on broken relationship with Skip Bayless: ‘We can’t vibe’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Khan confirms end of AEW Rampage ‘for the foreseeable future’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686414</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/aew/tony-khan-confirms-end-rampage-foreseeable-future.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T18:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When AEW first announced its new media rights deal, it didn’t include any news regarding the future of AEW Rampage. And with that new deal set to go into effect at the start of the new year, it appears that the weekly TNT program is nearing its end, with AEW owner and president Tony Khan Read more...
The post Tony Khan confirms end of AEW Rampage ‘for the foreseeable future’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Things We Saw In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176589</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-best-things-we-saw-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T17:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is what the Defector staff saw and enjoyed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL flags and celebrates Vikings’ ‘Camp Rock’ celebration on social media]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686426</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/vikings-camp-rock-celebration-penalty.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T17:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s peak NFL irony. Do as I say, not as I do. The league is celebrating the very moments it loves to punish. The latest example? Camryn Bynum and the Minnesota Vikings’ choreographed line dance after a big play — a celebration so perfectly timed it became a social media sensation. Vikings really hit the Read more...
The post NFL flags and celebrates Vikings’ ‘Camp Rock’ celebration on social media appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rupert Murdoch’s News Corp makes major sale to DAZN]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686419</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/dazn/rupert-murdoch-news-corp-major-sale-dazn-foxtel.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T17:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did the first shoe just drop on the future of Rupert Murdoch’s media empire? According to multiple reports, Murdoch’s News Corp has agreed to sell Foxtel, its Australian cable television business, to the prominent sports streaming platform DAZN. The deal is worth $2.1 billion and allows News Corp to maintain a 6% stake in the Read more...
The post Rupert Murdoch’s News Corp makes major sale to DAZN appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JAWS and the 2025 Hall of Fame Ballot: Dustin Pedroia]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453403</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/jaws-and-the-2025-hall-of-fame-ballot-dustin-pedroia/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A knee injury curtailed a career that might have carried the undersized second baseman to Cooperstown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Jaffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liverpool Has The Premier League In A Stranglehold]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177051</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/liverpool-has-the-premier-league-in-a-stranglehold"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T16:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's start with a flaw. Liverpool's defense is still the best in the Premier League, having allowed 13 goals in 15 matches entering Sunday's trip to North London for a match against often-feisty but currently-shambolic Tottenham Hotspur. Virgil van Dijk is back to world-beating form, and his various partners in the center—often Ibrahima Konaté, though not for the past two months, thanks to a knee injury—have been competent enough to lead the league in goals against. However, there have been some cracks showing, and Liverpool's two previous league matches saw that dominant defense give up five combined goals to Newcastle and Fulham.
Both of those matches ended in draws, only the third and fourth blemishes in Liverpool's league season so far, and though it is unfair to put the entirety of the blame on the defense, it certainly didn't help. And so, if one were to look at just how many goals Liverpool gave up on Sunday against Tottenham, it would read like another bad day at the office for van Dijk and co. Thankfully, soccer is played in both directions, and Tottenham's three goals on its home ground only felt like feeble attempts at holding off the siege that was Liverpool's high-line-abusing attack, which scored six goals but probably could have scored 10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to Bryce Young, sports media has egg on its face]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686378</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/bryce-young-sports-media-write-off.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T16:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe we should’ve held off on writing those think pieces about Bryce Young being done in Carolina. His NFL career was prematurely declared a cautionary tale as those in sports media piled on as if the ink had dried on Young’s NFL obituary. Just a handful of games into his second season in the league, Read more...
The post When it comes to Bryce Young, sports media has egg on its face appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shannon Sharpe warns Kirk Herbstreit after ‘First Take’ criticism: ‘Don’t play with me’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686434</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/stephen-a-smith-responds-kirk-herbstreit.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T16:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All things considered, Stephen A. Smith took a fairly diplomatic approach while replying to Kirk Herbstreit’s criticism of First Take. The same, however, can’t be said for Shannon Sharpe. Two days after ESPN’s top college football analyst took aim at the network’s morning debate show for its criticism of Ohio State head coach Ryan Day, Read more...
The post Shannon Sharpe warns Kirk Herbstreit after ‘First Take’ criticism: ‘Don’t play with me’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Dec. 23: Parting Ways]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177052</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-dec-23-parting-ways"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get your head in the game—it's time to solve the Monday crossword. This week’s puzzle was constructed by Jesse Cohn and Hoang-Kim Vu. Jesse, an oncology consultant, lives in Austin, Texas with his family and his derpy dog, and has been dunked on by two NBA players. Kim works in global public health in Washington, D.C., and is a member of the crossword editing team at Defector and AVCX. His puzzles have appeared in numerous outlets, including the New York Times, Los Angeles Times, and USA Today. 
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nate Burleson: Travis Hunter and fiancée ‘can’t complain’ about attention]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686402</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/cbs/nate-burleson-travis-hunter-and-fiancee-cant-complain-about-attention.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T15:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the weeks following Travis Hunter winning the Heisman Trophy, everyone seems to have an opinion about the Colorado star’s relationship with his fiancée, Leanna Lenee. That includes Nate Burleson, who told TMZ that the couple only has itself to blame for the amount of attention it’s received in recent weeks. “It’s their business. And Read more...
The post Nate Burleson: Travis Hunter and fiancée ‘can’t complain’ about attention appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Got Inside Tyson Fury’s Head For A Change]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177045</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/oleksandr-usyk-got-inside-tyson-furys-head"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T15:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tyson Fury once broke an opponent’s spirit with a story. He was set to fight Wladimir Klitschko, who’d been in possession of at least one major heavyweight belt for a full decade, looking near invincible throughout his run. Few expected Fury to do much before getting knocked out. Then, in a sit-down face-off, Fury recounted a tale of a long-ago training camp in which he outlasted Klitschko in a sauna, making it out to be a battle of wills. Just before Fury revealed that Klitschko departed the hot box first, Wlad gulped like somebody was holding him at gunpoint. Fury was equally effective in the ring, so bamboozling Klitschko with feints and twitches that the longtime champion seemingly forgot to throw punches. Fury won, then rubbed a tub of salt into the wound by serenading his wife with a harrowing version of Aerosmith’s “I Don’t Want To Miss a Thing.” Klitschko stood feet away, perhaps daydreaming of new career paths and better singers.
Fury figured never to meet an opponent he couldn’t out-talk. He approached the brash knockout artist Deontay Wilder with a furious torrent of psychological warfare, then knocked him out twice in their trilogy. He surely has said the word “dosser” more than any other boxer, or Earth resident. He could be at turns nasty, earnest, bigoted, kind, or silent, but he inevitably snuck into his foes’ heads and mangled their brains before he even started punching them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Owen Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Mild week with bigger changes ahead (MON-12/23)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3767671</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-mild-week-with-bigger-changes-ahead-mon-12-23/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T15:20:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mild weather will continue for the rest of the year. There are signs of changes coming through to start 2025 and stronger signs of much colder air coming down from Canada and elsewhere to be a big player in returning to not only cold but occasional snow chances as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN’s College Football Playoff coverage makes for a miserable, negative experience]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686252</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/college-football-playoff-coverage-miserable-herbstreit.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T15:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[College campuses hosted FBS playoff games for the first time this weekend. But instead of celebrating the first-of-its-kind matchups and incredible scenes, ESPN spent the entire weekend bashing schools, criticizing fans, and generally making it a miserable experience. It started Friday night when Cinderella Story Indiana played Notre Dame in the first playoff game in Read more...
The post ESPN’s College Football Playoff coverage makes for a miserable, negative experience appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Play-By-Play: Reviewing the best and worst of 2024 with the Awfulies]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686398</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/podcasts/the-play-by-play-reviewing-2024-awfulies.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T14:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s time for another episode of The Play-By-Play, Awful Announcing’s weekly sports media news podcast. On the latest episode, Awful Announcing managing editor Sean Keeley joins Ben Axelrod and Brendon Kleen to review the 2024 Awfulies, including the following awards: Person of the Year Best and worst moments Best personalities Best and worst in television Best Read more...
The post The Play-By-Play: Reviewing the best and worst of 2024 with the Awfulies appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Donutology’s Andrew Cameron]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866008</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-donutologys-andrew-cameron/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T14:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Andrew Cameron By and large, donuts are one of the nation’s most popular treats. Even though 10 billion are consumed annually, they often have a one-size-fits-all mentality.  That is until Andrew Cameron came along. He believed that donuts deserved a glow-up, and that’s exactly what he set out to do when he opened Donutology back in 2016. He designed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supersizing ‘Pardon the Interruption’ would be a mistake]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=682726</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/pardon-interruption-60-minutes-mistake.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T14:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bigger isn’t necessarily better. That belief could be tested if ESPN drastically changes the format of one of its most popular shows, Pardon the Interruption. Brace yourself for a supersized PTI. According to Andrew Marchand at The Athletic, ESPN is considering expanding Pardon The Interruption to one hour. Since its inception in 2001, the granddaddy Read more...
The post Supersizing ‘Pardon the Interruption’ would be a mistake appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Grant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector’s Favorite Sports Moments Of 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176562</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/favorite-sports-moments-of-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T13:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are the sports moments from 2024 that the Defector staff enjoyed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Microsoft Calendar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139971</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-microsoft-calendar/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T13:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Calendar is a personal calendar application which offers synchronization with various calendar services. We recommend the best free and open source alternatives.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Microsoft Calendar appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin O’Connell jokingly critiques Justin Jefferson’s Griddy celebration]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686276</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/kevin-oconnell-justin-jefferson-griddy-celebration.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T13:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minnesota Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell offered some good advice for star wide receiver Justin Jefferson Sunday. Watch where you Griddy. Jefferson got flagged for taunting after doing his iconic Griddy touchdown celebration against the Seattle Seahawks, the first time he’s been penalized for doing that familiar dance. O’Connell could be seen questioning an official Read more...
The post Kevin O’Connell jokingly critiques Justin Jefferson’s Griddy celebration appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL Network reportedly ‘undecided’ on future ‘RedZone’ advertising]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686275</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/network-undecided-redzone-advertising.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T13:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week 16’s edition of NFL RedZone was back to its usual ad-free self on Sunday, much to the delight of fans across the country. Viewers weren’t so sure that would be the case after host Scott Hanson used the updated version of his signature catchphrase on Sunday, beginning the show by saying “Seven hours of Read more...
The post NFL Network reportedly ‘undecided’ on future ‘RedZone’ advertising appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 23, 2024: how to watch MNF tonight]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686198</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/viewing-picks/december-23-2024-watch-mnf-tonight.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T12:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All Times Eastern Bundesliga Bundesliga Special Show #11-Seasonal Special: Midseason Review I + II — ESPN+, 5:30 p.m. College Basketball Men’s Aquinas at Bowling Green — ESPN+, 3 p.m. Middle Tennessee at Tennessee — SEC Network, 7 p.m. Cal State-Bakersfield at North Dakota State — WDAY Xtra/WDAZ Xtra/Summit League Network, 8 p.m. Seattle at Washington Read more...
The post TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 23, 2024: how to watch MNF tonight appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hop – terminal based file explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139967</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/hop-terminal-based-file-explorer/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T11:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hop is a terminal based file explorer designed to be fast, simple and user friendly. Hop runs on any operating system.
The post Hop – terminal based file explorer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guest rec from Illuminati Hotties]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/guest-recs-from-illuminati-hotties</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/guest-recs-from-illuminati-hotties"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T08:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we have a guest recommendation from Sarah Tudzin, the American producer and frontwoman of illuminati hotties and author of IH In Motion. Her new album, POWER, is available now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Tudzin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pages CMS – content management system for static site generators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139962</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pages-cms-content-management-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T07:39:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pages CMS is a content management system for GitHub. It is well suited for static site generators (e.g. Jekyll, Next.js, VuePress, Hugo).
The post Pages CMS – content management system for static site generators appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cris Collinsworth lauds Dallas DBs: ‘This may be one of the best games out of a secondary I’ve ever seen’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686369</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nbc/cris-collinsworth-cowboys-secondary-snf-win.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T05:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While they were eliminated from playoff contention earlier in the day, the Dallas Cowboys finished the day on a positive note with a 26-24 win over the Tampa Bay Buccaneers. Cris Collinsworth, who was called the Sunday Night Football game on NBC, was impressed with one part of Dallas’ team, in particular. Despite trailing for Read more...
The post Cris Collinsworth lauds Dallas DBs: ‘This may be one of the best games out of a secondary I’ve ever seen’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[D Roll]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3028/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3028/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cris Collinsworth talked about Mike McCarthy’s job security, Jerry Jones’ mindset on ‘SNF’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686306</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/cris-collinsworth-cowboys-jerry-jones-mike-mccarthy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T04:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things have not gone well for the Dallas Cowboys in 2024. While they won Week 16’s Sunday Night Football game against the Tampa Bay Buccaneers, they were officially eliminated from playoff contention earlier in the day. But while the postseason is no longer an option, Cris Collinsworth noted that the remainder of the season will Read more...
The post Cris Collinsworth talked about Mike McCarthy’s job security, Jerry Jones’ mindset on ‘SNF’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Tirico blasts lax enforcement of delay of game: ‘I can’t stand that rule’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686330</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nbc/mike-tirico-blasts-lax-enforcement-delay-game.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T04:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not often you hear a play-by-play announcer interrupt himself to blast a league rule, but NBC Sports’ Mike Tirico went there Sunday night. Early in the third quarter of the Tampa Bay Buccaneers-Dallas Cowboys matchup on Sunday Night Football, the Bucs ran a play after the play clock appeared to expire. “Off in time,” Read more...
The post Mike Tirico blasts lax enforcement of delay of game: ‘I can’t stand that rule’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers on Jets teammates: ‘We can really see who’s on board’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686255</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/aaron-rodgers-calls-out-jets-teammates.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T03:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Jets lost again Sunday, leading to some cryptic postgame comments from Aaron Rodgers. After losing to the Los Angeles Rams, 19-9, Rodgers seemed to hint that some of his teammates had quit. The veteran quarterback didn’t use that exact phrase, but reading between the lines, one could sense he thinks some of Read more...
The post Aaron Rodgers on Jets teammates: ‘We can really see who’s on board’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bucs’ WR Sterling Shepard’s daughters announce his college during ‘SNF’ player intros]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686266</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/sterling-shepard-daughters-player-introductions-snf.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T02:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFL players have gotten increasingly creative during games where they narrate their own player introductions. This is particularly true when it comes to a player’s college. Tampa Bay Buccaneers receiver Sterling Shepard did that during Sunday night’s game against the Dallas Cowboys — but not in a way we’ve seen before. When identifying their alma Read more...
The post Bucs’ WR Sterling Shepard’s daughters announce his college during ‘SNF’ player intros appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas on Repeat]]></title>
        <id>https://tedium.co/2024/12/22/christmas-nostalgia-psychology/</id>
        <link href="https://feed.tedium.co/link/15204/16926317/christmas-nostalgia-psychology"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T01:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas nostalgia is a hell of a drug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ernie Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat McAfee: NFL needs better flex scheduling to weed out ‘crahp’ games]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686200</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/pat-mcafee-gameday-morning-flex-scheduling-crap-games.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T01:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pat McAfee said Sunday he believes the NFL needs better flex scheduling to weed out some of the “crahp” late-season football games involving non-contenders. McAfee also must still believe in Santa, because he framed his criticism in the form of a request to “that fat man.” On NFL GameDay Morning, McAfee ran down his “Pat’s Read more...
The post Pat McAfee: NFL needs better flex scheduling to weed out ‘crahp’ games appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crumbl Bakes New Chocolate Cake, Salted Caramel Pretzel Pie, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.brandeating.com/2024/12/crumbl-new-chocolate-cake-salted-caramel-pretzel-pie-more.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.brandeating.com/2024/12/crumbl-new-chocolate-cake-salted-caramel-pretzel-pie-more.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crumbl bakes a trio of new desserts, including Chocolate Cake and Salted Caramel Pretzel Pie, as part of this week's limited-time lineup of desserts.

Here's the full lineup of desserts at Crumbl bakeries nationwide for the week ending December 28, 2024:


New Chocolate Cake - A two-layered chocolate cake with semi-sweet chocolate ganache, topped with fudge frosting.
New Salted Caramel Pretzel Pie Cookie - A chilled buttery pie cookie baked with pretzel pieces, topped with caramel, a dollop of caramel mousse, and more pretzel pieces.
New No-Bake Raspberry Cheesecake - Cheesecake pie filling served on a buttery graham crust, topped with a tart house-made raspberry jam.
Cinnamon Roll Cookie - A warm vanilla sugar cookie topped with cinnamon streusel and vanilla cream cheese frosting.
Peppermint Cupcake Cookie - A warm chocolate cookies & cream cookie topped with peppermint cream cheese frosting and a sprinkle of candy cane pieces.
Peanut Butter Munch Cookie - A warm peanut butter cookie topped with milk chocolate, peanut butter-coated cereal pieces, and powdered sugar.
Gingersnap Cookie - A warm gingersnap cookie coated with sugar crystals and featuring the flavors of molasses, brown sugar, cinnamon, and ginger.
Semi-sweet Chocolate Chunk Cookie - A warm cookie filled with semi-sweet chocolate chunks.


Photo via Crumbl.
Read more at Brand Eating!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brand Eating. Your Daily Fast Food Reading.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcers befuddled at Doug Pederson timeout call: ‘I don’t understand that at all’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686230</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/cbs/announcers-befuddled-doug-pederson-timeout-call-i-dont-understand-that-at-all.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T00:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2024 has not been a year to remember for Jacksonville Jaguars head coach Doug Pederson. And in one of the least appealing games of the day with Perderson’s Jags taking on the lowly Las Vegas Raiders, a weird timeout call by Pederson had the CBS broadcast crew of Andrew Catalon, Tiki Barber, and Jason McCourty Read more...
The post Announcers befuddled at Doug Pederson timeout call: ‘I don’t understand that at all’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Davis criticized for underplaying Jalen Hurts injury during Eagles-Commanders]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686195</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/joe-davis-criticized-underplaying-jalen-hurts-injury-eagles-commanders.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T00:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFC East rivalry between the Philadelphia Eagles and Washington Commanders proved to be a thriller early on Sunday afternoon. Unfortunately, the game hit a snag in the first quarter when star Eagles quarterback Jalen Hurts exited the game with a concussion and was replaced by former Pittsburgh Steelers quarterback Kenny Pickett. The Eagles backup Read more...
The post Joe Davis criticized for underplaying Jalen Hurts injury during Eagles-Commanders appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fox’s Mark Sanchez shouts out CBS rules analyst Gene Steratore]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686188</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/mark-sanchez-shoutout-cbs-rules-analyst-gene-steratore.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T23:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since 2021, Mark Sanchez has been calling NFL games for Fox. So when he decided to mention CBS rules analyst Gene Steratore on Sunday, it led to a bit of an awkward moment with his broadcast partner Adam Amin. On the call for the Week 16 matchup between the Minnesota Vikings and the Seattle Seahawks, Read more...
The post Fox’s Mark Sanchez shouts out CBS rules analyst Gene Steratore appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NBC expertly covered Charlie Woods’ first career hole-in-one at PNC Championship]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686146</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nbc/golf-channel-coverage-charlie-woods-first-hole-in-one.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T22:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tiger Woods has been the most beloved figure in golf for the better part of the last three decades. But on Sunday at the PNC Championship it was his son, Charlie Woods, who stole headlines after making his first-ever hole-in-one. For those unaware of how the PNC Championship works, it is a 36-hole scramble tournament Read more...
The post NBC expertly covered Charlie Woods’ first career hole-in-one at PNC Championship appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FS1 analyst on Lions’ fake fumble touchdown: ‘Coolest offensive play design I’ve ever seen’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686158</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/fs1-analyst-lions-fake-fumble-touchdown.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T22:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes the creativity of NFL play designers surprise even those whose job it is to breakdown football on television. And when Detroit Lions offensive coordinator Ben Johnson dialed up a sweet trick play for a touchdown against the Chicago Bears on Sunday, FS1 analyst and co-host of The Facility Emmanuel Acho took to social media Read more...
The post FS1 analyst on Lions’ fake fumble touchdown: ‘Coolest offensive play design I’ve ever seen’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jhon Durán Can’t Stop Putting Goals On Film]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177025</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jhon-duran-cant-stop-putting-goals-on-film"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T22:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Such is the strength of the hellish vortex Manchester City is presently trapped in—Saturday's loss at Aston Villa gives the Mancs just one win from their last 12—that you almost have to start taking performances against them with a pinch of salt. City has shat the bed so regularly, keeping just one clean sheet over this stretch of misery, that it's risky to read too much into what otherwise might appear to be a statement win against the Citizens. For proof of this notion, look no further than Tottenham.
With that in mind, when you look at the scoresheet from that 2-1 Villa win and see Jhon Durán's name there, you may be tempted to discount what the goal says about the forward's talent. This would be a mistake, because Durán is scoring all the time, against everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2025 Royals Top Prospects: Q&A]]></title>
        <id>https://farmtofountains.com/?p=6619</id>
        <link href="https://farmtofountains.com/2025-royals-top-prospects-qa/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=2025-royals-top-prospects-qa"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T22:11:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this week, a look at the updated Royals Top Prospects for 2025 dropped. Alongside the new list, it’s a great chance to answer questions or comments received from X. It’s one of my favorite elements of dropping any new list simply because it gives a chance to give more insight behind some of the […]
The post 2025 Royals Top Prospects: Q&A appeared first on Farm to Fountains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Farr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Vick gets emotional talking Norfolk State job on ‘Fox NFL Kickoff’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686131</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/michael-vick-emotional-talking-norfolk-state-job.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T21:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cast of a television show can often start to feel like family given the amount of time spent together. That was very apparent on Sunday’s episode of Fox NFL Kickoff. Since calling it a career in 2017, four-time Pro Bowl quarterback Michael Vick has served as a studio analyst for Fox where he has Read more...
The post Michael Vick gets emotional talking Norfolk State job on ‘Fox NFL Kickoff’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Hanson accidentally says ‘dick’ on ‘NFL RedZone’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686113</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/scott-hanson-accidentally-says-dick-on-nfl-redzone.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T21:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Hanson has become quite accustomed to smoothly jumping from highlight to highlight from each game each Sunday. But even he isn’t immune from the rare on-air hiccup, which he showed on the Week 16 NFL RedZone broadcast. NFL RedZone has, of course, received criticism over the past week after the program broke its long-standing Read more...
The post Scott Hanson accidentally says ‘dick’ on ‘NFL RedZone’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lou Merloni, Will Flemming set for increased Red Sox broadcasting roles]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686059</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/lou-merloni-will-flemming-red-sox-roles.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T20:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It looks like the Boston Red Sox TV and radio booths are set for some changes in 2025. In 2024, the TV broadcasts on NESN were helmed by play-by-play voices Dave O’Brien (primary) and Mike Monaco, with a rotating group of analysts including Lou Merloni, Will Middlebrooks, Kevin Millar, and Kevin Youkilis. On the radio Read more...
The post Lou Merloni, Will Flemming set for increased Red Sox broadcasting roles appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13 Best Free and Open Source Linux Clocks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=5847</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/clocks/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T19:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The clocks featured in this article are more sophisticated than the basic tray clock.
The post 13 Best Free and Open Source Linux Clocks appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blaze UI – framework-free UI toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139953</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/blaze-ui-framework-free-ui-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T19:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blaze UI provides structure for building websites quickly with a scalable and maintainable foundation.
The post Blaze UI – framework-free UI toolkit appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deepin Picker – simple color picker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139951</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/deepin-picker-simple-color-picker/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T19:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deepin Picker is billed as the simplest color picker.
The post Deepin Picker – simple color picker appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ohio State’s Jeremiah Smith kept receipts for Pro Football Focus after win over Tennessee]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686060</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/ohio-state-jeremiah-smith-pro-football-focus-social-media-post.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T19:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ohio State was able to take care of business in comfortable fashion in their First Round matchup in the CFP against Tennessee. But for Ohio State star Jeremiah Smith, the win wasn’t quite enough, taking to social media after the game to mock Pro Football Focus over their hypothetical question about Smith’s matchup with Tennessee Read more...
The post Ohio State’s Jeremiah Smith kept receipts for Pro Football Focus after win over Tennessee appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat McAfee: ‘I would like to be done with anonymous sources in the NFL.’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686105</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/pat-mcafee-ian-rapoport-anonymous-sources.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T19:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There have been a lot of people who have complained about anonymous sources in sports over the years. One of the most recent is ESPN host and commentator Pat McAfee, who did so in a guest appearance on NFL Network’s NFL GameDay Morning Sunday. There, McAfee said his Christmas wish would be for Santa to deliver an end Read more...
The post Pat McAfee: ‘I would like to be done with anonymous sources in the NFL.’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The College Football Playoff’s Shitty First Weekend Did Its Job]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177020</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-college-football-playoffs-shitty-first-weekend-did-its-job"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T18:48:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The College Football Playoff is a wild hit so far, in that everyone hates it. Notre Dame beat Indiana Friday in a spectacular nothingburger that turned out to be the closest game of the weekend, and the three Saturday games were the competitive equivalent of Week 2 bodybag games decided by an aggregate score of 118-51. Even the gambling conglomerates were screaming and flipping off their gigantic monitors.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=09BXg7fhijA]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Hanson’s NFL RedZone ‘commercial-free football’ intro absent, prompting mass dismay (updated)]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686096</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/redzone-statement-scott-hanson-intro.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T18:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most universally disliked broadcasting changes in a while came last Sunday when NFL RedZone broke from their long trend of “commercial-free football” to show ads. That drew massive backlash for the league, the show, and host Scott Hanson, who opened the show with his usual “seven hours of commercial-free football” despite the Read more...
The post Scott Hanson’s NFL RedZone ‘commercial-free football’ intro absent, prompting mass dismay (updated) appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL RedZone is again running ads, prompting mass dismay]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686096</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/redzone-is-again-running-commercials.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T18:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most universally disliked broadcasting changes in a while came last Sunday when NFL RedZone broke from their long trend of “commercial-free football” to show ads. That drew massive backlash for the league, the show, and host Scott Hanson, who opened the show with his usual “seven hours of commercial-free football” despite the Read more...
The post NFL RedZone is again running ads, prompting mass dismay appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Herbstreit’s criticism of Ohio State fans has lost the plot]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686044</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/kirk-herbstreits-criticism-ohio-state-fans-lost-the-plot.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T18:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Ohio State put the finishing touches on its blowout victory over Tennessee in the first round of the College Football Playoff on Saturday, the Buckeyes’ fanbase found itself fending off a potshot. Only it didn’t come from any of the players on the field or the thousands of orange-wearing fans in the stands, but Read more...
The post Kirk Herbstreit’s criticism of Ohio State fans has lost the plot appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Lesmerises blasts ‘wounded’ Kirk Herbstreit’s Ohio State comments: ‘He turns everything on fans’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686045</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/doug-lesmerises-blasts-kirk-herbstreit-lunatic-fringe-ohio-state.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T17:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ohio State Buckeyes’ 42-17 win over the Tennessee Volunteers in the first round of the College Football Playoff Saturday sparked a lot of discussion. Some of that came from analyst Kirk Herbstreit’s remarks on the ABC/ESPN broadcast, which included going after what he called the “lunatic fringe” of Buckeyes’ fans (as well as ESPN’s Read more...
The post Doug Lesmerises blasts ‘wounded’ Kirk Herbstreit’s Ohio State comments: ‘He turns everything on fans’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rickey Henderson Believed In Rickey Henderson]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177017</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rickey-henderson-believed-in-rickey-henderson"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T15:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arrogance is that most remarkable of pejoratives because it wears Janus's mask—a bad thing in normal society but an absolute requirement in all the arts. It is never enough to have the gift; one must strut it as well. There's way more money in being the guest of honor and the DJ simultaneously, even if the self-promotional moves are now boilerplate behavior for those who have to pimp their own ride.
Which is why, in the end, Rickey Henderson, who died Friday at 65 years old, was not merely arrogant and justifiably so, but the next step beyond merely arrogant. He had the gift, but he also knew that he didn't need to sell himself except to himself, because (a) he was his own best audience, as great performers tend to be, and (b) he figured that eventually everyone else would have to see it his way. And in this case, he was right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Van Pelt on CFP blowouts: ‘I don’t think there’s any clear, perfect answer.’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686038</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/scott-van-pelt-cfp-blowouts.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T15:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first round of the College Football Playoff Friday and Saturday saw its four games decided by 10, 28, 14, and 25 points. That prompted a lot of discussions, especially on social media, with many arguing that certain other teams should have been chosen instead and would have produced more competitive games and some pushing Read more...
The post Scott Van Pelt on CFP blowouts: ‘I don’t think there’s any clear, perfect answer.’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[talking-clock – highly configurable talking clock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139945</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/talking-clock-highly-configurable-talking-clock/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T15:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[talking-clock is a highly configurable clock written in bash with soundpack and voice options. It's written in Bash.
The post talking-clock – highly configurable talking clock appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Davis’ wife trolled him after Saturday’s win]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686002</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/anthony-davis-lakers-wife-rui-hachimura.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T14:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our toughest critics are often the ones closest to us. That was the case for Anthony Davis on Saturday after the Los Angeles Lakers defeated the Sacramento Kings. Davis had a chance to effectively ice the game in the final moments when he went to to free-throw line with 12.1 seconds left and the Lakers Read more...
The post Anthony Davis’ wife trolled him after Saturday’s win appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pitch’s 2024 Holiday Self-Gift Guide for spoiling yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861402</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/the-pitchs-2024-holiday-self-gift-guide-for-spoiling-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T14:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Keegan Hudspeth The holidays have arrived for 2024, and with 2025 looming on the horizon, we thought we’d take a different approach to this year’s gift guide. The Pitch has assembled an Avengers-style line-up of some of our favorite Kansas Citians, and offered the prompt: “What would you get for you?” A self-gift guide? Yes, we think you’ve earned it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USC women’s basketball coach Lindsay Gottlieb channels Gregg Popovich with short in-game interview]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686009</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-basketball/lindsay-gottlieb-usc-uconn-in-game-interview.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T13:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For some coaches, in-game interviews don’t seem to be a big issue. Other coaches, though, are still getting used to them. Lindsay Gottlieb, USC’s women’s basketball coach, is firmly in the second group. Gottlieb’s No. 7 USC team took on No. 4 UConn on Saturday in a game that could well be a Final Four Read more...
The post USC women’s basketball coach Lindsay Gottlieb channels Gregg Popovich with short in-game interview appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday Notes: Pondering Pedroia, Wright, and a HoF Ballot Dilemma]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453392</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/sunday-notes-pondering-pedroia-wright-and-a-hof-ballot-dilemma/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T12:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus Baltimore's Matt Blood on draft decisions, a 2005 conversation with Brian Bannister, Tomoyuki Sugano, Jeremy Zoll on Minnesota's promotions, facts and stats galore, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Laurila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 22, 2024: how to watch NFL Week 16]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685990</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/viewing-picks/december-22-2024-watch-nfl-week-16.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T12:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All Times Eastern Bundesliga Matchday 15 VfL Bochum 1848 vs. 1. FC Heidenheim 1846 — ESPN+, 9;20 a.m. VfL Wolfsburg vs. Borussia Dortmund — ESPN+, 11:20 a.m. Bundesliga Highlights Show — ESPN+, 3:30 p.m. College Basketball Men’s Braggin’ Rights Game Big Ten vs. SEC, Enterprise Center, St. Louis, MO Illinois vs. Missouri — ESPN, 1 Read more...
The post TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 22, 2024: how to watch NFL Week 16 appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vrite – collaborative developer content platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139941</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/vrite-collaborative-developer-content-platform/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T07:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vrite is a collaborative space to create, manage, and deploy product documentation, technical blogs, and knowledge bases.
The post Vrite – collaborative developer content platform appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Herbstreit rips Ohio State’s ‘lunatic fringe,’ ESPN’s ‘First Take’ in defense of Ryan Day]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686027</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/kirk-herbstreit-first-take-ohio-state.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T05:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first round of the College Football Playoff produced virtually no on-field suspense, as all four favorites cruised to a double-digit victory. That included Ohio State, who wrapped up the first round on Saturday night with a 42-17 win against Tennessee. But while there was no on-field drama, Kirk Herbstreit made some comments in the Read more...
The post Kirk Herbstreit rips Ohio State’s ‘lunatic fringe,’ ESPN’s ‘First Take’ in defense of Ryan Day appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Field Pass alternate cast of Ohio State-Tennessee CFP game with ‘The Pat McAfee Show’ was off the rails]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686000</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/pat-mcafee-show-alternate-broadcast-cfp-ohio-state-tennessee-nut-busting-comment.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T04:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those who decided to tune into ESPN2 Field Pass alternate cast of the CFP First Round matchup between the Ohio State Buckeyes and the Tennessee Volunteers starring the cast of The Pat McAfee Show got a very unique experience that certainly toed the line of controversy when some improper conversation broke out about “nut-busting.” Through Read more...
The post Field Pass alternate cast of Ohio State-Tennessee CFP game with ‘The Pat McAfee Show’ was off the rails appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Media pundits heavily critique Tom Brady on call of Steelers-Ravens Week 16 game]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685966</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/tom-brady-criticized-numerous-mistakes-ravens-steelers-broadcast.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T02:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thus far, Tom Brady has perhaps expectedly had a hard time living up to the incredibly lofty expectations for his broadcasting career following his legendary NFL career. And while some have argued that he has shown growth throughout the season, his performance on the call of the Steelers-Ravens Week 16 game was perhaps a bit Read more...
The post Media pundits heavily critique Tom Brady on call of Steelers-Ravens Week 16 game appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Utah Hockey Club alternate broadcast reverse-jinxed a goal]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685829</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nhl/utah-hockey-club-goal-reverse-jinx.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T01:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There have been a lot of announcer jinxes over the years, where commentators say something and are immediately proven wrong. But the field of reverse jinxes is perhaps more interesting, where announcers say something will happen and then it does. A data-focused alternate broadcast for the NHL’s Utah Hockey Club in their game against the Read more...
The post Utah Hockey Club alternate broadcast reverse-jinxed a goal appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wisconsin announcer Matt Lepay defends CFP, cites previous blowouts in four-team era]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685930</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/matt-lepay-cfp-blowouts-wisconsin-announcer.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T00:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since this is the first season of the 12-team format, the CFP is under a microscope. It doesn’t help that Indiana and SMU, regarded as two of the shakier teams going into the CFP, lost largely noncompetitive games to Notre Dame and Penn State, respectively. But as Matt Lepay, the radio voice of Wisconsin football and Read more...
The post Wisconsin announcer Matt Lepay defends CFP, cites previous blowouts in four-team era appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sports media pays tribute to late MLB legend Rickey Henderson]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685918</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/media-members-pay-tribute-rickey-henderson-death.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T00:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Saturday, baseball lost one of its most important figures with the passing of all-time stolen base leader, Rickey Henderson. The Hall of Fame outfielder died on Friday after a bout with pneumonia at 65 years of age. Shortly after the unfortunate news broke, countless sports media members weighed in with some of their favorite Read more...
The post Sports media pays tribute to late MLB legend Rickey Henderson appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joel Klatt roasts Lane Kiffin over CFP post: ‘If your team played half as well as you tweet you would likely be in’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685907</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/joel-klatt-roasts-lane-kiffin-cfp-post.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T23:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years, Ole Miss Rebels’ head football coach Lane Kiffin has drawn a lot of attention for his social media posts. His latest of note came on X Saturday, where he joined the chorus of people criticizing the College Football Playoff Committee for selections of Indiana and SMU after those teams’ disappointing playoff performances. Read more...
The post Joel Klatt roasts Lane Kiffin over CFP post: ‘If your team played half as well as you tweet you would likely be in’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2025 Royals Top Prospects]]></title>
        <id>https://farmtofountains.com/?p=6602</id>
        <link href="https://farmtofountains.com/2025-royals-top-prospects/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=2025-royals-top-prospects"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T22:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Royals prospects just outside the latest Top 30 update: Logan Martin, RHP: Martin offers a lot of the same notes as Ryan Ramsey (below). He’s an older prospect for his level, clouding just how real his season production was. He offers a four-pitch mix with great command. There’s enough strikeout stuff to notice, but doing […]
The post 2025 Royals Top Prospects appeared first on Farm to Fountains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Farr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Famed Red Wings/Tigers host John Keating retiring after 45 years of broadcasting]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685771</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/local-networks/john-keating-famed-red-wings-tigers-host-retiring.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T22:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As local sports broadcasts bring familiar faces into the homes of countless viewers, some personalities become as integral to the experience as the teams they cover. For John Keating, whose voice and presence have shaped Detroit sports coverage for over two decades, all of that’s true. Keating is set to retire after the Detroit Red Read more...
The post Famed Red Wings/Tigers host John Keating retiring after 45 years of broadcasting appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dick Vitale calls out Lane Kiffin, CFP critics after Indiana, SMU losses]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685910</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/dick-vitale-cfp-indiana-smu-lane-kiffin.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T21:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dick Vitale does not want to hear complaints about who did not make it into the College Football Playoff. To be blunt, the first-ever 12-team playoff started with a couple of duds. Despite surrendering two cosmetic touchdowns in the final two minutes of the game, Notre Dame had little trouble with Indiana in a 27-17 Read more...
The post Dick Vitale calls out Lane Kiffin, CFP critics after Indiana, SMU losses appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tank Dell’s injury created a tough situation for the NBC NFL broadcast]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685909</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nbc/tank-dell-injury-noah-eagle-todd-blackledge-texans-chiefs.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T21:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFL games see plenty of injuries, and even a notable amount of serious injuries. And any injury poses challenges for a broadcast team. But the one to Houston Texans’ wide receiver Tank Dell in Saturday’s game against the Kansas City Chiefs was particularly rough on a few fronts. One, it came as he caught a Read more...
The post Tank Dell’s injury created a tough situation for the NBC NFL broadcast appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review: Trader Joe's English Toffee Ice Cream]]></title>
        <id>https://www.brandeating.com/2024/12/review-trader-joes-english-toffee-ice-cream.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.brandeating.com/2024/12/review-trader-joes-english-toffee-ice-cream.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trader Joe's English Toffee Ice Cream features brown butter ice cream with chocolatey-coated toffee and almonds.

A pint was $3.79.
The brown butter ice cream was smooth, rich, creamy, and dense with a nice, buttery caramel note to it. The toffee provided a similar but bolder flavor and a mild dose of chocolate. The almond contributed a slight nuttiness.



Both provided a bit of crunch with the toffee offering a slight sticky chewiness as well.
If you're a fan of chunky ice cream along the lines of Ben & Jerry's, Trader Joe's English Toffee Ice Cream might disappoint. The toffee bits and almonds were quite small and only made very occasional appearances in the eating experience.



As a fan of English toffee, I liked Trader Joe's English Toffee Ice Cream as it provided a rather nuanced and layered take on the flavor. That being said, I would have liked more or at least bigger pieces of toffee and almonds.
Nutritional Info - Trader Joe's English Toffee Ice Cream
Serving Size - 2/3 cup (123g)
Calories - 330
Fat - 20g (Saturated Fat - 13g)
Sodium - 120mg
Carbs - 34g (Sugar - 31g)
Protein - 4g
Read more at Brand Eating!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brand Eating. Your Daily Fast Food Reading.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Post, TMZ confirm Rickey Henderson’s death, hours after reports from Dave Winfield, Ozzie Guillen, others]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685877</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/rickey-henderson-death-early-reports-eventually-confirmed.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T20:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest case of unusual reporting involves the passing of former MLB legend Rickey Henderson at 65. That news officially came out early Saturday afternoon, with the New York Post and TMZ key early sources there: Rickey Henderson, Hall of Famer and MLB’s all-time stolen bases leader, dead at 65 https://t.co/e554V5CzCU pic.twitter.com/IwUTZnZZQ0 — New York Read more...
The post New York Post, TMZ confirm Rickey Henderson’s death, hours after reports from Dave Winfield, Ozzie Guillen, others appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Best Free and Open Source Shutdown Timers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=96721</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-shutdown-timers/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T20:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux is blessed with an abundance of useful utilities. We feature interesting shutdown timers. Open source goodness as you'd expect.
The post 4 Best Free and Open Source Shutdown Timers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Herbstreit: Visiting Tennessee fans ‘by far the most’ in his 29-year ‘College GameDay’ history]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685792</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/kirk-herbstreit-tennessee-fans-college-gameday.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T20:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t long ago that Kirk Herbstreit apologized to Tennessee fans; now he’s praising them. The College GameDay star, who had his quote about Volunteers’ fans taken out of context, offered some praise — and then some on Saturday. Herbstreit was recently a guest on Barstool Sports’ Pardon My Take and doubted that the Volunteers Read more...
The post Kirk Herbstreit: Visiting Tennessee fans ‘by far the most’ in his 29-year ‘College GameDay’ history appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[littleutils – utilities for file compression, file manipulation, text cleanup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139935</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/littleutils-utilities-file-compression-file-manipulation-text-cleanup/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T19:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[littleutils include duplicate file finders, image optimizers, file rename tools, archive recompressors, a tempfile utility, and others.
The post littleutils – utilities for file compression, file manipulation, text cleanup appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joel Klatt calls out ‘partisan bias’ in college football narratives]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685802</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/joel-klatt-partisan-bias-college-football-narratives.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T19:40:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joel Klatt didn’t need to name names — his message was crystal clear. In the aftermath of Notre Dame’s 27-17 victory over Indiana, revisionist history was in full swing. Kirk Herbstreit suggested that the Hoosiers didn’t belong on the field, implying that teams like Alabama, Ole Miss, South Carolina, or even Miami might have been Read more...
The post Joel Klatt calls out ‘partisan bias’ in college football narratives appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[kleur – Node.js library for formatting terminal text with ANSI colors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139930</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/kleur-node-js-library-formatting-terminal-text/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T19:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[kleur bills itself as the fastest Node.js library for formatting terminal text with ANSI colors. It's written in JavaScript.
The post kleur – Node.js library for formatting terminal text with ANSI colors appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Penn State’s early dominance against SMU got SEC Network personalities mad over Mustangs’ CFP selection over Alabama]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685843</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/league-networks/penn-state-smu-sec-network-personalities-cfp.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T19:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regardless of how any particular version of the College Football Playoff actually plays out, many are always going to use its results to argue that other teams would have been better picks. That happened during and after Indiana’s 27-17 first-round loss to Notre Dame Friday, and it’s already going strong in the SMU-Penn State game, Read more...
The post Penn State’s early dominance against SMU got SEC Network personalities mad over Mustangs’ CFP selection over Alabama appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legendary Mississippi State voice Jim Ellis retires after 46 years calling their baseball team]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685744</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/ncaa/jim-ellis-mississippi-state-baseball-broadcasting-legend.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T19:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sports broadcasting world is no stranger to turnover, making it all the more remarkable when someone spends over four decades in the same role. Jim Ellis, the long-time voice of Mississippi State Bulldogs baseball, is one such rare talent, having called the team’s games for an incredible 46 seasons. Ellis announced this week that Read more...
The post Legendary Mississippi State voice Jim Ellis retires after 46 years calling their baseball team appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best Free and Open Source Replacements for ls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=70404</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-replacements-ls/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T18:48:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When invoked without any arguments, ls lists the files in the current working directory. We recommend some great replacements.
The post 10 Best Free and Open Source Replacements for ls appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Herbstreit, Nick Saban retroactively lobby for Cam Ward and Miami over Indiana in playoffs]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685795</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/nick-saban-kirk-herbstreit-cam-ward-miami-cfp-indiana.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T18:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Sunday, Dec. 8, before the College Football Playoff rankings reveal show, ESPN CFB analyst Kirk Herbstreit appeared on the network seemingly to discuss who’d be in and out but actually chose to offer no take. There, he said “After last year, I have learned, I have no opinions about anything.” But following the Indiana Read more...
The post Kirk Herbstreit, Nick Saban retroactively lobby for Cam Ward and Miami over Indiana in playoffs appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shutdown Scheduler – schedule shutdown and restart tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139925</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/shutdown-scheduler-schedule-shutdown-restart-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T18:15:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shutdown Scheduler is a simple cross-platform application that uses system utilities for scheduling shutdown and restart tasks.
The post Shutdown Scheduler – schedule shutdown and restart tasks appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Titans’ QB Will Levis roasted after bashing ESPN Fortnite branding for CFP]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685724</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/titans-qb-will-levis-roasted-fortnite-espn-branding-cfp.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T18:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Broadcast sponsorships have long been a source of awkwardness, but ESPN/ABC’s latest for this year’s College Football Playoff might take the cake. During Friday’s Notre Dame-Indiana game, the network heavily promoted its “Fortnite OG Kickoff” sponsorship, with announcer Sean McDonough repeatedly mentioning it on air. “You’re watching the Fortnite OG Kickoff.” pic.twitter.com/lDYQx1S9gl — Awful Announcing Read more...
The post Titans’ QB Will Levis roasted after bashing ESPN Fortnite branding for CFP appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Herbstreit: ‘Outclassed’ Indiana [shouldn’t] have ‘been on that field’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685708</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/kirk-herbstreit-indiana-outclassed-field.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T17:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rece Davis might have said that performance doesn’t validate or invalidate these selections, but that doesn’t mean everyone on the College GameDay set has to fall in line. Kirk Herbstreit tried not to frame Indiana’s 27-17 loss as a knock on the Hoosiers, but the GameDay analyst didn’t exactly shield them from criticism, either. In Read more...
The post Kirk Herbstreit: ‘Outclassed’ Indiana [shouldn’t] have ‘been on that field’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals, Junior Fernández Agree To Minor League Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=835404</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/12/royals-junior-fernandez-agree-to-minor-league-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T17:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have signed right-handed pitcher Junior Fernández to a minor league deal, the team announced. He last pitched in MLB during the 2022 season. Fernández signed with the Cardinals as an international free agent in 2014 and made his MLB debut in St. Louis five years later. Unfortunately, he was never able to establish…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leo Morgenstern</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Pasch is still chasing ‘a whole new way of broadcasting’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685456</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/dave-pasch-chasing-new-way-broadcasting-walton.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T17:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You always play for the touchdown. That’s what Dave Pasch insisted with Arizona State on the verge of punching its ticket to the Big 12 championship game in late November at home. “You win the game if you get in the end zone,” Pasch said on the ESPN broadcast. “Go score.” Yet with the ball Read more...
The post Dave Pasch is still chasing ‘a whole new way of broadcasting’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mac McClung on Bronny James performing despite pressure: ‘He’s doing a great job’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684940</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/mac-mcclung-bronny-james-performing-pressure.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T16:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bronny James has been the center of attention this season, with plenty of buzz about the Los Angeles Lakers’ plan to have him split time between their NBA squad and their G League affiliate, the South Bay Lakers. One player who’s in somewhat of a similar situation is Mac McClung. McClung is the reigning G Read more...
The post Mac McClung on Bronny James performing despite pressure: ‘He’s doing a great job’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix orders documentary about Broncos great John Elway]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685556</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/documentary-john-elway.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T16:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Somewhat overshadowed at different times during his Hall of Fame career by Joe Montana, Troy Aikman, Brett Favre, and Steve Young, Denver Broncos great John Elway is getting the star treatment from Netflix. Elway, who led the Broncos to five Super Bowl appearances, winning two to cap his record-breaking NFL career,  will be the focus Read more...
The post Netflix orders documentary about Broncos great John Elway appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Keeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to sports media rights, it’s better to buy than rent]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685219</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/sports-media-rights-buyer-renter.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T15:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In looking for a place to live, the decision to rent or buy a place can be among the most difficult parts of the process. Both options have inherent pros and cons. Renting a place requires less capital, allows for flexibility in terms of not being tied down in a certain location long-term, and is Read more...
The post When it comes to sports media rights, it’s better to buy than rent appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indiana’s Curt Cignetti tries to explain sad surrender punt]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685696</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/curt-cignetti-surrender-punt-explanation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T15:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a coach who likes to talk the talk, Curt Cignetti sure didn’t walk the walk. Clichés aside, everything that got Indiana to South Bend disappeared the second Cignetti saw his breath. The aggressiveness that saw the first-year head coach earn Coach of the Year honors and turn one of the worst football programs in Read more...
The post Indiana’s Curt Cignetti tries to explain sad surrender punt appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making spirits bright: Our exhaustingly festive list of holiday pop-up bars in Kansas City]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862594</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/making-spirits-bright-our-exhaustingly-festive-list-of-holiday-pop-up-bars-in-kansas-city/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T15:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miracle // Photo by Sarah Sipple We’re not sure how this list continues to grow each year. Nevertheless, Kansas Citians are clearly clamoring for the merriment, and we’re here for it. From Olathe to North KC, food and drink-focused festivities abound in the KC metro. Here, The Pitch has gathered the important details, done a vibe check, and included some...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making spirits bright: Our exhaustingly festive list of holiday pop-up bars in Kansas City]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862594</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/making-spirits-bright-our-exhaustingly-festive-list-of-holiday-pop-up-bars-in-kansas-city/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T15:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miracle // Photo by Sarah Sipple We’re not sure how this list continues to grow each year. Nevertheless, Kansas Citians are clearly clamoring for the merriment, and we’re here for it. From Olathe to North KC, food and drink-focused festivities abound in the KC metro. Here, The Pitch has gathered the important details, done a vibe check, and included some...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City's oldest restaurants: Where you can still eat your way through city history]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2024-12-21/oldest-restaurants-kansas-city-barbecue-history</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2024-12-21/oldest-restaurants-kansas-city-barbecue-history"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T14:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some restaurants across the Kansas City metro are still running strong after more than 100 years in business, serving up delicious meals and defining the culinary landscape for generations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hannah Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark DeRosa: ‘MLB Central’ offers ‘safe space’ to ’empower’ players]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685454</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/mark-derosa-empower-players.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T14:40:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MLB Central celebrates its 10th birthday in 2025, and the MLB Network show has become must-see TV for many baseball fans. San Diego Padres radio broadcaster Sammy Levitt talked to MLB Central co-host Mark DeRosa during the Winter Meetings about the show’s success through the years. In addition to the camaraderie of DeRosa and co-hosts Read more...
The post Mark DeRosa: ‘MLB Central’ offers ‘safe space’ to ’empower’ players appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Would sluggish CFP ratings be a blessing in disguise for TNT?]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685535</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/would-sluggish-cfp-ratings-blessing-disguise-tnt.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T14:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A feast of football awaits this Saturday with a trio of College Football Playoff games to go with a marquee NFL doubleheader. Much has already been said about the circumstances surrounding the crowded schedule. College football loyalists are upset that the NFL would dare to schedule such high-octane matchups on a Saturday — a day Read more...
The post Would sluggish CFP ratings be a blessing in disguise for TNT? appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sean McDonough calls out Indiana, questions CFP’s Big Ten bias]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685688</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/sean-mcdonough-indiana-big-ten-bias.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T13:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sean McDonough wasn’t having it. The veteran announcer, who, alongside Greg McElroy, ranked second in Awful Announcing’s 2024 college football announcer rankings, was in rare form Friday night as he took the Hoosiers to task. In a game that gave him and his partner little to work with, McDonough didn’t hold back, calling it exactly Read more...
The post Sean McDonough calls out Indiana, questions CFP’s Big Ten bias appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL social media team deletes Jalen Hurts shoes post after league fines QB]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685601</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/twitter/social-media-deletes-jalen-hurts-shoes-fine.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T13:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFL uniform violations usually fly under the radar in the news, but an infraction involving Jalen Hurts this week raised eyebrows for a bizarre reason. The NFL fined the Philadelphia Eagles quarterback $5,628 for a uniform and equipment violation in last Sunday’s win over the Pittsburgh Steelers. Hurts wore shoes that were mismatched shades of Read more...
The post NFL social media team deletes Jalen Hurts shoes post after league fines QB appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Schaap calls Boomer and Gunnar Esiason E:60 ‘one of the best things we’ve done’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685400</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/jeremy-schaap-boomer-gunnar-esiason-e60-best-things.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T13:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boomer and Gunnar Esiason’s work to find a medical miracle against cystic fibrosis is a story Jeremy Schaap is excited to tell on an upcoming edition of E:60. Earlier this week, ESPN announced The Boomer & Gunnar Esiason Story: Second Wind, an E:60 set to premiere at 7 p.m. ET next Tuesday on Christmas Eve. Read more...
The post Jeremy Schaap calls Boomer and Gunnar Esiason E:60 ‘one of the best things we’ve done’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matchroom’s Eddie Hearn sees Fury-Usyk 2 as chance for boxing fans to enjoy ‘real fights’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685139</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/boxing/eddie-hearn-matchroom-dazn-fury-usyk-tyson-paul.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T12:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A discussion of “boxing” can conjure quite different images at the moment. For some, that’s fights like 27-year-old YouTuber Jake Paul’s highly-publicized exhibition defeat of 58-year-old Mike Tyson in November. For others, the interest is more in actual title fights, such as the Oleksandr Usyk vs. Tyson Fury heavyweight title rematch (for the WBC, WBA, Read more...
The post Matchroom’s Eddie Hearn sees Fury-Usyk 2 as chance for boxing fans to enjoy ‘real fights’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 21, 2024 (Part II): how to watch the NFL doubleheader]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685682</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/viewing-picks/december-21-2024-part-ii-watch-nfl-doubleheader.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T12:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All Times Eastern Golf Exhibition PNC Championship, Ritz-Carlton Golf Club, Orlando, FL Day 1: Scramble — Golf Channel/Peacock, 11 a.m. Day 1: Scramble — Peacock, 12:30 p.m. Day 1: Scramble — NBC/Peacock, 4 p.m. Golf Central Pregame — Golf Channel, 10 a.m. DP World Tour Mauritius Open, Mont Choisy Le Golf, Grand Baie, Mauritius Final Read more...
The post TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 21, 2024 (Part II): how to watch the NFL doubleheader appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 21, 2024 (Part I): how to watch the CFP QF tripleheader]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685559</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/viewing-picks/december-21-2024-part-i-watch-cfp-tripleheader.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T12:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All Times Eastern Bundesliga Matchday 15 Eintracht Frankfurt vs. 1. FSV Mainz 05 — ESPN+, 9:20 a.m. Holstein Kiel vs. FC Augsburg — ESPN+, 9:20 a.m. SV Werder Bremen vs. 1. FC Union Berlin — ESPN+, 9:20 a.m. TSG Hoffenheim vs. Borussia Mönchengladbach — ESPN+, 9:20 a.m. VfB Stuttgart vs. FC St. Pauli — ESPN+, Read more...
The post TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 21, 2024 (Part I): how to watch the CFP QF tripleheader appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Best Free and Open Source GUI Tools for System Resources Monitoring in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139904</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-gui-tools-system-resources-monitoring/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T08:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tools featured in this roundup are targeted at a desktop user who wants to monitor resources being used on their machine.
The post 6 Best Free and Open Source GUI Tools for System Resources Monitoring in Linux appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effectively Wild Episode 2260: What We Might Remember About 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453378</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/effectively-wild-episode-2260-what-we-might-remember-about-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T06:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Lindbergh, Meg Rowley, and Pebble Hunting’s Sam Miller banter about Michael Lorenzen embracing an Effectively Wild hypothetical, Ben and Sam’s past predictions about baseball in the 2020s, and Paul Skenes and the ERA title, then discuss what will be remembered about baseball in 2024 (plus a postscript). Audio intro: Daniel Leckie, “Effectively Wild Theme” Audio outro: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Lindbergh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curt Cignetti boasts Indiana beats ‘s***’ out of Top 25 teams, then punts game away]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685621</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/curt-cignetti-boasts-hoosiers-notre-dame-punt-conservative.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T04:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indiana head coach Curt Cignetti baffled fans and even ESPN announcers Friday night with a conservative game plan as Notre Dame defeated the Hoosiers, 27-17, in the College Football Playoff. Complicating matters, that game strategy stood in sharp contrast to Cignetti’s pregame boasts on College GameDay, when he said he and the Hoosiers “beat the Read more...
The post Curt Cignetti boasts Indiana beats ‘s***’ out of Top 25 teams, then punts game away appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coach whose team lost to Kentucky at home shades Indiana’s CFP inclusion]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685651</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/lane-kiffin-ole-miss-lost-kentucky-indianas-inclusion-cfp.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T04:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The unfortunate thing about the Indiana Hoosiers’ loss to the Notre Dame Fighting Irish in the College Football Playoff on Friday night is that it opened the door for every angle critics want to take about their inclusion. If you wanted to argue Indiana didn’t deserve to be included in the CFP despite finishing 11-1, Read more...
The post Coach whose team lost to Kentucky at home shades Indiana’s CFP inclusion appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Keeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Thrill Was Never There]]></title>
        <id>https://tedium.co/2024/12/20/punk-rock-mba-youtube-quitting/</id>
        <link href="https://feed.tedium.co/link/15204/16925582/punk-rock-mba-youtube-quitting"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T03:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Takeaways from a punk-rock creator who says he doesn’t like punk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ernie Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local holiday music drops for when you need to rock around the Xmas tree]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865956</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/local-holiday-music-drops-for-when-you-need-to-rock-around-the-xmas-tree/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T03:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As demonstrated from coverage in years past, we’re big fans of Christmas music here at The Pitch, and love nothing more than to see that some local musicians have tried their hand at holiday fare. Here’s a selection of this year’s releases, with moods to suit every taste. Mark Murtha’s Christmas Party in Kansas City In addition to his work with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN’s new CFP scorebug heaped with praise, except when paired with BottomLine]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685615</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/scorebug-college-football-playoff-bottom-line.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T03:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s hard to explain to a non-sports fan just how much people love to analyze and discuss scorebugs. But trust us, we’re well aware. So we were not surprised to see ample discussion about ESPN’s new College Football Playoff scorebug, which debuted Friday night during the Notre Dame-Indiana game. ESPN debuts a new scorebug and Read more...
The post ESPN’s new CFP scorebug heaped with praise, except when paired with BottomLine appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Keeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Hanson apologizes for using commercial-free catchphrase during NFL RedZone with ads]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685606</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/scott-hanson-apologizes-commercial-free-catchphrase-redzone.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T03:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many NFL fans, their game-viewing experience hasn’t truly started until NFL RedZone host Scott Hanson welcomes them with a promise of “seven hours of commercial-free football.” This past Sunday, that promise was broken when RedZone viewers were treated to multiple commercials throughout the day. An NFL Media spokesperson later confirmed that RedZone’s most recent Read more...
The post Scott Hanson apologizes for using commercial-free catchphrase during NFL RedZone with ads appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Keeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nick Saban has perfect response for Shane Gillis’ ‘cheating’ joke]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685550</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/college-gameday-shane-gillis-nick-saban-paying-players-alabama.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T02:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comedian Shane Gillis appeared as the celebrity guest picker on College GameDay Friday night, but one of his jokes might have gotten under the skin of analyst Nick Saban. The CGD crew set up in South Bend ahead of the Notre Dame-Indiana game, and Gillis, a big Fighting Irish fan, told Pat McAfee that the team Read more...
The post Nick Saban has perfect response for Shane Gillis’ ‘cheating’ joke appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nick Saban: Angry Ohio State fans ‘need to quit all this negative bull****’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685519</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/nick-saban-college-gameday-ohio-state-angry-negative.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T02:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Ohio State fans are down on Ryan Day heading into the College Football Playoff, but the head coach found a surprising defender Friday night in Nick Saban. The former Alabama coach and now College GameDay analyst went after Ohio State fans who have vented their frustration with Day. While the Buckeyes are in the Read more...
The post Nick Saban: Angry Ohio State fans ‘need to quit all this negative bull****’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fox airing Bill Belichick-Madden Cruiser road trip special before Super Bowl]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685429</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/bill-belichick-madden-cruiser-road-trip.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T01:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fox will air a one-hour special, The Madden Cruiser: A Bayou Adventure with Bill Belichick, ahead of its Super Bowl LIX pregame show, and that title alone should be enough to capture the attention of many sports fans. The legendary coach will ride in the iconic RV made famous by broadcaster John Madden, traveling through Read more...
The post Fox airing Bill Belichick-Madden Cruiser road trip special before Super Bowl appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astros Get Early Christian-mas Present]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453360</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/astros-get-early-christian-mas-present/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T01:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This nerd favorite fills a massive need in Houston.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Baumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nick Saban, who left LSU before its bowl game, says players shouldn’t be allowed to leave before bowl games]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685523</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/nick-saban-players-shouldnt-be-allowed-leave-before-bowl-games.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T01:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[College football has always had something of a Wild West quality to it. Conferences and schools have been tweaking the rules in their favor since the sports began. The bowl system makes no logical sense when you stop and think about it with 2024 eyes. We’ve lost count of how many times a school promised Read more...
The post Nick Saban, who left LSU before its bowl game, says players shouldn’t be allowed to leave before bowl games appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Keeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirby Smart mixing up Indiana with ‘Purdue’ was a tough scene]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685426</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/kirby-smart-indiana-purdue-mix-up.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T00:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Indiana manages to beat Notre Dame and Georgia, perhaps we’ll look back at Kirby Smart’s College GameDay appearance as the turning point. Playing with house money, the Hoosiers enter Friday’s matchup in South Bend as clear underdogs. But anything feels possible with the expanded College Football Playoff in full swing. Since Friday’s game marks Read more...
The post Kirby Smart mixing up Indiana with ‘Purdue’ was a tough scene appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Desmond Howard: Ohio State brass put ‘too much pressure on’ Ryan Day to win]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685462</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/desmond-howard-ohio-state-ryan-day.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T00:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that Michigan has beaten Ohio State for a fourth consecutive season, Desmond Howard has finally wrapped up his victory laps. The former Heisman winner turned College GameDay analyst, however, now seems to feel a twinge of sympathy for Ryan Day. And during Friday’s GameDay broadcast from South Bend, Howard took up a collection for Read more...
The post Desmond Howard: Ohio State brass put ‘too much pressure on’ Ryan Day to win appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN’s Seth Greenberg takes up for Doug Gottlieb amid criticism: ‘Coaching isn’t easy’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685391</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-basketball/seth-greenberg-doug-gottlieb-criticism.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T23:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Gottlieb doesn’t exactly have a lot of allies in the media right now. The head men’s basketball coach at the University of Wisconsin–Green Bay is getting humbled — in more ways than one — to say the least. After engaging in a war of words with Adam Schefter, who implored Gottlieb to spend less Read more...
The post ESPN’s Seth Greenberg takes up for Doug Gottlieb amid criticism: ‘Coaching isn’t easy’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Al Michaels reflects on broadcasting future beyond 2025: ‘As long as I have the passion, I’ll continue’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685384</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/amazon/al-michaels-broadcasting-future-passion-continue.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T23:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Al Michaels has already committed to returning as the voice of Amazon Prime Video’s Thursday Night Football in 2025. But what about after that? That question came up Friday during an appearance on The Dan Patrick Show, where Patrick likened the 80-year-old Michaels to a legendary head coach like Joe Paterno or Bill Belichick and Read more...
The post Al Michaels reflects on broadcasting future beyond 2025: ‘As long as I have the passion, I’ll continue’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Job Posting: MLB Draft League / Appalachian League – Data Coordinator]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?post_type=instagraphs&amp;p=453367</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/instagraphs/job-posting-mlb-draft-league-appalachian-league-data-coordinator/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T22:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MLB Draft League is hiring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Appelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cris Collinsworth sheds light on why Buccaneers-Cowboys isn’t flexed out of primetime]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685360</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/cris-collinsworth-buccaneers-cowboys-flex-primetime.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T22:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you were asking yourself why the NFL didn’t flex the Dallas Cowboys out of Sunday Night Football, you might want to ask yourself that again. For better or worse, ‘America’s Team’ gets ratings — and Cris Collinsworth wasn’t kidding when he said NBC would air 17 Dallas Cowboys games if it could. The network Read more...
The post Cris Collinsworth sheds light on why Buccaneers-Cowboys isn’t flexed out of primetime appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals sign RHP Fernandez to Minor League Contract]]></title>
        <id>https://farmtofountains.com/?p=6597</id>
        <link href="https://farmtofountains.com/royals-sign-rhp-fernandez-to-minor-league-contract/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=royals-sign-rhp-fernandez-to-minor-league-contract"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T22:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kansas City Royals have added their second minor league free agent of the week. First, it was Taylor Clarke, followed by RHP Junior Fernandez on Friday. Fernandez, 27, started his professional career in the St. Louis Cardinals organization. He was signed as an international free agent before the 2014 season and went on to […]
The post Royals sign RHP Fernandez to Minor League Contract appeared first on Farm to Fountains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Farr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix Women’s World Cup deal keeps streaming dominant for U.S. soccer fans]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685285</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/soccer/netflix-fifa-womens-world-cup-streaming-soccer-american-fans.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T22:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Netflix shocked American soccer fans when they closed a busy 2024 of sports rights acquisitions by buying rights to the 2027 and 2031 FIFA women’s world cups. Unlike other sports streaming deals that offer global exclusivity, Netflix will now carry the event, which has been dominated by the U.S. women’s national team most Read more...
The post Netflix Women’s World Cup deal keeps streaming dominant for U.S. soccer fans appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Pederson struggles to find answers to Mac Jones question]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685333</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/doug-pederson-mac-jones-question.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T21:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s been no greater rivalry in the NFL this year than Doug Pederson and press conferences. When he’s not criticizing his own players or members of the media, Pederson is finding ways to dance around questions being asked. Like the latter of the example, in which he refused to explain a play to reporters, claiming Read more...
The post Doug Pederson struggles to find answers to Mac Jones question appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Herbstreit apologizes to Tennessee fans after quote taken out of context]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685282</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/kirk-herbestreit-tennessee-fans-viral-quote.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T21:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anytime Kirk Herbstreit says something that can even slightly be perceived as a jab at a college football fanbase, he immediately finds himself under the microscope. Florida State fans’ longstanding grievances with the “Mayor of College Football” are well-documented, and Herbstreit is no stranger to criticism. But, in this instance, he has a legitimate gripe Read more...
The post Kirk Herbstreit apologizes to Tennessee fans after quote taken out of context appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cam Newton scolds Stephen A. Smith over Lamar Jackson: ‘Watch what you say’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685264</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/cam-newton-stephen-a-smith-lamar-jackson.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T20:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cam Newton is accusing Stephen A. Smith of holding Lamar Jackson to a different standard than he holds Josh Allen. Friday morning on First Take, Smith, Newton and Canty were previewing this week’s Baltimore Ravens-Pittsburgh Steelers matchup by assessing whether a win would be a bigger statement for Jackson or Russell Wilson. According to Smith, Read more...
The post Cam Newton scolds Stephen A. Smith over Lamar Jackson: ‘Watch what you say’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Draymond Green goes statless in loss to Memphis, whose head coach he called ‘softie’ on his podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685262</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/draymond-green-memphis-grizzlies-statless-loss-taylor-jenkins-softie.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T20:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In mid-November after a loss to the Memphis Grizzlies, Draymond Green took to his podcast to called the opposing head coach a “softie” who was teaching his team bad habits by complaining to the media about foul calls in defeat. “You got janky Taylor Jenkins, who’s a softie,” Green said at the time. “Guess what, Read more...
The post Draymond Green goes statless in loss to Memphis, whose head coach he called ‘softie’ on his podcast appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Howard Eskin announces abrupt exit from WIP after 38 years]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685346</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/radio/howard-eskin-announces-exit-wip.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T20:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After nearly four decades with Philadelphia’s SportsRadio WIP, Howard Eskin announced he is parting ways with the station. Eskin made the announcement Friday afternoon, where the 73-year-old sports personality made it clear his departure from WIP should not be considered a retirement. After 38 years I am moving on from Sportsradio WIP where I launched Read more...
The post Howard Eskin announces abrupt exit from WIP after 38 years appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion: Inspecting Kansas and Missouri power players at the heart of the far-right’s porn censorship bid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865845</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/opinion-kansas-missouri-officials-at-the-heart-of-the-far-rights-porn-censorship-bid/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T20:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abode Images It’s no secret that I have many bones to pick with our state’s elected officials. I told the lot of them in a previous column for The Pitch to go fuck themselves for instilling a “MAGA virus” and far-right Christian nationalism throughout Missouri. This time around, there is just more evidence to share that several leaders in Missouri...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael McGrady Jr.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg McElroy uses ‘Mean Girls’ reference to describe Texas quarterback situation]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685267</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/greg-mcelroy-mean-girls-reference.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T19:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t know whether Greg McElroy wears pink on Wednesdays. But we do know how he feels about Texas’ current quarterback situation. Ahead of the Longhorns’ first-round matchup against Clemson in the College Football Playoff, McElroy — who will be on the call for the game — appeared on ESPN’s Get Up. And during the Read more...
The post Greg McElroy uses ‘Mean Girls’ reference to describe Texas quarterback situation appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix Reloaded: December 20, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453233</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/matrix-reloaded-december-20-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T19:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was far less hectic than the Winter Meetings last week, but there are still plenty of Matrix updates to go over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Becker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cubs beat writer defends Russell Martin Hall of Fame vote]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685226</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/cubs-beat-writer-defends-russell-martin-vote.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T19:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russell Martin had a good — even great — Major League Baseball career. Not many, however, would call it Hall of Fame worthy. But as it turns out, there is at least one exception when it comes to Martin’s Cooperstown candidacy. Taking to X on Thursday, Chicago Tribune Cubs beat writer Meghan Montemurro shared her Read more...
The post Cubs beat writer defends Russell Martin Hall of Fame vote appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RosterResource Chat – 12/20/24]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453351</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/rosterresource-chat-12-20-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T18:42:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Martinez and Jon Becker answer questions related to projected rosters and playing time, team needs, payroll, free agency, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rival exec accuses NFL of being ‘slanted’ towards Amazon, Thursday Night Football]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685220</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/rival-exec-accuses-nfl-of-being-slanted-towards-amazon-thursday-night-football.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T18:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t long ago that famed sportscaster Al Michaels was openly making fun of his own Thursday Night Football schedule on Amazon Prime Video and the number of stinkers that he and Kirk Herbstreit had to call. My how things have changed. The NFL can giveth and taketh away when it comes to schedules and Read more...
The post Rival exec accuses NFL of being ‘slanted’ towards Amazon, Thursday Night Football appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing Gets Jim Harbaugh’s Motor Running Like An Obscure Rule]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176965</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jim-harbaugh-cameron-dicker-fair-catch-kick"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T18:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Harbaugh has this look about him that screams dotty uncle—the blinky eyes behind the old-man glasses, the slightly slack jaw, the refusal to employ the newfangled play-sheet-and-face-shield look. He's perfectly cast for a man who thinks Lawrence Welk is the cutting edge.
Thus, it was right and proper that he be the one to return the fair catch kick to our notice by stealing a last-second three-banger right before halftime of last night's Amazonapalooza in which Harbaugh's Los Angeles Chargers defeated the almost as old but not nearly so physically arresting Sean Payton and the Denver Broncos. An arcane enclave of the rulebook which was successfully employed as recently as 1976, when Harbaugh was spiritually already in his mid-40s, the fair catch kick can be employed only on a fair catch as time expires, or a penalty on a fair catch, which the Broncos' Tremon Smith gifted the Chargers on a punt that Derius Davis tried to collect with no time left on the clock. The 15-yard penalty took the ball from the Charger 38 to the Bronco 47 and offered an untimed play to provide the punishment for the penalty that would otherwise go unpunished—why, you could hear the oldey-timey gears in a million old coaches' heads at the possibilities. “It’s my favorite rule in football,” Harbaugh said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timothée Chalamet wants to play TNT’s Ernie Johnson in a biopic]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685136</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/pop-culture/timothee-chalamet-play-ernie-johnson-biopic.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T18:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By this point, it’s become well-established that Timothée Chalamet knows ball. But while Chalamet previously showcased his sports bona fides while serving as the guest picker on College GameDay and by waxing poetic about MLS stars, the depths of his sports fandom are still being revealed. That includes an apparent affinity for Inside the NBA‘s Read more...
The post Timothée Chalamet wants to play TNT’s Ernie Johnson in a biopic appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Babygirl’ Wants To Know Your Fantasy]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176871</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/babygirl-wants-to-know-your-fantasy"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Babygirl, a movie written and directed by Dutch filmmaker Halina Reijn and starring Nicole Kidman and Harris Dickinson, is about facades. It's also about sex, but less about sex itself and more about what sex says about a person, and the ways we suppress our sexual appetites in order for it to say nothing about us at all. Babygirl, Reijn's second English-language film after 2022's Bodies Bodies Bodies, taps into a conservative cultural moment that is firmly anti-sex while still being in sex's thrall. It is the subject everyone wants to talk about but no one wants to see, or seemingly even have.
The movie follows tech CEO Romy Mathis (Kidman), an unabashed, all-caps GIRLBOSS who nominally "has it all": a powerful job, a big office, an eager assistant who looks up to her, a seemingly well-adjusted family that includes two daughters and a hot theater director for a husband (Antonio Banderas). But there is a restless beast inside of Romy, and vanilla sex with her husband can't appease it—so much so that Romy often finds herself having to watch dom-play porn in the bathroom afterwards in order to actually reach an orgasm. When a much younger intern for the company arrives, Samuel (Dickinson), she slowly finds herself ensnared in his web, and discovers that he is up for taming that beast. Both in spite and because of the power dynamics and the threat their affair poses to her life and career, they begin an ill-advised relationship that is hot and steamy, but most importantly effective and passionate. Romy finds her sexual needs met for the first time, which, in this movie, is as important as the tension or thriller aspects at play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even ‘Jeopardy!’ is pilling on the Jets’ misery]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685157</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/final-jeopardy-jets-super-bowl.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There aren’t many teams in professional sports that have had a more disappointing 2024 than the New York Jets. Ok, except maybe the Chicago Bears. And even the beloved game show Jeopardy! is taking stock of the franchise’s woes. Sports categories and clues on Jeopardy! can always be hit or miss. Ok, it’s mostly misses Read more...
The post Even ‘Jeopardy!’ is pilling on the Jets’ misery appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blob-Headed Fish Sets New Standard Of Fishy Blobbiness]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176910</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/blob-headed-fish-sets-new-standard-of-fishy-blobbiness"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:32:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the narrow, highly specialized field of fish with blob-like attributes, one fish has dominated for decades: One would hardly dare imagine a blobbish fish without first thinking of the blobfish. But has a new blobby fish emerged to unseat this age-old champion of blobdom?
Today, a group of researchers from the nonprofit Conservation International published a report of 27 new species discovered in Alto Mayo, a region in the Peruvian Amazon. Each of the species was a singular delight: the amphibious mouse that dwells in palm swamps called aguajales; the small, stubby chestnut-colored salamander that climbs trees. But as I scrolled through the report, one species was a clear standout—a born star, never readier to accept its place in the spotlight. This, of course, was the blob-headed fish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A guide to ESPN’s College Football Playoff studio coverage]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684958</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/college-football-playoff-studio-shows.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN has rolled out its official plans for extensive studio coverage of the College Football Playoff, and there’s a lot to parse through. The expanded 12-team playoff also means expanded coverage plans for the Worldwide Leader, who will deploy several studio teams across its various networks. ESPN’s flagship college football studio show College GameDay will Read more...
The post A guide to ESPN’s College Football Playoff studio coverage appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JAWS and the 2025 Hall of Fame Ballot: Brian McCann]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453284</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/jaws-and-the-2025-hall-of-fame-ballot-brian-mccann/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though he was a seven-time All-Star, McCann was somewhat underappreciated until the value of his elite pitch framing came to light.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Jaffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eat This Edible: Honeybee’s Queen Bee delivers a high-potency and piquant palate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865942</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/eat-this-edible-honeybees-queen-bee-delivers-a-high-potency-and-piquant-palate/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Proper Cannabis In November, Honeybee Edibles—an edible brand underneath the St. Louis-based cannabis company Proper Cannabis—released a new edible in the Missouri market. The gluten-free and vegan Queen Bee is now giving consumers an easier route to their high, compacting 100mg of THC and 100mg CBD into just a couple easy-going bites. Similar to Grön’s MEGA edible...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Ellett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More difficult days ahead for Nike as they re-invest in sports marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685133</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/sports/nike-sports-marketing-difficult-days.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elliott Hill has been the new CEO of Nike just around 60 days now, taking over for the beleaguered company whose stock is down 27 percent this year, an inverse of the broader market. After a whirlwind tour of Nike offices and meeting athlete and league endorsers, Hill outlined some of his plans on an Read more...
The post More difficult days ahead for Nike as they re-invest in sports marketing appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kaplan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McDonald's Serves Up a Whole Holiday Menu in the UK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.brandeating.com/2024/12/mcdonalds-uk-2024-holiday-menu.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.brandeating.com/2024/12/mcdonalds-uk-2024-holiday-menu.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Christmas and the holiday season at McDonald's in the US largely consists of the Holiday Pie and holiday cups, over in the UK, the chain offers a whole holiday menu each year that includes seasonal burgers/sandwiches, a side, and desserts. They call it the "Festive Food Range."

Here's what you'll find on the 2024 holiday menu at McDonald's in the United Kingdom:


New Cheesy McCrispy - A crispy-fried chicken breast filet served with lettuce, crispy-fried onions, pickled onion chutney, bacon, Emmental cheese, and "deluxe" cheese sauce on a toasted sesame seed sourdough-style bun.
Big Tasty - A beef patty, cheese made with Emmental (similar to processed Swiss cheese), onions, tomatoes, and Big Tasty sauce (a smoky, creamy sauce), served on a toasted sesame seed bun.
Cheese Melt Dippers with Rich Tomato Dip - Breaded and fried rounds of cheese dippers made with Camembert and served with a tomato dip.
Terry's Orange Chocolate Pie - A chocolaty turnover-style pie filled with a Terry’s Chocolate Orange-flavored chocolate ganache.
Galaxy Caramel Latte - A latte blended with Galaxy Caramel-flavored syrup, topped with caramel cream and Galaxy Chocolate stars. Galaxy in the UK is what we know as Dove chocolate.
Galaxy Caramel Hot Chocolate - Hot chocolate with Galaxy Caramel-flavored syrup, topped with caramel cream and Galaxy Chocolate stars.
Galaxy Caramel McFlurry - Vanilla soft serve mixed with Galaxy Chocolate stars and topped with a Galaxy Caramel sauce.
Terry's Chocolate Orange McFlurry - Vanilla soft serve swirled with mini segments of Terry’s Chocolate Orange and topped with a Terry’s Chocolate Orange sauce.


In addition to the Festive Food Range, McDonald's UK also has a Grinch Happy Meal that includes a Grinch-themed box:



Toys for the holiday Happy Meal include Grinch and Max plushies and three different card games:

Photos via McDonald's UK.
Read more at Brand Eating!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brand Eating. Your Daily Fast Food Reading.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Longenhagen Prospects Chat: 12/20/24]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453335</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/eric-longenhagen-prospects-chat-12-20-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T16:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Prospect Impresario is in Philadelphia for the holidays. Will he draw from the energy of his homeland and be extra salty in chat? Bring a snowball and find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Longenhagen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN’s Dan Graziano eviscerates ‘con artist’ and ‘narcissist’ Aaron Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685205</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/dan-graziano-aaron-rodgers-unsportsmanlike-rant.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T16:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It isn’t often — if ever — that the cast of ESPN Radio’s Unsportsmanlike finds itself speechless. Only that’s exactly what happened on Friday morning, as Dan Graziano engaged in an epic rant regarding Aaron Rodgers. Graziano’s skewering of the 41-year-old quarterback came as the show discussed The Athletic’s recent report regarding the New York Read more...
The post ESPN’s Dan Graziano eviscerates ‘con artist’ and ‘narcissist’ Aaron Rodgers appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Awfulies: The best in sports radio & sports media podcasts]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684706</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/orig/2024-awfulies-best-sports-radio-media-podasts-ourand-kay-canty.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T16:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we’re celebrating the highs, lows, best, and worst of the year with The Awfulies. Started in 2022 and expanded in 2023, the Awful Announcing staff has cast its votes for who we think should take home the coveted golden microphone. Keep an eye on category and winner reveals all week long. And be sure to let Read more...
The post The 2024 Awfulies: The best in sports radio & sports media podcasts appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Keeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Is Nolan Arenado Anymore, and How Can He Be Traded?]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453266</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/who-is-nolan-arenado-anymore-and-how-can-he-be-traded/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T16:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will Arenado loosen up his no-trade list and save a mediocre joke that was 10 years in the making?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Baumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Unionizing Protect Contestants From The Reality Of Reality TV?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176872</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/could-unionizing-protect-contestants-from-the-reality-of-reality-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T15:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an industry-wide first, the National Labor Relations Board argued last week that contestants participating in Netflix’s hit reality TV dating show Love Is Blind should be classified as employees. If implemented into policy—which, admittedly, seems unlikely given the fact that Donald Trump is expected to fire the current NLRB general legal counsel—the filing could not only give more on-set protection to participants of shows like Love Is Blind but potentially allow them to unionize. 
Since its oddly prescient premiere in February 2020, which saw 15 men and 15 women dating, falling in love and eventually getting engaged sight unseen, Love Is Blind has faced allegations of mistreatment and coercion. Early contestants have accused producers of plying them with alcohol while regularly denying them food and water; one contestant alleged that production pushed her to continue filming even after she told them that she was experiencing suicidal ideation and wanted to leave. Over the past four years and seven seasons, the two production companies behind Love Is Blind—Kinetic Content and Delirium TV—have faced multiple lawsuits from former contestants. One of them alleges “inhumane working conditions” while another accuses Kinetic and Delirium of negligence, false imprisonment and sexual assault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shane Gillis is ‘College GameDay’ guest picker for Notre Dame-Indiana]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685199</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/shane-gillis-college-gameday-guest-picker-notre-dame-indiana.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T15:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even though College GameDay has only one game to cover on Friday when they kick off the newly expanded 12-team playoff in South Bend, they aren’t taking a pass on inviting in a guest picker with comedian Shane Gillis joining the fun. College GameDay is pulling an ultra-rare doubleheader this weekend with the first ever Read more...
The post Shane Gillis is ‘College GameDay’ guest picker for Notre Dame-Indiana appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeLinuxCo Workstation – Manjaro spin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139890</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/delinuxco-workstation-manjaro-spin/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T15:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The goal and purpose of DeLinuxCo is to have a workstation experience right from the start. It's a spin of Manjaro.
The post DeLinuxCo Workstation – Manjaro spin appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Inside the NBA’ crew send condolences to Ernie Johnson: ‘We definitely feel his pain’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685154</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/charles-barkley-shaq-kenny-smith-inside-the-nba-condolences-ernie-johnson.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T15:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Lefkoe, Charles Barkley, Kenny Smith and Shaquille O’Neal opened Inside the NBA with somber news about Ernie Johnson and his family Thursday night. Filling in for the longtime host of Inside the NBA, Lefkoe informed the audience Johnson was absent after his sister Christine died from cancer this week at the age of 72. Read more...
The post ‘Inside the NBA’ crew send condolences to Ernie Johnson: ‘We definitely feel his pain’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Awfulies: Best & worst in sports television]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684325</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/tv/2024-awfulies-best-television-inside-nba-first-things.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T15:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we’re celebrating the highs, lows, best, and worst of the year with The Awfulies. Started in 2022 and expanded in 2023, the Awful Announcing staff has cast its votes for who we think should take home the coveted golden microphone. Keep an eye on category and winner reveals all week long. And be sure to let Read more...
The post The 2024 Awfulies: Best & worst in sports television appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod, Sam Neumann and Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2025 ZiPS Projections: Detroit Tigers]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453248</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/2025-zips-projections-detroit-tigers/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T15:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tigers right now look like a .500 team, but that makes them an AL Central contender.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Szymborski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix wins 2027, 2031 Women’s World Cup rights]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685168</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/netflix/netflix-wins-2027-2031-womens-world-cup-rights.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T14:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix is officially a player in live sports thanks to a stunning victory in winning Women’s World Cup rights for the next two tournaments in 2027 and 2031. The streamer has long been on the outside looking in at live sports while big tech competitors like Amazon, YouTube, and Apple entered into the space. But Read more...
The post Netflix wins 2027, 2031 Women’s World Cup rights appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Hater’s Guide To The Williams-Sonoma Catalog]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176334</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-2024-haters-guide-to-the-williams-sonoma-catalog"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T14:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[walks out to greet you as you pull into my circular driveway]
There you are! Oh my goodness, look at you! You look so festive! Why don't you leave your bags in the breezeway for now and come on in? And MERRY CHRISTMAS! My gosh, I can finally say it! No more "happy holidays" or any of that nonsense. Doesn't it feel great? You and I can talk like normal people again! Oh, it was AWFUL for a while, wasn’t it? We just got Andley back from Conn College and you can't say boo to that girl without her telling you that you're the worst person alive! Good luck trying that on your boss when you start your internship at Credit Suisse, young lady! You can't invest in pronouns!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chicago Cubs Top 37 Prospects]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453142</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/chicago-cubs-top-37-prospects/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T14:05:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As this system stands right now, it's a shade below average in terms of both depth and high-end impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Longenhagen and Travis Ice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caitlin Clark’s Time interview is just what the WNBA needed]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684542</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/wnba/caitlin-clark-time-interview-outspoken.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T14:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Was there a more obvious pick for Time 2024 Athlete of the Year than Caitlin Clark? Not only did she break the NCAA scoring record in her final year of college just weeks before going first overall in the WNBA Draft, but she made the WNBA All-Star Team and won the WNBA’s Rookie of the Read more...
The post Caitlin Clark’s Time interview is just what the WNBA needed appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katie Lever</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charles Barkley doesn’t believe in adults getting Christmas presents: ‘It’s for the kids’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685069</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/tnt-sports/charles-barkley-christmas-presents-for-the-kids.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T13:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charles Barkley has shared his fair share of controversial takes over the years. But perhaps none will upset and divide more people than his take shared on Thursday about Christmas. People all over the world have differing opinions about Christmas and how the day should be celebrated. Some use the day as a way to Read more...
The post Charles Barkley doesn’t believe in adults getting Christmas presents: ‘It’s for the kids’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Al Michaels says he ‘wasn’t allowed to’ talk Super Bowl XXIX spread]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685079</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/al-michaels-super-bowl-xxix-spread.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T13:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fascinating part of NFL broadcasting over the years has been the league’s relationship with gambling, and specifically the way its broadcasters are allowed (or not allowed) to discuss gambling. Betting on NFL games has long been a thing, even long before that was legal in most jurisdictions, and so have been some levels of Read more...
The post Al Michaels says he ‘wasn’t allowed to’ talk Super Bowl XXIX spread appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 20, 2024: how to watch Indiana-Notre Dame CFP QF]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684971</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/viewing-picks/december-20-2024-watch-indiana-notre-dame-cfp-qf.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T12:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All Times Eastern Bundesliga Matchday 15 Bayern München vs. Red Bull Leipzig — ESPN Deportes/ESPN+, 2:20 p.m. College Basketball Men’s HBCU Challenge HBCU Doubleheader, Mohegan Sun Arena, Mohegan Sun Resort & Casino, Uncasville, CT Norfolk State vs. Grambling State — ESPNU, 4 p.m. Delaware State vs. Alabama State — ESPNU, 6:30 p.m. Valparaiso at Western Read more...
The post TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 20, 2024: how to watch Indiana-Notre Dame CFP QF appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plasma System Monitor – monitoring tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139897</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/plasma-system-monitor-monitoring-tool/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T11:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plasma System Monitor provides an interface for monitoring system sensors, process information and other system resources.
The post Plasma System Monitor – monitoring tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awful Announcing Podcast: Jeff Marek on Sportsnet, NHL expansion, J.T. Miller]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685094</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/orig/podcast-jeff-marek-sportsnet-nhl.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T11:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week’s episode of the Awful Announcing Podcast, host Brandon Contes interviews former Sportsnet NHL host and current host of The Sheet with Jeff Marek, Jeff Marek. Brandon and Jeff discuss a wide range of topics including his dismissal from Sportsnet, which cities are prime for an NHL expansion team, his thoughts on J.T. Read more...
The post Awful Announcing Podcast: Jeff Marek on Sportsnet, NHL expansion, J.T. Miller appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Bupp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bogdan Raczynski (Interview)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/bogdan-raczynski-interview</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/bogdan-raczynski-interview"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T08:02:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Friday so we’re listening to something more upbeat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[picocolors – tiny and fast library for terminal output formatting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139887</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/picocolors-tiny-fast-library-terminal-output-formatting/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T07:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[picocolors is billed as the tiniest and the fastest library for terminal output formatting with ANSI colors.
The post picocolors – tiny and fast library for terminal output formatting appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusion Principle]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3027/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3027/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lakers’ coach JJ Redick blames critical NBA broadcasters, social media discourse for ratings slump]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685054</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/lakers-jj-redick-broadcaster-criticism-ratings.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T04:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s been a lot of discussion out there around the NBA’s ratings this year. On Thursday, former ESPN analyst and podcaster and current Los Angeles Lakers head coach JJ Redick waded in. And he attributed some of the decline to criticism of the on-court product from broadcasters, as The Athletic’s Sam Amick shared on Bluesky: Read more...
The post Lakers’ coach JJ Redick blames critical NBA broadcasters, social media discourse for ratings slump appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Gottlieb blasts ESPN for taking ‘Nobody U’ comment out of context]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685013</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/radio/doug-gottlieb-blasts-espn-out-of-context-nobody-u-comment.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T04:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CBS Sports Radio host and Green Bay Phoenix men’s basketball coach Doug Gottlieb has found himself at the center of controversy in recent days on a number of different fronts. On Thursday, Gottlieb not only defended himself but also took aim at his many critics, including ESPN. On Monday, Gottlieb responded to a report from Read more...
The post Doug Gottlieb blasts ESPN for taking ‘Nobody U’ comment out of context appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buster Olney seemingly slams Cubs for handling of Sammy Sosa]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684850</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/sammy-sosa-cubs-apology-buster-olney.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T03:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thursday marked a significant repair in the relationship between the Chicago Cubs and Sammy Sosa. ESPN MLB insider Buster Olney does not seem pleased with how things happened. Sosa last played with the Cubs in 2004 and retired following the 2007 season. While his career numbers are undeniably worthy, Sosa—like other stars of his era Read more...
The post Buster Olney seemingly slams Cubs for handling of Sammy Sosa appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former NBA player John Amaechi goes off on Stephen A. Smith for ‘creepy’ viral video about women in Miami]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685000</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/meadowlark/john-amaechi-stephen-a-smith-creepy-viral-video.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T03:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN’s Stephen A. Smith has always been unapologetically himself in front of a camera. Even when it perhaps toes the line of inappropriate, which Smith’s recent comments did in the eyes of former NBA player John Amaechi earlier this week. On Tuesday’s edition of The Stephen A. Smith Show, Smith answered a question from a Read more...
The post Former NBA player John Amaechi goes off on Stephen A. Smith for ‘creepy’ viral video about women in Miami appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Kornheiser says CFP and NFL scheduling competing games is ‘football on football crime’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684937</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/tony-kornheiser-cfp-competing-games-football-on-football-crime.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T02:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFL and college football typically go to great lengths not to program against each other. Save for some low-wattage Thursday night college football games on ESPN competing with Thursday Night Football on Amazon, football fans are generally able to watch every important game—college or pro—without worrying about missing another. That can all be thrown Read more...
The post Tony Kornheiser says CFP and NFL scheduling competing games is ‘football on football crime’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Kornheiser says CFP and NFL scheduling competing games is ‘football on football crime’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684937</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/tony-kornheiser-cfp-nfl-competing-games-football-on-football-crime.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T02:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFL and college football typically go to great lengths not to program against each other. Save for some low-wattage Thursday night college football games on ESPN competing with Thursday Night Football on Amazon, football fans are generally able to watch every important game—college or pro—without worrying about missing another. That can all be thrown Read more...
The post Tony Kornheiser says CFP and NFL scheduling competing games is ‘football on football crime’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dan Marino on potential return to broadcasting: ‘I think I could if I wanted to’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684956</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/dan-marino-potential-return-broadcasting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T02:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hall of Fame quarterback Dan Marino last served as an NFL studio analyst over a decade ago. But in a recent interview, he shared that he is still very capable of serving in his old role again if he decides to do so in the future. Marino, of course, served as a studio analyst on Read more...
The post Dan Marino on potential return to broadcasting: ‘I think I could if I wanted to’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your 2024 NFL Week 16 announcing schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684932</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/schedules/nfl-week-16-announcing-schedule.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T01:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a look at the announcing assignments for Week 16 of the NFL season, including a Saturday doubleheader. That includes some discussion of a featured game or games in each slot based on broadcasters, matchups, or both. All times are Eastern. Thursday, Dec. 19 Featured/only game: Denver at LA Chargers Prime Video 8:15 p.m. Al Read more...
The post Your 2024 NFL Week 16 announcing schedule appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Williams returning to mornings on Golf Channel]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684830</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/golf/gary-williams-returning-mornings-golf-channel-5-clubs.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T01:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Golf Channel is adding some new morning programming to its lineup which will feature the return of a familiar face. Longtime Golf Channel broadcaster Gary Williams will return to the network’s morning lineup as part of a new one-hour morning show titled 5 Clubs on Golf Channel that will debut Monday, Jan. 6th. Williams helped Read more...
The post Gary Williams returning to mornings on Golf Channel appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Johnson blames NBA ratings decline on stars yukking it up: ‘They don’t hate each other’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684839</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/magic-johnson-blames-ratings-decline-stars.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T00:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With NBA TV ratings in decline, Magic Johnson believes players from opposing teams need to get back to hating each other. Everybody has a theory on why NBA viewership is down. Commissioner Adam Silver blames the demise of cable television, Shaquille O’Neal faults the three-point shot, Mike Francesa points to load management, Joe Mazzulla blames Read more...
The post Magic Johnson blames NBA ratings decline on stars yukking it up: ‘They don’t hate each other’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Marchand and John Ourand both predict Tom Brady will return for second season as Fox NFL analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684872</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/andrew-marchand-john-ourand-tom-brady-return-second-season-analyst.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T00:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One and done for Tom Brady at Fox? Not so fast, say sports media insiders Andrew Marchand and John Ourand. In their latest conversation on the Marchand Sports Media podcast, both put a stake in the ground predicting that the new lead NFL on Fox game analyst will return for the second season of his record 10-year, Read more...
The post Andrew Marchand and John Ourand both predict Tom Brady will return for second season as Fox NFL analyst appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Finebaum: My ‘legacy’ will be showing college football elites ‘where the country really is’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684841</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/paul-finebaum-show-legend-representation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T00:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN college football analyst and radio host Paul Finebaum is synonymous with his callers. None more so than an Alabama superfan known as “Legend.” In a new episode of the Pablo Torre Finds Out podcast heading into the College Football Playoff, Finebaum appeared to discuss his connection to those callers and the impact of his radio Read more...
The post Paul Finebaum: My ‘legacy’ will be showing college football elites ‘where the country really is’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Kelce rips anti-flag planting legislation: ‘I don’t like it. I’m not gonna lie’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684769</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/travis-jason-kelce-ohio-flag-planting-bill.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T23:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An anti-flag planting bill proposed by Ohio state Rep. Josh Williams has earned two more prominent critics — Jason and Travis Kelce. After Michigan’s upset win over Ohio State in November, some of the Wolverines attempted to plant a Michigan flag at midfield at Ohio Stadium — which triggered a fight with some of the Read more...
The post Jason Kelce rips anti-flag planting legislation: ‘I don’t like it. I’m not gonna lie’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NBA Cup Final viewership down big versus Lakers’ win last year]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684862</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/cup-final-viewership-down-big.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T23:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Viewership for the second ever NBA Cup championship game declined significantly compared to last year’s debut, but still proved to be a substantial upgrade versus a normal regular season game. Tuesday’s NBA Cup Final between the Milwaukee Bucks and Oklahoma City Thunder averaged 2.99 million viewers on ABC, per Jon Lewis of Sports Media Watch. Read more...
The post NBA Cup Final viewership down big versus Lakers’ win last year appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new Kansas City program steers residents to mental health or drug care rather than custody]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865975</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/a-new-kansas-city-program-steers-residents-to-mental-health-or-drug-care-rather-than-custody/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T23:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Riders wait for the Prospect Max bus at the 31st Street stop, in the first corridor to be included in the REACH program. (Mili Mansaray/The Beacon) You see someone in the midst of a mental breakdown, or high on drugs. Call 911 and they may get arrested. Things could get worse from there. They might lose their job, their apartment....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mili Mansaray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeff Marek on dismissal from Sportsnet: ‘It was bizarre’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684796</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nhl/jeff-marek-dismissal-sportsnet-bizarre.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T23:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five months after an abrupt dismissal from Sportsnet following 13 years with the network, Jeff Marek is excited for the next chapter of his career. One of the most well-known NHL analysts, Marek recently partnered with The Nation Network and the Daily Faceoff to launch his new show, The Sheet. In July, Marek was let Read more...
The post Jeff Marek on dismissal from Sportsnet: ‘It was bizarre’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Awful Announcing NFL/CFB rules analyst rankings]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684754</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/2024-football-rules-analyst-rankings.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T22:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The votes are in for the top broadcast football rules analysts. We asked Awful Announcing readers to grade nine rules analysts working on NCAA and NFL football broadcasts across a wide selection of networks, and received responses from more than 400 voters, similar to what we received for our scorebug rankings earlier this year. As Read more...
The post The 2024 Awful Announcing NFL/CFB rules analyst rankings appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13 Best Free and Open Source Tools for Novelists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=486</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/novelists/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T22:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing is one of the essential skills in modern society.
The post 13 Best Free and Open Source Tools for Novelists appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Mike Tomlin interview nearly gave Erin Andrews a ‘panic attack’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684751</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/erin-andrews-mike-tomlin-panic-attack.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T22:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Tomlin feels like an easy guy to root for, especially for Erin Andrews. Sure, he can come across as abrasive, like he did after the Pittsburgh Steelers’ 27-13 loss to the Philadelphia Eagles in Week 15. Tomlin might’ve told an official to “Get the f*ck” out of his face and snapped at a reporter Read more...
The post Why Mike Tomlin interview nearly gave Erin Andrews a ‘panic attack’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to popular CLI tools: tree]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=105876</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alternatives-popular-cli-tools-tree/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T22:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article spotlights alternative tools to tree, a utility that lists the contents of directories in a tree-like format.
The post Alternatives to popular CLI tools: tree appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN reveals new graphics package for College Football Playoff]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684808</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/reveals-new-graphics-package-college-football-playoff.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T22:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new playoff format means a new graphics package for ESPN. The Worldwide Leader will debut a brand new set of graphics on Friday when the Indiana Hoosiers visit South Bend to take on the Notre Dame Fighting Irish in the first ever game of the expanded College Football Playoff. To celebrate, ESPN dropped a Read more...
The post ESPN reveals new graphics package for College Football Playoff appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feeling Like Ozymandias, With Susie Banikarim]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176553</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/feeling-like-ozymandias-with-susie-banikarim"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T21:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no reason for a normal person to know who Carlos Watson is. This is why I have made it my business to reach as many members of the normal-person community with the Good News about the disgraced and deliriously scammy founder and figurehead of Ozy Media, who was sentenced to nearly 10 years in prison for various oafish and common financial crimes earlier this week. I understand that my personal grievances with, say, Vice Media founder Shane Smith are my own, and my own problem; I understand, too, that there is no reason for really anyone to know who Jim Spanfeller is, although I have not always honored that. I get all this.
But it is my belief that Watson's baroquely thirsty and fraudulent public arc, while powered by the specific scamminess and scuzz of online media during the previous decade, is wild and weird enough to resonate even with people lucky enough to have avoided working in that field during that time. We put that to the test this week by having our buddy and former GMG executive editor Susie Banikarim on to talk about her new podcast about Watson's rise and fall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kylie Kelce doesn’t want to ‘feed any conflict’ after dethroning Joe Rogan atop podcast charts]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684757</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/kylie-kelce-joe-rogan-podcast-charts.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T21:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kylie Kelce is the latest member of her family to launch a hit podcast, and it took her no time at all to find an audience. As the wife of Philadelphia Eagles legend turned ESPN star Jason Kelce, she was already in the spotlight before she debuted Not Gonna Lie in partnership with Wave Sports + Read more...
The post Kylie Kelce doesn’t want to ‘feed any conflict’ after dethroning Joe Rogan atop podcast charts appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Tirico advocates for NFL schedule flexibility, calling for Premier League-inspired approach]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684688</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/podcasts/mike-tirico-nfl-schedule-premier-league.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T21:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether through New Year’s resolutions or a fresh perspective on long-standing traditions, everyone is searching for change. It’s that time of the year. We already saw Joel Klatt voice that Army-Navy should be moved to Week 0. And that idea seemed better in his head than in actuality. Meanwhile, Mike Tirico has his own proposal Read more...
The post Mike Tirico advocates for NFL schedule flexibility, calling for Premier League-inspired approach appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: New York Jets Plagued By Woody Johnson’s Meddlesome Teen Sons]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176739</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/report-new-york-jets-plagued-by-woody-johnsons-meddlesome-teen-sons"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T20:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a beloved media tradition: when a dysfunctional team's dysfunctional season reaches its dysfunctional end, reporters covering that team are permitted to write one big notebook-dumping explainer/eulogy. With a few outré exceptions, no one cares enough about bad teams to justify two such stories; with a few outré exceptions, no team is quite dysfunctional enough to fill out more than one. If you are a Tennessee Titans fan, to take one example, this is more or less the one big thing you have left to look forward to this season. You already know the team is lousy, inert, soggy and sodden and miserable; in a few weeks, once everyone goes home, you will find out whether that has anything to do with Tony Pollard's insistence upon letting his pet puma wander around the locker room or some such thing. That is how it usually works.
But the New York Jets are different. Everyone always and already knows about the pumas wandering around the locker room. Every week their ulcerous and increasingly haggard quarterback joins Pat McAfee's ESPN show via Zoom, seemingly from the Black Lodge, and starts Speaking Real Words about the germ theory of disease or whatever else is troubling him; this week, Aaron Rodgers testily demanded that critics of his (terrible!) recent play disclose their vaccination status, either as an indication of their bias or just as proof that they lack the courage that permitted Rodgers to self-immunize against infectious disease, possibly by eating hundreds of small, smooth rocks. This is just how the Jets are, and more or less how they have been since the pharmaceutical heir Woody Johnson bought the team 25 years ago. That they have the longest streak in American pro sports without a playoff appearance is not surprising given all that, but also feels somehow incidental to the organization's broader project, which under Johnson's blithely buttheaded stewardship has mostly been to generate news about people getting fired.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Best Free GUI Tools to Find and Delete Duplicate Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=56056</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-tools-find-delete-duplicate-files/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T20:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We feature free and open source software that lets you find and remove the duplicate files.
The post 6 Best Free GUI Tools to Find and Delete Duplicate Files appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Herbstreit addresses why son committed to Michigan and reaction from Ohio State fans]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684721</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/kirk-chase-herbstreit-ohio-state-michigan.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T20:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Dan Katz (Barstool Big Cat) pointed out, Kirk Herbstreit’s son, Chase, committing to the University of Michigan — his father’s alma mater’s fiercest rival — stirred up some serious waves. And rightfully so. For the first time publicly, Kirk addressed his son’s decision to commit to the University of Michigan, joining $10 million man Read more...
The post Kirk Herbstreit addresses why son committed to Michigan and reaction from Ohio State fans appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen A. Smith cringes at Dan Orlovsky’s mayonnaise admission]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684718</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/food/stephen-a-smith-cringes-dan-orlovsky-mayonnaise-admission.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T20:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN should be used to Dan Orlovsky dropping bad food takes by now, but this latest one really seemed to irk Stephen A. Smith. There are mayonnaise eaters and mayonnaise lovers. Consider Orlovsky among the latter. Because according to the former NFL quarterback, mayonnaise and more mayonnaise is all you need to make a great Read more...
The post Stephen A. Smith cringes at Dan Orlovsky’s mayonnaise admission appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eat This Now: Cookies at Sweet Kiss Brigadeiro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865750</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/eat-this-now-cookies-at-sweet-kiss-brigadeiro/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T20:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cookie at Sweet Kiss Brigadeiro // Photo by Sarah Sipple These cookies are less like a sweet kiss and more like a giant smooch! Sweet Kiss Brigadeiro bakes large, filled cookies in classic and creative flavors.  But what is a brigadeiro?   The Brazilian sweet is a truffle, known as brigadeiro. These bite-sized balls come in a variety of flavors including...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eat This Now: Cookies at Sweet Kiss Brigadeiro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865750</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/eat-this-now-cookies-at-sweet-kiss-brigadeiro/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T20:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cookie at Sweet Kiss Brigadeiro // Photo by Sarah Sipple These cookies are less like a sweet kiss and more like a giant smooch! Sweet Kiss Brigadeiro bakes large, filled cookies in classic and creative flavors.  But what is a brigadeiro?   The Brazilian sweet is a truffle, known as brigadeiro. These bite-sized balls come in a variety of flavors including...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Francesa scoffs at Adam Silver blaming NBA ratings problem on cable]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684689</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/mike-francesa-adam-silver-rating.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T19:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NBA has a ratings problem and Mike Francesa is convinced commissioner Adam Silver has no clue what it is. Silver addressed the league’s ratings dip this week while speaking to reporters ahead of the NBA Cup championship game. Reluctant to blame the product, Silver instead pointed to the trend of declining cable viewership. But Read more...
The post Mike Francesa scoffs at Adam Silver blaming NBA ratings problem on cable appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gtree – generate trees and directories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139766</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gtree-generate-trees-directories/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T19:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[gtree is a CLI-based utility which uses Markdown to generate directory trees and directories itself, and also verifies directories.
The post gtree – generate trees and directories appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Lawson Enters The Red Bull Second-Seat Gantlet]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176741</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/liam-lawson-enters-the-red-bull-second-seat-gantlet"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T19:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the news that everything was thinking about, Mercedes announced Thursday morning that Valtteri Bottas would be returning to the team as its reserve driver. Bottas spent the past three years as an unfortunate, i.e. racing for Alfa Romeo–turned–Kick Sauber, but up until 2021, Bottas had represented everything a championship-winning team needed in a second driver: fast enough to ensure 1-2 finishes, good enough in qualifying to occasionally beat Lewis Hamilton, not quite good enough to disrupt a clear 1-2 hierarchy. The full circle continues what has been considered one of the kinder arcs for a second driver post-eviction: freed from the pressure of one-year contracts and matching up against literally Lewis Hamilton, Bottas grew a mullet and a mustache, posted ass, and then managed to return to Mercedes with zero expectations.
If Sergio Pérez has half that, he will be fortunate. Red Bull announced yesterday that Pérez would be leaving the team after three seasons. Pérez is already missing out on the clean end-of-term-into-multi-year-contract-with-another-team sequence that Bottas got. Lest anyone forgets, Pérez's contract was initially due to expire at the end of the 2024 season, but six months ago, Red Bull Racing announced that they had extended his contract by two years. This was a baffling decision at face value, but could be explained by the disaster of Red Bull leadership, McLaren evading consideration as legitimate Constructors' Championship contender, Daniel Ricciardo still being in the second VCARB seat, and Pérez having a far worse second half of the season compared to his first—he had four podiums prior to the extension, and zero after. In the end, Red Bull had to worm its way out of an easily avoidable extension, and took a no doubt expensive route to an inevitable result; Sergio Pérez lasted for longer than expected, but he, too, fell victim to the curse of the second Red Bull seat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Woody Johnson reportedly shares links from Jets blogs with top football decision-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684638</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/woody-johnson-blogs-jets-x-factor.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T19:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, it’s well-known that Woody Johnson perhaps pays too much attention to the media. He’s not totally at fault for the New York Jets’ shortcomings. As previously outlined, the media narrative absolving now-former general manager Joe Douglas of blame misses the mark. But there’s a common denominator her, as best exemplified by the team Read more...
The post Woody Johnson reportedly shares links from Jets blogs with top football decision-makers appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Several bars and restaurants may not carry Netflix’s Christmas Day NFL games]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684616</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/netflix/several-sports-bars-wont-carry-christmas-day-games.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T18:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent surge in sporting events being exclusive to streaming services has led to many questions about the ability of bars and restaurants to carry such games. But while most establishments seem to have found ways to carry those games — albeit often at a hefty price — it doesn’t appear that will be the Read more...
The post Several bars and restaurants may not carry Netflix’s Christmas Day NFL games appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>