<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-10-23T12:31:27.874Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Previewing Upcoming Qualifying Offer Decisions: Pitchers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=827885</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/previewing-upcoming-qualifying-offer-decisions-pitchers-2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:49:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the baseball world’s immediate focus is on the upcoming showdown between two behemoths, the offseason looms just after the World Series. One of the first key decisions for teams is whether to issue a qualifying offer to any of their impending free agents. Clubs have until the fifth day after the conclusion of the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#1 In His Mind, But Not Where It Counts — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076512</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/1-in-his-mind-but-not-where-it-counts-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rose-Tinted Parenting Or Another Bold Lie?: Even Trump's praise needs fact checking.
No Jail Time For Steel: Georgia's Supreme Court has a much better grasp of how the courtroom should work.
Reading Is Fundamental!: Shame it took Jesse Binnall this long.
Parenting Ain't Easy: Especially when opposing counsel acts like this.
The post #1 In His Mind, But Not Where It Counts — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Short List Of Presidents That Really Understand The Supreme Court]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076513</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-short-list-of-presidents-that-really-understand-the-supreme-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They had a unique perspective on the institution.
The post The Short List Of Presidents That Really Understand The Supreme Court appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litera’s Former CEO Returns To That Role, As Current CEO Moves Into Temporary Advisory Role]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076483</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/10/literas-former-ceo-returns-to-that-role-as-current-ceo-moves-into-temporary-advisory-role.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T22:33:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avaneesh Marwaha and Litera have another surprise: He has returned as CEO 'to lead the company through the next chapter of integration and innovation,' the company said.
The post Litera’s Former CEO Returns To That Role, As Current CEO Moves Into Temporary Advisory Role appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: KU Basketball kicks off ’24-25 season with Late Night in the Phog featuring Lil Jon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857337</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-ku-basketball-kicks-off-24-25-season-with-late-night-in-the-phog-featuring-lil-jon/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T22:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lil Jon. // photo by Isabella Galvan Friday night, the University of Kansas Jayhawks kicked off basketball season with the annual Late Night in the Phog. It was the 40th annual installment of the event, which showcased both the teams on the court and the new renovations to Allen Fieldhouse, such as new scoreboards and screens and “new amenities throughout...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isabella Galvan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Lobbying Practices Bracing For Change In White House]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076486</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/biglaw-lobbying-practices-bracing-for-change-in-white-house/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will the financial picture for these practices change based on which party wins the White House?
The post Biglaw Lobbying Practices Bracing For Change In White House appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Courtroom To Center Stage: How Legal Drama And Startup Chaos Fuel ‘Dirty Legal Secrets’]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076412</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/from-courtroom-to-center-stage-how-legal-drama-and-startup-chaos-fuel-dirty-legal-secrets/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:28:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zhao brings a fresh, comedic, and thought-provoking look at the real-world chaos behind startup culture.
The post From Courtroom To Center Stage: How Legal Drama And Startup Chaos Fuel ‘Dirty Legal Secrets’ appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga V. Mack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruby Freeman And Shaye Moss Win Right To Collect Giuliani’s Unpaid Legal Bills From Trump Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076502</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/ruby-freeman-and-shaye-moss-win-right-to-collect-giulianis-unpaid-legal-bills-from-trump-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T20:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hourly or quantum meruit?
The post Ruby Freeman And Shaye Moss Win Right To Collect Giuliani’s Unpaid Legal Bills From Trump Campaign appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infuriating Story Of The Bullsh*t Working Parents Have To Deal With In The Legal Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076484</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/infuriating-story-of-the-bullsht-working-parents-have-to-deal-with-in-the-legal-industry/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T20:03:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It doesn't make you a worse attorney to have a modicum of compassion for your opposition.
The post Infuriating Story Of The Bullsh*t Working Parents Have To Deal With In The Legal Industry appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmarks And Outcomes — ‘Moneyball’ For GenAI (Part I)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076435</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/benchmarks-and-outcomes-moneyball-for-genai-part-i/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T19:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The movie 'Moneyball' has some lessons to impart about benchmarking AI in legal.
The post Benchmarks And Outcomes — ‘Moneyball’ For GenAI (Part I) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Crutchfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manor Records rings in seventh year of lifting local music at Friday night celebration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856519</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/manor-records-rings-in-seventh-year-of-lifting-local-music-at-friday-night-celebration/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T19:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Provided by Shaun Crowley After providing an outlet for local musicians for nearly a decade, Manor Records—a non-profit DIY record label and record store—will be celebrating its seventh birthday this Friday.  Manor Records started out as a house venue in a basement and has since become a beloved record label that supports artists across Missouri, Kansas, and Oklahoma. Manor Bands...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Your Law Degree For Good]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076497</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/using-your-law-degree-for-good/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T18:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law school clinics can be a bridge to practice.
The post Using Your Law Degree For Good appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Job, Jesse Binnall, You Finally Read The North Carolina Pleading Standards]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076493</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/good-job-jesse-binnall-you-finally-read-the-north-carolina-pleading-standards/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And you pro hac-ed in, too!
The post Good Job, Jesse Binnall, You Finally Read The North Carolina Pleading Standards appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Go Deaf]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171144</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-to-go-deaf"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T16:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew's book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you're at it. Today, we're talking about crutches, eye black, the wave, potluck, and more.
This'll be a more expedient Funbag than usual, given that I'm spending all week at the Defector offsite meetings, where we'll make subtle tweaks to our blueprint for global domination. The Jamboroo will also be lighter than usual. But don't worry, our commenters are adept at taking discussions from here and running with them. So join the scrum down below and the full-length Bag/Roo will be back before you know it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Brags That Daughter Tiffany Trump Graduated ‘No. 1’ In Class — But Georgetown Law Doesn’t Rank Students]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076487</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/donald-trump-brags-that-daughter-tiffany-trump-graduated-no-1-in-class-but-georgetown-law-doesnt-rank-students/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T16:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How completely and utterly embarrassing. Poor Tiffany Trump.
The post Donald Trump Brags That Daughter Tiffany Trump Graduated ‘No. 1’ In Class — But Georgetown Law Doesn’t Rank Students appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Global Law Firms Are Bridging Cultures With AI [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076329</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/how-global-law-firms-are-bridging-cultures-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T15:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frankie Williams of DeepL weighs in on AI-powered translation tools and the potential of emerging tech.
The post How Global Law Firms Are Bridging Cultures With AI appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ABOVE THE LAW</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Megadeth’s Big ‘Risk’ Did Not Pay Off]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169299</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/megadeths-big-risk-did-not-pay-off"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T15:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it is time for the Defector staff to go into seclusion for our annual company meetings and fall frolic. This year we are gathering in Atlantic City, America's abandoned playground. We decided to hold a mini theme week to keep the site robust and full of blogs while we're in meetings. This year's theme: Risk!
Eight years earlier, Metallica had become the biggest rock band in the world. How they did it depends on who you talk to. The self-titled "Black Album" was either softer, slower, more accessible than their previous epic thrash, a concession to the tastes of contemporary music fandom, or, if you ask an early Metallica fan, they sold out. No matter. They sold. It went 16x platinum. Metallica, once the band of nitrous-huffing burnouts and metal-militia headbangers and your older brother who can't keep a job and people who thought Guns 'n' Roses was for girls, was now MTV famous, solidly mainstream. This was absolutely not a given. It could have tanked. Their fans could have turned on them. Bruce Dickinson, frontman of Iron Maiden, gave Metallica credit for "taking the risk and deservedly reaping the enormous rewards."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fray return to Truman with nostalgic hits and post-hiatus EP tracks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857154</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/the-fray-return-to-truman-with-nostalgic-hits-and-post-hiatus-ep-tracks/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T15:03:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fray. // photo by Tommy Vean The Fray took the Truman stage Friday night, marking their first Kansas City performance since going on an indefinite hiatus in 2016. Now comprised of Joe King, Dave Welsh, and Ben Wysocki, the band returned in full form, proving that their pop-rock sound is as great as ever. Opening the night was Rett...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tommy Vean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calling All Biglaw Associates: 2024 Bonus Season Awaits]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076485</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/calling-all-biglaw-associates-2024-bonus-season-awaits/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T14:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Make your predictions and share your thoughts in our annual bonus season survey.
The post Calling All Biglaw Associates: 2024 Bonus Season Awaits appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: 2 more rain chances ahead (TUE-10/22)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3704267</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-2-more-rain-chances-ahead-tue-10-22/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T14:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well we finally cracked the dry string of days in KC! Last night while most of you were sleeping we had .05" of rain with a skinny line of showers/storms moving through quickly. That concluded our 27 day straight rain-free stretch, that while not a record in terms of all time dry stretches, certainly was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer Where A Piano-Playing Pig Once Summered]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076467</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/10/summer-where-a-piano-playing-pig-once-summered"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T14:02:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phil Falcone flogs another house.
The post Summer Where A Piano-Playing Pig Once Summered appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Cares: Housing History]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851113</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-cares-housing-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T13:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carmaletta Williams, CEO of the Black Archives of Mid-America, shows some of the objects a cabin believed to have belonged to a former slave named Lucy Willis, who lived in Missouri. // Photo by Beth Lipoff The Black Archives of Mid-America started as a collection in the trunk of a car. Now, it has its own building with numerous exhibits...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Lipoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Philadelphia Has A Lot To Lose On The New 76ers Arena]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170126</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/philadelphia-has-a-lot-to-lose-on-the-new-76ers-arena"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T13:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No $2 billion price tags or beloved local bars uprooted by eminent domain. But does that make it, you know, good?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neil deMause</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.22.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076474</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-22-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T12:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Central Park 5 have figured out what Dominion and Jean Carroll did -- Trump is a defamation machine and you don't have to take it. [NBC]
* Murdoch sues Perplexity for training on content which is dumb, but not as dumb as thinking the Wall Street Journal is good enough content to use for training. [Reuters]
* Goodwin pushes back against layoff narrative. [American Lawyer]
* Lawyer says trust accounts were needed to avoid becoming homeless. [ABA Journal]
* A government agency whose whole method of delivering results is now under siege? Which party could possibly be responsible? [Reuters]
* People having sex might not get pregnant if Joe Biden has his way. [Law360]
The post Morning Docket: 10.22.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: The Dead South at the Midland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857149</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-the-dead-south-at-the-midland/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T12:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dead South. // photo by Allison Scavo The Dead South with Henry Wagons The Midland Theatre Wednesday, October 16 The Dead South is an energetic Canadian folk-bluegrass band with haunting harmonies. Their alternative country style brings a gritty, foot-stomping sound while their distinctive attire only adds to their rustic, outlaw aesthetic. Banjo player Colton Crawford shared with us that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Scavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hickory Crawdads to play as Goat-Karts]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82791</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/21/hickory-crawdads-to-play-as-goat-karts/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T03:54:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hickory Crawdads, Single-A affiliate of the Texas Rangers in the Carolina League, introduced an alternate identity just moments ago that pays tribute one of the area’s earliest industries, as well as one of its popular contemporary pastimes. The Hickory Goat-Karts brand is an homage to both auto racing and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Caputo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Firm Sets The Record Straight On Layoffs — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076466</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/biglaw-firm-sets-the-record-straight-on-layoffs-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T23:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goodwin Is Watching Fishbowl & Reddit: And they're setting the rumors straight on layoffs.
Reconsider Studying At Harvard: Law students get in trouble for having a study group. This is what we're calling a protest now?
That's Some Expensive Parchment!: SNL has a recommendation on how to use your JD. I would avoid it.
Judge Cleans Up DeSantis's Stupidity: Maybe one day he'll understand how the First Amendment works.
Does Any Competent Lawyer Care?: World's richest goofball really could use some help.
The post Biglaw Firm Sets The Record Straight On Layoffs — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offhand Lie About Central Park 5 Lands Trump Back In Legal Trouble]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076464</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/offhand-lie-about-central-park-5-lands-trump-back-in-legal-trouble/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T23:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He is really good at being demonstrably wrong in public! 
The post Offhand Lie About Central Park 5 Lands Trump Back In Legal Trouble appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The City That’s The Exception To The Biglaw Lateral Partner Hiring Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076462</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-city-thats-the-exception-to-the-biglaw-lateral-partner-hiring-boom/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lateral party missed this city.
The post The City That’s The Exception To The Biglaw Lateral Partner Hiring Boom appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet The First-Ever Openly Transgender Lawyer To Argue Before SCOTUS]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076427</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/meet-the-first-ever-openly-transgender-lawyer-to-argue-before-scotus/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T21:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations on this outstanding accomplishment.
The post Meet The First-Ever Openly Transgender Lawyer To Argue Before SCOTUS appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: KC Mavericks claim a demanding victory over Wichita in home-opener]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857023</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-kc-mavericks-claim-a-demanding-victory-over-wichita-in-home-opener/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T21:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City Mavericks versus Wichita Thunder on Saturday, Oct. 19, 2024. // Photo by Eli Ralls The Kansas City Mavericks take down the Wichita Thunder 5-2 in home-opener of the ECHL 2024 Season on Saturday, Oct. 19. The boys in orange and white wasted no time getting the goals rolling this season, scoring their first of the game in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Ralls</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So Much For Free Speech: Harvard Law Students Punished For Reading Together At Campus Library]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076445</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/so-much-for-free-speech-harvard-law-students-punished-for-reading-together-at-campus-library/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T20:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even study groups are complex now. 
The post So Much For Free Speech: Harvard Law Students Punished For Reading Together At Campus Library appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Played Pretend In A McDonald’s I Once Knew Intimately]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170996</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/donald_trump_mcdonalds_feasterville_playing_pretend"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T20:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I will admit that it has shaken me to my very core, or at least to the point where I have not been able to get through a post that was supposed to be mostly jokes. On Sunday, Donald Trump went to a McDonald’s in Feasterville, Pa., that I have previously visited plenty of times, a McDonald’s just down from the restaurant where my high school girlfriend worked. (That restaurant is now an AutoZone.)
Trump was there for a photo op designed to push the story, which has been a favorite among the sort of people that would like this kind of thing, that Kamala Harris never worked at McDonald’s. Though there’s no record of that gig—paper short-term employment records from 1983 wouldn’t have been kept, I am forced to explain seriously—the Washington Post writes that McDonald’s “accepts” that Harris worked there. Trump's stunt was obviously a bit of pointless political theater; Trump was there for a photo op that would be considered embarrassing were it done by anyone else on the planet but the planet’s most embarrassing man. It was nonetheless covered pretty straightforwardly by the media, as they tend to do with Trump. He pretended to be a McDonald’s employee for 15 minutes; many news outlets used a headline that he “worked” there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Jayhawks try to turn season around with win over Houston at Arrowhead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856552</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-jayhawks-try-to-turn-season-around-with-win-over-houston-at-arrowhead/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T20:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas Jayhawks versus Houston Cougars on Saturday, Oct. 19. // Photo by Tarik Sykes The Jayhawks took over Arrowhead on Saturday, Oct. 19, as they clashed heads against the Houston Cougars. Both teams have underperformed this season, but KU comes out on top with a 42-14 win over the Texas school. Jalon Daniels and Devin Neal led the squad to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarik Sykes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conquering Conferences: The Art Of The Graceful Exit]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076299</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/conquering-conferences-the-art-of-the-graceful-exit/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T20:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knowing how to bow out gracefully is key to maintaining your social finesse.
The post Conquering Conferences: The Art Of The Graceful Exit appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEJAL PATEL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Temwa Chawinga shatters more records as Current breeze to victory on Saturday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856532</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-temwa-chawinga-shatters-more-records-as-current-breeze-to-victory-on-saturday/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T19:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KC Current versus San Diego Wave on Saturday, Oct. 19, 2024. // Photo by Tarik Sykes KC Current took down San Diego Wave in a dominant fashion on Saturday, Oct. 19, capping the game off with four goals scored, only letting up one in minute 88 of the match. The balls began flying into the back of the next in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarik Sykes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Rebukes DeSantis Admin: ‘It’s The First Amendment, Stupid.’]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076441</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/judge-rebukes-desantis-admin-its-the-first-amendment-stupid/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T19:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not 'speech,' it's 'sanitary nuisance!'
The post Judge Rebukes DeSantis Admin: ‘It’s The First Amendment, Stupid.’ appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SNL Nails The Dumbest Thing To Do With Your JD]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076446</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/snl-nails-the-dumbest-thing-to-do-with-your-jd/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T18:29:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Put your law degree to work -- but not like that.
The post SNL Nails The Dumbest Thing To Do With Your JD appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Southampton Is Too Stubborn For The Premier League]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171058</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/southampton-is-too-stubborn-for-the-premier-league"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T18:28:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Promotion from the Championship into the Premier League is a double-edged sword. On the one hand, it is the greatest financial boost in world soccer, one that can change a club's entire future. On the other, the clubs that make the trip into the top division often have to throw out everything that worked in the Championship in order to survive.
It's not too bold to say that teams reliant on possession in their chase for promotion must quickly adapt to playing without the ball against the Liverpools and Arsenals of the world. This is a lesson that Southampton is learning ever so painfully at the start of this season, and whether the club takes it to heart or not will likely dictate whether the Saints go marching back to the Championship next season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Judges Lays Into Biglaw Attorneys For Running Up Legal Bills]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076443</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/federal-judges-lays-into-biglaw-attorneys-for-running-up-legal-bills/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T17:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Benchslapped over an effort to 'gum up the works.'
The post Federal Judges Lays Into Biglaw Attorneys For Running Up Legal Bills appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bayern Munich Updates Colors to Comply With New German Accessibility Law]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82758</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/21/bayern-munich-updates-colors-to-comply-with-new-german-accessibility-law/soccer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T17:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[German Accessibility Improvement Act brings country's law into alignment with European Accessibility Act and includes guidelines on contrast ratio between colors on digital platforms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mets Ran Out Of Magic]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170974</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-mets-ran-out-of-magic"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T17:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's no percentage in being right about a baseball team you care about. It's nice to feel smart, I guess, but "feeling smart" and for that matter "being right" are not really what I got into any of this for. Those are for gamblers and pedants, and of all the reasons that have made me care about the New York Mets during my life—habit and family custom and various personality defects specific to me, including but not limited to stubbornness and fatalism and whatever it is that makes people bite their fingernails—it has never crossed my mind that doing so was somehow a reasonable thing to do.
In a sense, being right about the team you care about is the last thing a person would want. Again, pedants and gamblers will differ on this, but they're in it for different reasons. It fits, in a bleak sort of way, that those are the types of fans sports leagues seem to be selecting for, or actively trying to create; owners, being owners, would naturally prefer that their fans be consumers instead of ... whatever this other way of caring is. The consumer relationship is easier to produce and reproduce, and much more readily leveraged. It reflects the way in which owners and executive types understand more or less everything, but also it makes a sort of pragmatic sense. It is easier to understand a baseball team as an expensive entertainment product that generates revenue on various platforms than it is as a machine that helps people become insane in ways of their choosing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Biglaw Firm Shuts Down Layoff Rumors By Issuing Statement On Fishbowl, Reddit]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076428</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/goodwin-shuts-down-layoff-rumors-by-issuing-statement-on-fishbowl-reddit/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T17:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contrary to what you may have heard, there are no layoffs going on at Goodwin right now. 
The post Top Biglaw Firm Shuts Down Layoff Rumors By Issuing Statement On Fishbowl, Reddit appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If You Must Gamble, Gamble In Person, Like An Adult]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170863</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/if-you-must-gamble-gamble-in-person-like-an-adult"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again it is time for the Defector staff to go into seclusion for our annual company meetings and fall frolic. This year we are gathering in Atlantic City, America's abandoned playground. We decided to hold a mini theme week to keep the site robust and full of blogs while we're in meetings. This year's theme: Risk!
As a general rule, risk is overrated, both as a spur to future success and as a general way of life. The myth that risk begets reward has always been a self-aggrandizing lie told by the ones who won and stood on the skulls of the ones who didn't. The thought that risk is an excellent provider of adrenaline is actually provable nonsense. Risk, put simply, sucks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Notes]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170985</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/programming-notes-6"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello. Prepare to receive precious information. This week, the staff of Defector is once again gathering in a secret location to hold our all-company meetings. We are not going to the woods this year. Instead, we are going somewhere awful, because we are stupid. You know the drill by now. Due to these meetings, we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Liberty Were Built, Bought, And Blessed]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170999</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-liberty-were-built-bought-and-blessed"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a relief when it all ended: An ugly overtime. A straight-up bad Game 5. A gripping Finals series. The greatest, noisiest WNBA season in memory. And for the New York Liberty, winners of their first-ever championship on Sunday night, a decades-long tradition of heartbreak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Needs People Who Care About Him… And Have Law Degrees]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076437</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/elon-musk-needs-people-who-care-about-him-and-have-law-degrees/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk's new voter registration lottery is... certainly not what a lawyer would recommend.
The post Elon Musk Needs People Who Care About Him… And Have Law Degrees appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep Them Coming: Familiar Stranger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851106</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/keep-them-coming-familiar-stranger/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kristen Thomas // Photo by Nicole Bissey Role-play serves as a gateway between imagination and desire. Your brain is your biggest sex organ, so role-play offers a way to use it to build a highly erotic encounter. Whether you’re in a relationship and you two (or more) work together to formulate a playful time, or you’re single and turning to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristen Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Thomson Reuters Supercharged CoCounsel With Gen AI Advances [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076356</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/how-thomson-reuters-supercharged-cocounsel-with-gen-ai-advances/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T15:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CoCounsel 2.0 is a faster, more integrated, and smarter AI legal assistant.
The post How Thomson Reuters Supercharged CoCounsel With Gen AI Advances appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Took A TikTok Class. What Happened Next Blew My Mind]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170900</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-took-a-tiktok-class-what-happened-next-blew-my-mind"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T15:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inside me there are two wolves. The first is super embarrassed to admit that I paid lots of money to an influencer to teach me how to make TikToks this summer. The only thing less cool than putting effort into your social media presence is paying someone to teach you how to put effort into your social media presence. The second wolf is the one who writes this column, who is curious about the way the attention economy has led many of us to commodify our identities online, the way that commodification can translate directly to money, and how requisite it's all starting to feel.
Parasocial appeal is the core of what constitutes success on the internet right now. Are you able to convey your personality in such a condensed way that strangers feel like they know you, and even like you? Can you quickly tell the story of who you are through videos and images? It’s harder than it looks. If you don’t believe me, open up your front-facing camera right now and try recording yourself telling a funny story. Now, hit post. It’s miserable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thirteen Times Athletes Wore Typos on their Uniforms]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82753</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/21/thirteen-times-athletes-wore-typos-on-their-uniforms/featured/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T15:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typos on Jerseys? It happens! Here's a look at thirteen times players wore spelling errors during an actual game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Creamer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Oct. 21: Sub-liminal Messages]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171033</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-oct-21-sub-liminal-messages"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T15:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Man cannot live by bread alone, but maybe he can live by crosswords alone. This week's puzzle was constructed by Malaika Handa and Stephen Lurie, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Malaika has been publishing crossword puzzles since 2021, and currently contributes to Vulture's daily puzzle. Stephen has been publishing crossword puzzles since *checks calendar* October 21, 2024. You can find both of them in Brooklyn, where this puzzle will be financing a tasty treat.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Impossible Question Each For Harris And Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076424</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/one-impossible-question-each-for-harris-and-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T14:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You could ask Trump or Harris hard questions in interviews, but you'd never hear an answer. 
The post One Impossible Question Each For Harris And Trump appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Herrmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let Me Push The Win Button]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170998</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/let-me-push-the-dodgers-win-button"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T14:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear the Dodgers,
I saw that you have a Win Button, a button that Dodger Stadium music director/organist Dieter Ruehle hits when you win. This button is intriguing to me.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: At least there are some rain chances (MON-10/21)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3703246</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-at-least-there-are-some-rain-chances-mon-10-21/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T14:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's going to be another warm and breezy day for late October, with average highs in the mid-60s. Today, we will easily exceed those values as highs soar to around 80° or so before the end of the afternoon. While the records are in the 89° range for highs, and we won't get close to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedge Fund Manager Suggests Index Funds If You’d Like To Make Some Money]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076417</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/10/hedge-fund-manager-suggests-index-funds-if-youd-like-to-make-some-money"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T14:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As long as it lasts, because David Einhorn's sure as hell not gonna make any for the foreseeable future.
The post Hedge Fund Manager Suggests Index Funds If You’d Like To Make Some Money appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[History Is For The Dead And The Boring]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170976</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dodgers-yankees-world-series"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T13:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lots of fans can claim to be "long-suffering" as a labeling fetish, even if they aren't. New York Liberty fans, for instance, were long-suffering—until Sunday night, when they cashed in their 28 years without a championship and transitioned into "deliriously smug, smugly delirious, and not even pissed at Sabrina Ionescu any more." It happens that fast. The previous almost-three decades notwithstanding, they got their money's worth, and then some.
And then there's this World Series, which is the dead opposite, and more's the pity. Nothing will leaden eyelids quite like listening to Yankee fans and Dodger fans grind on the rest of us civilians about their respective places on the double-decker throne, let alone their shared hearkening back to their joint heritage as the keepers of the sport back when baseball had not yet cracked the Pacific Time Zone. A nation already hopelessly fractured and ready to go even more Serb and Croat two Tuesdays from now can safely unite as one, however briefly, in our hatred of both teams. The prognosis wasn’t good regardless, but expect the next fortnight to be hell with a Bob Costas voiceover. Fox has the games, but it's not his voice that offends, you see; rather the subject matter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.21.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076423</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-21-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T13:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Former Biglaw partner sentenced to 16 months in prison. What's the matter number on that time? [ABA Journal]
* Prosecutor sues Georgetown over data breach in rare instance where a Georgetown graduate doesn't want everyone to know about it. [Reuters]
* With a new film out there about Trump's relationship with Roy Cohn, the Advocate has a deep dive into the famed lawyer's life and times. [Advocate]
* Oklahoma is asking the Supreme Court to force the federal government to give back funding for medical services that it withheld after Oklahoma declared that it wasn't going to allow those medical services. [Law360]
* Law school clinic working on Supreme Court case aimed at protecting the rights of... straight people? [Balls and Strikes]
* FTC's new merger rules exemplify ongoing fight within the agency. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Biglaw firms building out alumni programs. [American Lawyer]
The post Morning Docket: 10.21.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Overland Park Convention Center’s Executive Chef David Ruiz]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855565</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-overland-park-convention-centers-executive-chef-david-ruiz/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T13:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of David Ruiz Listen up, foodies—Kansas City just upped the culinary ante when the Overland Park Convention Center hired David Ruiz as the venue’s new executive chef. Ruiz—a James Beard Foundation competition winner—has quite the impressive culinary background. From Aspen to Albuquerque, he’s honed his craft working in several award-winning restaurants. He quips his style meets at the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crying Deshaun Watson Carted Off Field After Non-Contact Leg Injury]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170948</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/crying-deshaun-watson-carted-off-field-after-non-contact-leg-injury"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T19:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deshaun Watson's stomach-churning presence in the NFL appears to have been put on a long hiatus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Sharp Withdraws Name From Giants’ GM Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=827702</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/scott-sharp-withdraws-name-from-giants-gm-search.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T15:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Giants continue their search for a new GM to take over for Pete Putila and serve as Buster Posey’s second-in-command following his installation as president of baseball operations, The Athletic’s Ken Rosenthal reports that one name under consideration has withdrawn himself from the mix for the job: Royals assistant GM Scott Sharp, who…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Temwa Chawinga Has Conquered The NWSL]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170943</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/temwa-chawinga-has-conquered-the-nwsl"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T15:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How would you imagine the greatest individual season in NWSL history? Our hypothetical player would need to score a lot of goals, obviously. Breaking Sam Kerr's single-season scoring record (18) would certainly get plenty of attention, so let's put that at the top of the list. How about assists? Assists are important, too. Let's say this player has ... five of those. Five sounds good. 
Let's go back to the goals for a second. We know that all goals aren't created equal, and that poachers and penalty specialists can often sneak their way to the top of the leaderboard. That just won't do—we're talking about the best season in history, here—so let's make sure our player didn't score any of her goals from the spot, and is out-performing her expected goals tally by two. We need more, though. Let's get crazy and say that this player is an NWSL rookie, and arrived from Chinese Women's Super League at age 25 to blitz the NWSL with the league's first 20-goal season. We'll need a fun, quirky statistic, too, so let's say this player became the first in league history to score a goal against every team. And we need moments. Like, what if the record-breaking goal happened to be a 25-yard strike that makes a convincing case for being the hardest a soccer ball has ever been struck by a woman in a professional match? What if that goal looked something like this:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Yankees Have Power In All The Right Places]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170938</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-yankees-have-power-in-all-the-right-places"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T13:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The playoffs tend to provide certain reminders about how postseason baseball works. The Yankees, in completing their 4-1 series win over the Cleveland Guardians to advance to the World Series, provided one about the importance of power. Hit 10 home runs in five games, as the Yankees did in this series, and you can overcome all manner of base-running errors, scuffed defensive work, and late-inning meltdowns. Just keep hitting the ball over the fence, and good things will happen for you.
Here's another reminder: There is probably no hitter in baseball more terrifying to pitch to in a high-leverage situation than Juan Soto. The Yankees right fielder came to the plate in the top of the 10th inning, with the score tied 2-2, two men on base, and two outs. Soto was looking for a fastball from Hunter Gaddis, and he wasn't going to let the at-bat end until he got one. What must it feel like to pitch to a locked-in Juan Soto, who possesses not only all the confidence and power that makes for a great clutch hitter, but one of the games most discerning eyes. I imagine it feels like being asked to chop down a redwood with a hatchet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL Week 7 Uniform Schedule: Packers Debuting White Helmets, Steelers Wearing Throwback Uniforms]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82746</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/20/nfl-week-7-uniform-schedule-packers-debuting-white-helmets-steelers-wearing-throwback-uniforms/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T07:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our weekly series that looks at every uniform matchup across the NFL continues with the Green Bay Packers debuting their new white alternate helmets and the Pittsburgh Steelers wearing throwback uniforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arizona Wildcats To Wear Iconic Cactus Logo On Helmets For Homecoming]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82738</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/19/arizona-wildcats-to-wear-iconic-cactus-logo-on-helmets-for-homecoming/college/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T20:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Arizona football program will wear the iconic cactus logo that used to be displayed on the basketball court at the McKale Center on its helmets during Saturday's Homecoming matchup with Colorado.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Lynx And Liberty Are Getting Too Close For Comfort]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170930</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-lynx-and-liberty-are-getting-too-close-for-comfort"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T19:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS — Somehow, this will end, though your guess is as good as mine. In Game 4 on Friday night, the Lynx and Liberty arrived in a familiar place by unfamiliar means. Neither team bothered with the pretense of an early lead or deficit. This time, they played a game that from tip to buzzer felt true to the series: weird, tense, a matter of execution more than scheme. A Jonquel Jones layup and-one to even things up, 80-80, with a minute left, was the 13th tying score of the game. With 18 seconds left, the Lynx searching for a last shot, Bridget Carleton grabbed an offensive rebound and was fouled on the putback attempt. She made two free throws for a 14th and final lead change, 82-80. The WNBA’s two best teams head where they have long seemed destined, to a decisive Game 5 in New York on Sunday night. 
Lynx head coach Cheryl Reeve explained the game’s closeness in terms of “information gathered.” Game 5 will be the ninth time these teams have played each other this season, and the familiarity is starting to show. “Everything is getting harder,” Reeve said. “There’s no secrets at this point.” The teams’ de facto captains, products of the same college program and models of the league’s richness at power forward, pose identical matchup problems to each other. The lead guards can claim crowning moments. Last night, the two starting centers traded threes. Styles make fights, maybe, but never discount the thrill of a pointing Spider-Man series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offseason Outlook: Kansas City Royals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=827533</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/offseason-outlook-kansas-city-royals-14.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T15:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Royals added 30 wins relative to the prior season, going from 56 to 86 and sneaking into the playoffs for the first time since their World Series win in 2015. Now they'll go into the winter as clear contenders for the first time in a while, but still with lots of uncertainty ahead.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developments In Equity Partnerships! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076391</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/developments-in-equity-partnerships-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T23:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mergers Bring Rank Changes: Biglaw firm decides on all-equity partnerships.
That's One Way To Get Lawyer's Fees: Screwing the judge has its benefits.
Speaking Of Priming The Judge: Elon pushes X cases toward one of his gaveled Texan fanboys.
Can't Jump The Line On Justice: State Supreme Court justice caught trying to rush investigation on her husband.
Another One Shuts The Door: Skadden cuts ties with Shanghai.
The post Developments In Equity Partnerships! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Exactly A Shining Example Of The Legal Profession]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076371</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/not-exactly-a-shining-example-of-the-legal-profession/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T23:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But he is entertaining.
The post Not Exactly A Shining Example Of The Legal Profession appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Trump & Harris Stand On Payers, AI, Drug Pricing, And CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076336</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/10/healthcare-president/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T22:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts from BRG recently discussed the two presidential candidates' stances on key healthcare issues, including drug pricing, Medicaid, and AI.
The post Where Trump & Harris Stand On Payers, AI, Drug Pricing, And CMS appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KATIE ADAMS - MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>