<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-03-15T16:17:56.620Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laboratory demonstration]]></title>
        <id>67d48f43e3b9960001dcc0b5</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-277/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-15T00:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Misha Angrist on science and authoritarianism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Science]]></title>
        <id>67d4b214e3b9960001dcc108</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/its-science/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-15T00:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a collective of 60 writers, on fire and hard to kill]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Misha Angrist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The RC Car Racing Nationals Is Where Racing Gets Small]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184043</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-rc-car-racing-nationals-is-where-racing-gets-small"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T16:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This piece was originally published in The Autopian, a member-supported blog for car enthusiasts formed by ex-Jalopnik writers/editors. If you think starting a website in the middle of the pandemic was a terrible idea, you should see the cars we buy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hardigree</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Chop]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184089</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/for-chop"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T16:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2017 a lady selling puppies texted me a photo, of a wrinkly, tiny, brand-new little sad-eyed Boxer puppy sitting on a beat-up dog bed, looking right into the camera. What I thought, sitting alone on my porch, and probably muttered out loud, was, "Aw, look at that little porkchop." And that became his name: Chop. Later I learned that I had inadvertently and embarrassingly given him the same name as the protagonist's pet Rottweiler in the video game Grand Theft Auto V, but by then it was too late. He'd fully inhabited the name, and that's who he was: Chop, Chopper, Choppeez. And at any rate what I mostly called him was "little buddy." As in, "C'mon little buddy," and "Hi little buddy!" and, when he would put his paws on my shoulders and lay down on my chest, face to face, "Oh, little buddy."
When we met him (as well as the puppy we named Grover and also took home), he tried to scramble up into my lap where I sat on the lady's couch, but he was too small. I scooped him up—it took one hand; he was so little—and he immediately and with intense purpose began licking my face. You would have thought he was performing CPR. It was like he was making up for all 37 of the years I had spent not having my face cleaned by him. He was so happy to be doing it, ears laid back, nose snuffling loudly, his entire back half fully a-wag, like this was a music recital he'd been rehearsing for all (10 weeks of) his life. To stop him would have been unkind, so I didn't, and so he kept at it, with brief interruptions, for seven years. He and I were, if not literally inseparable, then only grudgingly separable and for as briefly as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heartwarming: Hockey Executive Trades Son For Future Considerations]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184111</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/heartwarming-hockey-executive-trades-son-for-future-considerations"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T15:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all wish this story could be taken at face value as a victory for merit and against nepotism, a triumph of the lack of human spirit and a blow against familial gladhanding. We want it to be a message of total bastardy in action, because we are small people in a small era. We're probably wrong, but damn it, we can dream.
Dan MacKinnon, the assistant general manager of the New Jersey Devils and therefore the de facto general manager of the Devils' top minor league team, the American Hockey League's Utica Comets, did in fact trade his son Will to the Cleveland Monsters for future considerations. Future considerations including nothing whatsoever. We dare your heart to resist that strange warming sensation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real Madrid Is A Monster, And Every Derby Is Halloween]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183988</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/real-madrid-is-a-monster-and-every-derby-is-halloween"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T14:57:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you win as relentlessly as Real Madrid, you're destined to be perceived as the bad guy. Every club in Europe knows that when they face Madrid in the Champions League, they will confront an opponent endowed with the attributes of a comic-book villain. The Blancos have a vast array of superpowers, which only grow in number and potency in times of crisis. They are unaffected by the vicissitudes of battle, always supremely confident that the time will eventually come for them to turn the tables and win. Most of all, the moment you think you've finished them off is when they always, always, always land their biggest blow.
This dynamic takes on an even scarier tint when the team on the other side is Atlético Madrid. Real has haunted Atleti's dreams for generations now, and over the past decade has induced especially painful nightmares. When a Madrid Derby is on the horizon, the Colchoneros can't close their eyes at night without sleep sending them back to Lisbon or Milan, the sites of the most soul-crushing losses in the club's history. Surrounding the two losses to Real in those Champions League finals are a couple more UCL knockouts at the same hands, each one close and hard-fought and all the more excruciating for being so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How The Dunk Was Banned]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183960</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-the-dunk-was-banned"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T14:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following is excerpted from Mike Sielski's Magic in the Air, a narrative romp through the history of basketball, culture, and race in America. In this exclusive excerpt, Sielski details some of what led to one of the most infamous decisions in sports history: the banning of the dunk in high school and college basketball from 1967 to 1976.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Sielski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Walz Is Too Damn Nice]]></title>
        <id>67d43b9b669e16000109df8b</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/tim-walz-is-too-damn-nice/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T14:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can't forget about Walz's disastrous vice presidential debate performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Feinstein Never Stopped Doing Everything]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184075</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/john-feinstein-never-stopped-doing-everything"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T13:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Post database shows that John Feinstein wrote his first story for the newspaper in 1977. It was about college basketball. Feinstein also wrote a story about college basketball that ran in the Post on Thursday, the day he died.
Between his first and last Post pieces, Feinstein went from a local D.C. reporter to a national powerhouse and back. He’d recently moved to Farmville, Va., but was back in town to cover the A-10 Conference basketball tournament being held in the nation’s capital when he died, and had already filed a preview piece for the event that ran earlier this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Timely And Frankly Too Thorough 2025 Formula 1 Season Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183839</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-timely-and-frankly-too-thorough-2025-formula-1-season-preview"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T13:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dare we say that it is possible to get excited about the upcoming Formula 1 season? While history means that Red Bull and Max Verstappen should still be the favorites, McLaren and Ferrari are looking like contenders for both championships. Even in the event that there isn’t a multi-driver race for the title, back-of-the-napkin math offers at least a 50-50 chance at a new Drivers’ Championship winner. And yet it's arguably one of the least important changes in the 75th anniversary of F1's existence.
Rosters have been drastically overhauled. Carlos Sainz Jr. moved to Williams. Lewis Hamilton is at Ferrari. There’s a new second driver at Red Bull. There are five new drivers on the grid and not one pay driver among them, which makes this the biggest rookie class since the 2019 lineup of Lando Norris, Alexander Albon, and George Russell. With any luck, this year will produce a driver on their caliber. In an era of increasing engine reliability, rookie mistakes may infuse the kind of randomness and safety-car strategic shakeups that have been missing from recent seasons. It comes at the minor tradeoff of preexisting narratives, but who needs those? Lewis Hamilton is at Ferrari!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exquisite corpus]]></title>
        <id>67d33a84e3b9960001dcadf6</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-276/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T23:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kọ́lá Túbọ̀sún won’t let words fail]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebuilding Babel]]></title>
        <id>67d339cee3b9960001dcade6</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/rebuilding-babel/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T23:34:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a collective of 60 writers, on fire and hard to kill]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kọ́lá Túbọ̀sún</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hummingbirds Brought Me Around]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183941</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-hummingbirds-brought-me-around"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T20:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LAS VEGAS — For as long as I can remember, I have felt drawn to creatures often described as uncharismatic: deep-sea fish; an ugly bunch of bugs; maggots with faces on their butts; any creature with "blob" in its name. As I've grown older, this interest has felt increasingly moral, as these creatures are less likely to bask in the glow of a spotlight in conservation with the power to lift a species out of the trenches of endangerment, or even extinction. But sometimes I'll see a, let's say, conventionally adorable animal that makes me forget all these weirdos, at least for a moment, and think: Whoa. Now there's a cutie patootie. 
Last week, I experienced one of these rare moments of awe while appreciating in the biodiversity of Las Vegas, a city that, for all its illuminated turrets and spheres, borders some of the most beautiful nature I've seen. I was walking with a few friends in their neighborhood park, which snaked through a miniature valley of desert scrub. At first, it seemed like we were the only ones here. But the longer we walked, the more creatures emerged. We were mooned by sandy-colored desert cottontails foraging right before dusk. We were menaced by a small, striped rodent I would later identify as a male white-tailed antelope squirrel who sported two impressively pendulous balls below his wee little tail. We watched Gambel's quails scuttling from the shadows of one bush to another, their black plumes bobbing with every step. I recently got a pair of binoculars, and I watched each of these creatures go about their afternoon with much delight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yearning For The Mike White Era, With Jasper Wang]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183954</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/yearning-for-the-mike-white-era-with-jasper-wang"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T20:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We talk about a wide range of topics on The Distraction, and one of our goals is to eventually broaden it to include areas of interest beyond sports, aging, and lunch sometime in the next few years. Of the many possible options that we've discussed, a pivot to "true crime" had ranked pretty low. It's not the energy we seek to cultivate, and hearing Drew honking through the details of a high-profile unsolved kidnapping would be pretty upsetting regardless of what those details were. So it's likely that this week's episode, which begins with Jasper Wang's perplexing Montana real estate mystery, is as close to true crime as we're likely to get.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tabs Hiatus 2: Hike Harder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/tabs-hiatus-2-hike-harder</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/tabs-hiatus-2-hike-harder"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T18:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ok this time I’ll finish the Appalachian Trail for sure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Belichick: Please Email My Girlfriend]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183982</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bill-belichick-please-email-my-girlfriend"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T16:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Belichick has a lot of work to do to turn the University of North Carolina football program into a perennial success. That's why the 72-year-old has assembled a team of top football minds around him. All the heavy hitters are here: Michael Lombardi, Freddie Kitchens, Steve Belichick, Matt Lombardi, Mike Priefer, and Jordon Hudson. 
Hudson is Belichick's 24-year-old girlfriend. Their relationship was a queasy one from the moment it launched, and it has become only more grimace-inducing as time goes on. Last month, for example, Pablo Torre reported that Hudson has essentially been acting as Belichick's agent. That reporting is now seemingly backed up by an email uncovered by The Assembly reporter Matt Hartman while he was reporting on UNC's rapidly increasing athletics budget.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[United States Dollar Bills, Ranked]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183967</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/united-states-dollar-bills-ranked"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T15:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we were discussing gifts for young children, and Jasper surprised us all by telling us that kids "go wild for $2 bills." Kids, and Barry. Here are the best bills.
1. $2. So rare! So delightfully wrong; receiving one feels like briefly being transported to a parallel dimension where everything is just slightly off, like you'd break your $2 to purchase a Poca-Cola. Did you know, the front ("obverse") of the two-dollar bill is the oldest of any current U.S. banknote, going unchanged since 1929? Did you know the number of two-dollar bills being produced is actually increasing?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Aaron Rodgers “Open” To Possessing God-Like Dominion Over Earth, Sea]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183964</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/report-aaron-rodgers-open-to-possessing-god-like-dominion-over-earth-sea"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T14:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that the NFL’s free agency market is open, everyone is dying to know: Where will Aaron Rodgers end up? This is the ONLY free agency move any of us care about, and yet a resolution has proven frighteningly elusive. The reason? EVERYBODY wants to hire this man.
Don’t believe me? Dianna Russini of The Athletic is saying that Rodgers is “intrigued” by the idea of playing in Minnesota. And Peter Schrager of NFL Network told his audience that Rodgers might sign with the Steelers, but needs “up to four weeks” to make his decision, and that the Steelers are “giving him some space” to think it through. An uncharacteristically terse Adam Schefter says that the Giants “want” him. That’s a lot of suitors! But which of them will go all in to secure the services of this four-time MVP? Or will a surprise contender—Kansas City?—emerge from out of nowhere? WE NEED AN ANSWER, DAMMIT!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Had Diana?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183091</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/diana-taurasi-retirement-uconn-phoenix-mercury"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T13:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We have Diana, and they don’t,” the quote went. But who ever had Diana? It is the magic thing about her, the way she gave herself over to no one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offseason In Review: Kansas City Royals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=843708</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/03/offseason-in-review-kansas-city-royals-16.html"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T01:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals began the offseason with a three-year signing to keep their excellent rotation intact. They traded from that starting staff a month later to acquire a new leadoff hitter. Kansas City hoped to follow up with an impact offensive acquisition that never materialized. They instead turned to the relief market late in the winter…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pals on the screen / Enemies on the road]]></title>
        <id>67d1ecd8e010aa0001436405</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-275/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T01:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emily Flake’s imaginary friends, and Julianne Escobedo Shepherd on a modern Tantalus]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to My Parasocial Relationships]]></title>
        <id>67d1e7e6e010aa00014363a5</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/a-guide-to-my-parasocial-relationships-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T01:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Emily Flake]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Flake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vehicle for Resentment]]></title>
        <id>67d1eddae010aa000143641d</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/vehicle-for-resentment/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T01:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Julianne Escobedo Shepherd

Photo illustration by Joe MacLeod. Photo of Tesla car by Vauxford - CC BY-SA 4.0 via Wikipedia
In the armpit days of the 2010s, the Tesla was marketed as an advance in luxury electric vehicles, a savvy choice for moneyed people moderately concerned about climate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julianne Escobedo Shepherd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bobby Witt Jr. Suffers Forearm Contusion, Avoids Any Fractures After HBP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=844387</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/03/bobby-witt-jr-suffers-forearm-contusion-avoids-any-fractures-after-hbp.html"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T00:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals appear to have avoided the worst on Bobby Witt Jr. ESPN’s Jeff Passan reports that the superstar shortstop avoided any fractures after being hit by a pitch in the left forearm/wrist area this afternoon. Kansas City subsequently announced that Witt sustained a forearm contusion and said he’d be reevaluated tomorrow. Manager Matt Quatraro said…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AL Notes: Meadows, Pérez, Mateo, Estévez]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=844359</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/03/al-notes-meadows-perez-mateo-estevez.html"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T21:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tigers are facing a few injuries in their outfield mix, with each of Matt Vierling, Parker Meadows and Wenceel Pérez battling health issues. Vierling has already been ruled out for Opening Day due to a rotator cuff strain and Meadows might not make it for the opener either. Meadows has been experiencing a nerve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lamine Yamal Wows On Accident And On Purpose]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183863</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lamine-yamal-wows-on-accident-and-on-purpose"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T19:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lamine Yamal's first stardust play of the game began with an apology. Carrying the ball up the field 10 minutes into Tuesday's deciding leg of the Barcelona-Benfica Champions League tie, Lamine picked up his head, saw Raphinha opening up his stride, and lifted his hand in contrition.
The gesture communicated that he appreciated the Brazilian forward's run, which presented the duo a great chance for another one of the thunderbolts they've spent all season tossing back and forth to each other, but as he hadn't read the play quickly enough and wasn't prepared to hit the pass before its window of opportunity closed, the Spaniard couldn't reward his teammate's effort with the pass the moment called for. Coming from the talent it came from, implicit in this apology was another sentiment: "Don't worry, I'll make up for it."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Should Cooper Flagg End Up?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183870</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/where-should-cooper-flagg-end-up"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T17:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooper Flagg has been conceived of as the surefire top overall pick in this June's NBA Draft since he reclassified two years ago, and despite taking on the enormous pressure of getting into the draft sooner, Flagg has only strengthened his case this year. Around him in the lottery, Rutgers' Dylan Harper has been doing a convincing Ethical James Harden bit; Baylor's VJ Edgecombe has been making all the Draft hardcores I read flush in awe; and Harper's teammate Ace Bailey has finally learned to pass the basketball, showing both an awareness of other people lacking through the first three months of the season and the capacity to grow and change. Nothing that cohort, nor anyone else in college or international basketball, has done has been as impressive as what Flagg's been doing at Duke. Not only has he produced at a staggering level, he's playing tomorrow's basketball, today.
With hopefully just a few more games left in his college career, and with the stinky end of the NBA content to befoul the court now that the trade deadline has passed and its members can lose in peace, it is time to consider where Flagg could end up. Also, more to the point, where he should end up. Not every team in the lottery is as worthy, by my arbitrary standards, of capturing the Flagg. The NBA Draft's structure not only limits how much money Flagg can make for many years, the draft lottery means he has zero control over where he will work for the majority of the next decade. Such is life in the NBA, under the current Collective Bargaining Agreement. Some players walk the blessed path and end up in a great city and on a great roster, and others are drafted by the Sacramento Kings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The San Francisco 49ers Are Closing The Window]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183897</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-san-francisco-49ers-are-closing-the-window"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T17:17:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last time the San Francisco 49ers had the kind of crisis of faith they’re currently enduring, they wrote it off as a weird emanation from COVID. Back then, they went from ending a season with a Super Bowl loss to Patrick Mahomes to enduring one of double-digit losses, mostly because the bulk of their offensive playmakers were gone for some portion of the season and  their defense slipped from elite to meh, bordering on feh. That relative patience was rewarded with a bounce-back season in 2021 and a trip to the conference final, a double-down season in 2022 and another trip to the conference final, and finally another run of excellence in 2023 that ended with...losing another Super Bowl to Patrick Mahomes.
History has a way of repeating itself, especially where losing to Patrick Mahomes is concerned, but the 49ers do not seem to believe that this cycle is going to make another revolution. Last year was another injury-plagued season that saw the Niners go from double-digit wins to double-digit losses. This time, Kyle Shanahan, who runs the building with full acquiescence from the fully satisfied York family, has seemingly decided that the windows are not only closed but need full replacement and double-paning. At least we think that's what he decided. For the first time in his eight-plus years in charge, he might not actually be in charge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Should Be Consequences For Filming A Tesla Ad At The White House]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183849</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/there-should-be-consequences-for-filming-a-tesla-ad-at-the-white-house"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T16:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, the President of the United States filmed an advertisement for Tesla on the driveway of the White House. They might as well have erected a ginormous flag and one of those balloon men that flop around, because the South Lawn is a car dealership now. Maybe they could have unfurled a sign that read "Deals Deals Deals!"
Except there were no deals. Instead, there was a line of five Teslas looking like shiny garbage. The reason behind this is simple: Elon Musk is now the president's big boy best friend, and Elon Musk has four jobs (Twitter, SpaceX, destroying the government illegally, and Tesla). His fourth job, Tesla, is the one he seems the most sensitive about, probably because it's the only one that had even a slight chance of success. Instead, Tesla stock has been dropping since mid-December, because many Americans have realized that Elon Musk is a goon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They Should Call It The Free Piss]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183816</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/they-should-call-it-the-free-piss"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T16:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who likes The Free Press? This is a question I have found myself asking, more often than is good for me, about Bari Weiss's suddenly large and well-monied media company, which according to the New York Times Magazine has more than three dozen full-time employees and at least 100,000 paying subscribers. I recently went to the homepage, scanned the day's meager offering of bone-dry headlines—highlights: "How I Became A Wife" and "Things Worth Remembering: Money Can Ruin Your Life"—and there was the question again: Who is getting fired up to read this crap?
It's a question that has become easier to answer in recent days and weeks. Over the weekend, pro-Palestine activist and Columbia University graduate Mahmoud Khalil was detained by the Department of Homeland Security and disappeared to a detention facility in Louisiana without being charged with a crime. As a set of facts—a campus activist was arrested by the federal government over speech acts—this is a story that should have been red meat for Weiss and The Free Press. Weiss essentially built her career by positioning herself as one of the few people brave enough to ring the alarm bell about the rise of anti-speech illiberalism on college campuses and in broader society. It's something she and her cohort never really shut up about, in fact. And yet, so far, The Free Press has published one article about Khalil's arrest, which reads as a wholly dispassionate rundown of the facts of the case and cedes its point of view to the Some people say this is good, while others say it is bad framing that was long ago perfected by The New York Times:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pacers Drew Up A Beauty And Were Rewarded With A Miracle]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183825</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-pacers-drew-up-a-beauty-and-were-rewarded-with-a-miracle"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T16:03:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The play that won the game for the Indiana Pacers Tuesday night deserved a bucket. The ethical fan of the Milwaukee Bucks, otherwise mired in frustration and disillusionment this fine spring morning, cannot deny this much: Rick Carlisle sketched up a beaut. 
Down three points with just under four seconds to play, the Pacers used a timeout to move the ball into the front court, but then positioned the inbounder's four teammates in the backcourt, in a spread formation not unlike what you'd see before a Hail Mary pass in football. The possibility flashed through my mind; it must've occurred to the Bucks, who were gesturing and repositioning and glancing around in uncertainty until the moment the play was triggered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today's Politics Are Not Trapped In Amber]]></title>
        <id>67d177c55b79a900011bd6e3</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/todays-politics-are-not-trapped-in-amber-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T14:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Americans did not speak for the final time in 2024. Some high-profile Democrats don't seem to understand this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saturn Has 274 Moons Now; Jupiter Is Crying Itself To Sleep; It Literally Cannot Believe It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183828</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/saturn-has-247-moons-now-jupiter-is-crying-itself-to-sleep-it-literally-cannot-believe-it"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T13:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For centuries, Jupiter reigned as king of the moons. Initially, the Big Four, discovered by Galileo, and then as optics and astronomy advanced, more and more, smaller and smaller bodies, until Big J could proudly boast of 95 moons in its orbital thrall. But Jupiter got cocky. Jupiter rested on its laurels. Jupiter, it turns out, was playing against plumbers and mailmen when it put up its record numbers. 
Saturn, meanwhile, was hungry. Saturn ate the tape and put in the hours in the gym. In 2020, astronomers discovered 20 new Saturnian moons. In 2023, they racked up 62 more. This week, the International Astronomical Union formally recognized a whopping 128 further new satellites, giving Saturn a total of 274 moons, a record that will surely never be broken (in this solar system, which as we all know is the galaxy's top-tier league). Saturn has more moons than it knows what to do with! It has more moons than the rest of the planets combined! Jupiter can attempt to dry its tears with its pathetic 95 Jovian moons, which compared to mighty Saturn might as well be no moons at all. Jupiter? More like Venus!! When it comes to moon-having.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Payton Pritchard Brings The Hush]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183767</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/payton-pritchard-brings-the-hush"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T12:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 29, 1970, Dave DeBusschere of the New York Knicks hit a jump shot from the circle with three seconds left to give his team a 102-100 lead over the Los Angeles Lakers in the third game of the NBA Finals. LA’s Wilt Chamberlain inbounded the ball immediately to guard Jerry West. His first dribble was a feint to the left. West then cut back toward the middle of the court and let fly from 60 feet, over, I think, Dick Barnett . (The video looks like it was shot underwater on Mars.) On the video of the shot, the sound in the arena almost cuts out entirely until the ball goes through the net to force overtime—at the end of which, I would point out, the Lakers lost anyway.
It is probably as iconic a basket as was ever scored in the NBA, not only because it was scored by a certifiable NBA legend, but also because the shot was … a shot. It was not a heave. It was not a “desperation toss,” as Gene Hackman warned his Hickory Huskers against in the Sectional Finals against Linton. It was not some kind of baseball pass aimed roughly at the area code in which the basket is located. There was nothing freaky about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charles P. Pierce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confidence is real]]></title>
        <id>67d0b6c9e010aa0001435096</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-274/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-11T23:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Saward believes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detroit Pistons, Momentum, Belief]]></title>
        <id>67d0995be010aa0001435056</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/detroit-pistons-momentum-belief/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-11T23:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by John Saward

In late February, the Detroit Pistons beat the Boston Celtics 117-97. The Celtics, a kind of perverse, analytics-defiled basketball project joylessly hunting 3-pointers with the cold determination of a hedge fund manager, have scored under 100 points in just six games this year. It was Detroit’]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Saward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Artist’s Way’ Week 9: We Are Annoyed]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183771</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-artists-way-week-9-we-are-annoyed"/>
        <updated>2025-03-11T21:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can, of course, be an artist in total solitude. But it's more realistic, practical, and, some would argue, fulfilling to practice creativity in community. Human beings bring with them their own backstories and neuroses, sensitivities and idiosyncrasies, which are what make them special, and also what often make them annoying. This week, we reflected on the price we pay for community, which is having to tolerate people you may not entirely know, or like, but feel free to judge all the same.
This week we officially enter week 10, which begins the fourth quarter of The Artist's Way. Shout out to those of you who have endured so far. We're almost finished!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mahmoud Khalil Is The Target Of A Desperate Agenda]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183558</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mahmoud-khalil-is-the-target-of-a-desperate-agenda"/>
        <updated>2025-03-11T17:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Campus safety is a priority for a lot of people who haven't actually stepped foot on a campus in decades, or possibly ever. Is a campus actually safer after police are permitted to toss around protestors and arrest students? Of course not. But by finding the right face and name to agitate enough racists, it can be presented as a severe issue. Any breach of rights can be justified in service of that goal. In that way, what has happened to Mahmoud Khalil is an expansion of a long-existing logic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thank God For Weed Gummies]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183780</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/thank-god-for-weed-gummies"/>
        <updated>2025-03-11T16:41:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about weed, dog armpits, disc jockeying, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Was It Worth It?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183775</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/was-it-worth-it"/>
        <updated>2025-03-11T15:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the one hand, Simon Benoit got absolutely destroyed in his Monday night tilt with Utah's Michael Kesselring. The Leafs blueliner took five or six consecutive unblocked shots to the dome, and was pulled down to the ice, and dislocated his thumb and had to pop it back in while sitting in the penalty box. On the other hand, Benoit was captured in some impossibly cool photos going airborne with an attempted Superman punch. Some might argue that looking cool is the most important part of hockey, and life. Not me, though.

https://youtu.be/JpMFCg527EM?si=0NUXeAnzwbYJj8V-&t=36]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Premier League’s Tightest Race Is For Fifth Place]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183598</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-premier-leagues-tightest-race-is-for-fifth-place"/>
        <updated>2025-03-11T14:43:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With just about three-quarters of the Premier League season done and dusted, there's little drama on either extreme of the table. At the bottom, barring a collapse from one of the not-quite-relegation-fodder teams, the recently promoted trio of Ipswich Town, Leicester City, and Southampton will be yo-yoing back down to the Championship. Meanwhile, at the top, Arsenal's 1-1 draw against Manchester United on Sunday means Liverpool now sits on a surely insurmountable 15-point lead in what can't even really be called a title "race" anymore.
This doesn't mean the Premier League is devoid of drama, though, and in fact there is one fight in the standings that looks certain to go to the very last round. I'm referring here to the race for the third, fourth, and fifth spots on the table, all of which should give Champions League qualification for next season. A quick explanation for why there will likely be five rather than the usual four continental places for the Prem: the Champions League's new format grants an additional entry spot to the league with the highest coefficient on an annual basis, and this year the top dogs are practically a lock to be the English.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Senators Are So Back]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183734</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-senators-are-so-back"/>
        <updated>2025-03-11T13:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ottawa fans have had it rough, but if they've been waiting for the Senators to really make them feel something, Monday's win over the Detroit Red Wings was a night to savor. Just check out these clips from midway through the game, right after the Sens broke the 0-0 tie. Linus Ullmark, a goalie who's been shaky but ultimately an asset in his first year with the club, whipped the house into a frenzy with a showcase of quick reflexes and lucky breaks. I especially love the flying fist in the crowd that breaks the camera's sight line after the second clearance. You can imagine the person it's attached to shouting "Yes! Hahaha! Yes!"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Literary ambition / Boundless borders]]></title>
        <id>67cf490e2bb6620001521f89</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-273/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T22:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Cuomo analyzed by Harry Siegel, and Felipe De La Hoz on the oozing borders of the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case Against Andrew Cuomo]]></title>
        <id>67cd772e2bb6620001521cb2</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-case-against-andrew-cuomo/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T22:19:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Poem by Andrew Cuomo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harry Siegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Out of sight]]></title>
        <id>67cf25562bb6620001521f0d</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/out-of-sight/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T22:18:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the Everywhere Border and Its Consequences]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felipe De La Hoz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kara Lawson And Duke Get Revenge With A Conference Title]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183610</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/kara-lawson-and-duke-get-revenge-with-a-conference-title"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T20:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are the obvious reasons to cheer against a Duke basketball team, but for a long time, I’ve had my own special justification: Before she took a job as head coach of a program at the bottom of the ACC, Kara Lawson was a first-rate color commentator, and I selfishly wanted her back on my TV talking hoops. A mutual parting of ways, a sudden change of heart—anything would do! The private-school elites couldn’t get away with blocking access to a public resource for their own gain. 
It turns out private-school elites can and do get away with that, a lot. The Kara Lawson For All movement suffered a blow at this past weekend’s ACC Tournament. On Sunday, as she celebrated the Duke women’s first conference championship since 2013, Lawson reflected on a long journey. The pandemic cut short her first year at Duke—the team decided to suspend the 2020-21 season after four games—and in subsequent seasons, the Blue Devils struggled in a tough conference. “Five years later,” Lawson said in her postgame interview. “We’re at the top.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seahawks Replace Former Jets Punchline With Former Jets Punchline]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183701</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/seahawks-replace-former-jets-punchline-with-former-jets-punchline"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T19:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Darnold has a reassuring habit of overperforming when expectations are nonexistent. That was a trait that came in handy for him in the role of bridge quarterback for the Minnesota Vikings in 2024, and he’ll have to bank on it again now that the Seattle Seahawks have inked him to a three-year deal in the Baker Mayfield range of pay. If you’re a fan of the Seahawks, you’re probably not all that excited by this move. In fact, you might very well be stumped, if not apoplectic. You might be like WELL FUCK A DUCK WHAT THE FUCK IS THIS SHIT?
This is somewhat understandable. Darnold crapped out as a No. 3 overall pick by the Jets before heading to Minnesota last season and waging one of the more unlikely Pro Bowl campaigns in league history, throwing for 35 TDs and more than 4,000 yards as the Vikings went a gaudy 14-3. Darnold even beat these same Seahawks, in Seattle, with a big-boy TD pass to Justin Jefferson in the waning minutes. In the rain. On a busted leg. It was enough to make you wonder if Darnold, and not rookie J.J. McCarthy, was the answer at QB that Minnesota fans had been waiting for. And if you weren’t a Vikings fan, you could at least drool over the prospect of your team landing this man in free agency. If you told a Seahawks fan after that Minnesota loss that they were getting THAT Darnold, they’d be psyched.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yosuke Watanuki Is Here To Drink Soda And Cause Upsets]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183621</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/yosuke-watanuki-is-here-to-drink-soda-and-cause-upsets"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T19:26:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Yosuke Watanuki tennis experience is a heady mix: non-stop smiles, mid-match soda, dizzyingly good winners. There won't be a better storyline out of the men's draw at Indian Wells. He's the lowest-ranked man to reach the tournament's round of 16 since 2004.
Ahead of Sunday night's third-round match, I thought that the world No. 379 Watanuki, a qualifier, would beat No. 17 Frances Tiafoe. It wasn't quite as spicy a prediction as it might appear. Watanuki had been playing well since he qualified for the tournament, and I was unconvinced by Tiafoe's shaky round-of-64 win over qualifier Damir Dzumhur. There was also one small but relevant fact: Watanuki was currently working on a trial basis with Tiafoe's former coach, Wayne Ferreira, who must have alerted his new player to his old player's soft spots. Watanuki had played mind-melting tennis in the only prior meeting between these two, at the 2023 Miami Open, which Tiafoe narrowly won. History said it was a pretty good matchup for the underdog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Demi Vollering Revenge Tour Is Officially On]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183628</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-demi-vollering-revenge-tour-is-officially-on"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T18:29:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One month ago, Demi Vollering held her first press conference as a rider for FDJ-Suez and insisted that her season was not about revenge. Vollering, arguably the peloton's best rider, had spent four increasingly antagonistic seasons with SD Worx, inarguably the peloton's best team, so no matter what she says, everyone involved in last year's Tour de France Femmes debacle is necessarily going to be in conflict with each other. This presents a fascinating dynamic; this past weekend, it made for some fantastic racing.
Vollering claimed her second Strade Bianche on Saturday, destroying Anna van der Breggen on the run into Siena's Piazza del Campo and winning by 18 seconds. The men's race was fun, though all it taught us is that Tadej Pogacar is truly blessed by God; the women's race showed that Vollering versus her old team is going to be fun as hell to watch all year, and that Vollering might have the upper hand. FDJ was incredible, setting the pace alongside Jumbo with such authority that not even an obviously doomed breakaway was allowed to form (maybe they learned their lesson after the disaster at Omloop). Vollering's fellow FDJ newcomer Juliette Labous was tremendous in keeping her team leader at the front of the race and eventually helping her take part in what would turn out to be the winning move. When van der Breggen attacked just ahead of a foreboding 18-percent gradient, Vollering was fresh enough to follow her countrywoman, then destroy her on the famed run-up into town.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They Should Call Them The Dallas Even More Stars]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183604</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/they-should-call-them-the-dallas-even-more-stars"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T18:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Saturday, Mikko Rantanen scored his first goal in his first game for his third team of the season. At the start of a final period that saw Dallas nab a trio of goals to force Edmonton to white-knuckle a 5-4 win, the Stars' latest pickup comfortably one-timed a cross-ice feed from Matt Duchene. That play showed the kind of offensive skill that any Cup hopeful would love to add, even for a hefty bundle of picks.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RfUWgbI_tqo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wow, Perfect! A Hat You Can’t Read!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183623</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/wow-perfect-a-hat-you-cant-read"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a collector of many novelty hats, I know that sometimes there is joy in people struggling to read your hat. Sometimes, I wear my novelty Sharon Van Etten hat, and people ask me what it says, and then I get to talk about her music. This is fun!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rob Manfred Is The Face Of An Elite Mutiny Against Rays Owner Stuart Sternberg]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183503</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rob-manfred-is-the-face-of-an-elite-mutiny-against-rays-owner-stuart-sternberg"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T17:11:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is not easy to wade through this sentence without whiplash: "As he considers walking away from a stadium deal in St. Petersburg, Fla., Tampa Bay Rays owner Stu Sternberg is being pressured to sell his team by MLB commissioner Rob Manfred and some other owners."
Not that it's badly written—as constructed by Evan Drellich of The Athletic, it's perfectly understandable. What gives it that special feeling of traumatic brain injury is the idea that Rob Manfred, or any commissioner, would pressure any owner to do anything, ever. That's just not what commissioners do, because the first law of capitalist relationships is in force here: "Those who pay the salary give orders to those who receive it." And since the argument into which Manfred has allegedly insinuated himself involves hundreds of millions of dollars, the idea of "pressure" is essentially unfathomable. In other words, "What?"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland Stumbles In Six Nations, Rekindles Title Hopes For Failed Imperialist Country Where Rugby Was Invented]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183574</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ireland-stumbles-in-six-nations-rekindles-title-hopes-for-failed-imperialist-country-where-rugby-was-invented"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T16:52:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Europe really is in a shambolic state! As if being abandoned by the U.S. in favor of an Eastern bloc bully wasn’t enough, now comes word that Ireland likely won’t threepeat as Six Nations champions after all! 
Ireland took it on the chin and every other body part from France in a 42-27 loss on Saturday in Dublin. The final score doesn’t really reflect just how brutally the Irish were pounded in the second half of the match. The French players appeared to get bigger, stronger, and faster during a stretch in which they scored 34 unanswered points, crushing the hopes and dreams of the Aviva Stadium crowd and all fans of the tournament’s two-time defending champs. Ireland had a slight lead in the table heading into this much anticipated match, and was the betting favorite to beat France, which would have all but cemented another title in the world’s greatest annual international rugby competition. And what a big title that would be: The Six Nations tournament has been held among Europe’s finest squads since 1883, yet no country has ever won three consecutive outright championships in the event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, March 10: Double Speak]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183566</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-march-10-double-speak"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repeat after me: It’s solving time! This week's puzzle was constructed by Matt Sweeney and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Matt is a public librarian who lives in Boston with his partner and dog named Doc. He started constructing crosswords in 2024 and is thrilled to debut at Defector. 
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spring Training Is An Attack On Me Personally]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183597</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/spring-training-is-an-attack-on-me-personally"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T14:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like any good fan, I was delighted by the return to my television of Something Like Baseball. The Floridian and Arizonan existence of warmth and sunshine augurs their return to my own northern clime, and the ambient noises of baseball are comfort sounds in their own right. But I have gradually realized that spring training is not actually a time of hope, as I have long believed, but rather a time of despair. A time of pain.
A time to learn that your team's hotshot young starting pitcher, looking to follow up a star-making rookie season, couldn't complete a throwing session because of some back tightness. All subsequent updates—PRP injections! Shut down from throwing for a couple months!—are only ever more ominous.*]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Brady’s Vision For The 2025 Raiders Looks An Awful Lot Like The 2023 Seahawks]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183579</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tom-bradys-vision-for-the-2025-raiders-looks-an-awful-lot-like-the-2023-seahawks"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T13:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Brady isn’t officially the general manager of the Las Vegas Raiders, but let’s pretend that he is so that we can make fun of him. Ever since buying a minority stake in the team last year, Brady was reportedly going to be very hands-on with the team’s affairs. Hiring former Bucs executive John Spytek as official GM was an obvious indicator of that, as was Brady’s meet-cute with Matthew Stafford up at a Montana ski resort before Stafford re-upped with the Rams. Shit, Brady even convinced new head coach Pete Carroll that working for this clownshow would be more fulfilling than doing nothing at all!
But now that we’re about to enter the legal tampering period of free agency, also known as “the start of free agency,” Fancy Tom is gonna have to put together an actual roster. He got a head start on that process Friday night by acquiring Geno Smith for a third-round pick.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cavaliers Are Now Playing With Their Food]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183578</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-cavaliers-are-now-playing-with-their-food"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T13:13:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyle Kuzma knocked down a three-pointer from the wing in the fourth quarter Sunday night, to pull the Milwaukee Bucks to within five points of the East-leading Cleveland Cavaliers. The score at that moment was 89-84. The Bucks had done this a few times already, scrambled and shoved and shoulder-charged their way to within a couple buckets of the visitors, who despite their all-timer of a win percentage are just a game up on the Oklahoma City Thunder for the NBA's top overall record. Kuzma's three, nailed with 8:55 left in regulation, seemed to keep momentum on Milwaukee's side, after they'd closed a 15-point first-half deficit to four points late in the third quarter.
The sequence to follow, ah, went poorly for the home side. A little over four minutes later, Darius Garland slipped a pass in traffic to a rolling Jarrett Allen, Allen thundered home a right-handed dunk over Brook Lopez, the crowd went absolutely silent, and the scoreboard showed the Bucks still standing flat-footed on 84 points but somehow now 18 points behind the visitors. Doc Rivers called a timeout. The game was over, but Rivers—always a few beats slower about this kind of thing—needed another 92 seconds to fully internalize it, whereupon he emptied his bench for the game's final three minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Browns Convince Myles Garrett To Stay For Yet Another Rebuild]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183550</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/browns-convince-myles-garrett-to-stay-for-yet-another-rebuild"/>
        <updated>2025-03-09T19:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After spending the week before the Super Bowl issuing a trade request and saying that he was more interested in contending than money, defensive end Myles Garrett has agreed to stay with the Cleveland Browns for more money. That's great for him, but no fun for the rest of us.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cooper Flagg Has Had A Season For The Ages]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183373</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cooper-flagg-has-had-a-season-for-the-ages"/>
        <updated>2025-03-09T17:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because of Cooper Flagg, the Duke Blue Devils faced their first tough test in a while against UNC on Saturday. Thanks to Flagg, they wound up with a 13-point win anyway.
Flagg committed an obvious offensive foul with 3:18 left in the first half of last night's game, sending him to the bench with three fouls and as many points. The Tar Heels instantly ripped off a 10-2 run, then hit a bunch of difficult shots to give themselves a quick seven-point lead early in the second half. Rather than wilt, Flagg spent the game's final 15 minutes showing why NBA GMs are so high on him. Duke started to run everything through Flagg, and he notched five assists, four blocks, and zero fouls through the rest of the game as the Blue Devils won, 82-69. With little margin for error, Flagg made the right play every time, on both ends of the court. The 18-year-old is so huge and skilled that "the right play" was often something bombastic, like rotating over and erasing a layup despite his own teammate crashing into him, or driving left around intense ball pressure and dunking it, per Flagg's mother, on everyone's "fucking head."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtics Bring Lakers Back Down To Earth]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183527</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/celtics-bring-lakers-back-down-to-earth"/>
        <updated>2025-03-09T16:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Expectations this season for the Los Angeles Lakers have skyrocketed, which tends to happen after acquiring a franchise player from a team that appears to be practicing self-sabotage. Since the trade for Luka Doncic, the Lakers have looked more formidable than they have since their conference finals run in 2023, compiling an eight-game win streak that included a convincing 23-point victory over the Denver Nuggets, who swept them out of those conference finals. But Saturday night in Boston delivered a bit of a heat check.
It'd be excessive to say that the Celtics embarrassed the Lakers. Boston only led by four at halftime. The third quarter was where it all turned: The visiting team got cold, and the C's built a 22-point lead during that frame by outshooting their opponents 29-13. The Celtics didn't trail at any point in the second half as they won, 111-101.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Court Of Gold’ Is Brilliant When It Gets Specific]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182976</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/court-of-gold-is-brilliant-when-it-gets-specific"/>
        <updated>2025-03-09T14:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The willingness to embrace specificity is part of what distinguishes Court of Gold from the swelling canon of Netflix original sports programming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple me]]></title>
        <id>67cb4f3f2bb6620001520873</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-272/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T22:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Talia Lavin in the no-funhouse mirror]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Clone Wars]]></title>
        <id>67cb3cbb2bb6620001520842</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/my-clone-wars/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T22:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Talia Lavin

Illustration: Joe MacLeod
It’s never a good idea to search your own name online, but authors do it all the time—and by authors I mean me, a creature who, like Tinkerbell from Peter Pan, will instantly die without sufficient external acknowledgement. So, on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Talia Lavin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hot Whales In Your Area]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/hot-whales-in-your-area</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/hot-whales-in-your-area"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T20:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did they call you mad at the university? Then it's your day to shine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Draymond Green Pivots From Slander To Depraved Podcast Promo]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183453</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/draymond-green-pivots-from-slander-to-depraved-podcast-promo"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T18:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's some context for why Draymond Green followed up condolences with a status update on his donkey podcast, and it only makes him look worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Like A Dragon’ Breathed New Life Into The ‘Yakuza’ Series]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182540</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/like-a-dragon-breathed-new-life-into-the-yakuza-series"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T17:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to The Backlog, a series in which we will take a look back at 12 games from 2020 that, in one way or another, had a lasting impact on the video game industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixing a Hole While Teams Train This Spring To Stop the Central Clubs From Wondering What They Should Do]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=458448</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/fixing-a-hole-while-teams-train-this-spring-to-stop-the-central-clubs-from-wondering-what-they-should-do/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T17:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And it still really doesn’t matter if I’m wrong I’m right...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Szymborski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coups Aren’t What They Used To Be]]></title>
        <id>67cb0fbad4477f0001a1dca5</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/coups-arent-what-they-used-to-be/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T16:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no longer a singular bright line that countries cross between democracy and authoritarianism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Eephus’ Director Carson Lund On Baseball As A Way Of Being]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183332</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/eephus-director-carson-lund-on-baseball-as-a-way-of-being"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T15:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eephus, which opens theatrically in limited release beginning March 7, is “designed to break your heart.” Directed and co-written by Carson Lund in his feature debut, the film unfolds across the length of a single Sunday afternoon adult recreational baseball league between Adler’s Paint and the Riverdogs, beginning as the players get dressed in the parking lot and warm up with soft toss, continuing through nine innings of hamstring-testing hustle doubles and crushed cans of Narragansett, and ending as the October dusk fades to night. It’s the last game, and not just of the season: The field will soon be bulldozed to make way for a new elementary school.
Shot over the course of a month on a local field in Douglas, Mass., Eephus is something like the concentrated essence of baseball, packing in a season’s worth of sense memory—the saltiness of a sunflower seed shell, the weight of a batting donut, the greasiness of a streak of eye black—at the languid tempo of a second baseman holding up his index and pinkie finger for the right fielder after the second out of an inning. The banter ebbs and flows between baserunners and fielders, between teammates on either side of the dugout, alternately hotheaded and banal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Asch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired NOAA Budget Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183219</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-noaa-budget-analyst"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T15:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growing up, Sabrina Valenti felt like she was genetically predetermined to work for the government. Her dad's father was in the Navy. Her dad was in the Air Force. Two of her uncles served in the armed forces, one eventually moving to a job at NASA and the other leaving for the postal service. Her mom's father was a state senator in Maine. One of Valenti's sisters is a teacher, and the other works for a transit agency in a major American city. "I was going to work in the public sector, one way or another," Valenti said.
Valenti grew up in the Florida panhandle, where she witnessed Hurricane Katrina whip through the gulf. And she was in high school when the oil drilling rig Deepwater Horizon exploded and sank in the Gulf of Mexico, killing 11 workers and causing the largest offshore oil spill in U.S. history. During the spill, Valenti recalls seeing "no wake zone" signs everywhere to prevent boats' waves knocking tar balls ashore. Every day before school, Valenti would grab the newspaper from the front porch and see a photo of oil billowing out of a wellhead. For months, Valenti wondered if the paper would say that the well was finally capped. The spill was eventually contained after 87 days. "You're sitting there powerless, knowing that this oil is going to kill shorebirds and seabirds, that it's going to kill fish, that it's going to cause birth defects in dolphins," Valenti said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Live And Age In Rap Music]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183018</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/to-live-and-age-in-rap-music"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T14:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Listening Habits, a new column where I share the music I’ve been fixated on recently.
In the first quarter of the year, a number of the notable new rap albums have come from older rappers, many of whom were most relevant to me when I was a teenager in the 2000s. Some of these albums are more successful than others. One of the stronger efforts comes from 2 Chainz, the Alchemist, and (the much younger) Larry June, who released the collaborative album Life Is Beautiful last month. Here, Chainz and Larry make what could be called Yacht Rap over luxurious, though a little monotonous, Alchemist beats. In this same vein, we've gotten a new Busta Rhymes album, an album from Webbie and his son Tre Savage, and a new album from Jim Jones, fresh off beefing with Cam'ron online over old Dipset drama (again).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How “Ball Don’t Lie” Became More Than A Basketball Mantra]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183207</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-ball-dont-lie-became-more-than-a-basketball-mantra"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T14:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shorthand for the service of karmic justice, often invoked in a smug told-you-so tone, the words remain heard at all levels of the game, from playgrounds to pro arenas. But “Ball don’t lie” has evolved from being an aggrieved athlete’s on-court motto, and achieved wider cultural relevance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Prewitt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complicated victim / Simple plunder]]></title>
        <id>67c9f2be2bb662000151f55e</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-271/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T00:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arwa Mahdawi confronts crime(s), and Jennie Rose Halperin considers copyright shenanigans]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Solve a Murder: Part Two]]></title>
        <id>67ca1d642bb662000151f60d</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/how-to-solve-a-murder-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T00:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Arwa Mahdawi

In July 1996, 36-year-old Susan Walsh supposedly left her house in New Jersey and never came back. She is presumed dead but a body has never been found. This is part two of a series on my five-year investigation into her unsolved disappearance. You can find part]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arwa Mahdawi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Real Copyright Pirates]]></title>
        <id>67ca21362bb662000151f622</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-real-copyright-pirates/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T00:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Jennie Rose Halperin


In 2003, five major record labels sued Boston University graduate student Joel Tenenbaum for copyright infringement based on 30 songs he had shared on Kazaa. Tenenbaum fought back, and six years later the case went to trial; he lost, and a jury awarded the labels $675,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennie Rose Halperin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Live From The Bad Times, With Denny Carter]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183235</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/live-from-the-bad-times-with-denny-carter"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T21:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a general rule, I do not relisten to episodes of the podcast. I spend all day hearing my own voice, inside my head and out, and the idea of going back for more me is ... well, I was going to write horrifying, which seems harsh. I will just say it's not what I want. I would honestly love less me, if that option were available. But of all the episodes of the podcast that I have not relistened to, the one that we put out last November, in which Drew and the excellent sports-and-politics newsletter writer Denny Carter tried to get me pumped up for the election, is the one I have not relistened to the most. Not because it wasn't a good episode—I remember it as having a good number of laughs and an ideal 50/50 split between politics and not politics—but for reasons that are very obvious. We are, of course, wrong all the damn time on this podcast; it is something like our brand, give or take Talking About Lunch and sudden monologues about the Minnesota Vikings. But some ways of being wrong sting more than others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JJ Redick Invented A New Way To Defend Nikola Jokic, And It’s Working]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183311</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jj-redick-invented-a-new-way-to-defend-nikola-jokic-and-its-working"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T20:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you watch Kings–Nuggets last night? So did Nikola Jokic. The three-time MVP had one of his worst games of the season against the mediocre and shorthanded Kings, laboring to 22 points and 15 rebounds with seven turnovers and a relatively ghastly minus-seven. Jokic has been struggling a bit by his incredible standards since the all-star break, which is mostly due to opposing coaches borrowing a hilarious stratagem rolled out by Lakers coach JJ Redick in L.A.'s impressive blowout win over Denver two weeks ago. The scheme is simple: Deny Jokic the ball, at any cost, compromising every single other part of your defense if you have to. The scheme runs counter to almost every modern maxim of defense, yet it's working.
In practice, here's what it looked like against Sacramento. Jake LaRavia's only job in the clip below is to essentially box Jokic out, while Markelle Fultz and DeMar DeRozan give like 10 feet of space to Peyton Watson and Russell Westbrook in order to be able to double Jokic the second he gets the ball. You hear maxims like "Force the rest of the team to beat you!" all the time, but rarely do you see defenses contort themselves like this. The Kings keep all five guys within a foot of the paint for the duration of the play, and Westbrook was kind enough to give them what they wanted by running into a poorly considered midrange jumper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Small Gene Hackman Memory for You]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183272</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-small-gene-hackman-memory-for-you"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T19:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gene Hackman died last week. He was one of the greatest actors America has ever produced. A performer of near infinite utility, able to carry a film single-handedly (Hoosiers) or loom over it with just a few minutes of screen time (No Way Out). Ask a dozen people what their favorite Hackman performance was, and they’ll give you a dozen different answers, none of them wrong. Mine was Crimson Tide. Let me tell you why.
It was 1995. I’d just finished a disastrous freshman year of college that saw me transfer from one school to another at the turn of second semester. I was lonely, disappointed, and deeply unsettled. More important, my spine was fucking killing me. What I thought was some sort of hip pointer—to this day, I don’t actually know what a hip pointer is—turned out to be a blown disc in my back. I needed surgery to fix it. At the end of the school year, a doctor in Manhattan cut into my back, removed the piece of disc lodged against my spinal cord, and then stitched me back up. From there, my mom drove me all the way back to my folks’ house in Connecticut, where a long, manic summer of convalescence awaited me.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ah, Jeez: Goodbye Ball! Goodbye Again! Goodbye A Third Time!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183276</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ah-jeez-goodbye-ball-goodbye-again-goodbye-a-third-time"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T19:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baseball is a beautiful game. Sometimes, you get to watch your team perform incredible feats of athletic prowess while wearing tight pants, and sometimes you watch them give up back-back-to-back home runs. That's America's pastime, baby!
This chaotic state of life extends to managers, too. They're just like us! Take, for example, this spring training game that the Phillies played against the Tigers on Wednesday. In the bottom of the second, Phillies pitcher Jesús Luzardo loaded the bases with two outs. In the dugout, his manager Rob Thomson was on the air, wearing a pop-star microphone while a camera stared directly at him. As a result, we got to watch him watch Luzardo give up not one, not two, but three home runs on three consecutive pitches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liverpool Pulled Off The Heist Of The Season]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183265</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/liverpool-pulled-off-the-heist-of-the-season"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T18:19:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty-seven shots to two. Ten shots on target to one. A whopping 71 to 29 possession split. Hell, even on corners it was 14 to 2. Paris Saint-Germain hosted Liverpool in the first leg of the Champions League round of 16 on Wednesday, and thoroughly demolished what has been the best team in Europe this season. The stats were solidly in PSG's favor, as was the flow of the game, the kind that the phrase "one-way traffic" was invented for. In every way but one, this would indicate a dominant win for the Ligue 1 leaders. Unfortunately for the Parisiens, the one advantage they didn't enjoy is the only one that matters.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7REYuzGyswU]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cavaliers Are Going To Take Some Getting Used To]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183324</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-cavaliers-are-going-to-take-some-getting-used-to"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T17:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[America got its first unofficial glimpse at Adam Silver's definition of institutional despair on Wednesday night. Cleveland and Oklahoma City, back to back on national television—five hours of the future, including ads. We needn't tell you that your entertainment mileage may vary. The business considerations for a league whose best teams play in those sub-optimal markets are no one’s problem but Silver's and his network overlords, but the commissioner must be shitting a pewter tea set just thinking about it, and Disney the rest of the flatware.
In a league in which LeBron James and Stephen Curry and the Boston Celtics and New York Knicks continue to dominate thanks to some not-very-deeply buried biases, Wednesday’s glimpse into the new reality was illuminating. Lord knows the NBA tried. Example: during a review on an out-of-bounds play, referee Pat Fraher described the ruling by referring to Shai Gilgeous-Alexander, the league newest badass di tutti badasses, as "SGA"—the hardest of sells for a new big-name player by the weirdest of salesmen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Ovechkin Is Getting All The Help He Needs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183271</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/alex-ovechkin-is-getting-all-the-help-he-needs"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T17:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Midway through Wednesday night's 3-2 Capitals OT win over the Rangers, the two teams got mad enough to hurt each other with more than just goals. As the first of two second-period fights brewed, TNT analyst Darren Pang alerted the viewers: "Here we go, Wilson and Rempe."
Whoa, would have been one of many proper reactions to this news. Matt Rempe, the Rangers' big beautiful hammer on skates, against Tom Wilson, history's greatest villain? Two players who know the Department of Player Safety's disciplinary process as well as anyone? I can't imagine a more dangerous confrontation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What The Corrections Officer Strike Means To Incarcerated People Like Me]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183254</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-the-corrections-officer-strike-means-to-incarcerated-people-like-me"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T16:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Feb. 17, an illegal wildcat strike was initiated by corrections officers with the New York State Department of Corrections and Community Supervision (DOCCS). One of their primary demands is to repeal the Humane Alternatives to Long Term Solitary Confinement (HALT) Act. Though New York State has pursued mediation to reverse this work stoppage, including offering to temporarily suspend elements of the HALT Act, the majority of striking officers have yet to return to their posts, leaving the incarcerated population, including myself, locked down and surrounded by chaos. At least seven people have died behind bars since this began. According to eyewitness testimony, at least one of these deaths—that of 22 year old Messiah Nantwi—was caused by a brutal beating at the hands of corrections officers. Other deaths are reportedly due to medical neglect. It is also worth noting that the strike was initiated only three days before the much anticipated announcement of murder charges brought against a group of corrections officers from Marcy Correctional Facility over the death of Robert Brooks. 
As its name suggests, the HALT Act  was designed to ensure incarcerated individuals were treated in more humane ways. Choosing to focus on rehabilitating prisoners rather than continuously and excessively penalizing us, this act prioritizes both the physical and mental health of incarcerated individuals by increasing the amount of time we are permitted social interaction with each other and with our families, while also retaining access to productive programming, such as education and job training.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Pastore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Enough People Are Taking The Wallet Inspector Seriously]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183264</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/not-enough-people-are-taking-the-wallet-inspector-seriously"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T16:24:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a weird amount of overlap between the people who insist that we take climate experts seriously when they warn of big changes on the horizon, and people who refuse to take the wallet inspector seriously when he warns that there is a problem with their wallet that he must examine immediately. Huh! Interesting! Peculiar! I find it curious to say the least!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Not Be Bamboozled By The New Fluffy Mouse]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183066</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/do-not-be-bamboozled-by-the-new-fluffy-mouse"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T14:57:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I see it, there are a few unofficial laws of science journalism when it comes to covering new research. The first and most obvious is that outlets are more likely to cover a press release if it is accompanied by nice-looking, high-resolution photos, because these make readers more likely to click on the story. Outlets are even more likely to pick up the story if those photos are of a charismatic animal: a beloved pachyderm, a striking bird, a sweet little rodent. The second law is that well-funded companies can produce better press releases than most institutions, with galleries of photos, videos, and lists of experts who are just a call away, making these stories easier to write on a tight deadline. The third law is that many journalists are overworked and underpaid, sometimes racing to meet a quota. So when a lavishly produced press release about seemingly feel-good research drops into their lap, featuring an adorable critter as a cherry on top, it is easy to write a simple story, meaning an uncritical one.
All of these laws conspired this week after the biotechnology company Colossal Bioscience released their newly created "woolly mice," which the company describes as a mouse that has been gene-edited to have traits similar to those of woolly mammoths. I have previously written about the many logistical, ethical, and scientific problems with de-extinction, so I will only briefly say that de-extinction is a morally questionable gambit in a time when tens of thousands of species are threatened by extinction. I am thoroughly unconvinced by Colossal's argument that returning extinct species to modern-day habitats, which have considerably warmed since the mammoth went extinct, will make these ecosystems more resilient to climate change. Despite its colossal promises and frequent press releases announcing secondary plans to de-extinct other animals, the company appears more invested in raising capital than restoring an actual mammoth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women’s Sports Happened By Accident, And Could Be Taken Apart On Purpose]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182469</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/womens-sports-happened-by-accident-and-could-be-taken-apart-on-purpose"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T14:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Monday night, and I check my local TV listings to see what women's college basketball games are on. I make a note to catch all the big women's college gymnastics meets coming up on Friday. I dutifully add all the dates for my local NWSL team's games to my calendar. It seems and at some level just is incredibly normal to be watching women's sports at big stadiums and on TV, but I'm also old enough to know that all this progress is due not to moral clarity or some belated public awakening to how good women's sports can be, but to a pair of classic American forces: unintended consequences and bureaucracy.
Women's sports has always hung on by the thinnest of threads. They are not mentioned even once in the law that created them, and once the powers that be realized what that law had done, they went all the way up to the presidency to try and undo it. The NCAA objected to supporting women's sports, and searched for years to find a way out of that obligation. Even President Gerald R. Ford's office seemed concerned about those "women's organizations." Our country's perch atop global women's sports happened not because our leadership desired it, or even cared all that much about it, or held strong feelings about the place of women in society in general. It happened due to a collection of random factors all happening in a specific time and space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>