<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-08-27T17:10:49.145Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Padres broadcast shocked by sparse St. Louis Cardinals crowd]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=633107</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/padres-broadcast-sparse-st-louis-cardinals-crowd-busch-stadium.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T17:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Busch Stadium continues to set record lows for St. Louis Cardinals attendance, San Diego Padres announcers Don Orsillo and Mark Grant were stunned by the turnout. The Cardinals aren’t great this season, but they were buyers at the trade deadline and were sitting right at .500 before welcoming the Padres to St. Louis begin Read more...
The post Padres broadcast shocked by sparse St. Louis Cardinals crowd appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Chore Gets Forgotten The Most Often?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=165491</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/which-chore-gets-forgotten-the-most-often"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! Let me start with a confession: When I was asked to guest-host the Funbag I figured it would be pretty easy, given the fact that I’ve written an advice column of my own on and off for the past six or seven years. How different could it be? Well, it turns out that having a facility for firmly but gently telling depressed socialists to get over themselves and ask someone out doesn’t help much when it comes to answering questions about front-office management techniques or, bizarrely, deciding who in recent history had the most skin. (I’m sorry, Michael, but I do not know. Surely someone large, or with a rare medical condition.)
Anyway, I tried my best. Please forgive me for not weighing in on the Mariners’ decision to fire Scott Servais. I did manage to have a very good time with this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Jensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Kruk predicted Bryce Harper’s walk-off two innings before it happened]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=633068</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/john-kruk-predicted-bryce-harper-walk-off.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Kruk might be known for his one-liners and wild stories on Philadelphia Phillies broadcasts, but he’s capable of making some impressive predictions too. Monday night, Bryce Harper hit a walk-off single in the bottom of the 10th inning, leading the Phillies to a 3-2 win over the first-place Houston Astros to start their seven-game Read more...
The post John Kruk predicted Bryce Harper’s walk-off two innings before it happened appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is There Still Gold Hidden in Them Thar Hills?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43362_is-there-still-gold-hidden-in-them-thar-hills.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43362_is-there-still-gold-hidden-in-them-thar-hills.html?newsletter-cat=science-history"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Eli Yudin   Published: August 27th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL will not use automated first down technology for 2024 season]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=633043</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/automated-first-down-technology-2024-season.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFL is a gazillion dollar enterprise, but for the 2024 season it will once again use an incredibly primitive system worth a handful of dollars to determine what is and is not a first down. After running preseason trials on their new automated first down technology that mimics the Hawk-Eye system in tennis, the Read more...
The post NFL will not use automated first down technology for 2024 season appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Judge Tells Undocumented Spouses Of US Citizens To GTFO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/federal-judge-tells-undocumented</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/federal-judge-tells-undocumented"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:11:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tearing families apart is the American Way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doktor Zoom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Burkhardt reveals Tom Brady’s popularity affected pregame routine]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632993</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/kevin-burkhardt-tom-brady-popularity-pregame-routine.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone knew Tom Brady would face a learning curve in his first season as Fox Sports’ lead NFL analyst. Probably no one guessed that part of that process would involve Brady learning how to get to the broadcast booth without being stopped by players, coaches and others who just want to chat and even take Read more...
The post Kevin Burkhardt reveals Tom Brady’s popularity affected pregame routine appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conservatives Who Sold Their Souls for Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698429</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/the-conservatives-who-sold-their-souls-for-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Nichols: “Stepping outside of years of partisan tribal affiliations comes with professional and social costs (and for politicians, electoral consequences). But principles are sometimes burdensome things; that’s part of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Trend In Book Covers Is Old-Timey Animals]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=164555</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-new-trend-in-book-covers-is-old-timey-animals"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:44:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don't judge "Don't judge a book by its cover" by its cover. I mean that in the specific and general senses, as a book cover can answer many questions about what's going on in there: What feeling does this book hope to evoke? And what other works does this book want to, visually, place itself alongside? Consider the phenomenon of the blob.
If you perused a bookstore's new fiction section anytime between 2019 and 2023, you probably saw a bunch of books festooned by indistinct, pastely swatches of color. A bunch of smart, incisive things have been written about the color blob trend over the course of its moment as the book cover trend du too many jours, and the template was so ubiquitously adhered to that you didn't even have to have read You Exist Too Much or The Vanishing Half to have understood its deal. Book cover design, like any other field of design, moves in waves. While the color blob was preceded by the two-dimensional color block meta and the headless woman fad, there are some particularities to note. Blobwave's rise was contemporaneous with that of algorithmic book-buying, both on Amazon and on social media, and as Print noted three years ago, color blob design represented a "'safe' route disproportionately taken in service of women of color and debut authors."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Smith Officially Asks 11th Circuit To Hand Judge Aileen Cannon Her Ass Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/jack-smith-officially-asks-11th-circuit</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/jack-smith-officially-asks-11th-circuit"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:36:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He asked nicely, though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Hurst</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-Trump Group Plans $60 Million Ad Blitz]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698424</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/pro-trump-group-plans-60-million-ad-blitz/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:35:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“A super PAC started by supporters of Donald Trump is launching what is expected to be a $60 million advertising campaign to boost the former president’s campaign right after Labor […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senate Race Deadlocked in Maryland]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698422</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/senate-race-deadlocked-in-maryland/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new AARP poll in Maryland finds Larry Hogan (R) and Angela Alsobrooks (D) tied in the U.S. Senate race, 46% to 46%. In the presidential race, Kamala Harris leads […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venu Sports backers claim $74 million investment in Fubo ruling appeal]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=633065</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/venu-sports/backers-claim-74-million-investment-in-fubo-appeal.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a little more than a week since the ESPN-Warner Bros. Discovery-Fox joint streaming venture Venu Sports has been sidelined. And now the triumvirate of media companies have officially launched an appeal to see the decision overturned, arguing that they’ve already spent tens of millions of dollars on what they argue is “an innovative Read more...
The post Venu Sports backers claim $74 million investment in Fubo ruling appeal appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Hinchcliffe Says His Podcast Is ‘Eating ‘Saturday Night Live’s Lunch’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43369_tony-hinchcliffe-says-his-podcast-is-eating-saturday-night-lives-lunch.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43369_tony-hinchcliffe-says-his-podcast-is-eating-saturday-night-lives-lunch.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Matt Solomon   Published: August 27th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump to Put Kennedy and Gabbard on Transition Team]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698423</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/trump-to-put-kennedy-and-gabbard-on-transition-team/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Donald Trump plans to name his former rival, Robert F. Kennedy Jr., and Tulsi Gabbard, a one-time Democrat, as honorary co-chairs of a presidential transition team that will help him […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s Trending Up And Trending Down After ‘Industry’ Episodes 2-3]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=165414</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/whos-trending-up-and-tending-down-after-industry-episodes-2-3"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:18:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With only three episodes under its belt, Industry Season 3 has been going at warp speed with drama, shakeups, and plot, plot, plot. Practically an entire season's worth of story has happened with nearly every character already. Just thinking about where things could possibly go from here overwhelms me. With that in mind, let's check back in on our beloved characters' delightfully volatile trajectories.
Harper Stern: Going Up! Up! Up! Harperhive, we are so back! And we are eating good in this neighborhood. Last week, she was scratching that girlboss itch with Petra Koenig that had been dormant for so long, already showing that she has not learned a thing after being fired from Pierpoint, and salivating for her moment of revenge. She helped Petra undermine their boss Anna by balancing out Lumi's nosediving stock and got her an advantageous price by doing a little cheating. But last week was merely an appetizer for Harper's full supervillain pivot on Sunday. Her and Petra test the waters of striking out on their own and right when it looked like it was going to blow up on the launchpad, she decides to put all the chips on the table and make her move in public, bridge-burning fashion. And not only is she rewarded for this, with a billionaire benefactor who seems to favor her even more than Petra, but she gets the added benefit of forcing Pierpoint's (and specifically Eric's) hand by becoming a client. Harper played the hits in this episode and it was absolute magic, showing a wolfish delight in forcing Eric to bend the knee, puppet-mastering her supposed friend Yasmin and business partner Petra, and winning the respect of Otto Mostyn. Her downfall is inevitable and will be one for the ages certainly, but for the moment, Harper and the Harper fanbase are shining bright like a diamond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Takes Lead Nationally]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698416</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/kamala-harris-takes-national-lead/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:14:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Florida Atlantic University poll finds Kamala Harris has taken the lead over Donald Trump nationally among likely voters, 49% to 45%. Key finding: “Harris has made significant inroads […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Holds Small Edge in Arizona]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698415</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/trump-holds-small-edge-in-arizona/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Noble Predictive Insights poll in Arizona finds Donald Trump edging Kamala Harris in a multi-candidate race, 44% to 43%. In a head-to-head match up, Trump leads 47% to 44%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris Releases New Ad on Housing Costs]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698414</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/harris-releases-new-ad-on-housing-costs/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new ad from Kamala Harris, part of a $150 million ad campaign for the month of August, focuses on housing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vance to Campaign Behind Bulletproof Glass]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698413</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/vance-to-campaign-behind-bulletproof-glass/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Sen. J.D. Vance will deliver remarks on the economy on Tuesday in Big Rapids, Michigan, at an outdoor farm — during which he will speak from behind bulletproof glass, the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CBS Sports HQ to launch college football pregame show for 2024 season]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632954</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/cbs/college-football-pregame-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joining the ever-expanding college football pregame fray, CBS Sports HQ is launching its own Saturday morning pregame show. Aptly named College Football Pregame, the show will premiere Aug. 31 at 9 a.m. (ET). Hosted by Jordan Giorgio and Jeremy St. Louis, College Football Pregame will preview each week’s action with a bevy of analysts and Read more...
The post CBS Sports HQ to launch college football pregame show for 2024 season appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Food Preparation Methods That Will Make You Say ‘I Actually Just Ate’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43364_5-food-preparation-methods-that-will-make-you-say-i-actually-just-ate.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43364_5-food-preparation-methods-that-will-make-you-say-i-actually-just-ate.html?newsletter-cat=science-history"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Eli Yudin   Published: August 27th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[great exhibition]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205242</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205242/great-exhibition"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hidden beneath the streets of London, the Crystal Palace Subway is a Victorian foot tunnel and a relic of a bygone era. Opened in 1865 alongside the 'High Level' railway station, the subterranean maze features include ornate design elements, including a grand Italianate facade. [ad (also includes 9 other places)]
previously: globally unique monuments, archaeological method & conscience, audience, it's still rock & roll to me

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Great_Exhibition]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HearHere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eat This Now: Worm Dip at The Drunken Worm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=845347</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/eat-this-now-worm-dip-at-the-drunken-worm/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worm Dip // Photo by Sarah Sipple I’ve never explicitly asked you to trust me, but for this dish, I’m playing that card. Worm dip ($10) at The Drunken Worm just might be the worst dish to feature when it comes to food photography. I’m not sure that a true professional photographer could make it look any more appealing. Then...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consider: Gatorwine]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=165463</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/consider-gatorwine"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:43:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week I traveled to Tuscany, the birthplace of the Renaissance, the home of Chianti, land of cobblestones and no air conditioning and extremely rare T-bone steaks. What better place to expand your palate and acquaint yourself with new ways of tasting, living, being? What better place to mix one of the most cursed beverages known to mankind: Gatorwine?
I met up with my best friend and some of her friends, who have a tradition of trying horrifying drink combinations; some of their greatest hits include BORG night and Flamin' Hot Mountain Dew night. When we met, they were reviewing the Monster Energy gelato they had just tried (disgusting, allegedly). So it was a natural segue to talk about their next culinary conquest for the trip.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CBS video challenges Kevin Harlan to identify his greatest calls]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632968</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/cbs/kevin-harlan-greatest-calls.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:35:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those fans who can’t get enough of Kevin Harlan’s electric calls on big plays and iconic moments, CBS Sports just dropped a fun “greatest hits” video on YouTube. And to make the video even more enjoyable, Harlan is challenged to a game, “Name That Call,” where he is asked to identify those calls. It’s Read more...
The post CBS video challenges Kevin Harlan to identify his greatest calls appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Judge Blocks Biden From Letting Sandwich Shop Workers Change Jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/trump-judge-blocks-biden-from-letting</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/trump-judge-blocks-biden-from-letting"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop thinking your employer doesn't own you, silly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doktor Zoom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Norm Macdonald Auditioned for the Aflac Duck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43359_norm-macdonald-auditioned-for-the-aflac-duck.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43359_norm-macdonald-auditioned-for-the-aflac-duck.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Matt Solomon   Published: August 27th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angel Reese announces new weekly podcast ‘Unapologetically Angel’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=633082</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/wnba/angel-reese-announces-new-weekly-podcast.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:20:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chicago Sky star rookie Angel Reese is one of the most talked about athletes in all of sports. Ever since she led LSU to a national championship, her rivalry with Caitlin Clark has helped women’s basketball soar in ratings and interest from the college game now to the WNBA. But now Reese will be the Read more...
The post Angel Reese announces new weekly podcast ‘Unapologetically Angel’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quote of the Day]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698395</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/quote-of-the-day-3938/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I was sort of like a hot guy. I was hot as a pistol. I think I was hotter than I am now, and I became president. Okay. I don’t […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weirdo States Want In Trans Drivers' Pants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/weirdo-states-want-in-trans-drivers</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/weirdo-states-want-in-trans-drivers"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kids too! And actually there's something wrong with that!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Crip Dyke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kelce brothers reach $100 million-plus deal with Amazon for ‘New Heights’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=633031</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/podcasts/kelce-brothers-new-heights-amazon-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Travis in training camp and Jason preparing for his new role at ESPN, New Heights with Jason and Travis Kelce has been on hiatus since July 3. And when it returns, it will have a new home. According to Variety, the Kelce brothers have inked a deal for their popular podcast with Amazon’s Wondery. Read more...
The post Kelce brothers reach $100 million-plus deal with Amazon for ‘New Heights’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Christmas Comes Early and Airborne]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=445091</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/big-christmas-comes-early-and-airborne/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Guardians seem to be modernizing, thanks in part to Il Natale Grande.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Baumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Ambition Is Good in Politics]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698364</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/why-ambition-is-good-in-politics/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Bernstein: “The way I talk about is that all politicians are ambitious, but the content of that ambition varies, so that one politician might be interested in one or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Was ‘Seinfeld’ at the Vanguard of the Public Urination Debate?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43368_was-seinfeld-at-the-vanguard-of-the-public-urination-debate.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43368_was-seinfeld-at-the-vanguard-of-the-public-urination-debate.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  JM McNab   Published: August 27th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hostage Rescued in Gaza Tunnels]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698394</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/hostage-rescued-in-gaza-tunnels/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:59:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Israeli forces rescued an Arab citizen of Israel taken hostage in the Hamas-led attacks last Oct. 7 during an operation in the southern Gaza Strip, the Israeli military said on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The morning read for Tuesday, August 27]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scotusblog.com/?p=317241</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotusblog.com/2024/08/the-morning-read-for-tuesday-august-27/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each weekday, we select a short list of news articles, commentary, and other noteworthy links related to the Supreme Court. Here’s the Tuesday morning read: The Supreme Court is sowing confusion over how it will handle election disputes this fall (John Fritze, CNN) Special counsel...
The post The morning read for Tuesday, August 27 appeared first on SCOTUSblog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ellena Erskine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QAnon Prophet: Trump To Get Endorsement From Dead Celebrity Of Some Sort]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/qanon-prophet-trump-to-get-endorsement</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/qanon-prophet-trump-to-get-endorsement"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's obviously Elvis, right?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robyn Pennacchia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon reportedly withdraws $115 million offer to Diamond Sports Group]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=633007</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/bally/amazon-withdraws-115-million-diamond-sports-group.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon has reportedly withdrawn its $115 million offer to struggling Diamond Sports Group, but the regional sports network carrier still apparently has the necessary funding to proceed in its bid to emerge from bankruptcy. Sports Business Journal reported Monday that Amazon has dropped its offer. Diamond, parent company of Bally Sports Regional Sports Networks, announced Read more...
The post Amazon reportedly withdraws $115 million offer to Diamond Sports Group appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four-Star General Under Bush Endorses Kamala Harris]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698378</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/four-star-general-under-bush-endorses-kamala-harris/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[General Larry Ellis, a retired four-star general who served in that rank under George W. Bush’s administration, is endorsing Vice President Kamala Harris,  ABC News reports. Said Ellis: “Donald Trump […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 08.27.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074367</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/morning-docket-08-27-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:14:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Associates growing increasingly suspicious as Biglaw firms balk at joining the Milbank summer bonus train. [American Lawyer]
* America's terminally online nature makes it harder and harder to control what a jury learns. [Legal Intelligencer]
* Prosecutors pursuing cases based upon racial animus remains a problem in America. Unfortunately this is a story about Trump claiming Black prosecutors are racist against him. [Washington Post]
* Jack Smith delivered a scorcher to the Eleventh Circuit, taking Judge Aileen Cannon to task for failing to grasp "precedent and history." [Law360]
* Trump campaign claims it's a conflict of interest that Harris is getting debate prep from Karen Dunn because the latter represents Google in the DOJ's case against the tech giant. That's not really how conflicts of interest work but the campaign suggests it shows Harris is in the pocket of Big Tech as opposed to the Peter Thiel, Larry Ellison, Elon Musk backed Trump. [Fox News]
* As Biglaw firms continue to grow, one firm shakes off the prospect of a merger. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Election suits begin early with Democrats challenging new Georgia election laws pushed by Republicans to allow local level officials (where election denialists can thrive) to deny vote certification. [Reuters]
The post Morning Docket: 08.27.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[August Is For Weird Baseball]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=165443</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/august-is-for-weird-baseball"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is unwise to expect too much from August baseball. The new car smell of a season built on hope is gone, the daily grind of playing in 102-degree heat and 98 percent humidity has become oppressive, and the significant stuff doesn’t start until next month. The most you can really expect from the fauna who bring us baseball is strictly improv. Not pure athleticism, which we can see every day in every other sport, or jaw-slackening power, which we see every day from Aaron Judge, or even child-searing heartbreak, which is implicit if we are for whatever macabre reason watching Little League baseball on television. And this doesn’t even include the White Sox, who are plenty weird but also exist in context and in any event are still 19 losses away from their own version of nirvana. What you want, and the best you might get, is something inconsequential that you will most likely never see again.
So we should start with Danny Jansen, who became the first player in MLB history to play for both teams in the same game on Monday. You likely already know this, because we've had days to prepare for it—and, given that it’s August and all, because there has been plenty of coverage from a baseball media reduced to waiting for its local team's next soon-to-be-failed phenom to be promoted from Double-A. Jansen had just fouled off the first pitch he saw while batting for Toronto against the Red Sox in Fenway Park on June 26 when a storm blew up the game; when it was resumed 61 days later, Jansen found himself catching the conclusion of his at-bat for those very Sox, who acquired him at the trade deadline exactly a month earlier. He struck himself out, with Daulton Varsho playing the role Jansen originated; Jansen convinced Nick Pivetta to beat Faux Jansen with a four-seam fastball and a slider in the dirt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calculating WAR Using RE24]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=445062</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/calculating-war-using-re24/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How valuable are a player's offensive contributions? It depends on how you define "value" - and WAR lets you pick.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Clemens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When will we get the next Tony Kornheiser in the broadcast booth?]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632881</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/next-tony-kornheiser-broadcast-booth-mina-kimes-peter-schrager.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Kornheiser’s tenure as a Monday Night Football game analyst is one of the strangest experiments in sports broadcasting history. The longtime columnist’s departure in 2009 was the last time an NFL color commentator was not a former athlete or coach, and the way his time in the booth ended may be why. There was a Read more...
The post When will we get the next Tony Kornheiser in the broadcast booth? appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Americans Have a Constitutional Right to an AR-15?]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698354</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/do-americans-have-a-constitutional-right-to-an-ar-15/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street Journal: “Should the conservative Supreme Court take up the case in its new term, it could put some of the gun-control movement’s biggest victories in jeopardy.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Malkovich Gave Charlie Day From ‘It’s Always Sunny in Philadelphia’ This Advice for Acting in Commercials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43363_john-malkovich-gave-charlie-day-from-its-always-sunny-in-philadelphia-this-advice-for-acting-in-commercials.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43363_john-malkovich-gave-charlie-day-from-its-always-sunny-in-philadelphia-this-advice-for-acting-in-commercials.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Keegan Kelly   Published: August 27th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waaait A Minute, You're Telling Us The Trump Campaign Is A GRIFT?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/waaait-a-minute-youre-telling-us</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/waaait-a-minute-youre-telling-us"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T12:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This horse is out of the barn and halfway across the continent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Legum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reporters across borders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cjr.org/?p=102436</id>
        <link href="https://www.cjr.org/the_media_today/russia_kursk_journalists_ukraine_durov.php"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T12:52:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this month, Russian social media posts indicated that something significant might be happening at the border between the region of Kursk and Ukraine. “Everything was a little bit vague,” Andrew Kramer, a reporter at the New York Times, recalled on the paper’s Daily podcast last week. “We were seeing reports of fighting along the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Allsop</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fox reportedly opposes UConn joining Big 12]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632951</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/fox-opposes-uconn-joining-big-12.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T12:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UConn’s possible move to the Big 12 got a big promotional push Monday from a consulting firm that pitched the benefits of adding the basketball power to the conference. However, one party with a vested interest in UConn’s future, Fox Sports, reportedly opposes the move, according to CBS Sports. In a virtual briefing with Big Read more...
The post Fox reportedly opposes UConn joining Big 12 appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beat the Streak Picks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153683</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153683"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T12:22:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Log5 Method yields these top project hit averages against starting pitchers: 0.340 — Luis Arraez batting against Miles Mikolas. 0.320 — Aaron Judge batting against Patrick Corbin. 0.314 — Donovan Solano batting against Miles Mikolas. 0.311 — Jackson Merrill batting against Miles Mikolas. 0.305 — Vladimir Guerrero Jr. batting against Cooper Criswell. 0.302 — […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canadian PM Justin Trudeau's government announces foreign worker changes]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205241</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205241/Canadian-PM-Justin-Trudeaus-government-announces-foreign-worker-changes"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T12:21:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These changes will impact foreign workers and people applying for permanent residency. The Toronto Star did an investigation about how the process is abused by employers with very little oversight from the federal government.  (originalTO Star link here)
Sectors that will not be impacted are: agriculture, healthcare, construction, and food security.

Speaking for myself, the workers do not deserve the racist invective hurled at them. The blame lays at the employers deliberately exploiting the program. The FWP system is a current favourite racist bugbear for many white Canadians.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kitteh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL analytics expert Warren Sharp on what to expect for the 2024 season]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=630697</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/analytics-expert-warren-sharp-2024-season.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T12:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFL returns next week, and we all can’t wait to see how the season will unfold. There are many unknowns, and every fan hopes their team will exceed expectations. Will the Kansas City Chiefs three-peat? Will the Philadelphia Eagles bounce back? Will Caleb Williams live up to the hype? We caught up with Warren Read more...
The post NFL analytics expert Warren Sharp on what to expect for the 2024 season appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Grant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Around the Horn’ goes in on Deion Sanders for columnist ban: ‘He needs to grow up’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632935</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/deion-sanders-around-the-horn-columnist-ban.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T12:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the topic of Deion Sanders banning a columnist from asking questions went round and round on ESPN’s airwaves Monday, it certainly made for good fodder. Just because it lasted until Around the Horn and likely Pardon the Interruption before hitting Tuesday’s new cycle doesn’t mean it lost its luster. The show, which has become entrenched in the Read more...
The post ‘Around the Horn’ goes in on Deion Sanders for columnist ban: ‘He needs to grow up’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top of the Order: The Other Mike Baumann Continues His World Tour]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=445006</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/top-of-the-order-the-other-mike-baumann-continues-his-world-tour/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T12:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The right-handed pitcher, not the FanGraphs writer, is racking up the frequent flyer miles. Plus, Danny Jansen makes history.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Becker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bewildering Politics of Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698353</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/the-bewildering-politics-of-telegram/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“When Telegram founder Pavel Durov was arrested late Saturday at an airport outside Paris, accused of complicity in illegal online behavior and refusing to disclose information to authorities, right-leaning American […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Gross Ways Our Ancestors Used Animals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43351_5-gross-ways-our-ancestors-used-animals.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43351_5-gross-ways-our-ancestors-used-animals.html?newsletter-cat=science-history"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Ryan Menezes   Published: August 27th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153681</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153681"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T11:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Averts All-Out War With Hezbollah]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698355</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/israel-averts-all-out-war-with-hezbollah/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T11:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“After weeks of foreboding, an all-out war between Israel and Hezbollah has been averted, at least for now, as both sides returned on Monday to more contained confrontations along the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delayed Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153679</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153679"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T11:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Due to technical difficulties, the update of the Day by Day Database is delayed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Know About the First Harris-Trump Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.teenvogue.com/story/first-harris-trump-debate-what-to-know</id>
        <link href="https://www.teenvogue.com/story/first-harris-trump-debate-what-to-know"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T11:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Including when and how to tune in to watch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Breaking US, World &amp; College News | Teen Vogue | Teen Vogue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris Taunts Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698365</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/harris-taunts-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T11:35:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“When former President Trump suggested he might back out of the Sept. 10 debate, the Harris campaign posted sound effects of squawking, whining chickens, layered over video of Trump speaking,” […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Painterly depiction of material properties]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205240</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205240/Painterly-depiction-of-material-properties"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T11:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Furthermore, painters are not constrained by reality, meaning that they could paint materials without exactly following the laws of nature, while still evoking the perception of materials." [SLPDF]
(This post brought to you as a research "offcut" associated with a story I'm working on that involves mental processing of art images.)

Abstract: 

Painters are masters of depiction and have learned to evoke a clear perception of materials and material attributes in a natural, three-dimensional setting, with complex lighting conditions. Furthermore, painters are not constrained by reality, meaning that they could paint materials without exactly following the laws of nature, while still evoking the perception of materials. Paintings have to our knowledge not been studied on a big scale from a material perception perspective. In this article, we studied the perception of painted materials and their attributes by using human annotations to find instances of 15 materials, such as wood, stone, fabric, etc. Participants made perceptual judgments about 30 unique segments of these materials for 10 material attributes, such as glossiness, roughness, hardness, etc. We found that participants were able to perform this task well while being highly consistent. Participants, however, did not consistently agree with each other, and the measure of consistency depended on the material attribute being perceived. Additionally, we found that material perception appears to function independently of the medium of depiction—the results of our principal component analysis agreed well with findings in former studies for photographs and computer renderings.

Citation:

van Zuijlen, Mitchell JP, Sylvia C. Pont, and Maarten WA Wijntjes. "Painterly depiction of material properties." Journal of vision 20, no. 7 (2020): 7-7.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cupcakeninja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Donald Trump and Kamala Harris actually debate?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.poynter.org/?p=1121308</id>
        <link href="https://www.poynter.org/commentary/2024/trump-skip-back-out-presidential-debate-harris/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T11:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there going to be a presidential debate between Donald Trump and Kamala Harris or what? A debate is officially scheduled for Sept. 10 on ABC. But Trump is already […]
The post Will Donald Trump and Kamala Harris actually debate? appeared first on Poynter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Five Kennedys Most Likely To Take RFK Jr.'s Calls (Number Four Is NOPE). Tabs, Tues., Aug. 27, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/the-five-kennedys-most-likely-to</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/the-five-kennedys-most-likely-to"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T11:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NOPE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Hurst</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for August 27, 2024: how to watch college volleyball]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632978</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/viewing-picks/tv-and-streaming-viewing-picks-for-august-27-2024-how-to-watch-college-volleyball.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T11:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All Times Eastern Carabao Cup Second Round Brighton & Hove Albion vs. Crawley Town — Paramount+, 2:45 p.m. Everton vs. Doncaster — Paramount+, 2:45 p.m. Leicester City vs. Tranmere — Paramount+, 2:45 p.m. Birmingham vs. Fulham — CBS Sports Network, 3 p.m. Crystal Palace vs. Norwich City — CBS Sports Golazo Network, 3 p.m. CBS Read more...
The post TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for August 27, 2024: how to watch college volleyball appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Agenda Would Explode Deficit]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698351</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/trumps-agenda-would-explode-deficit/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Penn Wharton Budget Model: “We estimate that the Trump Campaign tax and spending proposals would increase primary deficits by $5.8 trillion over the next 10 years on a conventional basis […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump falsely claimed that Joe Biden and Kamala Harris manipulated job data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.poynter.org/?p=1121265</id>
        <link href="https://www.poynter.org/fact-checking/2024/job-data-manipulated-fact-check/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The federal agency that calculates how many people are working handed Democrats an unwelcome present during the week of their national convention in Chicago: a downward adjustment of the past […]
The post Donald Trump falsely claimed that Joe Biden and Kamala Harris manipulated job data appeared first on Poynter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Jacobson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Isn’t Nikki Haley Campaigning for Trump?]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/why-isnt-nikki-haley-campaigning-for-trump/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/why-isnt-nikki-haley-campaigning-for-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T10:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Semafor: “The biggest impasse seems to be surrounding who should officially reach out first: It’s unclear whether there’s been formal discussions between the two campaigns in recent weeks about getting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris Campaign Mulls First Major Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/harris-campaign-mulls-first-major-interview/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/harris-campaign-mulls-first-major-interview/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T10:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris’ campaign aides have been asking reporters who she should sit down with for her first interview, Politico reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris Won’t Use AI-Generated Trump for Debate Prep]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/harris-wont-use-ai-generated-trump-for-debate-prep/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/harris-wont-use-ai-generated-trump-for-debate-prep/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T10:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The Harris-Walz campaign will not use an AI-generated Donald Trump as a stand-in for the former president during debate prep,” Semafor reports. “Why did we ask? Sheera Frenkel of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats Go on Offense Over Taxes]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/democrats-go-on-offense-over-taxes/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/democrats-go-on-offense-over-taxes/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T10:33:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Politico: “Traditionally, taxes haven’t been a winning issue for Democrats. Republicans claimed the mantle of the party of tax cuts in the 1980s and put their opponents on the defensive. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Campaign Airs Ads Near Mar-a-Lago]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/trump-campaign-airs-ads-near-mar-a-lago/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/trump-campaign-airs-ads-near-mar-a-lago/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T10:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bulwark: “Palm Beach County is a Democratic stronghold in a Republican state that Trump has little chance of losing. But Trump’s staff is at some risk of incurring his […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White Sox Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153676</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153676"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T10:26:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tigers beat the White Sox 6-3 on Monday, lowering the White Sox winning percentage on the season to .235. That is below the .250 winning percentage of the 1962 Mets, the modern record for mediocrity. Time to update the probability of Chicago finishing with no more than 40 wins. They need to go no […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sunshine follows thunder]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205238</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205238/sunshine-follows-thunder"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T10:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oasis are back together. 15 years after the band broke up, they have announced a reunion tour of 14 dates in 2025 in Cardiff, Manchester, London, Edinburgh and Dublin, with tickets on sale on Saturday. "The guns have fallen silent. The stars have aligned. The great wait is over. Come see. It will not be televised," the band said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fight or flight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Short and to the Point: Peter Bukowski on Brandon Aiyuk, Jordan Love, Aaron Rodgers, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632824</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/orig/peter-bukowski-jordan-love-aaron-rodgers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T10:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Host Jessica Kleinschmidt interviews Locked on Packers host and co-founder of The Leap, Peter Bukowski. Jessica and Peter discuss a wide range of topics including the ongoing Brandon Aiyuk trade reports, Jordan Love taking over the Packers offense, covering Aaron Rodgers, and more. Here’s the full breakdown. 2:08: Welcome Peter to Short and to the Read more...
The post Short and to the Point: Peter Bukowski on Brandon Aiyuk, Jordan Love, Aaron Rodgers, and more appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Bupp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. May Be Unable to Remove Name from Some Ballots]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/rfk-jr-may-be-unable-to-remove-name-from-some-ballots/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/rfk-jr-may-be-unable-to-remove-name-from-some-ballots/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T09:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“After spending several months and millions of dollars overcoming onerous requirements to try to get on the ballot in all 50 states, Robert F. Kennedy Jr. is now facing new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A Weirdo Campaign Just Got Weirder’]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/a-weirdo-campaign-just-got-weirder/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/a-weirdo-campaign-just-got-weirder/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T09:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Democrats say they have a simple plan for discrediting Robert F. Kennedy Jr. now that he has dropped out of the race and endorsed former President Donald Trump: calling him […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Harris’ Lead Last?]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/will-harris-lead-last/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/will-harris-lead-last/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T09:22:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nate Cohn: “As the name implies, bounces don’t usually last. But sometimes, bounces permanently reshape the race — they become bumps, if you prefer. The 1992 presidential election, for instance, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justices Sow Confusion Over Handling of Election Disputes]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/justices-sow-confusion-over-handling-of-election-disputes/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/justices-sow-confusion-over-handling-of-election-disputes/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T09:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The recent US Supreme Court decision changing voter registration rules in Arizona has voting rights advocates anxious about how the justices will approach emergency election appeals in the runup to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Forecast Gives Harris the Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/new-forecast-gives-harris-the-edge/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/new-forecast-gives-harris-the-edge/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T09:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The replacement of Vice President Harris for President Biden at the top of the ticket has tilted the races for the White House and Congress in the direction of Democrats, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats Sue Over Georgia Election Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/democrats-sue-over-georgia-election-rules/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/democrats-sue-over-georgia-election-rules/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The state and national Democratic parties sued Monday to block two recent rules adopted by Georgia’s State Election Board that could be used by county officials who want to refuse […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jake Sullivan Visits Beijing]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698335</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/jake-sullivan-visits-beijing/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T09:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“A top White House official arrived in China on Tuesday for talks on a relationship that has been severely tested during President Joe Biden’s term in office,” the AP reports. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Army Private Who Fled to North Korea Will Plead Guilty]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/army-private-who-fled-to-north-korea-will-plead-guilty/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/27/army-private-who-fled-to-north-korea-will-plead-guilty/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“U.S. Army Private Travis King, who last year ran into North Korea and was taken into custody there, will plead guilty to five charges, including desertion, while taking responsibility for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We work to create information that we will never own]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205237</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205237/We-work-to-create-information-that-we-will-never-own"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T08:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This hellscape is no place for free information to thrive. The digital hoarder must take stock, and set out in search of somewhere independent from such distractions. A simple spreadsheet, maybe, a private are.na channel, a USB drive, or even a Minecraft map. What matters here is not the hoard's form, but its capacity to be consumed outside the limits of the commodity. Free from the profit-churning debris of their social media feeds, visitors to this hoard might gain a better idea of how they, too, can use the information they find in service of principled, radical action. from Life in Fifteen Gigabytes by Bami Oke [e-flux]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chavenet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Self-driving cars have got a kangaroo problem]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205236</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205236/Self-driving-cars-have-got-a-kangaroo-problem"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T07:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Self-driving cars have got a kangaroo problem. Self-driving cars are a game changer for disabled Australians, but they've got a kangaroo problem. Darren waits hours and hours and hours for taxis in Queensland, and hopes self-driving cars might be the answer. But an unpredictable marsupial is standing in the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chariot pulled by cassowaries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flow State Episode 242]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-episode-242</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-episode-242"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T07:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good morning – we’ll be off Monday and Tuesday next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Impeachment Backlash Builds Within GOP]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/biden-impeachment-backlash-builds-within-gop/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/biden-impeachment-backlash-builds-within-gop/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T02:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“House Republicans are furious about being forced into a last-minute Biden impeachment vote — which they say could hurt their campaigns,” Axios reports. “Even leadership doesn’t want it. But just […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Bush, Romney and McCain Aides Back Harris]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/ex-bush-romney-and-mccain-aides-back-harris/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/ex-bush-romney-and-mccain-aides-back-harris/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T02:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 200 people who previously worked for President George W. Bush and Senators Mitt Romney and John McCain have signed a letter endorsing Vice President Kamala Harris, the New […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Asked to Join Trump’s Transition Team]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/rfk-jr-asked-to-join-trumps-transition-team/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/rfk-jr-asked-to-join-trumps-transition-team/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T02:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. said in an interview that ran tonight that he had been asked to join the Trump campaign’s presidential transition team to “help pick the people who […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sweep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153674</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153674"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T01:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals took game two of their doubleheader from the Guardians 9-4 to close Cleveland’s lead to one game. While young legend Bobby Witt Jr. proved the hero of game one, veteran legend Salvador Perez hit two home runs, including a grand slam, and drove in six runs in game two. The Royals have plenty […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quentin Tarantino Loves Jerry Seinfeld’s ‘Bee Movie’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43366_quentin-tarantino-loves-jerry-seinfelds-bee-movie.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43366_quentin-tarantino-loves-jerry-seinfelds-bee-movie.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  JM McNab   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Pauses Biden Program for Undocumented Spouses]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/judge-pauses-biden-program-for-undocumented-spouses/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/judge-pauses-biden-program-for-undocumented-spouses/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T01:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“A federal judge in Texas temporarily blocked on Monday a Biden administration program that could offer a path to citizenship for up to half a million undocumented immigrants who are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly Look at Offense]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153672</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153672"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T01:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every Monday Baseball Musings compares offense in the current season to offense in the previous season through the same number of weeks. For the second week in a row, 2024 lost ground to 2023. The current season produced 8.83 runs per game compared to 9.21 runs per game last year. The big reason is fewer […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Sandler’s Top Five Fashion Pieces Are Hilariously On-Brand]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43365_adam-sandlers-top-five-fashion-pieces-are-hilariously-on-brand.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43365_adam-sandlers-top-five-fashion-pieces-are-hilariously-on-brand.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Keegan Kelly   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Woof. Nate. Not cool man."]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205235</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205235/Woof-Nate-Not-cool-man"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T00:29:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a thread on BlueSky, political science professor Dave Karpf dissects Nate Silver's new doorstop of a book on gambling and risk, and finds several interesting - and disturbing - things within.
Probably the biggest (and where the thread title comes from) is the revelation that Silver was betting 7 figures on the NBA at the same time that 538 under his leadership was undergoing mass layoffs. Karpf also notes that the venture capital chapter focuses around Palantir founder (and his new boss) Peter Thiel, as well as Silver's lack of consideration of systemic risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NoxAeternum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Too Tall for Short]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153670</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153670"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T00:13:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pirates decided to move Oneil Cruz from shortstop to centerfield: Cruz is likely to be the designated hitter for the three-game series against the Chicago Cubs that starts Monday night. He will go through pregame workouts during the early part of the week before likely making his center-field debut sometime during a three-game weekend series at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen A. Smith ‘disappointed’ in how Deion Sanders, Colorado handled ‘utterly ridiculous’ columnist ban]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632903</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/stephen-a-smith-deion-sanders-colorado-columnist-ban.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T00:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deion Sanders has already stepped into the headlines before his team has even stepped onto the field for the 2024 season. In advance of the Buffaloes’ Week 1 matchup against North Dakota State, Colorado made waves by banning the Denver Post‘s Sean Keeler from asking Coach Prime questions, citing “a series of sustained, personal attacks.” Read more...
The post Stephen A. Smith ‘disappointed’ in how Deion Sanders, Colorado handled ‘utterly ridiculous’ columnist ban appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With Landlords Like These, Who Needs The DOJ? — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074357</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/with-landlords-like-these-who-needs-the-doj-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T23:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Like They Wanted To Get Caught: Landlord shares gleaming product review on how AI helps them price fix together.
Biglaw Firm Invites First Years To Start Early: Gotta love a jump start!
*Checks Cue Card* ...Scalia Is Woke Now?!: Maybe this will help you realize how bat shit Bruen is.
Grandma Isn't Safe From Paxton: Texas AG send raids to homes of voter outreach activists.
Now That Is A Good Open!: Former Weil attorney brings back the art of stylish departure.
The post With Landlords Like These, Who Needs The DOJ? — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dan Orlovsky: Steelers ‘bamboozled’ media with QB competition farce]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632870</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/dan-orlovsky-steelers-quarterback-competition.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T23:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saying the word “bamboozled” on an ESPN show means something. It meant something when Stephen A. Smith went on SportsCenter and claimed that Phil Jackson and the Knicks had “hoodwinked, bamboozled, led astray, run amok and flat out deceived” New York Knicks fans after Kristaps Porziņģis was selected with the No. 4 pick in the Read more...
The post Dan Orlovsky: Steelers ‘bamboozled’ media with QB competition farce appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peyton Manning to moderate Larry David live event]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632830</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/pop-culture/peyton-manning-larry-david-live-event.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T22:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peyton Manning is creeping into the Shaquille O’Neal territory of “What won’t he do?” But when it comes to having a sit-down conversation with Larry David in front of a live audience, that seems like a thing that’s hard to say no to. Since retiring from the NFL, Manning has continued to showcase his comedic Read more...
The post Peyton Manning to moderate Larry David live event appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ted Danson May Have Broken a TV Record With His Latest Sitcom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43361_ted-danson-may-have-broken-a-tv-record-with-his-latest-sitcom.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43361_ted-danson-may-have-broken-a-tv-record-with-his-latest-sitcom.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  JM McNab   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Heard on TV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153668</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153668"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T22:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have heard broadcast play by play announcers discussing on-base streaks. As you might imagine, it is much easier to earn your way on base than just by a hit. This list is a bit out of date, but the top remains the same. Twice hitters exceeded 70 games in a season. Joe DiMaggio set […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Profits Per Equity Partner Are Skyrocketing For Top 50 Biglaw Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074356</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/profits-per-equity-partner-are-skyrocketing-for-top-50-biglaw-firms/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T22:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The money is rolling in.
The post Profits Per Equity Partner Are Skyrocketing For Top 50 Biglaw Firms appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sterling Sharpe praises little brother Shannon Sharpe for handling Skip Bayless fallout: ‘He was so hurt’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632759</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/sterling-sharpe-praises-brother-shannon-sharpe-skip-bayless-undisputed.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T22:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shannon Sharpe is taking his hit new show Nightcap on the road this summer, and in Atlanta over the weekend, he welcomed big brother and fellow NFL All-Pro Sterling Sharpe to the stage for a wide-ranging conversation that only siblings could have. In their first recorded conversation since the early days of Shannon Sharpe’s interview show Club Read more...
The post Sterling Sharpe praises little brother Shannon Sharpe for handling Skip Bayless fallout: ‘He was so hurt’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Season of ‘The Simpsons’ Has the Best Animation, According to Superfans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43360_this-season-of-the-simpsons-has-the-best-animation-according-to-superfans.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43360_this-season-of-the-simpsons-has-the-best-animation-according-to-superfans.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Keegan Kelly   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Stuff of Legends]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153666</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153666"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T21:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals took game one of the their doubleheader against the Guardians 4-3. Kansas City’s MVP candidate, Bobby Witt Jr. loomed large in the decision. The Guardians tied the game at three in the bottom of the seventh inning. Bobby Witt Jr. homered leading off the eighth inning to break a tie as the Kansas […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Belichick lands yet another NFL media gig with ‘Let’s Go!’ podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632777</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/bill-belichick-another-media-gig-lets-go-podcast.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T21:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Belichick won’t be on an NFL sideline this fall for the first time since 1975, but he’s staying incredibly busy. In addition to recurring roles on multiple ESPN properties and a weekly co-hosting role on a popular NFL recap show, SiriusXM on Monday announced that Belichick would join the Let’s Go! Podcast, hosted by longtime Read more...
The post Bill Belichick lands yet another NFL media gig with ‘Let’s Go!’ podcast appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conquering Fear In Your First Year Of Law School]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074352</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2015/08/conquering-fear-in-your-first-year-of-law-school/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T21:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law school is a good place to overcome your fears, but how can you do that? Allow this law professor to help you out.
The post Conquering Fear In Your First Year Of Law School appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LawProfBlawg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dustin Fox addresses past personal struggles while announcing departure from 92.3 the Fan]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632873</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/radio/dustin-fox-announces-departure-923-the-fan.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T21:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A staple of Cleveland’s sports radio scene is leaving the sports talk station he helped build, with Dustin Fox announcing on Monday that Thursday will mark his final episode as a co-host on 92.3 The Fan’s Afternoon Drive on The Fan. “This is something that is kind of a long time coming. This is going Read more...
The post Dustin Fox addresses past personal struggles while announcing departure from 92.3 the Fan appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Defending Champs Aren’t Defending]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=165123</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-defending-champs-arent-defending"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T21:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kelsey Plum spent much of this past Wednesday's Lynx-Aces game complaining to and about the refs. She brought up uneven officiating in a halftime sideline interview: The Lynx “move on all their screens.” But by the time the postgame press conference started, the Vegas guard had somewhat changed her tune. “She cooked me,” Plum said, trying to explain Minnesota guard Courtney Williams's 22-point performance that night. “She had it tonight, and when you get your ass kicked, you gotta give the other people credit.”
That's one reason not to read too much into that game, and why I felt uncomfortable using it to construct some broader point about the Las Vegas Aces' defense, which dominated last season but has so far disappointed in 2024. Sometimes other team will just shoot well. The Lynx finished 11-for-19 from behind the arc in their 98-87 win on Wednesday. Williams indeed cooked Plum, but as head coach Becky Hammon pointed out afterward, Williams almost exclusively takes the “long, off-the-dribble twos” teams can live with giving up. Minnesota punished every botched defensive rotation—the same thing they've done to 10 other teams. That probably says more about the Lynx than it does about the Aces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Right Wing Bonus Tracks: The Demons Inside]]></title>
        <id>https://www.rightwingwatch.org/?p=546805</id>
        <link href="https://www.rightwingwatch.org/post/right-wing-bonus-tracks-the-demons-inside/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T21:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right-wing pastor Paul Blair claims that he really hates liars: “When somebody can just look you in the eyes …. and lie intentionally trying to deceive, to me, that’s just about as disgusting and evil as you get.” Blair, of course, is a big fan of pathological liar Donald Trump. QAnon conspiracy theorist/self-proclaimed “prophet” Johnny […]
The post Right Wing Bonus Tracks: The Demons Inside appeared first on Right Wing Watch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Mantyla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Fans Of World’s Most Popular Musician Just Like The Rest Of Us]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074348</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/08/report-fans-of-worlds-most-popular-musician-just-like-the-rest-of-us"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T21:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who knew that hundreds of millions of people would make a pretty good sample size?
The post Report: Fans Of World’s Most Popular Musician Just Like The Rest Of Us appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Griffin III opens up after ESPN firing: ‘There is no act here.’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632812</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/robert-griffin-iii-opens-up-after-espn-firing-there-is-no-act-here.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T21:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Griffin III may have exited ESPN unceremoniously, but that hasn’t caused the retired quarterback to sour on his now-former employer. Earlier this month, ESPN surprised everyone by firing Griffin and Sam Ponder three weeks before the start of the NFL season. On Monday afternoon, Griffin joined The Jim Rome Show and was asked about his ESPN departure. Monday: 1:00p Read more...
The post Robert Griffin III opens up after ESPN firing: ‘There is no act here.’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The long, destructive path of fire: Talking to Source NM’s Patrick Lohmann about a never-ending wildfire season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cjr.org/?p=102430</id>
        <link href="https://www.cjr.org/podcast/lohmann-wildfire-hermits-peak-calf-canyon-new-mexico-propublica.php"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T20:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In early 2023, Patrick Lohmann, a reporter for the nonprofit Source NM, moved to the small town of Las Vegas, New Mexico, to learn how residents were coping with the aftermath of the largest wildfire in state history. What he learned there was that the destruction brought on by wildfires doesn’t end when the fire […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hersh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lindsey Graham Grovels After Trump Criticism]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698205</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/lindsey-graham-grovels-after-trump-criticism/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T20:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-SC) vowed to stand by former President Donald Trump despite Trump saying he “doesn’t care” what Graham thinks, CNN reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the Last Weeks of RFK Jr.’s Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698200</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/inside-the-last-weeks-of-rfk-jr-s-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T20:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time: “As his poll numbers sagged— in a recent CBS News poll, Kennedy drew 2%—and his campaign ran out of cash, Kennedy blamed his lack of momentum on a multi-front […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Farewell Memo Is A Classic Of The Genre]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074320</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/biglaw-farewell-memo-is-a-classic-of-the-genre/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T20:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good ol' departure memo fun!
The post Biglaw Farewell Memo Is A Classic Of The Genre appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oasis superfan Kevin Brown had best reaction to band’s reported reunion]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632791</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/pop-culture/oasis-kevin-brown-reported-reunion-reaction.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T20:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s happening. Noel and Liam Gallagher are seemingly getting the band back together. After rumors surfaced across social media—yet again—that there would be an Oasis reunion come 2025, the band, which has been broken up since 2009, lent some credence to those rumors. From The Reading Festival on Sunday, Liam dedicated “Half the World Away,” Read more...
The post Oasis superfan Kevin Brown had best reaction to band’s reported reunion appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trey Parker and Matt Stone’s Surprise NYU Class Contains Some Great Writing Advice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43358_trey-parker-and-matt-stones-surprise-nyu-class-contains-some-great-writing-advice.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43358_trey-parker-and-matt-stones-surprise-nyu-class-contains-some-great-writing-advice.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  JM McNab   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[50 Megadonors Pump $1.5 Billion Into Presidential Race]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698201</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/50-megadonors-pump-1-5-billion-into-presidential-race/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T20:28:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The 50 biggest donors this cycle have collectively pumped $1.5 billion into political committees and other groups competing in the election,” according to the Washington Post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Numbers Nerd Says RFK Jr.'s Brainworm Probably Won't Save Trump’s Loser Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/numbers-nerd-says-rfk-jrs-brainworm</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/numbers-nerd-says-rfk-jrs-brainworm"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T20:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Hurst</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Record-Breaking 17 California Condor Chicks Hatched at the L.A. Zoo]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205234</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205234/Record-Breaking-17-California-Condor-Chicks-Hatched-at-the-LA-Zoo"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T20:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Record-Breaking 17 California Condor Chicks Hatched at the LA Zoo This Year. The successful breeding season offers more hope for the endangered species, which has come back from the brink of extinction due to captive breeding efforts.
"This is a historic moment for the California Condor Recovery Program and the Los Angeles Zoo's animal care team," Rose Legato, curator of birds at the LA Zoo, says in the statement. "Our condor team has raised the bar once again in the collaborative effort to save America's largest flying bird from extinction. What we are seeing now are the benefits of new breeding and rearing techniques developed and implemented by our team."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chariot pulled by cassowaries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I Left The Network]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205233</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205233/Why-I-Left-The-Network"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T20:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finding a therapist who takes your insurance can be nearly impossible. NPR reports on a ProPublica investigation into why therapists, psychologists, and psychiatrists are leaving insurance networks and only accepting cash for treatment.
You may not be surprised to learn that the primary cause is that insurance companies are actively trying to avoid paying for mental health treatment. As insurance networks add more ghost therapists and refuse to raise reimbursement rates, many independent mental health providers have stopped taking insurance entirely. I definitely noticed this in my recent search for a mental health provider, none of the psychiatrists I looked into would accept insurance for initial payment (but some were in network and would help file for reimbursement).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JZig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Craig Carton’s new FS1 show debuts with Mark Schlereth in the driver’s seat]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632750</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/craig-carton-fs1-mark-schlereth.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T20:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Craig Carton is prominently featured on the show, which used to bear his name, but this definitely isn’t The Carton Show anymore. FS1 debuted Breakfast Ball Monday afternoon at noon, although the show will air regularly from 8-10 a.m. ET once the network formally launches its new post-Skip Bayless lineup next week. It marks the Read more...
The post Craig Carton’s new FS1 show debuts with Mark Schlereth in the driver’s seat appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Short Already Has A Replacement Lined Up If He Ever Needs A New Steve Martin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43357_martin-short-already-has-a-replacement-lined-up-if-he-ever-needs-a-new-steve-martin.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43357_martin-short-already-has-a-replacement-lined-up-if-he-ever-needs-a-new-steve-martin.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Keegan Kelly   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TX AG Ken Paxton Is Beating Down Doors Of Little Old Abuelas For ‘Election Integrity’]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074327</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/tx-ag-ken-paxton-is-beating-down-doors-of-little-old-abuelas-for-election-integrity/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:58:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who's gonna stop him?
The post TX AG Ken Paxton Is Beating Down Doors Of Little Old Abuelas For ‘Election Integrity’ appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just a generic "Ohio" polo provided to me by my business partners]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205232</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205232/Just-a-generic-Ohio-polo-provided-to-me-by-my-business-partners"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operation Desperado: The long con of Vivek Ramaswamy A local muckraker who covers the Ohio state legislature plays a long con on the former presidential candidate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>slogger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Special Counsel Seeks to Revive Classified Docs Case]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698182</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/special-counsel-seeks-to-revive-classified-docs-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:50:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“U.S. prosecutors are seeking to reinstate the criminal case charging Donald Trump with mishandling classified documents and obstruction, arguing a Florida judge was wrong to toss out the indictment this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tulsi Gabbard Endorses Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698181</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/tulsi-gabbard-endorses-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Rep. Tulsi Gabbard (D-HI) formally endorsed Donald Trump in Detroit, the New York Times reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stupid And Contagious]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=165423</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/stupid-and-contagious"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter, examining the apocalyptic politics and coverage of Campaign 2024.
The Robert F. Kennedy Jr. presidential campaign, in its final incarnation, pretty clearly seemed to be illegal and unconstitutional. It feels petty and niggling to talk about details like that, next to the delusions of grandeur that got Kennedy so much attention and publicity. Here was an avatar of how antivax conspiracies and other antisocial quackery operate as a political force. Here was billionaire money in a state of such unhinged entitlement that it could prop up a naked spoiler campaign and profess to be performing a public service. Here was, God willing, the last cooling and crumbling briquette of the Kennedy family's long-burning equity as an electoral brand name.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jill Stein to Remain on Wisconsin Ballot]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698177</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/jill-stein-to-remain-on-wisconsin-ballot/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Green Party presidential candidate Jill Stein will remain on the ballot in the crucial swing state of Wisconsin after the state Supreme Court decided on Monday not to hear a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Shifts Abortion Messaging Yet Again]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698174</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/trump-shifts-abortion-messaging-yet-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:37:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Donald Trump has said abortion is an issue best left to the states, complained about Republican messaging and avoided mentioning it in a speech accepting his party’s nomination,” Bloomberg reports. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Judge Rejects Lily-Livered Wokeness Of Antonin Scalia]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074338</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/trump-judge-rejects-lily-livered-wokeness-of-antonin-scalia/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas judge rules that Second Amendment covers unfettered access to machine guns... something Scalia was very clear it did not.
The post Trump Judge Rejects Lily-Livered Wokeness Of Antonin Scalia appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-Vaxxers Being Super Weird About Tetanus Shots Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/anti-vaxxers-being-super-weird-about</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/anti-vaxxers-being-super-weird-about"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new 'that happened' genre has emerged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robyn Pennacchia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Your ideas are intriguing to me, and I wish to subscribe to your Newsletter"]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205231</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205231/Your-ideas-are-intriguing-to-me-and-I-wish-to-subscribe-to-your-newsle"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['The Simpsons': 34 Times the Fox Comedy Successfully Predicted the Future or,  50 Predictions From 'The Simpsons' That Came True or, The Simpsons 17 Predictions for 2024 Is Insane!. However, don't forget The Simpsons conspiracy theories that AREN'T TRUE including False 'Simpsons' prediction resurfaces after Trump shooting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chavenet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Leaf accuses Pat McAfee of being ‘high 80% of the time’ on his show]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632734</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/ryan-leaf-accuses-pat-mcafee-being-high-80-his-show.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pat McAfee generated quite the buzz by getting buzzed during Friday’s episode of The Pat McAfee Show. More accurately, the former All-Pro-punter-turned-ESPN personality was seemingly hammered. Jesus Christ Pat McAfee was a disaster today 😂😂 Dude puked during his show and introduced himself to the guy he had been interviewing for 10+ minutes 😭 pic.twitter.com/tXS8oRDQjx Read more...
The post Ryan Leaf accuses Pat McAfee of being ‘high 80% of the time’ on his show appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Choose The Right Legal Research Platform For Your AI Journey [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074251</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/how-to-choose-the-right-legal-research-platform-for-your-ai-journey/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future of legal research is AI.  Read on to get the definitive guide to choosing a Gen AI legal research solution
The post How To Choose The Right Legal Research Platform For Your AI Journey appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LexisNexis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California high school announcer caught on hot mic calling player ‘a dumba**’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632755</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/high-school/mater-dei-pa-announcer-hot-mic.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T19:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to high school announcers — or any announcers for that matter — you should always be under the assumption that the mic is hot. It would perhaps lead to a lot less Awful Announcing content, but it would also save some people their livelihoods. Earlier this year, an Oklahoma high school announcer Read more...
The post California high school announcer caught on hot mic calling player ‘a dumba**’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Next for the Cincinnati Reds?]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=444768</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/whats-next-for-the-cincinnati-reds/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Their plan to paper over holes this season by moving third basemen around has not been successful. Here’s how they can turn things around in 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Szymborski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Undercuts His Campaign on Debate Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/trump-undercuts-his-campaign-on-debate-rules/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/trump-undercuts-his-campaign-on-debate-rules/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Donald Trump appeared to undercut his campaign’s efforts to keep the same rules in place for his debate against Vice President Kamala Harris next month,” CNN reports. “Trump’s team would […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fanatics Refiles, Adds New Marvin Harrison To Marvin Harrison Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=165378</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/fanatics-refiles-adds-new-marvin-harrison-to-marvin-harrison-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This past Friday, Fanatics refiled its May lawsuit against Arizona Cardinals rookie Marvin Harrison Jr., adding two new counts and naming his father as a new defendant. As Fanatics wrote in the amended complaint, the involvement of multiple Marvins Harrison helped facilitate and further their alleged defrauding of one of the most loathed companies in sports.
At issue in the initial suit was a contract dispute between Harrison Jr. and Fanatics over a name, image, and likeness (NIL) term sheet the two parties agreed to in 2023, before Harrison Jr. got to the NFL. Fanatics claims that this document is legally binding—in the suit, the company repeatedly refers to it in headline case as a Binding Term Sheet, though traditionally what differentiates a term sheet from a contract is that the former is not legally binding—and that Harrison Jr. has not fulfilled his obligations under it. Harrisons Jr. and Sr. posit, in return, that as they only signed a term sheet and not a contract, they do not in fact have a binding deal with Fanatics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Clemency Recipient Could Be Sent Back to Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/trump-clemency-recipient-could-be-sent-back-to-prison/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/trump-clemency-recipient-could-be-sent-back-to-prison/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“A New York federal judge ordered U.S. probation officials to investigate the recent arrest of a convicted drug dealer who was released from prison in early 2021 after his 10-year […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris Stands by Decision to Leave Afghanistan]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/harris-stands-by-decision-to-leave-afghanistan/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/harris-stands-by-decision-to-leave-afghanistan/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Vice President Kamala Harris said that she stands behind President Joe Biden’s decision to leave Afghanistan, as the Democratic nominee came under attack from Donald Trump on the third anniversary […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Of University Of Alabama Now A Safe Space For White Kids. Again.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/all-of-university-of-alabama-now</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/all-of-university-of-alabama-now"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:15:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's always the 1950s somewhere, apparently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Legum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Rapert Says Members of the Arkansas State Library Board ‘Probably Should Be Tarred and Feathered’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.rightwingwatch.org/?p=546796</id>
        <link href="https://www.rightwingwatch.org/post/jason-rapert-says-members-of-the-arkansas-state-library-board-probably-should-be-tarred-and-feathered/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2023, Arkansas Gov. Sarah Huckabee Sanders appointed Christian nationalist activist and a zealously anti-LGBTQ and anti-choice former state senator Jason Rapert to the state library board. Predictably, his tenure on the board has been anything but smooth, with Rapert regularly lashing out at his fellow board members for refusing to support his far-right agenda […]
The post Jason Rapert Says Members of the Arkansas State Library Board ‘Probably Should Be Tarred and Feathered’ appeared first on Right Wing Watch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Mantyla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats Have Finally Found Trump’s Achilles’ Heel]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/democrats-have-finally-found-trumps-achilles-heel/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/democrats-have-finally-found-trumps-achilles-heel/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Tomasky: “Harris’s campaign so far has been a work of genius on several levels, but maybe the most ingenious stroke of all has been the decision to mock Trump—to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Firm So Busy It Will Let First Years Start Early]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074319</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/biglaw-firm-so-busy-it-will-let-summer-associates-start-early/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No pressure!
The post Biglaw Firm So Busy It Will Let First Years Start Early appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Ted Lasso’ revival will likely be without Jamie Tartt]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632720</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/pop-culture/ted-lasso-jamie-tartt-phil-dunster.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s a show without one of its most integral characters? Well, we’re about to find out once another season of Ted Lasso is officially greenlit. No, we aren’t talking about Jason Sudeikis but Phil Dunster, who plays Jamie Tartt. According to Deadline, Dunster’s option has not been picked up for the next season, presumably due Read more...
The post ‘Ted Lasso’ revival will likely be without Jamie Tartt appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Why Pixar Refuses to Remake Its Classics As Live-Action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43354_heres-why-pixar-refuses-to-remake-its-classics-as-live-action.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43354_heres-why-pixar-refuses-to-remake-its-classics-as-live-action.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Matt Solomon   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Danielson Makes Every Last Match Count]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=165338</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bryan-danielson-makes-every-last-match-count"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T17:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No pro wrestler thrives more off making you believe that he's about to be maimed than Bryan Danielson. Selling the damage of a match is a non-negotiable part of the job for anyone in the business, but for Danielson, acting out his character's pain feels almost like an act of sadism. He's 43 years old, near the end of a full-time run that began 25 years ago, and still carrying the weight of a multi-year hiatus due to a little thing called "career-ending" concussion problems. Particularly after making the move from the PG WWE to PG-13 AEW in 2021, his matches became bloodier, grittier, and more of a high-wire act for his visibly deteriorating body.
While Danielson's time with the company has cemented his legacy, his road with AEW has also been continually blocked by legitimate injuries, like the broken arm he suffered during a PPV main event last summer (he finished the match) or the broken orbital bone he picked up in the fall shortly after returning. Mixed in with those real-life scares, however, have been creative choices that prey on the emotions they've stirred—mid-match doctor checks, mimed fencing responses, and this drama, following a PPV match in April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Clemens FanGraphs Chat – 8/26/24]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=445044</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/ben-clemens-fangraphs-chat-8-26-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T17:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's talk baseball.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Clemens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why This Is Not An ‘English Teacher’ Review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43350_why-this-is-not-an-english-teacher-review.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43350_why-this-is-not-an-english-teacher-review.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Tara Ariano   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN announces reorganization, including Mike McQuade as EVP of sports production]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632713</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/reorganization-mike-mcquade-promotion.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T17:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the pivotal 2024 football season approaches, major changes are coming to ESPN. And not just on the air. In a memo sent to staffers on Monday from president of content Burke Magnus, the Worldwide Leader announced a major reorganization of its behind-the-scenes staff. The highlight of the reorg comes in the form of Mike Read more...
The post ESPN announces reorganization, including Mike McQuade as EVP of sports production appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas AG Ken Paxton Will Raid Democrats' Houses Until The Voting Stops]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/texas-ag-ken-paxton-will-raid-democrats</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/texas-ag-ken-paxton-will-raid-democrats"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T17:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you can’t beat ‘em, raid em!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcie Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Is Getting More Out Of Its Lawyers]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074325</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/biglaw-is-getting-more-out-of-its-lawyers/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T17:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyer productivity keeps improving.
The post Biglaw Is Getting More Out Of Its Lawyers appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2024: Green Bay Packers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=165211</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2024-green-bay-packers"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:56:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the Green Bay Packers. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the Green Bay Packers. This 2024 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: Show the pick.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cornel West Courts Anti-Vax Voters]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698131</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/cornel-west-courts-anti-vax-voters-after-rfk-jr-drops-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Cornel West seems to see an opening in the field after Robert F. Kennedy Jr. dropped his bid for the office this past week,” the Daily Beast reports. “In what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JD Vance Reminds 'Meet The Press' Who's The REAL Weird Trump Running Mate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/jd-vance-reminds-meet-the-press-whos</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/jd-vance-reminds-meet-the-press-whos"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:32:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a loveseat, not a couch, RFK, Jr.!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NBA: Warner Bros. Discovery tried to alter Amazon’s ‘poison pill’ in rights deal]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632687</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/warner-bros-discovery/wbd-eliminate-amazon-poison-pill-nba-rights-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the NBA’s media rights deal came into focus earlier this summer, it became increasingly clear that Warner Bros. Discovery would be left on the outside looking in. And one of the biggest red flags came in the form of the “poison pill” that Amazon put in its own agreement with the league. Bill Simmons Read more...
The post NBA: Warner Bros. Discovery tried to alter Amazon’s ‘poison pill’ in rights deal appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Band Set the Guinness World Record for Loudest Concert Three Separate Times]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43334_this-band-set-the-guinness-world-record-for-loudest-concert-three-separate-times.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43334_this-band-set-the-guinness-world-record-for-loudest-concert-three-separate-times.html?newsletter-cat=music"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Eli Yudin   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boeing Starliner Astronauts Electively Spending Five More Months In Space To Hitch Ride In Different Vehicle Due To Preference For Not Dying]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=165339</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/boeing-starliner-astronauts-electively-spending-five-more-months-in-space-to-hitch-ride-in-different-vehicle-due-to-preference-for-not-dying"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suni Williams and Barry Wilmore, the NASA astronauts whose eight-day June jaunt to space is now on Day 82 due to problems with their Boeing Starliner spacecraft—and, ugh, their own fussy entitled preference for not being incinerated—will attempt a return to Earth in 2025 aboard a SpaceX capsule. I hope to hell somebody has been feeding their cats.
Here is a funny bit from the New York Times story about the change of plans:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colorado Republicans Oust Their Leader]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698123</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/colorado-republicans-oust-their-leader/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colorado Republicans voted to oust state party chairman Dave Williams from his leadership position, Colorado Public Radio reports. “Williams dismissed the meeting as ‘illegal’, possibly setting up a legal showdown […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Says Trump Will Announce Democratic Defections]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698121</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/rfk-jr-says-trump-will-announce-democratic-defections/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:21:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. claimed that Donald Trump will make a “series of announcements about other Democrats who are joining his 2024 campaign,” Newsweek reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giuliani Claims Steve Bannon Is Being ‘Tortured’ In Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698120</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/giuliani-claims-steve-bannon-is-being-tortured-in-prison/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:18:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rudy Giuliani said that Steve Bannon is being “tortured” by not having access to television in prison, the HuffPost reports. Said Giuliani: “Steve Bannon is not being treated the way […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Origin of Adderal shortages]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205230</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205230/The-Origin-of-Adderal-shortages"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Is Why You Can't Get ADHD Treatment Musician / Investigative Documentarian Benn Jordan breaks down the core reasons for the USA's ADHD medication shortage, the hassle of trying to solve it yourself, why it's so profitable for so many drug companies, the scams that have popped up in response, and the dangers of seeking treatment via the dark web.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philipschall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jackson Merrill Has Already Achieved Dude Status]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=165348</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jackson-merrill-has-already-achieved-dude-status"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Skenes of the Pittsburgh Pirates may win the National League Rookie of the Year. In one of the most fucked-up baseball developments I can remember, Skenes has only allowed more than three runs in a start once all season, and has not failed to pitch at least five complete innings since his first appearance with the Pirates, way back on May 11. He has more starts where he has allowed zero runs (four) than starts where he has allowed more than two runs (three). He doesn't qualify for any of the Baseball Reference leaderboards, but his 11.3 strikeouts per nine innings would rank second in the National League behind only Chris Sale of the Braves, and his .942 WHIP would be good for second in the majors, behind only Seattle's Logan Gilbert. He's just over a year from his first-ever professional appearance, and he's already one of the handful of best pitchers in baseball.
Given all of that, it's possibly freakier to suggest that Skenes might not win Rookie of the Year. He might not! Jackson Merrill, the extremely cool rookie center fielder for the Padres, is mounting a charge. He's more than held his own as a 21-year-old natural shortstop playing the most important outfield position, and his consistent and solid offensive production has been clutch for an otherwise top-heavy Padres lineup thinned out by key injuries. Baseball Reference says there are 23 fellows in the majors who've played at least 80 games in center field this season, and among that group Merrill ranks fourth in OPS+, and is tops in the National League. The only center fielder in baseball who has driven in more runs this season than Merrill is Aaron damn Judge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen A. Smith rebukes landing on ‘most annoying’ media list: ‘Your list is trash’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=632692</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/stephen-a-smith-rebukes-most-annoying-media-list.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Skip Bayless might not mind being the ‘most hated man in sports media,’ but Stephen A. Smith definitely doesn’t want to be known as the most annoying. Last week, The Spun dropped a bracket featuring the 64 “most annoying” figures in sports media. It’s an apparent attempt at determining the “most annoying” sports media personality Read more...
The post Stephen A. Smith rebukes landing on ‘most annoying’ media list: ‘Your list is trash’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FanGraphs Power Rankings: August 19–25]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=444996</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/fangraphs-power-rankings-august-19-25/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NL West leads the way in the FanGraphs Power Rankings this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Mailhot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Only Murders in the Building’s Stuntcast Celebrities Are the New Season’s Least Shocking Element]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43349_only-murders-in-the-buildings-stuntcast-celebrities-are-the-new-seasons-least-shocking-element.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43349_only-murders-in-the-buildings-stuntcast-celebrities-are-the-new-seasons-least-shocking-element.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Tara Ariano   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A Box of Surprises']]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205229</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205229/A-Box-of-Surprises"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T15:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a Rotterdam Apartment That's Only 74 Square Feet. Two architects in the Netherlands made the most of the tiniest of spaces, "maximizing absolutely everything." Julie Lasky for the NYT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Marks Anniversary of Afghanistan Withdrawal]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698112</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/trump-marks-anniversary-of-afghanistan-withdrawal/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T15:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump visited Arlington National Cemetery on Monday to mark the three-year anniversary of the U.S. withdrawal from Afghanistan as he sought to turn the chaotic pullout into a resonant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Nudge]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1694342</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/a-nudge-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T15:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have been meaning to become a Political Wire member but haven’t gotten around to joining. I totally get it… life gets busy. So consider this a nudge: The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cult of Wellness]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205228</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205228/The-Cult-of-Wellness"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T15:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We live in a time when intensity serves as a stand-in for virtue and the hardness of conviction is valued over the fuzziness of nuance. (slTOLife)
If you are a MeFite in a major city, I am sure you are aware of these wellness places! These just happen to be in Toronto...and NYC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kitteh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wayne Brady Got Revenge on ‘Chappelle’s Show’ With the Help of Dave Chappelle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43353_wayne-brady-got-revenge-on-chappelles-show-with-the-help-of-dave-chappelle.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43353_wayne-brady-got-revenge-on-chappelles-show-with-the-help-of-dave-chappelle.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Matt Solomon   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poor Steve Bannon Being 'Tortured' In Prison, Can't Even Watch His 'Special Shows' On TV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/poor-steve-bannon-being-tortured</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/poor-steve-bannon-being-tortured"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T15:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Rudy Giuliani, that is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robyn Pennacchia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foo Fighters Object to Donald Trump’s Use of Song]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698109</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/foo-fighters-object-to-trump-using-song/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T15:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s campaign is disputing the Foo Fighters’ claim that the use of their song “My Hero” during a campaign rally was unauthorized, The Hill reports. However, a spokesperson for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poor J.D. Vance]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698094</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/poor-j-d-vance/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T15:23:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump shared a post describing Trump and Robert F. Kennedy Jr as a “ticket.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Fake Movies on ‘Seinfeld,’ Ranked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43317_7-fake-movies-on-seinfeld-ranked.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43317_7-fake-movies-on-seinfeld-ranked.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Matt Solomon   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Aug. 26: Cut To The Chase (Themeless)]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=165342</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-aug-26-cut-to-the-chase-themeless"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As always, we're ending the month with a challenging themeless—keep an eye out for tricky clues and fun wordplay. This week's puzzle was constructed by Trent Evans and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Trent has been constructing crossword puzzles since 2018. His work has appeared in the New York Times, Los Angeles Times, Wall Street Journal, and other major publications and independent puzzle venues. He publishes free puzzles at gridtherapy.com. He is a clinical psychologist in private practice in Catonsville, Md., where he lives with his wife Beth and their dog Donut. A rotating cast of five young adult children breeze in and out at their leisure, much to Trent and Beth’s delight. 
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The One Where RFK Jr. Decapitates A Dead Whale With A Chainsaw And The Whale Juice Gets All Over His Kids]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/the-one-where-rfk-jr-decapitates</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/the-one-where-rfk-jr-decapitates"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['I thought I could change him!' - the brain worm, maybe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcie Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada's new drake]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205227</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205227/Canadas-new-drake"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lewis Mallard is an "interdimensional psychedelic folk artist" who appears in public only in a mallard costume. He is behind public art installations in Hamilton (CBC), Victoria (Instagram), and most recently Toronto (CityNews).
Lewis recently sat down for an interview with the host of the 3 Books podcast. 

The artist's official site and Instagram.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>invokeuse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Games of the Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153664</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153664"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals and the Guardians play a doubleheader today, the Royals three games back in the AL Central. The Royals lead the season series 4-2. The Blue Jays and the Red Sox play a sort of doubleheader as well, game one is the continuation of a game stopped by rain in June. Danny Jansen makes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Brown Told Eddie Murphy to Bury All His Money in the Woods]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43352_james-brown-told-eddie-murphy-to-bury-all-his-money-in-the-woods.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43352_james-brown-told-eddie-murphy-to-bury-all-his-money-in-the-woods.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Matt Solomon   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shohei Ohtani Joins the 40-40 Club in Grand Style, and He Could Have Company]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=444988</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/shohei-ohtani-joins-the-40-40-club-in-grand-style-and-he-could-have-company/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A time of high stolen base and home run rates has helped produce some exotic and fun combinations of power and speed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Jaffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deadline for Missouri’s new marijuana plain packaging is Sept. 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=845268</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/deadline-for-missouris-new-marijuana-plain-packaging-is-sept-1/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:23:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under Missouri’s new cannabis regulations, labels and packages for marijuana-related products must have limited colors and can’t appeal to children or resemble candy. (Photo by Rebecca Rivas/The Missouri Independent) Marijuana companies face a hard deadline to meet Missouri’s new plain packaging requirements on Sept. 1 — more than a year after the rule was initially put in place. For decades,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Rivas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premiere: The Uncouth’s recent music video for “Adam’s Got a Boxcutter” is lean and mean]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=845167</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/premiere-the-uncouths-adams-got-a-boxcutter-is-lean-and-mean/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From L-R: Oz Overshiner, Markel Randle, Steve Gardels, CJ Wilson, Cody Blanchard, Todd Rainey (seated). // photo by Jessica Morman Back in April of last year, The Pitch premiered the first video from Kansas City street punk foursome the Uncouth’s self-titled, full-length LP. That album released in Sept. of last year, but the band now has a new video for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Trump Chicken Out Of Debate Because Harris Is Allowed To Talk Back To Him?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/will-trump-chicken-out-of-debate</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/will-trump-chicken-out-of-debate"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bawk bawk bawk bawk bawk!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Legum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[24 Recently-Canceled TV Shows That Actually Deserved It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43208_24-recently-canceled-tv-shows-that-actually-deserved-it.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43208_24-recently-canceled-tv-shows-that-actually-deserved-it.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Amanda Mannen   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Kamala Harris Can Run as an Insurgent]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/?p=1698082</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/why-kamala-harris-can-run-as-an-insurgent/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T13:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris is having it both ways as she simultaneously takes credit for the Biden-Harris record while casting herself as a new leader who “won’t go back.” She seems to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Readers prefer to click on a clear, simple headline — like this one]]></title>
        <id>https://www.niemanlab.org/?p=230028</id>
        <link href="https://www.niemanlab.org/2024/08/readers-prefer-to-click-on-a-clear-simple-headline-like-this-one/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T13:40:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an era when people trust news less than ever, how can journalists break through and attract the attention of average people to provide information about their communities, the nation and the world? By not complicating things. Our research, published in Science Advances, shows that simple headlines significantly increase article engagement and clicks compared with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Markowitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need A Better Phrase For Back-To-Back-To-Back Home Runs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=165316</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/we-need-a-better-phrase-for-back-to-back-to-back-home-runs"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T13:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My colleague Lauren Theisen mused to me earlier this season that there should be a phrase for when Aaron Judge and Juan Soto homer in the same game, a thing that has now happened 12 times this year. I appreciate the impulse; baseball doesn't become mythos without a cool nickname. What would the Bash Brothers or Murderers' Row be without their names? Just some guys hitting home runs. But the Judge-Soto pairing's demand for a moniker lacks staying power—to the looming distress of Yankees fans—given Soto's willingness to enter a true free agency.
This does not mean our duties to dinger nomenclature are discharged. The heart of the Yankees' order threw down the gauntlet on Sunday, with Soto, Judge, and Giancarlo Stanton hitting three straight home runs in the seventh inning of a one-run game to help put away the Rockies, 10-3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Arkansas So Scared To Let Voters Decide On Abortion?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/why-is-arkansas-so-scared-to-let</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/why-is-arkansas-so-scared-to-let"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T13:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think we know!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robyn Pennacchia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Won't somebody think of the database administrators?]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205226</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205226/Wont-somebody-think-of-the-database-administrators"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T13:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Danny Jansen will be the first baseball player to play for both teams in the same game. 
Eric Money is the only NBA player to have scored for two teams in one game, although there were others that played for both sides. 

I can't find any evidence that this has happened in the NFL or NHL, but would love to know if it has.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jacquilynne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI Copyright Law Is Being Guided By Spirits From Atlantis]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=164704</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-ai-copyright-law-is-being-guided-by-spirits-from-atlantis"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T13:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With scant guidance for how to handle copyright requests for AI-generated works, the law is playing catch-up. As copyright offices around the world have consistently denied protections to AI art, you run across phrases like “the copyrightability of the monkey’s work,” as judges ruling on lawsuits are forced to rely on case law related to crested macaque photographers. And that’s not even close to the weirdest precedent cited. 
The 2023 case Thaler v. Perlmutter dealt with a copyright battle over an AI-generated picture. In ruling for the U.S. Copyright Office and its refusal to grant copyright protection, District Court Judge Beryl A. Howell wrote that a copyright has never been granted to “a work originating with a non-human.” To support this, Judge Howell called back to an 83-year-old case, Oliver v. Saint Germain Foundation, which involved a legal battle over a book purportedly dictated by an ancient Atlantean spirit. The story behind that book, and that case, is worth telling on its own merits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin McHenry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Jacobs’ book Hell on Wheels—Tour Stories: Remembered, Remixed, and Remastered collects adventures of rock’n’roll on the road]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=839744</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/greg-jacobs-book-hell-on-wheels-tour-stories-remembered-remixed-and-remastered-collects-adventures-of-rocknroll-on-the-road/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T13:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Chris Valle. In 1994, San Diego’s Rockpress published Greg Jacobs’ Hell on Wheels, a collection of tour stories by some of the author’s favorite bands. After discovering via social media that people were still interested in the book, Jacobs—a band manager and former employee of record labels like Cruz and SST—began curating 20 of its best stories and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Woods</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Doug Funnie Approach to Roster Construction]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=444961</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/the-doug-funnie-approach-to-roster-construction/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T13:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consistency didn't help Doug land Patti Mayonnaise, but it can help your favorite team win the World Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiri Oler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 U.S. Presidents Who Were Obsessed With UFOs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43341_6-us-presidents-who-were-obsessed-with-ufos.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43341_6-us-presidents-who-were-obsessed-with-ufos.html?newsletter-cat=science-history"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Jesse   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wonkette Presents THE SPLIT: Chapter Forty-Two.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/wonkette-presents-the-split-chapter-452</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/wonkette-presents-the-split-chapter-452"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T12:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In which our heroine hurtles toward another scary place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Radlauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["They like to feel like they're in a place where books matter"]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205225</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205225/They-like-to-feel-like-theyre-in-a-place-where-books-matter"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T12:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tiny New York Town Where Bookstores Rule (CBS News, NYT, previously)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>box</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exit, pursued by a dead bear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cjr.org/?p=102422</id>
        <link href="https://www.cjr.org/the_media_today/exit-pursued-by-a-dead-bear.php"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T12:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, the Democratic National Convention wrapped up in Chicago, and the echoes of 1968—so often invoked in media coverage ahead of time—had, we were told, fallen silent. Sure, there were dozens of arrests at street protests—including those of three journalists who were covering a demonstration at the Israeli consulate—but those were mostly peaceful, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Allsop</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The morning read for Monday, August 26]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scotusblog.com/?p=317239</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotusblog.com/2024/08/the-morning-read-for-monday-august-26/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T12:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each weekday, we select a short list of news articles, commentary, and other noteworthy links related to the Supreme Court. Here’s the Monday morning read: The Supreme Court’s recent decisions could undo big Biden accomplishments (Marcia Brown, Politico) Apache Group is Carrying a Petition to...
The post The morning read for Monday, August 26 appeared first on SCOTUSblog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ellena Erskine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Evidence That Maduro Won]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/no-evidence-that-maduro-won/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/no-evidence-that-maduro-won/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T12:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“One of Venezuela’s top election officials, in a declaration sure to jolt the crisis-weary nation, said in an interview that he had no proof that Venezuela’s authoritarian president won last […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big Squeeze]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205224</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205224/The-Big-Squeeze"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T12:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One reporter wipes away the mystery to reveal the truth, rolled up in a very thorough article that seeks to answer: Why toilet paper keeps getting smaller and smaller]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aya Hirano on the Astral Plane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic Polling Firm Sees Small Shift Towards Harris]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/polling-firm-sees-small-shift-towards-harris/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/polling-firm-sees-small-shift-towards-harris/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T12:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Public Policy Polling said that across 30 private polls done for clients over the last 10 days, Kamala Harris “is doing an average of one percentage point better than Joe […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[hot goss]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205223</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205223/hot-goss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T12:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conventional wisdom about heat islands — urban areas that are hotter than nearby rural areas because of the way the built environment absorbs and reemits heat from the sun — suggests that cities work to restore parks, trees and vegetation to keep things cool. But scientists and urban planners have found that another approach is even more beneficial to Dhaka's predicament: conserving wetlands [mongabay]
urban dictionary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HearHere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The wild and wacky media reaction to RFK Jr.’s endorsement of Donald Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.poynter.org/?p=1121135</id>
        <link href="https://www.poynter.org/commentary/2024/rfk-family-siblings-endorse-kamala-harris-polling-data/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T12:01:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. suspended his presidential campaign on Friday and threw his support behind Donald Trump. Does it matter? Can Kennedy’s endorsement actually influence what appears to be an […]
The post The wild and wacky media reaction to RFK Jr.’s endorsement of Donald Trump appeared first on Poynter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the members of this year’s Leadership Academy for Diversity in Media]]></title>
        <id>https://www.poynter.org/?p=1121003</id>
        <link href="https://www.poynter.org/from-the-institute/2024/introducing-the-members-of-this-years-leadership-academy-for-diversity-in-media/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T12:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. (Aug. 26, 2024) — The Poynter Institute is pleased to announce the 22 journalists selected for its 2024 Leadership Academy for Diversity in Media, a prestigious, weeklong, […]
The post Introducing the members of this year’s Leadership Academy for Diversity in Media appeared first on Poynter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barbara Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Games the Government Took Way Too Seriously]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43301_5-games-the-government-took-way-too-seriously.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43301_5-games-the-government-took-way-too-seriously.html?newsletter-cat=science-history"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Ryan Menezes   Published: August 26th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Undecided’ Panelist Says CNN Knew He Backed Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/undecided-panelist-says-cnn-knew-he-backed-trump/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/undecided-panelist-says-cnn-knew-he-backed-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T11:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A longtime Donald Trump supporter who was billed by CNN as an “undecided” voter said he told network before his appearance that he backed Trump.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Young Disabled Athletes Make the Sports World Work for Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.teenvogue.com/story/2024-paralympics-young-disabled-athletes</id>
        <link href="https://www.teenvogue.com/story/2024-paralympics-young-disabled-athletes"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T11:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elite disabled athletes have to battle systemic barriers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Breaking US, World &amp; College News | Teen Vogue | Teen Vogue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quote of the Day]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/quote-of-the-day-3937/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/quote-of-the-day-3937/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T11:47:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Our understanding is that Trump’s handlers prefer the muted microphone because they don’t think their candidate can act presidential for 90 minutes on his own.” — Harris campaign adviser Brian […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Was Not Promised a Trump Cabinet Post]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/rfk-jr-was-not-promised-a-trump-cabinet-post/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/rfk-jr-was-not-promised-a-trump-cabinet-post/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T11:44:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. told Fox News he was not promised a Cabinet position in exchange for endorsing Donald Trump. Said Kennedy: “There’s been no commitments.” He added that he […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven States Are Up for Grabs]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/seven-states-are-up-for-grabs/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/seven-states-are-up-for-grabs/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T11:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NPR now has all seven of the most closely watched swing states as toss-ups, “moving all of the Sun Belt states from Lean Republican previously.” “NPR’s analysis in this map […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Trump’s Campaign Rallies Working?]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/are-trumps-campaign-rallies-working/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/are-trumps-campaign-rallies-working/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T11:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“As Donald Trump emerged to a thunderous roar of approval in the heart of Pennsylvania’s Rust belt, he was back in his comfort zone among the people who once put […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LET'S F*CKING GOOOOOOOOO! Tabs, Mon., Aug. 26, 2024!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/lets-fcking-gooooooooo-tabs-mon-aug</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/lets-fcking-gooooooooo-tabs-mon-aug"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T11:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Morning news rounduuuuuuuuuuuup!!!!!!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Schoenkopf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beat the Streak Picks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153662</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153662"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T11:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Log5 Method yields these top projected hit averages averages against starting pitchers: 0.337 — Bobby Witt Jr. batting against Logan Allen. 0.314 — Luis Arraez batting against Kyle Gibson. 0.310 — Xavier Edwards batting against Ryan Feltner. 0.308 — Freddy Fermin batting against Logan Allen. 0.305 — Nolan Arenado batting against Randy Vasquez. 0.304 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. suspended his 2024 presidential bid. Here are 6 fact checks from his campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.poynter.org/?p=1121145</id>
        <link href="https://www.poynter.org/fact-checking/2024/robert-f-kennedy-fact-check/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T11:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A day after Vice President Kamala Harris officially accepted the Democratic Party’s nomination for president, independent candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. held a press conference to announce he was suspending […]
The post RFK Jr. suspended his 2024 presidential bid. Here are 6 fact checks from his campaign appeared first on Poynter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Madison Czopek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Book Review Ever]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205222</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205222/Best-Book-Review-Ever"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T10:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["A burglar who broke into an apartment in Rome on Tuesday night was arrested after stopping in the middle of the robbery to read a book about Greek mythology."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cupcakeninja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris Ramps Up Strategy for Sprint to Election]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/harris-ramps-up-strategy-for-sprint-to-election/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/harris-ramps-up-strategy-for-sprint-to-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T10:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Kamala Harris’ strategy for the 71-day sprint to the Nov. 5 election is built around a few key goals: Outwork Donald Trump, stay in the news, and campaign aggressively in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Suggests He May Skip Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/trump-suggests-he-may-skip-debate/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/trump-suggests-he-may-skip-debate/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T10:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump suggested Sunday evening that he might skip a Sept. 10 ABC News debate with Vice President Kamala Harris (D), after agreeing to participate as the GOP presidential nominee […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Prepares for Sprint to November]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/trump-prepares-for-sprint-to-november/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/trump-prepares-for-sprint-to-november/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Fresh off a week of daily counterprogramming events and an effort to steal the spotlight from his new opponent, Donald Trump and his campaign are seeking to harness that pace […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Economic Gamble]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/trumps-economic-gamble/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/trumps-economic-gamble/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T10:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump “is talking down the economy like his election depends on it,” Axios reports. “It might. Trump knows that nothing matters more than economic issues. That makes the next […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Keeps Low Profile on Vacation]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/biden-keeps-low-profile-on-vacation/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/26/biden-keeps-low-profile-on-vacation/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Washington Post: “The president has not spoken publicly or to the press since Monday night — after he gave an emotional speech, formally passing the torch to Vice President Kamala […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hockey player Phoenix Herron to attend Kansas City’s first Total Package Academy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=841063</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/hockey-player-phoenix-herron-to-attend-kansas-citys-first-total-package-academy/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T10:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phoenix Herron skating in 2023. Photo courtesy of Juaquan Herron. This fall, Phoenix Herron will be one of the first hockey players to attend Kansas City’s Total Package Academy, a 10-month training program for student athletes with campuses across the country. Kansas City’s program will begin operating in September at the AdventHealth Sports Park at Bluhawk in Overland Park.  At...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Woods</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["No sense in being pessimistic. It wouldn't work anyway."]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205221</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205221/No-sense-in-being-pessimistic-It-wouldnt-work-anyway"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T08:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pessimists Archive is a project to jog our collective memories about the hysteria, technophobia and moral panic that often greets new technologies, ideas and trends.
A few examples: 
When the Surgeon General Warned About Pac-Man
The New York Times Banned Word Games Before Embracing Them
The Forgotten War on Beepers
When the Mac 'Ruined' Writing
Remember Typewriter Licenses?
A Warning About AI from 1863 (!)
Predictions about 2023 made in 1830
An Ancient Poem Against Sundials (250 B.C.)

Source for the title]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chavenet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Werribee Zoo welcomes birth of male rhino calf]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205220</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205220/Werribee-Zoo-welcomes-birth-of-male-rhino-calf"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T07:36:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Werribee Zoo welcomes birth of male rhino calf, who already has the zoomies. Victoria's Werribee Open Range Zoo has welcomed the birth of a male southern white rhino, more than a year after the passing of a female calf.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chariot pulled by cassowaries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The birb's the word ... and it's your Free Thread]]></title>
        <id>tag:metafilter.com,2024:site.205219</id>
        <link href="https://www.metafilter.com/205219/The-birbs-the-word-and-its-your-Free-Thread"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T07:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent post on Metatalk discusses posts about birds. Ergo, have you seen, heard, or encountered any comment-worthy birds (keep it clean) recently or in the past? Perhaps hopping or waddling birds, birds which say "pew", some clever magpies, some parakeets, a lovely pair of boobies or just any birds ... Or write about whatever is on your mind, in your heart, on your plate or in your journal, because this is your weekly free thread [lateliestish]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wordshore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ryuichi Sakamoto]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/ryuichi-sakamoto-e32</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/ryuichi-sakamoto-e32"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T07:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Kinds of Research]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2977/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2977/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Are GOP Trump Critics Not Endorsing Harris?]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/why-are-gop-trump-critics-not-endorsing-harris/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/why-are-gop-trump-critics-not-endorsing-harris/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T03:16:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Miller: “So puzzle me this: There are two options for president. On the one hand you have a woman who just presented herself as a mainstream Democrat who plans […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[538 Model Criticized for Lack of Transparency]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/538-model-criticized-for-lack-of-transparency/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/538-model-criticized-for-lack-of-transparency/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T02:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Semafor: “It reappeared Friday with a forecast showing Harris winning 58 times out of 100. The results largely mirror those shown by other election forecasters, including the Economist.” “The polling […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris Builds Army of House Surrogates]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/harris-builds-army-of-house-surrogates/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/harris-builds-army-of-house-surrogates/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T02:56:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The Harris campaign is casting a drastically wider net in recruiting House Democrats to stump for the presidential ticket, gauging the interest of almost every member,” Axios reports. “Over a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Batter Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153660</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153660"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T02:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Judge and Juan Soto of the Yankees remain one and three respectively in the Baseball Musings Batter Rankings after games of Sunday. Judge produced the third best game score of the day, a 76, as he went two for four with a walk and two home runs, bringing his season HR total to 51. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOP Battle Brewing Over Fall Spending Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/gop-battle-brewing-over-fall-spending-bill/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/gop-battle-brewing-over-fall-spending-bill/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T02:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell’s office has been working behind the scenes to get House conservatives to drop their demands that a short-term funding bill include an immigrant voting crackdown,” […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monday Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153658</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153658"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T02:38:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Loses Secret Service Protection]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/rfk-jr-loses-secret-service-protection/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/rfk-jr-loses-secret-service-protection/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T01:09:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr., who suspended his third-party presidential bid last week and endorsed Donald Trump, has lost his Secret Service protection following the decision to leave the race, CBS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vance Promises Trump Would Veto Abortion Ban]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/vance-promises-trump-would-veto-abortion-ban/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/vance-promises-trump-would-veto-abortion-ban/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T01:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[J.D. Vance said Donald Trump would not support a national abortion ban if elected president and would veto such legislation if it landed on his desk, the AP reports. Said […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Says Musk Wouldn’t Have Time for Cabinet Post]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/trump-says-musk-wouldnt-have-time-for-cabinet-post/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/trump-says-musk-wouldnt-have-time-for-cabinet-post/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T01:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump said that Tesla and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk likely couldn’t serve in his hypothetical White House cabinet due to the demanding schedule of running his various companies, CNBC […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[H.R. McMaster Rips Trump White House]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/h-r-mcmaster-rips-trump-white-house/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/h-r-mcmaster-rips-trump-white-house/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T01:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Until now, Lt. Gen. H.R. McMaster has held his fire about his stint in the Trump White House. McMaster served with distinction in key American conflicts of the past decades: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Tale of Two Seasons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153656</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153656"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T00:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a rather fascinating season. Coming into today, none of the eight teams who were in the top eight in the majors through June 30th were in the top eight at the start of Sunday. It looked early on that there would not be many good division races, and now we have three or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Leave It to Beaver’ Went to War with Network Censors to Show a Toilet on TV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43348_leave-it-to-beaver-went-to-war-with-network-censors-to-show-a-toilet-on-tv.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43348_leave-it-to-beaver-went-to-war-with-network-censors-to-show-a-toilet-on-tv.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  JM McNab   Published: August 25th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White Sox Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153654</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153654"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T23:52:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tigers beat the White Sox 9-4 on Sunday, lowering the White Sox winning percentage on the season to .237. That is below the .250 winning percentage of the 1962 Mets, the modern record for mediocrity. Time to update the probability of Chicago finishing with no more than 40 wins. They need to go no […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pandemic pod-people horror-romance The Becomers goes full GooAnon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=844222</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/pandemic-pod-people-horror-romance-the-becomers-goes-full-gooanon/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T21:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Becomers. // Courtesy Dark Star Pictures I adore Zach Clark. His coked-up Christmas film White Reindeer is a holiday rewatch tradition in this household, and 2016’s goth’d-out Little Sister is a must-watch. His work always hits a specific indie discomfort, keeping audiences guessing as he bobs and weaves across unexpected genres. They’re always funny and packed with heart, but can...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153652</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153652"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T20:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Judge of the Yankees hit two more home runs on Sunday, part of a Yankees barrage that beat the Rockies 10-3. He now owns 51 homers on the season. His probability of breaking his own AL record of 62 homers in a season is now at 0.28 a little better than one in four. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three on A Match]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153650</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153650"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T20:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juan Soto, Aaron Judge, and Giancarlo Stanton hit three solo home runs in a row in the bottom of the seventh inning to give New York a 7-3 lead over the Rockies. Stanton looks like he’s getting his swing back. If he stays healthy the rest of the season, that heart of the order is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Seeks to Dull Democratic Attacks on Abortion]]></title>
        <id>https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/trump-seeks-to-dull-democratic-attacks-on-abortion/</id>
        <link href="https://politicalwire.com/2024/08/25/trump-seeks-to-dull-democratic-attacks-on-abortion/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T19:29:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Donald Trump attempted to strike a new tone on the issue of abortion this week, saying he would be ‘great for women and their reproductive rights’ — to the frustration […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taegan Goddard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side the Head]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153648</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153648"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T19:12:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The home plate umpire Nick Mahrley in the Rockies-Yankees game just took a blow in the side of the neck from a broken bat. Giancarlo Stanton took a swing and his bat cracked at the handle. The barrel came around and got the home plate umpire in the side of the neck. It looks like […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Candids at Kauffman during the Royals’ 7-4 victory over Philly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=845194</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-candids-at-kauffman-during-the-royals-7-4-victory-over-philly/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T18:17:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Created with RNI Films app. Profile ‘Agfa Optima 200 Warm’ On Friday, the Kansas City Royals beat the Philadelphia Phillies in a 7-4 game. Our photographer Stephen Fuller was there to capture something a little bit different this time—with some atmospheric shots from the stadium, some fans, and some patriotism. Categories: Politics Tags: baseball, Kauffman Stadium, KC Royals, mlb, Philadelphia...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Fuller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fifth 50]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153646</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153646"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T18:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Judge of the Yankees hit the fiftieth home run of his 2024 season in the first inning to put his team up 2-1 on the Rockies. He is the fifth players in the history of the game to post at least three seasons of at least 50 home runs. Babe Ruth, Mark McGwire, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Superbad’ DVDs Sparked a Major Controversy in Hawaii]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43346_superbad-dvds-sparked-a-major-controversy-in-hawaii.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43346_superbad-dvds-sparked-a-major-controversy-in-hawaii.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  JM McNab   Published: August 25th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas women rally adjacent to J.D. Vance fundraiser, with vulnerable plea for reproductive rights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=845166</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kansas-women-rally-adjacent-to-j-d-vance-fundraiser-with-vulnerable-plea-for-reproductive-rights/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T16:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amber Dickinson speaks on reproductive rights at the “Kansas Women for Harris” rally Aug. 22, 2024, in Leawood. (Grace Hills/Kansas Reflector) Trigger warning: This story references rape. Help is available.  LEAWOOD — Amber Dickinson took a personal and vulnerable stand for reproductive freedom as she talked publicly for the first time about being raped. Before her speech Thursday in Leawood...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grace Hills</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DNC 2024: A Full And Complete Recap Of Everything That Happened, All At Once]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/dnc-2024-a-full-and-complete-recap</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/dnc-2024-a-full-and-complete-recap"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T16:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are watching. Always watching.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shypixel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Conservative Party Ad Cheers On Russian Jets Heading for Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/new-conservative-party-ad-cheers</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/new-conservative-party-ad-cheers"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T15:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['Mistakes happen' sez Tory spox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Fleming</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Earliest Known Dick Joke Is Thousands of Years Old]]></title>
        <id>https://trivia.cracked.com/article_43333_the-earliest-known-dick-joke-is-thousands-of-years-old.html</id>
        <link href="https://trivia.cracked.com/article_43333_the-earliest-known-dick-joke-is-thousands-of-years-old.html?newsletter-cat=trivia"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  JM McNab   Published: August 25th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Games of the Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153644</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153644"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T14:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Diamondbacks send Merrill Kelly against Tanner Houck and the Red Sox. Kelly missed three months due to a strained muscle in his shoulder. He pitched one good and one bad outing since his return, overall giving up eight runs in ten innings. Houck’s 3.01 ERA is now second in the AL, and he leads […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top ‘Simpsons’ Moments That Left Superfans Gasping for Breath]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43345_the-top-simpsons-moments-that-left-superfans-gasping-for-breath.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43345_the-top-simpsons-moments-that-left-superfans-gasping-for-breath.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Keegan Kelly   Published: August 25th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White Sox Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153642</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153642"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T12:44:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tigers beat the White Sox 13-4 on Saturday, lowering the White Sox winning percentage on the season to .238. That is below the .250 winning percentage of the 1962 Mets, the modern record for mediocrity*. Time to update the probability of Chicago finishing with no more than 40 wins. *It was pointed out to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animals With the Weirdest Poop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43329_animals-with-the-weirdest-poop.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43329_animals-with-the-weirdest-poop.html?newsletter-cat=science-history"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Amanda Mannen   Published: August 25th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday Notes: Walter Pennington Ponders His Zero-Zero Slider]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=444944</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/sunday-notes-walter-pennington-ponders-his-zero-zero-slider/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T11:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus Josh Hader on his heater and slider, an NL MVP poll, a Dan Wilson-Grady Sizemore comp, some Craig Counsell and A.J. Hinch wisdom, and much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Laurila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beat the Streak Picks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153640</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153640"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T11:43:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Log5 Method yields these top projected hit averages against starting pitchers: 0.336 — Jose Iglesias batting against Martin Perez. 0.315 — Bobby Witt Jr. batting against Kolby Allard. 0.296 — Luis Arraez batting against Jose Quintana. 0.295 — Starling Marte batting against Martin Perez. 0.293 — Aaron Judge batting against Austin Gomber. 0.291 — […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Batter Today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153638</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153638"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T11:08:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vladimir Guerrero Jr. of the Blue Jays moves past Juan Soto of the Yankees into second place in the Baseball Musings Batter Rankings. Guerrero posted a two for three with a walk, a double, and a home run in a 3-1 victory over the Angels. Soto singled in a 9-2 Rockies victory. His teammate, Aaron […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153636</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153636"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T10:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wonkette Movie Night: The Secret Of Kells]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/wonkette-movie-night-the-secret-of</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/wonkette-movie-night-the-secret-of"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T00:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['I have lived through many ages, through the eyes of salmon, deer, and wolf.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ziggywiggy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COVID-19 Update: New Vaccines Ready and Free Tests Are Coming Back]]></title>
        <id>https://www.teenvogue.com/story/covid-19-update-new-vaccines-ready-and-free-tests-are-coming-back</id>
        <link href="https://www.teenvogue.com/story/covid-19-update-new-vaccines-ready-and-free-tests-are-coming-back"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T23:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Households will be able to order up to four free tests, and the FDA has authorized updated COVID-19 vaccines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Breaking US, World &amp; College News | Teen Vogue | Teen Vogue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Trivia Tidbits for Saturday, August 24, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://trivia.cracked.com/article_43300_15-trivia-tidbits-for-saturday-august-24-2024.html</id>
        <link href="https://trivia.cracked.com/article_43300_15-trivia-tidbits-for-saturday-august-24-2024.html?newsletter-cat=trivia"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Ryan Menezes   Published: August 24th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got Milk?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153634</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153634"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T22:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colton Cowser made a terrific play to keep the Orioles inning alive in the bottom of the sixth. Trailing the Astros 2-0, with men on first and second, Cowser grounded to first baseball Jon Singleton, playing behind the bag. Pitcher Framber Valdez did not rush to cover, because it looked like it would be an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Record Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153632</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153632"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T21:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rockies beat the Yankees 9-2 on Saturday, holding Aaron Judge of the Yankees to a walk and a hit by pitch. That lowers Judge’s probability of breaking his AL single season home run record of 62 to 0.14. He is on a pace for 61 home runs, and his expected total is 59 home […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Francis in the Ninth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153627</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153627"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T21:08:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bowden Francis of the Blue Jays comes out to pitch the ninth inning with a no-hitter on the line against the Angels. He walked three and struck out 12 so far, throwing 111 pitches. He is scheduled to face the top of the Angels order, Taylor Ward, Zach Neto, and Kevin Pillar. The Blue Jays […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowden Oh-n]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153620</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153620"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T20:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bowden Francis of the Blue Jays held the Angels hitless through six innings. He found himself in his three previous starts, allowing three runs in 19 innings while walking one and striking out 22 batters. He walked two and struck out ten so far as Toronto leads 2-0 at the end of six. Update: Francis […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calls from Missouri to new 988 crisis hotline up 136% since 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=845077</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/calls-from-missouri-to-new-988-crisis-hotline-up-136-since-2022/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T20:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crisis counselor answers a 988 call at the Ozark Center, which covers four southwestern counties (Photo courtesy of Freeman marketing). Missouri has seen one of the nation’s largest increases in calls to the revamped national hotline that aids people facing mental health crises. The number of calls to 988 from Missouri jumped 136% in May 2024 compared to May...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clara Bates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nice Time! AZ’s 41k Federal-Only Voters Not Getting Kicked Off Rolls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/nice-time-azs-41k-federal-only-voters</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/nice-time-azs-41k-federal-only-voters"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T19:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amy Comey Barrett's tip check must have bounced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcie Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That Time We Executed Sacco And Vanzetti]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/that-time-we-executed-sacco-and-vanzetti</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/that-time-we-executed-sacco-and-vanzetti"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday in labor history.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Loomis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s What Jodie Sweetin Tried to Steal From the ‘Fuller House’ Set]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43337_heres-what-jodie-sweetin-tried-to-steal-from-the-fuller-house-set.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43337_heres-what-jodie-sweetin-tried-to-steal-from-the-fuller-house-set.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Matt Solomon   Published: August 24th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Suspends Campaign, Ending His Brainworm's Dream Of A Cabinet Position]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/rfk-suspends-campaign-ending-his</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/rfk-suspends-campaign-ending-his"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T16:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bear with us while we shed a tear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Legum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Mosquitoes Really Bite Certain People More Than Others?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43331_do-mosquitoes-really-bite-certain-people-more-than-others.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43331_do-mosquitoes-really-bite-certain-people-more-than-others.html?newsletter-cat=science-history"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Eli Yudin   Published: August 24th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21 Parodies That Outclassed the Genres They Spoofed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43130_21-parodies-that-outclassed-the-genres-they-spoofed.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43130_21-parodies-that-outclassed-the-genres-they-spoofed.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Amanda Mannen   Published: August 24th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Games of the Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153615</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153615"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T15:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Astros and Orioles continue their battle in Baltimore as Framber Valdez takes on Albert Suarez. Since the start of the 2018 season, Valdez’s first in the majors, he ranks second in fewest HR allowed per 9 IP a 0.74 (800 IP). Only Logan Webb does better. Suarez is tough this season on sluggers as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Drives Trump To Melt Down Like Eleventy Billion Chernobyls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/kamala-harris-drives-trump-to-melt</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/kamala-harris-drives-trump-to-melt"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T15:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fun, and way less chance of the rest of us getting radiation poisoning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Legum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[George Burns’ Final Joke Came from Beyond the Grave]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43335_george-burns-final-joke-came-from-beyond-the-grave.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43335_george-burns-final-joke-came-from-beyond-the-grave.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  JM McNab   Published: August 24th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ohtani at 40]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153617</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153617"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T14:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am not a big fan of the steals-home runs clubs, but I have to admit that entering it with a walk-off grand slam gives it some pizazz. That’s how Shohei Ohtani reached the 40-40 club of home runs and steals in a season. He is the fastest player in major league history to reach […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Strange Music Day!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/happy-strange-music-day</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/happy-strange-music-day"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T14:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So many presents for you!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robyn Pennacchia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Julia Louis-Dreyfus Has Never Seen the First Episode of ‘Seinfeld’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43342_julia-louis-dreyfus-has-never-seen-the-first-episode-of-seinfeld.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43342_julia-louis-dreyfus-has-never-seen-the-first-episode-of-seinfeld.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  JM McNab   Published: August 24th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White Sox Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153613</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153613"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T12:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tigers beat the White Sox 5-2 on Friday, lowering the White Sox winning percentage on the season to .240. That is below the .250 winning percentage of the 1962 Mets, the modern record for mediocrity. Time to update the probability of Chicago finishing with no more than 40 wins. They need to go no […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pettiest Grudges Held by Historical Figures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43327_the-pettiest-grudges-held-by-historical-figures.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43327_the-pettiest-grudges-held-by-historical-figures.html?newsletter-cat=science-history"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Amanda Mannen   Published: August 24th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beat the Streak Picks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153611</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153611"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T11:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Log5 Method yields these top projected hit averages against starting pitchers: 0.320 — Amed Rosario batting against Jake Woodford. 0.297 — Luis Arraez batting against David Peterson. 0.293 — Bobby Witt Jr. batting against Ranger Suarez. 0.286 — Steven Kwan batting against Jon Gray. 0.284 — Yainer Diaz batting against Albert Suarez. 0.284 — […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Batter Today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153609</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153609"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T10:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Still no movement as the top five in the Baseball Musings Batter Rankings remain the same. Teammates Aaron Judge and Juan Soto of the Yankees remain 1-2 respectively, but Judge, with five home runs in his last four games, now leads Soto by 29 points. Both came to the plate four times in the 3-0 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saturday Update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153607</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153607"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T10:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Record Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153605</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153605"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T01:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Judge of the Yankees homered for the fourth straight game, pushing his total for the season to 49. That raises his probability of breaking his own AL record of 62 to 0.162, or about 1 in 6. He is on a pace for 62 homers, and his expected total is 60. He would be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Sometimes You Have to Kill Your Darlings’: Ryan Reynolds Explains Why He Cut Rob McElhenney From ‘Deadpool &amp; Wolverine’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43347_sometimes-you-have-to-kill-your-darlings-ryan-reynolds-explains-why-he-cut-rob-mcelhenney-from-deadpool-wolverine.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43347_sometimes-you-have-to-kill-your-darlings-ryan-reynolds-explains-why-he-cut-rob-mcelhenney-from-deadpool-wolverine.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Keegan Kelly   Published: August 23rd, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Knock The Side Hustle! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074281</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/dont-knock-the-side-hustle-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T23:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Skadden Associates Are Turning Up The Heat In The Kitchen: Read up on how the cookie crumbles!
Yale Law Has A Simple Path To Redemption: Still won't be easy.
Show Me The Money!: Lawyers from this swing state are sending money to Kamala.
Stop, Do Not Pass Go: Disqualified lawyer kept on filing motions.
Signs Of A Prosecutor: Kamala still has her cross examination skills!
The post Don’t Knock The Side Hustle! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Roast of Rob Lowe That Became the Roast of Ann Coulter Is Once Again Topical]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43344_the-roast-of-rob-lowe-that-became-the-roast-of-ann-coulter-is-once-again-topical.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43344_the-roast-of-rob-lowe-that-became-the-roast-of-ann-coulter-is-once-again-topical.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Keegan Kelly   Published: August 23rd, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Biglaw Really Needs Is More Nonequity Partners]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074262</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/what-biglaw-really-needs-is-more-nonequity-partners/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T23:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Income partner headcount is up.
The post What Biglaw Really Needs Is More Nonequity Partners appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Appealing Weekly Roundup]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074249</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/how-appealing-weekly-roundup-83/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T22:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The week in appellate news.
The post How Appealing Weekly Roundup appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steve Martin Asked Permission to Show ‘STEVE!’ Documentary to His Shrink]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43343_steve-martin-asked-permission-to-show-steve-documentary-to-his-shrink.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43343_steve-martin-asked-permission-to-show-steve-documentary-to-his-shrink.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Matt Solomon   Published: August 23rd, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DC Judge Bars Missouri AG From Prosecuting Media Matters For Aggravated Making Elon Sad]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074271</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/dc-judge-bars-missouri-ag-from-prosecuting-media-matters-for-aggravated-making-elon-sad/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T22:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GTFOH
The post DC Judge Bars Missouri AG From Prosecuting Media Matters For Aggravated Making Elon Sad appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lorne Michaels Had No Input in Jason Reitman&#039;s ‘SNL’ Movie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43338_lorne-michaels-had-no-input-in-jason-reitmans-snl-movie.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43338_lorne-michaels-had-no-input-in-jason-reitmans-snl-movie.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  JM McNab   Published: August 23rd, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Places at Once]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153603</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153603"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T21:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Danny Jansen will appear in a game for both teams on Monday: Danny Jansen will make baseball history Monday when he appears in the same game for both teams. The unique scenario was set in stone July 27, when the Toronto Blue Jays traded Jansen to the Boston Red Sox — about a month after a game between the two […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Still Time to Buy History]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153601</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153601"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T21:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The jersey worn by Babe Ruth in the 1932 World Series when he called his home run is on auction right now. The current bid stands at $15.1 million. Please read the article for the fascinating look at how the process of photo matching authenticated the jersey. Companies such as Resolution Photomatching rely on checks […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Green Day’s Tuesday night show at Azura was the best of all possible nostalgia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=844951</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/green-days-tuesday-night-show-at-azura-was-the-best-of-all-possible-nostalgia/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T21:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Green Day. // photo by Kylee Gregg Green Day with Rancid and the Linda Linda’s Azura Amphitheater Tuesday, August 20 To be honest, it’s a decent confrontation of one’s own mortality when you attend a concert of a band playing two albums in their entirety, back-to-back. Reckoning with whether you enjoy both albums enough to stay out until nearly 11...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Right Wing Round-Up: Rules for Chaos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.rightwingwatch.org/?p=546774</id>
        <link href="https://www.rightwingwatch.org/post/right-wing-round-up-rules-for-chaos/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T21:22:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josh Fiallo @ The Daily Beast: RFK Jr. Suspends Failing Campaign to Throw His Support to Donald Trump The independent never made it on a debate stage and had his polling numbers drop significantly after Kamala Harris became Democrats’ presumptive nominee. Media Matters: Roger Stone and Alex Jones endorse RFK Jr. as CIA director in […]
The post Right Wing Round-Up: Rules for Chaos appeared first on Right Wing Watch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Mantyla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Right Wing Bonus Tracks: This Leftist March to Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.rightwingwatch.org/?p=546775</id>
        <link href="https://www.rightwingwatch.org/post/right-wing-bonus-tracks-this-leftist-march-to-hell/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T21:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump-loving right-wing activist Jim Garlow watched the DNC and he’s “never ever seen so much deceit, so many blatant, intentional lies. Frankly, it saddens me. I really care for these people. But, SO much delusion.” Mario Murillo also watched the convention and says that Kamala Harris “must be exposed”: “That is the solemn duty of […]
The post Right Wing Bonus Tracks: This Leftist March to Hell appeared first on Right Wing Watch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Mantyla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sean Feucht ‘Can’t Take’ the DNC, Calls for ‘Jehus’ and ‘Madmen for Jesus’ to ‘Rise Up’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.rightwingwatch.org/?p=546777</id>
        <link href="https://www.rightwingwatch.org/post/sean-feucht-cant-take-the-dnc-calls-for-jehus-and-madmen-for-jesus-to-rise-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T20:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christian nationalist musician-politician Sean Feucht “can’t take it anymore.” On Thursday, Feucht sent his followers a video fuming about the fact that all Christian leaders are not outspoken MAGA activists like him, which he called a “leadership crisis.” Feucht is associated with the dominionist New Apostolic Reformation movement, whose U.S. leaders see politics through the […]
The post Sean Feucht ‘Can’t Take’ the DNC, Calls for ‘Jehus’ and ‘Madmen for Jesus’ to ‘Rise Up’ appeared first on Right Wing Watch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Montgomery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Having Yu Back]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153599</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153599"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T20:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Padres reinstated Yu Darvish from the restricted list and placed him on the fifteen day illjured list. He last pitched on May 29th. Since that date, San Diego is 48-33, the third best record in the majors. The Diamondbacks at 50-31 and the Astros at 48-32 are the only teams better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris, A Presidential Nominee For The People]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074265</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/kamala-harris-a-presidential-nominee-for-the-people/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T20:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An excerpt from the Vice President's touching speech as she accepted the Democratic nomination for the presidency.
The post Kamala Harris, A Presidential Nominee For The People appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marketing Roundup: How To Help Lawyers Become Thought Leaders]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074172</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/marketing-roundup-how-to-help-lawyers-become-thought-leaders/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T20:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LMA shares insights on handling AI with outside vendors and leveraging firm culture for business development. 
The post Marketing Roundup: How To Help Lawyers Become Thought Leaders appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KATHERINE HOLLAR BARNARD</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Norm Macdonald and David Spade Loved to Burn Each Other on Talk Shows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43340_norm-macdonald-and-david-spade-loved-to-burn-each-other-on-talk-shows.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43340_norm-macdonald-and-david-spade-loved-to-burn-each-other-on-talk-shows.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Matt Solomon   Published: August 23rd, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Reminds Kraken Lawyer That Getting Disqualified Really Does Mean You Have To Stop Filing Stuff]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1073955</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/judge-reminds-kraken-lawyer-that-getting-disqualified-really-does-mean-you-have-to-stop-filing-stuff/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T20:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bye, Felicia!
The post Judge Reminds Kraken Lawyer That Getting Disqualified Really Does Mean You Have To Stop Filing Stuff appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Rick and Morty: The Anime’ Spoiled the Only Watchable Scene From Today’s Episode Five Months Ago]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43339_rick-and-morty-the-anime-spoiled-the-only-watchable-scene-from-todays-episode-five-months-ago.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43339_rick-and-morty-the-anime-spoiled-the-only-watchable-scene-from-todays-episode-five-months-ago.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Keegan Kelly   Published: August 23rd, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DNC Denies Palestinian Speaker for Final Night of Convention After Protests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.teenvogue.com/story/dnc-denies-palestinian-speaker-for-final-night-of-convention-after-protests</id>
        <link href="https://www.teenvogue.com/story/dnc-denies-palestinian-speaker-for-final-night-of-convention-after-protests"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T19:15:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One Uncommitted delegate said after Harris's speech, "This is just a bad look. You're going to lose Michigan.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Breaking US, World &amp; College News | Teen Vogue | Teen Vogue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Money From This Swing State’s Laywers Bleeds Overwhelmingly Blue]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074261</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/the-money-from-this-swing-states-laywers-bleeds-overwhelmingly-blue/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Send in that money! 
The post The Money From This Swing State’s Laywers Bleeds Overwhelmingly Blue appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Skadden Associates Star In ‘Side Hustlers,’ Showcasing Their New Cookie Business, Brune Kitchen]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074202</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/former-skadden-associates-star-in-side-hustlers-showcasing-their-new-cookie-business-brune-kitchen/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T18:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Biglaw to the bakery, watch how these former associates land their dream jobs in the kitchen.
The post Former Skadden Associates Star In ‘Side Hustlers,’ Showcasing Their New Cookie Business, Brune Kitchen appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris’s Cross Examination Skills Highlighted At DNC]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074255</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/08/kamala-harriss-cross-examination-skills-highlighted-at-dnc/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T17:43:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris took her courtroom skills to Washington.
The post Kamala Harris’s Cross Examination Skills Highlighted At DNC appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alyson Hannigan Doesn’t Want Her Teen Kids Watching ‘American Pie’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43336_alyson-hannigan-doesnt-want-her-teen-kids-watching-american-pie.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43336_alyson-hannigan-doesnt-want-her-teen-kids-watching-american-pie.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Matt Solomon   Published: August 23rd, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gulf War Forced Disney to Change the Setting of ‘Aladdin’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cracked.com/article_43326_the-gulf-war-forced-disney-to-change-the-setting-of-aladdin.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.cracked.com/article_43326_the-gulf-war-forced-disney-to-change-the-setting-of-aladdin.html?newsletter-cat=movies-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By  Eli Yudin   Published: August 23rd, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cracked: All Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rays Are Running Rampant]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=444915</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/the-rays-are-running-rampant/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a slow start to the season, the Rays have been the best base-stealing team in the league this summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leo Morgenstern</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome To Wonkette Happy Hour, With This Week's Cocktail, The Brandy Alexander!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/welcome-to-wonkette-happy-hour-with-88d</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/welcome-to-wonkette-happy-hour-with-88d"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T15:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How about some nice dessert after a lovely convention?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Hooper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The morning read for Friday, August 23]]></title>
        <id>https://www.scotusblog.com/?p=317232</id>
        <link href="https://www.scotusblog.com/2024/08/the-morning-read-for-friday-august-23/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T15:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each weekday, we select a short list of news articles, commentary, and other noteworthy links related to the Supreme Court. Here’s the Friday morning read: Supreme Court partly grants GOP request to enforce Arizona’s proof-of-citizenship voting law (Lawrence Hurley, NBC News) Divided Supreme Court rejects...
The post The morning read for Friday, August 23 appeared first on SCOTUSblog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ellena Erskine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Games of the Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153597</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153597"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T14:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rangers take on the Guardians with Nathan Eovaldi facing Tanner Bibee. The Guardians lead in the AL Central is down to two games against both Kansas City and Minnesota. Eovaldi’s strength this season is his walk rate, 2.06 per nine IP. That’s well below his career rate to 2.54. Note that the Guardians rank […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revisiting the Trevor Rogers Trade. Oof.]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=444879</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/revisiting-the-trevor-rogers-trade-oof/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T14:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it's wise to reserve judgment on a trade. Sometimes you don't have to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Baumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What if the Fences Were All the Same Distance Away?]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=444849</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/what-if-the-fences-were-all-the-same-distance-away/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T13:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If baseball were different, how different would it be?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Clemens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Sept. 2024 Events Calendar highlights Twin Temple, CannaBrew Kansas City, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=843558</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/our-sept-2024-events-calendar-highlights-twin-temple-cannabrew-kansas-city-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T13:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Chris Ortiz. // Art by Cassondra Jones ONGOING Sept 2-8 Dancefestopia, Wildwood Outdoor Education Center Sept 3-22 Once, KCRep Spencer Theatre Sept 6-8 Art Westport, Westport Neighborhood Sept 13 & 14 Sommore, Funny Bone Comedy Club Sept 13-15 Fiesta Hispana, 1701 American Royal Ct. Sept 17-22 Peter Pan, Starlight Theatre Sept 20-22 Plaza Art Fair, Country Club Plaza...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Batter Today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153595</id>
        <link href="https://www.baseballmusings.com/?p=153595"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T12:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, the top five remain the same in the Baseball Musings Batter Rankings. Aaron Judge and Juan Soto of the Yankees stand one and two respectively after a 6-0 win over the Guardians. Judge posted a one for three with a walk and a home run, while Soto experience a rare poor day, 0 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pinto@baseballmusings.com (David Pinto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fact-checking, unburdened by what has been]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cjr.org/?p=102416</id>
        <link href="https://www.cjr.org/the_media_today/dnc_fact_checking_harris_speech.php"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T12:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was the final day of the Democratic National Convention in Chicago, and social media was abuzz with rumors of a surprise guest. Would it be Beyoncé or Taylor Swift? What about Mitt Romney or George W. Bush? Or the drug baron El Chapo, or the viral Olympic breakdancer Raygun? Okay, so the last two […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Allsop</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thank You, Thank You, Thank You Friends, From Your Wonkette]]></title>
        <id>https://www.wonkette.com/p/thank-you-thank-you-thank-you-friends</id>
        <link href="https://www.wonkette.com/p/thank-you-thank-you-thank-you-friends"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T12:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wonkette accepts the nomination *of your hearts*.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dominic Gwinn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top of the Order: Jordan Montgomery’s Option Transforms Arizona’s Offseason]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=444834</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/top-of-the-order-jordan-montgomerys-option-transforms-arizonas-offseason/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T12:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 31-year-old lefty has been bad this season. That’s a big deal for the Diamondbacks’ 2025 payroll.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Becker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 8 Most Absurd Moments of the 2024 Campaign (So Far)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.teenvogue.com/story/most-absurd-moments-2024-election</id>
        <link href="https://www.teenvogue.com/story/most-absurd-moments-2024-election"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From couch jokes to dead bears.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Breaking US, World &amp; College News | Teen Vogue | Teen Vogue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Media reaction to Kamala Harris’ acceptance speech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.poynter.org/?p=1120832</id>
        <link href="https://www.poynter.org/commentary/2024/media-reaction-kamala-harris-dnc-acceptance-speech/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris accepted the Democratic nomination for president on Thursday night. It was a historic moment. Harris became the first woman of color to become a major party’s nominee for […]
The post Media reaction to Kamala Harris’ acceptance speech appeared first on Poynter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fact check: How accurate was Kamala Harris’ 2024 DNC speech in Chicago?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.poynter.org/?p=1120847</id>
        <link href="https://www.poynter.org/fact-checking/2024/fact-check-how-accurate-was-kamala-harris-2024-dnc-speech-in-chicago/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHICAGO — Reflecting Democrats’ optimism that the presidential race has shifted in their favor over the past month, Vice President Kamala Harris formally accepted the Democratic presidential nomination. Harris is the […]
The post Fact check: How accurate was Kamala Harris’ 2024 DNC speech in Chicago? appeared first on Poynter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PolitiFact</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roman Flügel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/roman-flugel</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/roman-flugel"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T07:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>