<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-08-11T01:44:13.514Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Victoria Mboko Is Here To Break Brains]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=198019</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/victoria-mboko-is-here-to-break-brains"/>
        <updated>2025-08-10T15:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elena Rybakina must have figured she had the match won. She’d just battered 18-year-old Victoria Mboko in a 25-shot rally late in their Montreal semifinal, sending her sprinting from corner to corner until Mboko’s desperate lob drifted long. Mboko hunched over in exhaustion afterwards, her racket pressed hard into the ground as a crutch. Losing a miserable point like this, reminiscent of the godforsaken PACER test, typically comes with a hangover. The fatigued player often pulls the cord early in the rally in a desperate bid to get their breath back and misses by a mile, or produces a meatball drop shot. The score here was tied—4-all in the do-or-die third-set tiebreak—but Rybakina had all the momentum and a seemingly significant fitness advantage. 
So I thought. At 4-all, Mboko clobbered four forehands, but coherently rather than desperately. The last one tagged the sideline for a winner. Mboko grabbed the next two points as well to win the match, leaving my tennis logic in tatters. Rybakina’s epic rally just a minute earlier had somehow worked against her, proving the last point she would win rather than the boon I’d expected. That wasn’t Mboko’s only miracle act of the match: She’d saved a match point half an hour earlier. This proved too much for my Tennis Channel stream, which promptly buckled under the tension and crashed. Mboko broke serve to prolong the match twice, outlasting both Rybakina and TC’s notorious technical difficulties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Owen Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why A Bunch Of Real Dicks Keep Throwing Fake Ones]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=198002</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-a-bunch-of-real-dicks-keep-throwing-fake-ones"/>
        <updated>2025-08-10T14:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every misogynist joke poses a question to its female audience: Can you laugh along? Will you be chill or are you going to make a big deal out of this? Are you going to be a bitch about it? Arriving in the form of a dildo, the joke that is also the question becomes a double entendre: Can you take it?
The first time someone threw a sex toy onto the court, during a July 29 game between the Golden State Valkyries and the Atlanta Dream, many players were inclined to say Yes, we can laugh about this. Sydney Colson of the Indiana Fever joked about it on Twitter, as did Angel Reese. And why not? As a bizarre one-off, it’s easy enough to laugh. Dildos, especially the ones that aim for anatomical fidelity, are funny objects when they appear somewhere you don’t expect to see one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Jensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[And Just Like That… It’s Over]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=198005</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/and-just-like-that-its-over"/>
        <updated>2025-08-10T13:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s pretty common these days for a television show to hold its viewers in contempt. Most “big-hearted comedies” treat you like a child, most crime shows assume you are very stupid, most dramas take for granted that you are easily manipulated. It’s not unusual to feel like whoever wrote the show you’re watching hates you.
The Sex and the City sequel And Just Like That…, which HBO execs announced would be ending this Thursday after just three seasons, is different. It’s the rare show brave enough to hate the viewer a little bit, and its own characters so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Jensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday Notes: Jack Dreyer Is a Dodger With a Sneaky Heater and a “Bad Slider”]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=470172</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/sunday-notes-jack-dreyer-is-a-dodger-with-a-sneaky-heater-and-a-bad-slider/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-10T11:32:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus Hunter Brown and Noah Cameron on gophers, Jeff Montgomery on shaking Mike Macfarlane, Nic Wilson on Kyle Karros, facts and stats galore, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Laurila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[POLL results: Your Top 11 Movies That are Fun]]></title>
        <id>68964efc70a83e000179e25b</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/poll-results-your-top-11-movies-that-are-fun/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T23:22:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here as promised are the TOP ELEVEN films that are fun, with the number of votes received by each, as chosen by nearly 150 readers of Flaming Hydra in our recent poll from a list of 333 such films compiled by our contributors. 
After a trying week, we hope some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perfect employees / Happy pictures]]></title>
        <id>68963e5a70a83e000179e21b</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-378/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T23:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Saward on robots, slaves, and robot slavers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Naked Game]]></title>
        <id>6896509470a83e000179e268</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-naked-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T23:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a great many things that might send you howling into insanity. Israel’s ongoing carnival of perverted and psychotic violence, either gleefully facilitated or strategically ignored by your government. Your college, hosting and financing avant-garde sting operations where state trooper burnouts chase student protestors into coffeeshops. The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Saward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HYDRANYM No. 11: Vote!]]></title>
        <id>68966d4270a83e000179e2f3</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hydranym-no-11-vote/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T23:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by The Editors

Apologies for our tardiness, players of HYDRANYM! The 21 best entries from Game No. 11 are ready for your perusal, on the theme of
ISSUE
HYDRANYM is the Creative Writing word game especially for Flaming Hydra subscribers (RULES appear below). Join in by subscribing! It’s]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Notes]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197969</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/programming-notes-7"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T19:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! We’re about to close up shop for the week, but before we park up our vans and lock up our warehouse, I must relay some precious information to you. Next week, the Defector staff will be convening for our annual Business and Innovation Summit, which means we will once again be leaving you in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Media Bias Wars Are Over]]></title>
        <id>6896407483c87b0001892eaf</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/the-media-bias-wars-are-over/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T19:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American right's conquering of CBS is the product of generations of bad-faith complaining]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Well Look At That, It’s Time To Chat With The Defector Staff Again]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197967</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/well-look-at-that-its-time-to-chat-with-the-defector-staff-again"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! It's Friday afternoon and we are ready to chat with our pals. Hit us with your best questions below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Bobby Dalbec To Minor League Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=863317</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/08/royals-sign-bobby-dalbec-to-minor-league-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T17:42:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced, via their official player development account, that they have signed infielder/outfielder Bobby Dalbec to a minor league contract. He opted out of a minor league deal with the Brewers last week. He will presumably join Triple-A Omaha in the coming days. The book on Dalbec is well known around baseball at this…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poll: Who Had The Best Deadline In The AL Central?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=863287</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/08/poll-who-had-the-best-deadline-in-the-al-central.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T17:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trade deadline has come and gone. While trade season was slow to get started this year, when all was said and done, there were several dozen trades made in a flurry of movement over the final few days before the deadline arrived. The full impact of these trades won’t be known for years to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You’re Invited To Defector’s Fifth Birthday Party And Also Some Baseball Games]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197923</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/youre-invited-to-defectors-fifth-birthday-party-and-also-some-baseball-games"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T16:21:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defector started publishing blogs on September 10, 2020. We are somehow mere weeks away from our fifth anniversary. To celebrate, Defector is throwing a birthday party at Union Pool in Williamsburg on Wednesday Sept. 10, 2025. We’ll have the run of the place, with musical performances in the back room by Avery Friedman and Speedy […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: Indianapolis Colts]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197852</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-indianapolis-colts"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T16:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the Indianapolis. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the Indianapolis Colts. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: Indianapolis Colts, like it says in the intro.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Put Down Your Phone And Read A Book]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197855</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-to-put-down-your-phone-and-read-a-book"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T15:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Ask The Book Doctor, a recurring series about books and reading them.
The beautiful shiny phone is killing us. We all know it, but there it is. We want it. It is made to keep us captivated. We are moths to its flame. Often, when I am around people I love, and one of us is looking at our phone, the other will say "What's happening on your phone?" This is embarrassing. It is so rare that anything is happening on the phone. About 99 percent of the time, the other person says "nothing," and puts their phone down. I see this in people in every generation. No one is immune.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How College Mascots Conceal Their Identity And Their Ass]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197857</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-college-mascots-conceal-their-identity-and-their-ass"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T14:14:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This piece was originally published on FOIAball, a new publication covering college football programs using this country’s robust Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) laws. If you like this story, consider becoming a FOIAball subscriber and receive a 33 percent early bird discount.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Covucci</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lamest Members Of Society Claim Responsibility For WNBA Dildo-Throwing Epidemic]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197902</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lamest-members-of-society-claim-responsibility-for-wnba-dildo-throwing-epidemic"/>
        <updated>2025-08-08T13:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People keep throwing dildos onto the court at WNBA games, which is an incredibly wack trend even before you hear who is taking credit for it: Crypto bros.
On Wednesday, a powerful loser and crypto enthusiast who calls himself Lt. Daldo Raine—you may have just instinctively reached for a blunt object—spoke to ESPN's Katie Barnes and claimed that he and his fellow crypto shitheads have been orchestrating recent dildo tosses at WNBA games for the sake of pumping their meme coin. "We wanted to really make memes funny again," he told Barnes. Mission not accomplished, my friend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poultry politics / Soul music]]></title>
        <id>6894fcd770a83e000179cb5d</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-377/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T22:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Felipe De La Hoz on risk assessment, and piano lessons with Misha Angrist]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Change]]></title>
        <id>6894df9870a83e000179ca9e</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/key-change/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T22:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last fall, in a dark club a couple of hours before showtime, I accosted my future piano teacher—an affable, clean-living hippie who spent five years making sublime music as part of my favorite local (and perhaps favorite ever) band, who were celebrating their 20th anniversary that night. I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Misha Angrist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Play Chicken and Win]]></title>
        <id>6894f22d70a83e000179caf2</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/play-chicken-and-win/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T22:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The unambiguous clarity of U.S. District Judge James Boasberg’s mid-March order for the Trump administration to turn back El Salvador-bound deportation flights—planes filled with people removed under an absurd Alien Enemies Act proclamation—only made Trump’s noncompliance that much more nakedly obvious.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felipe De La Hoz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Very Fine Cheerwine, With Emma Baccellieri]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197734</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-very-fine-cheerwine-with-emma-baccellieri"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T20:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are only so many ways to describe a podcast, as regular readers of these little blogs already know. Because they are cut in two by our ad break, it is easy enough to mentally divide them; because they all begin with Drew's signature skronking vocal overture, they all have a shape. But what does it mean, really, to say that something like half of a podcast is given over to soda-related discourse, and that the other component parts are about going to a Marlins game, the demi-crisis in WNBA officiating, and also a frank discussion about the frustration of duffing the preparation of a familiar recipe? You can put all that together and reach 100 percent of a podcast and 63 minutes, but also those things do not, on their face, fit together at all. I realize that. And yet:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josh Naylor Is So Slow That Nobody Can Catch Him]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197779</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/josh-naylor-is-so-slow-that-nobody-can-catch-him"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T19:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josh Naylor is slow. Not slow in the way that catchers are considered slow by default, or how some tall lanky guys seemingly can't get their legs moving, or even slow in the way that Kyle Schwarber is. Josh Naylor is third-percentile sprint speed slow. Josh Naylor is the 16th-slowest guy in baseball, and the third-slowest first baseman—he'll beat Triston Casas and Rowdy Tellez in a footrace, but if you put him against a fast shortstop like Trea Turner, he's never winning.
But if you're only counting stolen bases, it's a different story. Turner currently has 25 stolen bases this year, on pace for a very respectable 35-steal season. He has been caught stealing six times, for a roughly 80 percent success rate, which satisfies the heuristic—though it is only a heuristic—of the 70 percent breakeven point. Not shabby at all! Bobby Witt Jr. has 30 stolen bases on the season and has been caught stealing seven times, for a roughly 81 percent success rate. Again, that's about what you'd expect. Meanwhile, Naylor has 21 stolen bases on the season and has been caught stealing only twice, for an absurd 91 percent success rate. Those are Oneil Cruz numbers, with the caveat that Cruz has attempted to steal 15 more times than Naylor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: Miami Dolphins]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197815</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-miami-dolphins"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T18:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the Dolphins. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the Dolphins. This 2024 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: Miami Dolphins]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Tanier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Seven Gallons of Milk in the Pocket Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/the-seven-gallons-of-milk-in-the-pocket-challenge-d7a7</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/the-seven-gallons-of-milk-in-the-pocket-challenge-d7a7"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T18:33:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Holy moly, me oh my.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Built In Birmingham’ Can’t Save Tom Brady From Himself]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197742</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/built-in-birmingham-cant-save-tom-brady-from-himself"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T18:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Brady may be incredibly famous, obscenely successful, and (formerly?) outrageously handsome, but he has never been cool. This is a plain fact, one that Patriots fans like myself overlooked during his tenure there and one that Patriots haters loved to mock him for. Since his retirement, Brady has lost the magnetic appeal of his abilities with the ball in his hands, which has made stark his absent coolness. His commentary stint has been mediocre at best and awful at worst, and his unwavering but erroneous belief in his own charm is fully insufferable without the touchdowns and wins to mask it. In place of any kind of recognizably human personality, there is nothing but coach speak and corporate speak and brand consciousness, which makes it close to impossible for him to forge any kind of connection with an audience when he's not wearing pads. That hasn't stopped him from trying, which brings us to soccer.
Built in Birmingham: Brady & The Blues is the latest attempt to humanize and propagandize Brady, and in a perverse way it succeeds at painting what feels like a true portrait of the former quarterback-turned-commentator-and-owner. This is not to say that the show succeeds in making Brady a compelling figure, or even a sympathetic one. Instead, the show—which is terrible for a variety of reasons, almost all Brady-related—proves what has been obvious for years: post-football Tom Brady is nothing but a platitude-spouting Robotron incapable of self-awareness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweating Through The Existential Angst Of A Las Vegas Table Tennis Tournament]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197684</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/sweating-through-the-existential-angst-of-a-las-vegas-table-tennis-tournament"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T15:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LAS VEGAS — From July 3-13, World Table Tennis staged a Grand Smash tournament in Las Vegas for the first time. Like the Grand Slams of tennis, the Grand Smashes sit atop WTT’s tournament hierarchy, and with $1.55 million in prizes and main draws of 64 top players, the Smash was the largest international table tennis event to take place in the United States.
Vegas is no stranger to big table tennis tournaments. The city often plays host to the U.S. Open, which is run by USA Table Tennis and features a handful of pros competing side by side with hundreds of amateurs. American players who have been to previous U.S. Opens arrived at the Grand Smash already familiar with the little hells that a tournament in Vegas can produce: blast-furnace heat and slot machine-choked hotels on the way to a convention center floor, undergirded by concrete so slick that players pour out drinking water to wet their soles between points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>E.Y. Zhao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Not Guess Wrong Against Mason Miller]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197741</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/better-not-guess-wrong-against-mason-miller"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T15:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you respond to a guy who's proven that he can crush your 103.9-mph fastball deep into left field for a four-bagger? Well, you don't throw him your 103.9-mph fastball; you dissolve him with your slider. That's how Mason Miller was able to begin his ninth-inning save on Wednesday night.
The Padres' big deadline add from not-Oakland was in the news for the wrong reason after Tuesday's game, when Diamondbacks DH Lourdes Gurriel Jr. tied the score in the eighth by making Miller's flameball the fastest pitch ever homered on (probably ever, but at least since they started keeping track of those things in 2008). San Diego recovered to win in extra innings, but it was hard to forget the fact that Miller's searing heat had been made to look so vincible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Player’s View: Pitchers Weigh in on Their Catch Play Partners (Some Are Nasty)]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=470014</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/players-view-pitchers-weigh-in-on-their-catch-play-partners-some-are-nasty/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T15:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Casual games of catch they're not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Laurila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Brief Adventures Of Wavy Dave]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197626</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-brief-adventures-of-wavy-dave"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T14:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone who ever met Wavy Dave and lived to tell the tale—which is, in point of fact, everyone who has ever met Wavy Dave—would tell you about his claw. It was big, that's for certain, but this was not unusual for male fiddler crabs, which wield one enormous front claw, much larger than its counterpart. This is what gets the the female fiddlers going: a large claw that can wave back and forth quickly; the kind of claw that sends a message. These major claws can comprise more than 30 percent of a male's total body mass, which is a big burden on such a little crab. But if a female likes the size and motion of a male's claw, she may enter his burrow and let him fertilize her eggs.
But Wavy Dave's large claw, according to those who've seen it, kept growing larger. On the first day he scuttled into town, his claw was nearly two inches from base to tip. But the next time he came 'round these parts, his claw was even bigger. If you'd had gotten close enough to measure it, you'd find it had grown to a whopping 2.7 inches, making it the largest major claw on record for the species Afruca tangeri. You might think twice before crossing Wavy Dave.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You Aware Of The Alan Dershowitz Martha’s Vineyard Pierogi Situation?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197541</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/are-you-aware-of-the-alan-dershowitz-marthas-vineyard-pierogi-situation"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T13:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is perhaps unfair to the rest of humanity to slot Alan Dershowitz in as a specific type of guy. He fits into a number of variously rancid cohorts: Inner Circle Jeffrey Epstein Associates; Celebrity Attorneys (Derogatory); People With "Harvard" As Their Personality; People With "Actually I Have Voted Democratic" As Their Personality; Podcaster. But the category into which he fits the most cleanly is more abstruse, and has less to do with anything Dershowitz has done or the (many) scary monsters and super-creeps that he has represented, than the way that Dershowitz himself is, and the uniquely grating hazard he represents.
So while it is true that Alan Dershowitz is quite literally someone who got into a huffy argument with a pierogi vendor at a farmer's market on Martha's Vineyard, was escorted from the premises by police, and subsequently threatened a lawsuit, it is also and more significantly true that Alan Dershowitz is exactly the sort of person who would do all those things, to the point where my first reaction upon hearing this news was trying to remember whether this was the first time he'd done it. And while I can now confirm that this was Dershowitz's first pierogi-specific Martha's Vineyard contretemps—as I was writing this, there was a second—there have been enough other things like it that it was a reasonable enough thing to be confused about. Give or take going on TV whenever anyone asks and writing books with titles like The Price Of Principle: Why Integrity Is Worth The Consequences, Guilt By Association: The Challenge Of Proving Innocence In The Age Of #MeToo, and Palestinianism: The Newest Attack On Peace And Human Rights And Democracy, this is just how Dershowitz spends his time—getting into weird public disputes and treating himself to outlandish takings of umbrage re: his seemingly very unhappy experience on Martha's Vineyard, where he has vacationed for 50 years, and then threatening lawsuits and recording emergency episodes of his delightfully named podcast, The Dershow, about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dummymander: A Manifestation of Bad Faith Politics]]></title>
        <id>6893ebda83c87b000189276d</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/the-dummymander-a-manifestation-of-bad-faith-politics/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T12:36:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's only so much gerrymandering a party can do before they fuck it up for themselves]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elusive future]]></title>
        <id>6893dd2070a83e000179a3ac</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-376/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T00:48:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What Kim Kelly couldn’t find on Facebook]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Facebook Used to Be]]></title>
        <id>6893c27870a83e000179a352</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/what-facebook-used-to-be/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T00:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was checking Instagram one last time before going offline last night, and a stray post from someone I don’t really talk to anymore alerted me that a man I once loved is dead. It was a cold way to learn such a thing. The news was already]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HYDRANYM No. 11]]></title>
        <id>6893f48070a83e000179b436</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hydranym-no-11/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-07T00:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cameron Brink Is Back And Ready To Swat]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197663</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cameron-brink-is-back-and-ready-to-swat"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T19:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh yeah, Cameron Brink! The Los Angeles Sparks’ No. 2 pick in 2024 last played in the WNBA over a year ago, when she tore her ACL in the first quarter of a game against the Sun. There's not really a convenient time for a torn ACL, but the timing of this one was rough: The injury happened just weeks before she was set to go to the Paris Olympics as a member of the U.S. 3x3 basketball team, an opportunity that once delighted her to the point of tears. It also cut short a promising rookie season in which she’d looked like she’d soon be among the best defensive players in the league. 
In the final days of July, some thrilling news popped up on the Sparks' injury report: Brink was upgraded from “out” to “doubtful” before a road game against the Liberty. The next game, against the Aces, she was “in.” She returned to play this month to fill a Defensive Player of the Year-sized hole on a talented but incomplete Sparks roster. On the very outside of the playoff picture with a 13-15 record, Los Angeles has heated up but could very much use some help from their young franchise star.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: Dallas Cowboys]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197650</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-dallas-cowboys"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T18:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the Dallas Cowboys. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the Dallas Cowboys. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: “I no longer want to be here.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mason Miller’s Balls Were Fast, But Lourdes Gurriel’s Dong Was Faster]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197646</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mason-millers-balls-were-fast-but-lourdes-gurriels-dong-was-faster"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T17:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are more intricate ways to measure a pitcher's talent and effectiveness than the digits on a radar gun, but none quite so visceral. The Padres acquired Mason Miller from the California Athletics because of the fact that he strikes out an absurd number of hitters on his fastball/slider combo. That fastball, however, is thrilling just on its own terms, because Miller throws it an average of 101 miles per hour. When you see a pitcher with that kind of cannon, watching the radar readings becomes its own sort of sport: Can he top 102? Can he do it again? Since every fan has traveled in a car with a speedometer at some point in their life, that data is far more comprehensible than, say, inches of break. And when you see a number like "104," there's not much more that needs to be said beyond "Whoa."
Miller's first outing at a Padre, last Friday, saw him start by allowing two hits but quickly clean them up with a K and a double play. Returning to the mound in the eighth inning on Tuesday against the Diamondbacks, with his team leading 5-3, his stuff was just as eye-popping. But the results were a little rockier. Miller got a line-out to right on his first pitch, and he used his slider four out of five pitches to get a strikeout on Ketel Marte. But then he struggled to tame his own strength as he walked Geraldo Perdomo on exclusively fastballs that went by in a blink. That brought Lourdes Gurriel Jr. to the plate, with the chance to tie the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Can’t Stop Thinking About The Underwater Waterslide Of Horror]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197658</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-cant-stop-thinking-about-the-underwater-waterslide-of-horror"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T16:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As summer marches on sweatily, and languid thoughts turn to relief, I am put in mind of the solution to all of our temperature-related troubles: the waterslide that kills you. Please send me down this slide immediately.
I am of course speaking of the Fly Over slide at the Duinrell amusement park in the Netherlands, the first and logically only waterslide that was entirely filled with water, forcing riders to hold their breath for the duration of the ride. Unlike boring, standard, "safe" waterslides, the water was not merely a lubricant to help riders go faster have "fun," but filled the tube to the brim and completely submerged anyone brave enough to ride it, and generated tangible anxiety in anyone who even heard about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Harrison Butker’s PAC Coffers Are As Empty As His Head]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197647</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/report-harrison-butkers-pac-coffers-are-as-empty-as-his-head"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T15:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harrison Butker, an NFL placekicker best known for his wide-right worldview, hoped to parlay clutch kicks into political clout. His plan is not working out. 
A report released yesterday by the investigative team at Open Secrets shows Butker’s fledgling political action committee, known as Upright, is having trouble getting any lift. The PAC’s recent filing with the Federal Election Commission oozed lots of malaise and showed little money. Through the end of June 2025, Butker’s PAC had taken in only $4,023 in contributions this year and had just $1,786.43 left in its coffers. And, according to Open Secrets, of the $7,400 Upright has spent, “none of it benefitted Republican political candidates, either through direct donations to candidate committees or via advertisements that boost Republicans or criticize Democrats.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN Now Partially Owned By Biggest League It Reports On]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197636</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/espn-now-partially-owned-by-biggest-league-it-reports-on"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T14:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN's position on the NFL is not unlike that of every other network with a significant sports presence, which is to say it scrubs where Roger Goodell says there's a stain. The football thing is the only provably and relentlessly bankable thing in the entire play-for-play diaspora, so ESPN is handing a 10 percent equity stake over to the league in exchange for the NFL Network, the RedZone channel, and other NFL media assets.
The long-awaited deal that subsumed ESPN's journalistic integrity, re: the NFL, is done. Alarm bells about diminished independence and the damage to journalistic integrity are ringing quite loudly, but in a diminishing number of circles. And besides, the days when anyone in ESPN's executive class are expected to care about any of that are long gone. ESPN is the cymbal-playing windup toy in the NFL's media orchestra, and that's just how ESPN president Jimmy Pitaro likes it. This, to appropriate a quote from prototypical owner-without-a-team Hyman Roth, is the business they've chosen, and being bed-partners is simply the logical extension of the way it works now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13 Things I Learned From The Larry King Estate Sale]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197278</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/13-things-i-learned-from-the-larry-king-estate-sale"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T14:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An estate sale gives you a chance to look inside a person’s life. Did they own nice silverware? Were they a hoarder of worthless little tchotchkes? Did they have a creepy doll collection? A normal and not that creepy doll collection? At the higher end, this can offer a window into a public figure’s private life. Maybe you realize an athlete needs money. Maybe you learn some movie star was actually a big dork and heavily into comics. Or maybe you find out that Larry King had a corporate-desk ornament hologram of Larry King.
King, the longtime infomercial pitchman and cable news presence, died in 2021. His heirs are finally getting rid of all his crap. The Larry King Collection is now at Julien’s Auctions, and there’s a lot there. Before he flogged loans on TV, King hosted a live talk show on CNN for 25 years on a set that looked suspiciously like the one he’d later use to sell fish oil pills. Larry King Live landed big interviews on non-Omega 3 topics with celebrities, politicians, and other newsmakers. The Larry King Cardiac Foundation’s website now directs to the spam URL clockwork-game.com, but he also did some charity work. He had public speaking engagements. He went to thousands of Dodgers games. People gave him lots of stuff. There really is a ton of crap to get rid of.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scared silly / Transcendent travel]]></title>
        <id>6892920170a83e0001798d85</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-375/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T01:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harry Siegel reckons with history, and Laurie Woolever takes flight]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Art for Art’s Sake]]></title>
        <id>6891268970a83e0001796c0b</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/art-for-arts-sake/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T01:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurie Woolever</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘History Is a Conspiracy,’ or, The Paranoid Suffer Twice]]></title>
        <id>689116cc70a83e0001796b26</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/history-is-a-conspiracy-or-the-paranoid-suffer-twice/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T01:22:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future wasn’t just foreseeable but foreseen; some selected and presently relevant excerpts from Richard Hofstadter’s 1965 essay on The Paranoid Style in American Politics as “time is forever running out.”

There is a style of mind, not always right-wing in its affiliations…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harry Siegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Jonathan Heasley To Minor League Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=863095</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/08/royals-sign-jonathan-heasley-to-minor-league-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-06T01:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals signed right-hander Jonathan Heasley to a minor league contract. The 28-year-old has not pitched in a game since being released by the White Sox at the end of March. Heasley returns to his original organization. K.C. selected him in the 13th round of the 2018 draft. The Oklahoma State product debuted three years later…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Chatterton Classes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/the-chatterton-classes-4440</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/the-chatterton-classes-4440"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T19:37:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We should know when to stop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aw Shit, My Favorite Genre Just Got Changed Forever]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197342</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/aw-shit-my-favorite-genre-just-got-changed-forever"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T19:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was scrolling the Steam store aimlessly a few Saturdays past, avoiding my various anxieties and responsibilities as a professional, when I happened upon a game whose banner appeared to be the old guy from Darkest Dungeon digging a hole (I wasn't looking very closely). Enticed by the prospect of hole-digging, I investigated further. It was a brand new point-and-click adventure called The Drifter, with a bleak art style and promises of a grand conspiracy to unwind. I never buy stuff at full price on a whim, but I made an exception this once.
The game tells the story of Mick Carter, the titular Drifter, and his attempt to return to his hometown and pay his respects to his recently departed mother. Mick is also homeless, has made a ton of terrible decisions leading up to the point where we meet him, and has caught a pretty rotten streak of luck as well. His circumstances are such that his major problems are often interrupted by very minor ones, which are nonetheless just as obstructive. How do you face your sister after all these years away? Well, first you have to find someone or something that will let you charge your dead phone, because you can't face your sister if you can't learn her address because your phone is dead. It does a lot of zooming in and out like this, big picture to small and back again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Bloom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Don’t Have To Let Big Allen Wrench Control Your Life]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197570</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/you-dont-have-to-let-big-allen-wrench-control-your-life"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T18:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. You can also read Drew over at SFGATE, and buy Drew’s books while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about loaded fries, USC football sucking shit, toothpaste, Lamar Jackson, and more.
Hey now, let’s all give a big round of applesauce to Albert Burneko for presiding over this column a week ago. I don’t think it’s hyperbole to say that Albert is our greatest living American, now and forever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is One Real Bad Baseball Swing]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197560</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/here-is-one-real-bad-baseball-swing"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T16:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's all that baseball fans can talk about this morning: the huge memorable swing of the bat at the narrative and emotional climax of Monday night's dramatic game in Arlington, Texas. An incredible, historic moment!
Allow me to set the scene: It's the bottom of the 10th inning, the ghost runner is stationed on second base, and into the box steps Rangers veteran Marcus Semien. On the mound to face him is Yankees reliever Jake Bird. The Yankees are in trouble, and not only because they had to give an important inning of work to someone recently acquired from the Colorado Rockies: Back on June 6, they were 16 games over .500 and had the second-best record in baseball, but they are presently foundering, beset by bullpen suckitude, horrendous defense, injuries to all the wrong dudes, and what is starting to look like more than a fair share of bad luck. They dropped six straight in mid-June and then another six straight in early July, and have lost 10 of 17 since the break, including a sweep over the weekend at the hands of the Miami Marlins. They are presently third in the AL East, and falling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: San Francisco 49ers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197551</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-san-francisco-49ers"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T16:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the San Francisco 49ers. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the San Francisco 49ers. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: San Francisco 49ers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street Journal Calls For Congressional Investigation Into Caitlin Clark Getting Fouled]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197549</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/wall-street-journal-calls-for-congressional-investigation-into-caitlin-clark-getting-fouled"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T15:35:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this point it's clear that the Caitlin Clark conversation, for lack of a better term, isn't going anywhere. Some things just become so ubiquitous and so useful as a culture-war cudgel that they can never be put down. You have to accept the fact that everyone is eventually going to get their swings in.
Let this process go on long enough, and you are guaranteed to see some things you never expected. The only utility that comes from typing "Caitlin Clark" into a search bar is potentially encountering a set of thoughts that you previously could not have imagined springing from a human mind. One day you live in a world where no professional sportswriter has ever taken umbrage with a league for not responding to three requests for comment about a player suffering a minor injury, and then the next you have to make sense of Christine Brennan doing just that. There's some rueful entertainment to be had in these moments, which is all I could take from the Wall Street Journal's unbelievably odd attempt at plugging into the Caitlin Clark discourse machine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ari Aster Wants You To Take The Bait]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197536</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ari-aster-wants-you-to-take-the-bait"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T13:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November 2020, the Washington Post ran a story with the headline “Shakespeare wrote King Lear during a plague. What great work will emerge from this pandemic?” It was a stupid question at the time, and five years on, a cursory survey of the cinematic output that deals in some way with COVID turns up very little of significance. The films range from the justly forgotten star-studded comedy The Bubble to the superb, though substantively unrelated, Zoom horror film Host. Mainly, filmmakers rely on shallow, obvious references to recognizable hallmarks: masks, social distancing, toilet paper hoarding, Fauci. This is inevitably shot through with a degree of gravity that, while understandable, treads a careful, deliberately inoffensive line. Perhaps it’s because those early years were also marked by massive political upheaval and what might be, politely, termed social breakdown that it’s so difficult to fully dramatize what was happening. 
Plus, no one wants to think about COVID anymore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auto responder / Working stiff]]></title>
        <id>6890b1f770a83e000179697c</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-374/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T00:23:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An epistemological crisis with Hamilton Nolan; Rax King on 'Boogie Nights']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can You Expect When You’re On Top?]]></title>
        <id>6890f19970a83e0001796a0a</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/what-can-you-expect-when-youre-on-top/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T00:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['Boogie Nights' reconsidered]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rax King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cars]]></title>
        <id>6891374170a83e0001796c90</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/cars/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-05T00:20:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s an issue a lot of people would like to sweep under the rug: Sometimes you call a car to take you to the airport and you put your bag in the trunk, and then you reach up to shut the trunk and the driver yells, “STOP!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamilton Nolan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twins Claim Thomas Hatch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=862935</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/08/twins-claim-thomas-hatch.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T22:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Twins claimed righty Thomas Hatch off waivers from the Royals, reports Dan Hayes of The Athletic. Kansas City had designated him for assignment over the weekend. The Twins subsequently announced the claim and added that the corresponding active roster move will be announced when Hatch reports to the team tomorrow. Minnesota had two vacancies on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heartbreaking: Ferrari Once Again Makes Two Men Lose Their Joie De Vivre]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197496</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/heartbreaking-ferrari-once-again-makes-two-men-lose-their-joie-de-vivre"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T19:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ferrari had a great weekend at the Hungarian Grand Prix, so long as you ignore the bad parts. After an upgrade package, the team has been on the rise. They are currently second in the Constructors' Championship, and that's factoring in their double disqualification in China earlier this year. During Saturday's qualifying session, Charles Leclerc even managed to steal pole position away from the McLarens (and, somehow, Aston Martins) by a margin of .026 seconds. "Today I don't understand anything in Formula 1," Leclerc said, expressing his surprise by the pole during an "extremely difficult" qualifying.
As long as you stop there, the sentiment is optimistic rather than ominous. And if you memory hole every other moment of the weekend, you will forget Lewis Hamilton's Q2 exit—material evidence of Ferrari's "extremely difficult" qualifying—and his shockingly despondent media comments after the fact. Every all-time great is bound to have some decline in form, but even factoring in the margins from his teammate this year, Hamilton's comments felt extreme. "I'm useless, absolutely useless," Hamilton said. Prompted to expound, Hamilton added, "The team, they have no problem. You've seen the car is on pole. So, they probably need to change driver."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Marlins Are Actually Doing Some Stuff]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197533</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-marlins-are-actually-doing-some-stuff"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T18:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a measure of the history of the Florida/Miami Marlins that Sunday feels like the third-biggest day in franchise history. It wasn't, but this is what happens when your franchise has two World Series victories and seven other playoff games in 33 years. That third spot on the podium remains very much available.
Still, you take your moments when you can, and this is the Miami Marlins' moment. The moment in question being when the Marlins swept the New York Yankees at home before 101,000-some-odd announced mammals over the weekend to get their once-dismal record to a deliciously mediocre .500, and in so doing moved within hailing distance of the final wild card spot. That last thing doesn't seem like much, and it probably isn't, but the Marlins' fan base has decided that the Yankees are their archrivals despite the fact that Yankees, who are in a different league, barely acknowledge that the Marlins even exist. Yankees fans weren't even sure the Marlins existed in 2003 when the Marlins beat the Yankees to win their last World Series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Copa América Femenina Final Had It All: Goals, Controversy, And Marta]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197501</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-copa-america-femenina-final-had-it-all-goals-controversy-and-marta"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T18:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If conventional wisdom holds that international tournament finals are often boring and conservatively played, the Copa América Femenina final between Brazil and Colombia was a glorious exception. Eight goals, an under-punished headbutt, four total comebacks, a returning legend contributing yet another legendary feat, a tense if not stellar penalty shootout ... Saturday's match in Quito, Ecuador had just about everything. The only thing it lacked was an upset, as the favored Brazil fought back time and time again to win the shootout, lifting its fifth straight Copa trophy.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dvj3RGopxE4]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marlins Claim Joey Wiemer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=862873</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/08/marlins-claim-joey-wiemer-waivers-royals.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T17:42:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Marlins have claimed outfielder Joey Wiemer off waivers from the Royals and optioned him to Triple-A Jacksonville, reports Craig Mish of SportsGrid and the Miami Herald. He was designated for assignment by Kansas City last week. Wiemer, 26, once ranked among the game’s top 100 prospects during his time in the Brewers system. The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats Might Finally Be Tired Of Losing]]></title>
        <id>6890ce36921837000142036b</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/democrats-might-finally-be-tired-of-losing/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T16:59:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hardball tactics have to be met with hardball tactics, no matter what the norms adorers say]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s The Big Deal About Jhoan Durán’s Entrance?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197505</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/whats-the-big-deal-about-jhoan-durans-entrance"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T15:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jhoan Durán was one of the prizes of a busy trade deadline, moving from the suddenly tanking Twins to a Phillies team in a dogfight with the very best of the National League. Durán is not just an electric arm, but a very marketable one, as well. Along with his 2.01 ERA in 49 games with Minnesota, the closer arrived in Pennsylvania with his own A/V package. According to The Athletic, the Twins sent over all the assets that the Phillies would need to recreate the entrance that Durán's old club gave him at their home field. That package includes lights, music, and an animation of a tarantula (Durántula) crawling across a video board.
"We collectively thought, ‘This is for the greater good of baseball fans,’" said Dustin Morse, Twins VP of communications. "This is a fun atmosphere. All baseball fans should get to see it and experience it. We all know that the atmosphere at Citizens Bank is already nuts. This would go over well."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fifty-Six Hits Is Too Damn Many]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197477</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/fifty-six-hits-is-too-damn-many"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T15:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miguel Cairo, interim manager for the woebegone Washington Nationals, recently referred to the Milwaukee Brewers as a "pain-in-the-butt team." He'd just watched the Brewers rough up Washington's helpless pitchers in the first game of a weekend series, and struggled to put his observations into admiring terms. "They make contact. They put the ball in play. They find a way to create runs." It's all true: The Brewers have the best team batting average and on-base percentage in the National League; they don't do a lot of slugging but they swipe a lot of bases, and they will absolutely doink and small-ball your ass all the way to death. Per Statcast, the Brewers have the lowest barrel percentage and the third-lowest average exit velocity in all of baseball. These guys love to hit a baseball so softly that the bat makes a sound like the snapping of a stale breadstick and the ball flies into the outfield grass at velocities that would not earn a speeding ticket on any interstate highway in America.
Who am I to judge? After all, it works: The Brewers today boast the best record in all of baseball. If their offense is broadly outperforming the quality of the balls they put in play—Statcast says their expected weighted on-base average on contact is fourth worst in the majors, and their team batted ball profile is remarkably unsexy—I am inclined to credit them with making some of their own luck. They're disciplined: They see a lot of pitches, and they don't chase, and because they're very zippy on the bases they put a lot of pressure on an opposing defense. For a team like the Nationals, one that runs out a bunch of sad-sack juiceless pitch-to-contact bozos and backs them with deeply lousy defense, the Brewers are basically a nightmare. Well-placed soft liners accumulate at what certainly feels like an exponential rate, overwhelming your very sorry and helpless baseball team the way flood debris conquers the pilings of a flimsy old bridge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, August 4: Big Finish]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197392</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-august-4-big-finish"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your long wait for the Monday crossword has come to an end. This week's puzzle was constructed by Mat Holmes and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Mat lives in Maine and is a Portland Hearts of Pine fan. Mat is psyched to be back in Defector and you can look for his puzzles coming soon at AVCX, Universal, Spyscape, and the Los Angeles Times. 
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: Chicago Bears]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197494</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-chicago-bears"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T14:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the Chicago Bears. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the Chicago Bears. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: Chicago Bears.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Tanier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kiyoshi Kurosawa’s Visions Of Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197479</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/kiyoshi-kurosawas-visions-of-hell"/>
        <updated>2025-08-04T13:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A computer screen is a mirror, a conduit, a threshold, and a void. We peer into them for work, insight, entertainment, communication, companionship, and we peer for so long that the outside world comes to seem like an addendum, an antechamber of the vision granted by the screen. “The internet has many potentials,” says the Japanese master filmmaker Kiyoshi Kurosawa, “and one of them is this ability to amplify what’s inside us.” Any desire, impulse, resentment, or prejudice: Like the characters in those myths of self-obsession told around the world, we gaze into our reflection, and disappear.
In his new film Cloud, those who touch this void become it, a game of annihilation where everyone loses. At the start, Yoshii (Masaki Suda) is hustling a small business owner for the last of his merchandise. The man has a sob story—he invented a medical device and went bankrupt—but Yoshii isn’t interested. He pays bottom dollar for the last of the inventory, and packs them into a rental truck.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Rubsam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLB’s Speedway Classic Featured Only A Mild Amount Of Mayhem! Mayhem! Mayhem!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197458</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mlbs-speedway-classic-featured-only-a-mild-amount-of-mayhem-mayhem-mayhem"/>
        <updated>2025-08-03T21:13:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Braves and Reds finally got back to baseball at the Bristol Motor Speedway in Tennessee, even if it took them until Sunday! Sunday! Sunday! The game was originally scheduled for Saturday, but it began to rain late in the afternoon. After a long delay and an aborted start, the “Speedway Classic” resumed at 1 p.m. today, and ended with a 4-2 Atlanta victory.
A record crowd was expected. There was pregame pomp and circumstance featuring both Pitbull and Tim McGraw. Then the weather kicked in. The game was delayed for 2 hours and 17 minutes while it rained. When it resumed, the teams recorded four total outs before the game was pushed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A WNBA Team In Boston Seems Like A No-Brainer]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197442</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-wnba-team-in-boston-seems-like-a-no-brainer"/>
        <updated>2025-08-03T18:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The days of WNBA basketball in Uncasville could be numbered. According to Gary Washburn of the Boston Globe, Boston Celtics minority owner Steve Pagliuca has agreed to a deal with the Mohegan Tribe to purchase the Connecticut Sun, and he has aspirations to relocate the team. I bet you can guess where.
Per Washburn's report, Pagliuca's offer is for $325 million, which would be $75 million more than the price for a WNBA expansion team these days. If approved, it would be the most expensive sale for a professional women's sports team. On top of that amount, Pagliuca would earmark $100 million for a new practice facility to be built in Boston. The Sun would have their games in TD Garden by 2027, even if that meant spending the early part of their season in Rhode Island to get around any playoff schedules for the Bruins or Celtics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baby Racer Stunts On Competitors By Standing Up And Walking]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197441</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/baby-racer-stunts-on-competitors-by-standing-up-and-walking"/>
        <updated>2025-08-03T16:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Minnesota Lynx absolutely obliterated the Las Vegas Aces on Saturday, 111-58—the 53-point victory breaking a 1998 record for the biggest road win in WNBA history. While Aces fans didn't get much of a showing from the home team, they were treated to a better effort from the contestants of the halftime baby race.
The baby race is the best: a game in which confused infants attempt to crawl to a parent at the other end of a court. As halftime shows go, it’s up there with Red Panda, little kids playing basketball, and either of the two guys I’ve seen who balance things on their chin. (I prefer Amazing Tyler to the Amazing Chin Balancer.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cowboys’ Annual Contract Stalemate Has A Fun New Twist]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197433</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-cowboys-annual-contract-stalemate-has-a-fun-new-twist"/>
        <updated>2025-08-03T13:59:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerry Jones has yet to find a contract negotiation he won't drag out. Since 2023, the Dallas Cowboys owner has run the same routine with star players Zack Martin, CeeDee Lamb, and Dak Prescott: Lowball, refuse to budge in public, then end up paying more at the last minute. This recurring saga livens up the period before the season begins, and it's certainly more compelling than any of the Cowboys' recent playoff runs.
But this year's edition, featuring Micah Parsons, has taken an interesting turn. The Pro Bowl defensive end chose not to drag out this process until the start of September. On Friday, he publicly requested a trade as he explained his frustration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minor MLB Transactions: 8/2/25]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=862742</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/08/minor-mlb-transactions-8-2-25.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-03T03:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s the latest on a trio of players who were recently designated for assignment. All information is courtesy of the transactions log on that respective player’s MLB.com profile page. Veteran southpaw Rich Hill has elected free agency after being DFA’d by the Royals earlier this week. Hill, 45, is the oldest active big leaguer and held…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Designate Thomas Hatch For Assignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=862625</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/08/royals-designate-thomas-hatch-for-assignment-2.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-02T15:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals activated recent trade acquisitions Bailey Falter and Ryan Bergert this morning, ahead of their afternoon matchup with the Blue Jays. To make room on the roster, Jonathan Bowlan was optioned to Triple-A, while Thomas Hatch was designated for assignment. In additional news, the team also announced that Michael Massey has been returned from…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leo Morgenstern</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Be cool / Stay dry]]></title>
        <id>688d169b1a5c3900016b0fdb</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-373/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T22:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amy Chu’s surprising holiday destination, and a new story from Miles Klee and Mads Gobbo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ambassadors]]></title>
        <id>688d05291a5c3900016b0f72</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-ambassadors/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T22:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I inspected the water’s surface for scum, leaning slightly to block the light, pressing two fingers against my forehead to see if this time they might sink through the skull. There would be a dinner party next to the pool, at the wrought-iron patio table Georgia had had]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miles Klee  and Mads Gobbo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Window Unit Wanderer]]></title>
        <id>688cf10a1a5c3900016b0ee7</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/688cf10a1a5c3900016b0ee7/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T22:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salutations, weary travelers! Camoot here. I created my travel blog, The Window Unit Wanderer, to inspire solo travelers who want to follow their wanderlust to wherever the window unit blows. Here are my top five places to visit, including tips on how you can turn every day into a vacation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Chu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instant Expert On: The Economy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/instant-expert-on-the-economy-2ae3</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/instant-expert-on-the-economy-2ae3"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T21:09:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING—HUGE BBQ DEBATE EXPERTISE BEAT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jerry Dipoto Will Never Stop Doing Jerry Dipoto Things]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197378</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jerry-dipoto-will-never-stop-doing-jerry-dipoto-things"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T17:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the 2023 season, when the Mariners narrowly missed out on the playoffs despite having 90 percent odds of making it at the start of September, Jerry Dipoto traded Eugenio Suárez to the Arizona Diamondbacks in exchange for relief pitcher Carlos Vargas and White Sox legend Seby Zavala. The decision was, ostensibly, to trot out a lineup that struck out less often—Suarez's 214 strikeouts led the league. A fine explanation. Without it, the trade would have resembled a salary dump. Unrelatedly, this was also the offseason when Dipoto set his famous goal of winning 54 percent of games in a season.
Never mind that strikeout rates aren't correlated with raw offensive production. They certainly don't look very nice, and why not build a team for aesthetics if you aren't going to build one to win? If cutting down on strikeouts was the goal, trading away Suárez didn't immediately do the trick. The Mariners' overall strikeout rate went from 25.9 percent in 2023, or second-worst in the league, to 26.8 percent in 2024, which tied for worst in the league. At least the Mariners have improved in 2025—their 23.0 percent is only ninth-worst in MLB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: New Orleans Saints]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197344</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-new-orleans-saints"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T16:41:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the New Orleans Saints. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the New Orleans Saints. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: New Orleans Saints.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Emmanuel Clase Market Is Perhaps Understandably Bearish]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197298</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-emmanuel-clase-market-is-perhaps-understandably-bearish"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T15:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emmanuel Clase's paid leave has screwed up some plans. The news that the All-Star closer is involved in MLB’s sports betting investigation “did not simply deprive the Cleveland Guardians of their top trade chip,” The Athletic’s Ken Rosenthal reports, but also “ended any chance of the Guardians becoming a buyer.” Officially in sell mode, and without the guy expected to net a haul in a hot reliever market, the team flipped ace Shane Bieber to the Blue Jays and Paul Sewald to the Detroit Tigers on Thursday, and reportedly shopped around Gold Glove outfielder Steven Kwan.
Guardians execs were not the only ones with a lot staked on Clase. He’s one of seven baseball players who signed an agreement with the company Finlete, which allows fans to purchase shares in a player’s future earnings. The concept is a variation on the income-sharing agreements some young athletes sign to guard against career uncertainty, promising an investment firm a percentage of their future earnings in exchange for a cash advance. Big League Advance, now doing business as Big League Advantage, might be the best known of these firms: Fernando Tatis Jr. recently sued BLA, accusing them of using “exploitative, predatory business practices” when they signed him to one of these contracts at age 17. Overwhelmingly, the players signing income-sharing agreements are young Latin-American players, who are able to sign with MLB teams at a younger age and tend to receive lower signing bonuses than their drafted U.S.-born counterparts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Make Smart, Marginal Upgrades]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=469548</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/royals-make-smart-marginal-upgrades/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T15:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bailey Falter and Mike Yastrzemski fill key holes on the big league roster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Rosen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Journey With Lady Gaga Is Ever Wasted]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197214</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/no-journey-with-lady-gaga-is-ever-wasted"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T14:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to run the following tally for famous people with whom I shared a birthday: Vince Vaughn, also tall, famously made a movie where Las Vegas plays a big role; the poet Ada Limón, not so tall, whom I only learned of after high school, not that my friends at the time would have cared anyway; and Lady Gaga, not tall at all (see: her documentary Gaga: Five Foot Two), famously one of the few pop stars who loves Vegas and seems to take it on its own terms. To this day, at the mention of any of these people, I mutter “Birthday bestie.”
I believe we are all linked in some way, but reality has yet to bear this out. Once, Vaughn was shooting a movie down the street from my job, but I never saw him. I’ve not met Limón, though I know other poets who know her. As for Lady Gaga, the closest I’ve gotten thus far was the second night of her Mayhem Ball tour, which started this month. I felt a thrill of vindication that she chose to start the tour here, though it’s not so surprising. Gaga and Vegas go hand in hand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Fall Guys’ And ‘Among Us’ Gave 2020 The Parties It Needed]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196996</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/fall-guys-and-among-us-gave-2020-the-parties-it-needed"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T14:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to The Backlog, a series in which we will take a look back at 12 games from 2020 that, in one way or another, had a lasting impact on the video game industry. 
The summer of 2020 was a strange one. I remember spending afternoons in a park by my apartment in Brooklyn, a park that had drawn circles in the fake grass six feet apart from each other. I saw friends there, sat on picnic blankets and drank out in public, and even got a ticket for it once like an idiot. It was a beautiful summer, as far as the weather went, and for every long walk I took, I could push down a bit of the existential paranoia that crept along day-by-day as the COVID pandemic raged on with only whispers of a future vaccine to ebb the tide of disease and death.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Padres And Twins Did The Absolute Most At The MLB Trade Deadline]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197339</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-padres-and-twins-did-the-absolute-most-at-the-mlb-trade-deadline"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T13:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathtakingly unhinged baseball executive A.J. Preller wasted a lot of time this week calling every other dealmaker in Major League Baseball when all he really had to do was make one call to Minneapolis. Derek Falvey, the head of ball ops with the Minnesota Twins was clearing out his entire showroom, and all Preller would have had to do in order to facilitate his annual restock of the San Diego Padres was say, "I'll be over in 15 minutes with a tour bus. Pack lunches for everyone you want to get rid of and we'll have them off the lot before drinks."
Sadly, it didn't work that way, if only for efficiency's sake. Still the deed was there to be done, and the gods know Falvey and Preller tried in their own separate ways to make Thursday’s MLB trade deadline one of the most ludicrous redeployment festivals in the history of human arbitrage. Both Preller and Falvey succeeded in their personal missions, but they got something like two-thirds of the league involved in the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>