<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-03-09T16:15:42.529Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Court Of Gold’ Is Brilliant When It Gets Specific]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182976</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/court-of-gold-is-brilliant-when-it-gets-specific"/>
        <updated>2025-03-09T14:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The willingness to embrace specificity is part of what distinguishes Court of Gold from the swelling canon of Netflix original sports programming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple me]]></title>
        <id>67cb4f3f2bb6620001520873</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-272/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T22:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Talia Lavin in the no-funhouse mirror]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Clone Wars]]></title>
        <id>67cb3cbb2bb6620001520842</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/my-clone-wars/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T22:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Talia Lavin

Illustration: Joe MacLeod
It’s never a good idea to search your own name online, but authors do it all the time—and by authors I mean me, a creature who, like Tinkerbell from Peter Pan, will instantly die without sufficient external acknowledgement. So, on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Talia Lavin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hot Whales In Your Area]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/hot-whales-in-your-area</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/hot-whales-in-your-area"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T20:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did they call you mad at the university? Then it's your day to shine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Draymond Green Pivots From Slander To Depraved Podcast Promo]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183453</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/draymond-green-pivots-from-slander-to-depraved-podcast-promo"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T18:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's some context for why Draymond Green followed up condolences with a status update on his donkey podcast, and it only makes him look worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Like A Dragon’ Breathed New Life Into The ‘Yakuza’ Series]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182540</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/like-a-dragon-breathed-new-life-into-the-yakuza-series"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T17:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to The Backlog, a series in which we will take a look back at 12 games from 2020 that, in one way or another, had a lasting impact on the video game industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixing a Hole While Teams Train This Spring To Stop the Central Clubs From Wondering What They Should Do]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=458448</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/fixing-a-hole-while-teams-train-this-spring-to-stop-the-central-clubs-from-wondering-what-they-should-do/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T17:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And it still really doesn’t matter if I’m wrong I’m right...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Szymborski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coups Aren’t What They Used To Be]]></title>
        <id>67cb0fbad4477f0001a1dca5</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/coups-arent-what-they-used-to-be/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T16:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no longer a singular bright line that countries cross between democracy and authoritarianism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Eephus’ Director Carson Lund On Baseball As A Way Of Being]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183332</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/eephus-director-carson-lund-on-baseball-as-a-way-of-being"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T15:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eephus, which opens theatrically in limited release beginning March 7, is “designed to break your heart.” Directed and co-written by Carson Lund in his feature debut, the film unfolds across the length of a single Sunday afternoon adult recreational baseball league between Adler’s Paint and the Riverdogs, beginning as the players get dressed in the parking lot and warm up with soft toss, continuing through nine innings of hamstring-testing hustle doubles and crushed cans of Narragansett, and ending as the October dusk fades to night. It’s the last game, and not just of the season: The field will soon be bulldozed to make way for a new elementary school.
Shot over the course of a month on a local field in Douglas, Mass., Eephus is something like the concentrated essence of baseball, packing in a season’s worth of sense memory—the saltiness of a sunflower seed shell, the weight of a batting donut, the greasiness of a streak of eye black—at the languid tempo of a second baseman holding up his index and pinkie finger for the right fielder after the second out of an inning. The banter ebbs and flows between baserunners and fielders, between teammates on either side of the dugout, alternately hotheaded and banal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Asch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired NOAA Budget Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183219</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-noaa-budget-analyst"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T15:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growing up, Sabrina Valenti felt like she was genetically predetermined to work for the government. Her dad's father was in the Navy. Her dad was in the Air Force. Two of her uncles served in the armed forces, one eventually moving to a job at NASA and the other leaving for the postal service. Her mom's father was a state senator in Maine. One of Valenti's sisters is a teacher, and the other works for a transit agency in a major American city. "I was going to work in the public sector, one way or another," Valenti said.
Valenti grew up in the Florida panhandle, where she witnessed Hurricane Katrina whip through the gulf. And she was in high school when the oil drilling rig Deepwater Horizon exploded and sank in the Gulf of Mexico, killing 11 workers and causing the largest offshore oil spill in U.S. history. During the spill, Valenti recalls seeing "no wake zone" signs everywhere to prevent boats' waves knocking tar balls ashore. Every day before school, Valenti would grab the newspaper from the front porch and see a photo of oil billowing out of a wellhead. For months, Valenti wondered if the paper would say that the well was finally capped. The spill was eventually contained after 87 days. "You're sitting there powerless, knowing that this oil is going to kill shorebirds and seabirds, that it's going to kill fish, that it's going to cause birth defects in dolphins," Valenti said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Live And Age In Rap Music]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183018</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/to-live-and-age-in-rap-music"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T14:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Listening Habits, a new column where I share the music I’ve been fixated on recently.
In the first quarter of the year, a number of the notable new rap albums have come from older rappers, many of whom were most relevant to me when I was a teenager in the 2000s. Some of these albums are more successful than others. One of the stronger efforts comes from 2 Chainz, the Alchemist, and (the much younger) Larry June, who released the collaborative album Life Is Beautiful last month. Here, Chainz and Larry make what could be called Yacht Rap over luxurious, though a little monotonous, Alchemist beats. In this same vein, we've gotten a new Busta Rhymes album, an album from Webbie and his son Tre Savage, and a new album from Jim Jones, fresh off beefing with Cam'ron online over old Dipset drama (again).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How “Ball Don’t Lie” Became More Than A Basketball Mantra]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183207</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-ball-dont-lie-became-more-than-a-basketball-mantra"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T14:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shorthand for the service of karmic justice, often invoked in a smug told-you-so tone, the words remain heard at all levels of the game, from playgrounds to pro arenas. But “Ball don’t lie” has evolved from being an aggrieved athlete’s on-court motto, and achieved wider cultural relevance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Prewitt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complicated victim / Simple plunder]]></title>
        <id>67c9f2be2bb662000151f55e</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-271/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T00:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arwa Mahdawi confronts crime(s), and Jennie Rose Halperin considers copyright shenanigans]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Solve a Murder: Part Two]]></title>
        <id>67ca1d642bb662000151f60d</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/how-to-solve-a-murder-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T00:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Arwa Mahdawi

In July 1996, 36-year-old Susan Walsh supposedly left her house in New Jersey and never came back. She is presumed dead but a body has never been found. This is part two of a series on my five-year investigation into her unsolved disappearance. You can find part]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arwa Mahdawi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Real Copyright Pirates]]></title>
        <id>67ca21362bb662000151f622</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-real-copyright-pirates/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T00:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Jennie Rose Halperin


In 2003, five major record labels sued Boston University graduate student Joel Tenenbaum for copyright infringement based on 30 songs he had shared on Kazaa. Tenenbaum fought back, and six years later the case went to trial; he lost, and a jury awarded the labels $675,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennie Rose Halperin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Live From The Bad Times, With Denny Carter]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183235</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/live-from-the-bad-times-with-denny-carter"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T21:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a general rule, I do not relisten to episodes of the podcast. I spend all day hearing my own voice, inside my head and out, and the idea of going back for more me is ... well, I was going to write horrifying, which seems harsh. I will just say it's not what I want. I would honestly love less me, if that option were available. But of all the episodes of the podcast that I have not relistened to, the one that we put out last November, in which Drew and the excellent sports-and-politics newsletter writer Denny Carter tried to get me pumped up for the election, is the one I have not relistened to the most. Not because it wasn't a good episode—I remember it as having a good number of laughs and an ideal 50/50 split between politics and not politics—but for reasons that are very obvious. We are, of course, wrong all the damn time on this podcast; it is something like our brand, give or take Talking About Lunch and sudden monologues about the Minnesota Vikings. But some ways of being wrong sting more than others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JJ Redick Invented A New Way To Defend Nikola Jokic, And It’s Working]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183311</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jj-redick-invented-a-new-way-to-defend-nikola-jokic-and-its-working"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T20:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you watch Kings–Nuggets last night? So did Nikola Jokic. The three-time MVP had one of his worst games of the season against the mediocre and shorthanded Kings, laboring to 22 points and 15 rebounds with seven turnovers and a relatively ghastly minus-seven. Jokic has been struggling a bit by his incredible standards since the all-star break, which is mostly due to opposing coaches borrowing a hilarious stratagem rolled out by Lakers coach JJ Redick in L.A.'s impressive blowout win over Denver two weeks ago. The scheme is simple: Deny Jokic the ball, at any cost, compromising every single other part of your defense if you have to. The scheme runs counter to almost every modern maxim of defense, yet it's working.
In practice, here's what it looked like against Sacramento. Jake LaRavia's only job in the clip below is to essentially box Jokic out, while Markelle Fultz and DeMar DeRozan give like 10 feet of space to Peyton Watson and Russell Westbrook in order to be able to double Jokic the second he gets the ball. You hear maxims like "Force the rest of the team to beat you!" all the time, but rarely do you see defenses contort themselves like this. The Kings keep all five guys within a foot of the paint for the duration of the play, and Westbrook was kind enough to give them what they wanted by running into a poorly considered midrange jumper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Small Gene Hackman Memory for You]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183272</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-small-gene-hackman-memory-for-you"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T19:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gene Hackman died last week. He was one of the greatest actors America has ever produced. A performer of near infinite utility, able to carry a film single-handedly (Hoosiers) or loom over it with just a few minutes of screen time (No Way Out). Ask a dozen people what their favorite Hackman performance was, and they’ll give you a dozen different answers, none of them wrong. Mine was Crimson Tide. Let me tell you why.
It was 1995. I’d just finished a disastrous freshman year of college that saw me transfer from one school to another at the turn of second semester. I was lonely, disappointed, and deeply unsettled. More important, my spine was fucking killing me. What I thought was some sort of hip pointer—to this day, I don’t actually know what a hip pointer is—turned out to be a blown disc in my back. I needed surgery to fix it. At the end of the school year, a doctor in Manhattan cut into my back, removed the piece of disc lodged against my spinal cord, and then stitched me back up. From there, my mom drove me all the way back to my folks’ house in Connecticut, where a long, manic summer of convalescence awaited me.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ah, Jeez: Goodbye Ball! Goodbye Again! Goodbye A Third Time!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183276</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ah-jeez-goodbye-ball-goodbye-again-goodbye-a-third-time"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T19:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baseball is a beautiful game. Sometimes, you get to watch your team perform incredible feats of athletic prowess while wearing tight pants, and sometimes you watch them give up back-back-to-back home runs. That's America's pastime, baby!
This chaotic state of life extends to managers, too. They're just like us! Take, for example, this spring training game that the Phillies played against the Tigers on Wednesday. In the bottom of the second, Phillies pitcher Jesús Luzardo loaded the bases with two outs. In the dugout, his manager Rob Thomson was on the air, wearing a pop-star microphone while a camera stared directly at him. As a result, we got to watch him watch Luzardo give up not one, not two, but three home runs on three consecutive pitches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liverpool Pulled Off The Heist Of The Season]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183265</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/liverpool-pulled-off-the-heist-of-the-season"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T18:19:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty-seven shots to two. Ten shots on target to one. A whopping 71 to 29 possession split. Hell, even on corners it was 14 to 2. Paris Saint-Germain hosted Liverpool in the first leg of the Champions League round of 16 on Wednesday, and thoroughly demolished what has been the best team in Europe this season. The stats were solidly in PSG's favor, as was the flow of the game, the kind that the phrase "one-way traffic" was invented for. In every way but one, this would indicate a dominant win for the Ligue 1 leaders. Unfortunately for the Parisiens, the one advantage they didn't enjoy is the only one that matters.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7REYuzGyswU]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cavaliers Are Going To Take Some Getting Used To]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183324</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-cavaliers-are-going-to-take-some-getting-used-to"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T17:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[America got its first unofficial glimpse at Adam Silver's definition of institutional despair on Wednesday night. Cleveland and Oklahoma City, back to back on national television—five hours of the future, including ads. We needn't tell you that your entertainment mileage may vary. The business considerations for a league whose best teams play in those sub-optimal markets are no one’s problem but Silver's and his network overlords, but the commissioner must be shitting a pewter tea set just thinking about it, and Disney the rest of the flatware.
In a league in which LeBron James and Stephen Curry and the Boston Celtics and New York Knicks continue to dominate thanks to some not-very-deeply buried biases, Wednesday’s glimpse into the new reality was illuminating. Lord knows the NBA tried. Example: during a review on an out-of-bounds play, referee Pat Fraher described the ruling by referring to Shai Gilgeous-Alexander, the league newest badass di tutti badasses, as "SGA"—the hardest of sells for a new big-name player by the weirdest of salesmen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Ovechkin Is Getting All The Help He Needs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183271</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/alex-ovechkin-is-getting-all-the-help-he-needs"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T17:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Midway through Wednesday night's 3-2 Capitals OT win over the Rangers, the two teams got mad enough to hurt each other with more than just goals. As the first of two second-period fights brewed, TNT analyst Darren Pang alerted the viewers: "Here we go, Wilson and Rempe."
Whoa, would have been one of many proper reactions to this news. Matt Rempe, the Rangers' big beautiful hammer on skates, against Tom Wilson, history's greatest villain? Two players who know the Department of Player Safety's disciplinary process as well as anyone? I can't imagine a more dangerous confrontation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What The Corrections Officer Strike Means To Incarcerated People Like Me]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183254</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-the-corrections-officer-strike-means-to-incarcerated-people-like-me"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T16:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Feb. 17, an illegal wildcat strike was initiated by corrections officers with the New York State Department of Corrections and Community Supervision (DOCCS). One of their primary demands is to repeal the Humane Alternatives to Long Term Solitary Confinement (HALT) Act. Though New York State has pursued mediation to reverse this work stoppage, including offering to temporarily suspend elements of the HALT Act, the majority of striking officers have yet to return to their posts, leaving the incarcerated population, including myself, locked down and surrounded by chaos. At least seven people have died behind bars since this began. According to eyewitness testimony, at least one of these deaths—that of 22 year old Messiah Nantwi—was caused by a brutal beating at the hands of corrections officers. Other deaths are reportedly due to medical neglect. It is also worth noting that the strike was initiated only three days before the much anticipated announcement of murder charges brought against a group of corrections officers from Marcy Correctional Facility over the death of Robert Brooks. 
As its name suggests, the HALT Act  was designed to ensure incarcerated individuals were treated in more humane ways. Choosing to focus on rehabilitating prisoners rather than continuously and excessively penalizing us, this act prioritizes both the physical and mental health of incarcerated individuals by increasing the amount of time we are permitted social interaction with each other and with our families, while also retaining access to productive programming, such as education and job training.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Pastore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Enough People Are Taking The Wallet Inspector Seriously]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183264</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/not-enough-people-are-taking-the-wallet-inspector-seriously"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T16:24:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a weird amount of overlap between the people who insist that we take climate experts seriously when they warn of big changes on the horizon, and people who refuse to take the wallet inspector seriously when he warns that there is a problem with their wallet that he must examine immediately. Huh! Interesting! Peculiar! I find it curious to say the least!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Not Be Bamboozled By The New Fluffy Mouse]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183066</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/do-not-be-bamboozled-by-the-new-fluffy-mouse"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T14:57:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I see it, there are a few unofficial laws of science journalism when it comes to covering new research. The first and most obvious is that outlets are more likely to cover a press release if it is accompanied by nice-looking, high-resolution photos, because these make readers more likely to click on the story. Outlets are even more likely to pick up the story if those photos are of a charismatic animal: a beloved pachyderm, a striking bird, a sweet little rodent. The second law is that well-funded companies can produce better press releases than most institutions, with galleries of photos, videos, and lists of experts who are just a call away, making these stories easier to write on a tight deadline. The third law is that many journalists are overworked and underpaid, sometimes racing to meet a quota. So when a lavishly produced press release about seemingly feel-good research drops into their lap, featuring an adorable critter as a cherry on top, it is easy to write a simple story, meaning an uncritical one.
All of these laws conspired this week after the biotechnology company Colossal Bioscience released their newly created "woolly mice," which the company describes as a mouse that has been gene-edited to have traits similar to those of woolly mammoths. I have previously written about the many logistical, ethical, and scientific problems with de-extinction, so I will only briefly say that de-extinction is a morally questionable gambit in a time when tens of thousands of species are threatened by extinction. I am thoroughly unconvinced by Colossal's argument that returning extinct species to modern-day habitats, which have considerably warmed since the mammoth went extinct, will make these ecosystems more resilient to climate change. Despite its colossal promises and frequent press releases announcing secondary plans to de-extinct other animals, the company appears more invested in raising capital than restoring an actual mammoth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women’s Sports Happened By Accident, And Could Be Taken Apart On Purpose]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182469</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/womens-sports-happened-by-accident-and-could-be-taken-apart-on-purpose"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T14:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Monday night, and I check my local TV listings to see what women's college basketball games are on. I make a note to catch all the big women's college gymnastics meets coming up on Friday. I dutifully add all the dates for my local NWSL team's games to my calendar. It seems and at some level just is incredibly normal to be watching women's sports at big stadiums and on TV, but I'm also old enough to know that all this progress is due not to moral clarity or some belated public awakening to how good women's sports can be, but to a pair of classic American forces: unintended consequences and bureaucracy.
Women's sports has always hung on by the thinnest of threads. They are not mentioned even once in the law that created them, and once the powers that be realized what that law had done, they went all the way up to the presidency to try and undo it. The NCAA objected to supporting women's sports, and searched for years to find a way out of that obligation. Even President Gerald R. Ford's office seemed concerned about those "women's organizations." Our country's perch atop global women's sports happened not because our leadership desired it, or even cared all that much about it, or held strong feelings about the place of women in society in general. It happened due to a collection of random factors all happening in a specific time and space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[History lessens]]></title>
        <id>67c8c92a2bb662000151e2fa</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-270/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-05T23:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jídé Salawu on the political memoir du jour]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An African Dictator’s Bestseller]]></title>
        <id>67c8bee52bb662000151e2d5</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/an-african-dictators-bestseller/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-05T23:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Jídé Salawu

Military dictator General Ibrahim Babangida
I grew up knowing the name of the military dictator General Ibrahim Babangida in my hilly hometown, Shao, one of several Northern Yoruba agrarian communities leading up to the River Niger. I spent my teenage years there, climbing hills]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jídé Salawu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fanatics And Ticketmaster Announce Plan To Get Even Worse, Together]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183193</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/fanatics-and-ticketmaster-announce-plan-to-get-even-worse-together"/>
        <updated>2025-03-05T20:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know those two companies you most associate with incompetence, miserable user experiences, and hostility toward their customers? Well, they're going to join forces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Bully The National Park Service?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183008</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-bully-the-national-park-service"/>
        <updated>2025-03-05T18:25:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Feb. 24, a surprising new directive filtered down from the U.S. Department of the Interior to ground-level workers at the National Park Service. Weird policy initiatives were by then a fact of life for workers in the federal government, who blew a couple of weeks immediately following Donald Trump's second inauguration frantically chasing DEI phantoms out of their agencies' contracts and charters, at the expense of operational priorities. Chaos is the new norm. "You always get these statements ahead of a transition, from agency leadership, where they say, 'Hey, it's a change in governance, a change of policy, it's going to be difficult, but we'll all get through it together,'" a veteran of the National Park Service described to Defector. "But then on Day One it was executive order after…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Jaguars GM Talks How He Looks]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183099</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/new-jaguars-gm-talks-how-he-looks"/>
        <updated>2025-03-05T17:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Jaguars general manager James Gladstone looks like every NFL owner’s great grandnephew. He looks like he just ordered employees at the NIH to email him “five things that made you hype today.” He looks like someone an NFL player would beat the shit out of after mistaking him for Ben Solak. He looks like he believes the future of global economics lies in Queefcoin. You get the idea.
But Gladstone arrives in Jacksonville with a decent pedigree, including a nine-year stint—did he start work after graduating from middle school?—in the Rams’ front office. The Rams are a good NFL organization. They have their shit together, so it would stand to reason that Gladstone, despite the remarkable amount of Charlottesville energy he gives off, would prove surprisingly eloquent up on the podium. Sean McVay is a young guy too, you know! Not every young is hopeless! Maybe this paperboy is just what the moribund Jaguars have always needed!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Love Watching Warm-Ups]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183148</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-love-watching-warm-ups"/>
        <updated>2025-03-05T16:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I first learned to appreciate warm-ups because of Michigan hoops. The football culture at that school was intense to the point where I had multiple panic attacks in that gigantic stadium, but the basketball arena felt something like home. If you got there early enough, on the one or two times a week that the men's team would play, you could sit right behind the bench, practically on the floor. I liked it so much more than football not only because of the decreased BAC and ambient hysteria but also for the way you could see the athletes as real people—your peers, really—and not just maize and blue gladiators. With the pep band playing familiar tunes—"I Want You Back" and "You Can Call Me Al" and so on—I could get lost in their preparations: the careful stretching-out of recent injuries, the slightly forbidden thrill of attempting a showy dunk or an ultra-long-range shot, the choreography of staff members each with their own small role to play, even if it was just fetching rebounds. It was an almost meditative way to settle in before the emotional stress to come.
I still make a point of arriving early enough to catch warm-ups—especially when I'm watching hockey, where the beauty of the skate-around a half-hour before the advertised start time carries the warmth of a religious ritual. On Tuesday, as the New York Islanders hosted the Winnipeg Jets, I was one of a very few in position to enjoy this routine—the lack of fans symbolic of an uninspiring season. But the empty seats did not portend a desolate night.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jimmy Johnson Retires From Retirement]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183089</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jimmy-johnson-retires-from-retirement"/>
        <updated>2025-03-05T15:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re familiar with Jimmy Johnson’s career arc, you know that few people in history have been more openly grateful to no longer be coaching. Johnson said as much publicly ever since leaving the profession back in 1999. My man wanted more time to fish, to hang out in the Florida Keys, and to pretend he enjoys being with his wife and children. So what does a thinking Hall of Famer do when he wants to chill, but also doesn’t mind making a few million per year on the side? You guessed it: He becomes a replacement-level yapper on television, until he doesn’t feel like doing it anymore.
“I’ve been thinking about it for the last four or five years and I’ve decided to retire from Fox. I’m going to miss it. I’m going to miss all the guys,” he said, while announcing his retirement on Colin Cowherd's show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LeBron Damn James]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183136</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lebron-damn-james"/>
        <updated>2025-03-05T14:05:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the perks of observing LeBron James's 22 NBA seasons is constantly being presented with new, concise ways to sum up the absurdity of that career. Here's one he gave us during last night's 136-115 win over the Pelicans: In a game where James went for 34-8-6 and became the first player in league history to score 50,000 combined postseason and regular-season points, his son played four minutes of garbage time and scored two points.
Give a night like that to any other NBA player navigating the downslope of his career, and it might land like a party. One last game in which the old man summons what remains of his guile and athleticism to remind people that he really used to be like that. Michael Jordan spent the last years of his career sweating out turnaround jumpers in Washington for the sake of chasing nights like these. For LeBron James, who is 40 years old, Tuesday night was just another routine game in what might be the most impressive season of this guy's career.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ball leaguers / Bald eagles]]></title>
        <id>67c77ff41901c800015de619</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-269/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T23:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A.J. Daulerio considers coaching, Anna Merlan watches bird watchers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can I Teach These Young Boys?]]></title>
        <id>67c738c81901c800015de54a</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/what-can-i-teach-these-young-boys/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T23:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by A.J. Daulerio

Little League 1989
My seven-year-old began Little League a few weeks ago, and even though the thought of him competing with anyone at this age infuriates me, I have made peace with the idea that maybe, perhaps, it is time he does realize that the world]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>A.J. Daulerio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pip Watch]]></title>
        <id>67c7789e1901c800015de5e5</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/pip-watch/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T23:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Anna Merlan
Image: Friends of Big Bear Valley
For the past few days, thousands of people have been watching a live camera aimed at a bald eagle nest in Big Bear Valley, California, where a mated pair named Jackie and Shadow are sitting on three eggs. While the nest]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Merlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bad Opinions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/bad-opinions</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/bad-opinions"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T21:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I give up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Not A Real NBA Season Until Steve Kerr Complains About Traveling]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183098</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-not-a-real-nba-season-until-steve-kerr-complains-about-traveling"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T20:50:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve Kerr has visibly aged in his time as an NBA coach, which makes sense given that (a) he will turn 60 during his next training camp, and (b) Thursday's game in Brooklyn will be his 1,000th between regular and postseason, give or take the 55 games he missed but was given credit for while recovering from back surgery. He has also been a general manager for three years in Phoenix under noted loonball Bob Sarver, worked alongside Marv Albert at ESPN, which is to say listened to Marv Albert, nearly took the Knicks job when they were embarking on a seven-year stretch of .315 basketball, voiced himself on an episode of Clone High scouting for something called "Tropical Hospital," and has worked alongside all the versions of Draymond Green for more than a decade. Hell, with all that he should look like Dick Van Dyke sticking his head out of a speeding car window, spaniel-style.
But Kerr has managed all this while seeming like a much younger fellow in spirit, which in the industry is almost as revivifying as casting your get-out-of-jail-free-card lot with Stephen Curry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Tate McRae Fans Explain Everything They Know About Tate McRae]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183022</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/two-tate-mcrae-fans-explain-everything-they-know-about-tate-mcrae"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tate McRae has a brand new album out called So Close To What. This is a very popular album, but you may be asking yourself the same questions that we were asking ourselves a mere week ago—questions like Who is Tate McRae? and What other song does this Tate McRae song remind me of? and Why are people mad at Tate McRae? These are all good and important and valid questions to be asking. Thank you so much for asking them.
Luckily, the two of us are garbage monsters who eat garbage all day long, so we are qualified to introduce you to Tate McRae and all of her mundane scandals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[George Lowe Had To Be Brilliant To Make Space Ghost That Stupid]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183046</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/george-lowe-had-to-be-brilliant-to-make-space-ghost-that-stupid"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T19:28:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watching Space Ghost Coast to Coast always felt like I was getting away with something. I just wasn't sure what. Staying up past my bedtime, both my parents asleep, sitting in the dark and watching this bizarre cartoon on a cable channel ostensibly for children, not quite getting many of the jokes, or anti-jokes, but understanding on some level that it was all very funny. I assumed I wasn't old enough to understand it, which at that age is one of the most thrilling feelings in the world.
It was a talk show, featuring actual famous guests, and if I had more laughs at the obvious humor of Zorak (evil mantis; bandleader) and Moltar (somewhat less evil lava man; director), none of it would have worked without the straight man—dimwitted host/former superhero Space Ghost—grounding everything with his signature authoritative idiocy. And Space Ghost as a character owed everything to the commanding voice of George Lowe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mavericks Are Staring Into The Abyss]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183029</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-mavericks-are-staring-into-the-abyss"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T18:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten minutes into the first quarter of the Dallas Mavericks' Monday night blowout loss to the Sacramento Kings, Kyrie Irving maneuvered around a Kai Jones screen and into the lane, where he split two help defenders, took a bump, and landed oddly on his left foot. His knee crumpled and he immediately went to the floor, calling for the Mavs' athletic training staff. That unit is as used to this sort of thing as any in the NBA. Irving's insistence on staying in the game to shoot his free throws (he made them both) was initial cause for optimism, but ESPN's Shams Charania reported on Tuesday morning that Irving had torn his ACL. The Mavericks, who were already screwed, are now totally terminal.
The theory of the Luka Doncic-Anthony Davis trade, or at least the most coherent available rationalization, was that the Mavericks were trying to win a championship right now, this year. In L.A., Davis had begun agitating to play alongside a true center (touching; was the Boogie Cousins experiment really so formative?), and he'd finally get his wish in Dallas. The Mavs could play their new do-it-all big man alongside either Daniel Gafford or Dereck Lively II and reliably beat the crap out of opponents while Irving shouldered the majority of the shot-creation burden. One could look around at the rest of the Western Conference and credibly think this formula could win three playoff series, provided P.J. Washington and the newly acquired Caleb Martin could hit their threes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Artist’s Way’ Week 8: We Are Burnt-Out Sims]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183011</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-artists-way-week-8-we-are-burnt-out-sims"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T17:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daily life can be so boring in its predictability, the ways we are forced to feed and clothe these bodies we are responsible for. So on its face, playing a game like The Sims should be miserable. You're just playing god as you watch little people try to fit all their bodily functions into one day and still feel spiritually fulfilled. There's something satisfying in achieving full green bars for your little digital people, even as your human body aches from poor posture and not enough exercise because it's still too cold outside.
It's funny how talking about your Sims' lives can feel a bit like when a child is in therapy acting out their complicated emotions with a doll. The Sims themselves have their own sort of agency and desires separate from the player, but you can override them in your power as all-powerful god/player. This week Sabs realized they were diverting one Sim away from their true calling to be a comedian. It was surprising how much their realization sounded like a Julia Cameron anecdote out of The Artist's Way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can’t Arrest Me For Drowning My Burger In Ketchup]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182995</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/you-cant-arrest-me-for-drowning-my-burger-in-ketchup"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T17:01:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about shitty teenagers, the end of Playboy, penis tattoos, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mets, Royals Discussed Starling Marte Earlier This Offseason]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=843421</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/03/mets-trade-rumors-royals-starling-marte.html"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T16:46:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals showed interest in Starling Marte earlier in the offseason, per Joel Sherman of the New York Post. Those talks obviously didn’t produce a deal, but Sherman adds that Kansas City hasn’t completely closed the door on the possibility. There’s no indication talks are active, but it’s nevertheless notable that the Royals are still…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired USFWS Biologist]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182675</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-usfws-biologist"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T15:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A week into February, Kaesee Bourne was nervous about her job. Last August, she had joined the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service as a fish and wildlife biologist working in California and Nevada. "What should have been a stable job had started to become very unstable," she said. After Donald Trump took office, Bourne and her colleagues begun receiving a barrage of concerning emails, memorandums, and instructions—not from their supervisors, or even people who were a part of the Fish and Wildlife leadership, but from representatives of the United States Office of Personnel Management (OPM). This obscure federal agency has been tasked with the campaign of mass firings of federal workers led by Elon Musk's Department of Government Efficiency, or DOGE.
When Bourne saw an OPM email asking for a list of probationary employees at Fish and Wildlife—a status that refers to recently hired employees, or employees recently moved into a new position—she asked her supervisor about it. But Bourne's supervisor had no additional insight; they had both received the email at the same time. "I've been hearing that the goal of the new administration was to make people feel stressed out and just make them feel the chaos," Bourne said. "It definitely worked."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Buy A Gun, Even If It Comes In Rainbow]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182874</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dont-buy-a-gun-even-if-it-comes-in-rainbow"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T14:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of fear in this country is directly caused by guns. According to the CDC, there were over 48,000 firearm-related deaths in the U.S. in 2022, and the specific way in which a gun can kill you—without warning, painfully, at any age, in basically any place—only multiplies the dread. I grew up inundated with stories of mass murder: Columbine, Virginia Tech, Aurora, Sandy Hook. The worst nightmares come when it hits home—when the people shot are from your community (Pulse), your roots (Oxford, Michigan), or a critical part of your everyday life (the NYC subway). But gun violence is no less devastating when it doesn't make national news: a child shot on the street in your neighborhood, a friend's older brother's suicide, domestic violence taken to lethal extremes. The capacity to destroy bestowed by a gun on whoever holds it—a cop, a kid, a hunter—is a power that should be regarded with horror.
Over the past several months, another fear has increased in prevalence among trans people in particular: the fear of a government that is not just ignorant or apathetic about our existence but is actively working to eradicate us from public life. It is the position of the Trump administration that trans people do not exist, and therefore do not have rights. Confronted with the inconvenient fact of our ongoing lives, the President, Elon Musk, and their cronies are fighting to block our access to healthcare, fire us from our jobs, threaten our safety, and limit our ability to leave the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Duvall Seeking $3MM+ In Free Agency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=843397</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/03/adam-duvall-seeking-3mm-in-free-agency.html"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T01:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Duvall remains unsigned a few weeks into Spring Training. That was also the case last offseason. It wasn’t until March 14 that the veteran outfielder inked a $3MM contract with the Braves. Duvall is evidently seeking a similar or better deal this time around. Joel Sherman of The New York Post reports that the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Without exception / Developing community]]></title>
        <id>67c608c32412be0001c60579</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-268/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T00:14:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Hioe on the #(*$&! geopolitics; a Brooklyn community gallery visit with David Moore]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Abhorrent Vacuum]]></title>
        <id>67c613832412be0001c605d4</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/an-abhorrent-vacuum/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T00:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a collective of 60 writers, on fire and hard to kill]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Hioe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Local (Gallery)]]></title>
        <id>67c5e7f72412be0001c6049b</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/my-local-gallery/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T00:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a collective of 60 writers, on fire and hard to kill]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Moore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Moustakas To Retire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=843393</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/03/mike-moustakas-to-retire.html"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T23:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that they will have a ceremony on May 31st to honor Mike Moustakas as he retires as a Royal. Presumably, he will sign a ceremonial one-day contract to retire with the club with whom he spent most of his career. Moustakas, now 36, was selected second overall in the 2007 draft. Taken…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gervonta Davis Escapes With A Draw After Hair Care Debacle]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182912</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/gervonta-davis-escapes-with-a-draw-after-hair-care-debacle"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T22:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE NOSEBLEEDS AT BARCLAYS CENTER — A fighter can’t call a timeout in boxing. Unless, that is, you’re Gervonta "Tank" Davis. 
Because in the heat of battle during the ninth round of a shockingly fabulous and dramatic WBA lightweight title fight Saturday night, against underdog challenger Lamont Roach in Brooklyn, Davis did just that. And he got away with it. Then again, this fight was full of the unexpected, not least of which was the majority draw the judges gave the fight after 12 fascinating rounds. The Barclays Center crowd, which was very pro-Davis at the beginning of the night, booed loudly when the decision was announced, knowing the champ had been saved by the referee and feeling Roach was robbed on the scorecards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is Uvalde]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182965</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-is-uvalde"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T21:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter, examining the apocalyptic politics, coverage, and consequences of Campaign 2024.
Should Democrats attend Donald Trump's address to the joint session of Congress Tuesday night? The party can't decide what to do. Some Democratic senators and representatives want to boycott the event, to deny Trump's frenetic and lawless program of misrule any of the ceremonial trappings of the presidency. Others want to show up and participate as a rebuke to Trump—including the party's leaders in both chambers, Hakeem Jeffries and Chuck Schumer, who, Axios wrote, "want members to attend and bring special guests who have been negatively affected by the administration."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JD Vance Screamed Out Of Planned Ski Vacation In Vermont]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182901</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jd-vance-screamed-out-of-planned-ski-vacation-in-vermont"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T21:05:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This might feel somewhat discordant, given that JD Vance's most prominent physical feature is a golf-ball head that makes his body look like a tee, but the administration he's part of is one that understands the value of performance. How else are you supposed to read Vance aligning himself with a broccoli-cut racist and against his own children? Or Vance joining Marco Rubio and Donald Trump to stage an ambush on Ukraine President Volodymyr Zelenskyy this past Friday? That they invited him to the Oval Office to call him an ungrateful broke boy is itself pretty nasty and evil, though the most striking aspect of the airing of grievances was its staging. It was less a forum for diplomacy and more a show for the public, captured by several cameras and conducted in front of a jeering press corps. The point was not just to humiliate a soon-to-be former ally, but to be seen humiliating him by a public who is being told that this counts as action.
That sort of geopolitical kabuki feels maddening and somewhat abstract, and while the nature of Vance's arrangement with political power and capital is such that he is largely insulated from consequences, the good news is that Vance still can be told to fuck off when he deigns to be among the people. That is not the same as meaningfully fucking off, but it must have felt so good to be among the gathered Vermonters who protested Vance's planned ski getaway this past weekend. Vance and his family went up to Sugarbush Resort in Vermont's Mad River Valley—if you ever find yourself there, check out Canteen Creemee—and instead of the peaceful vacation they imagined for themselves, they got screamed at. Around 1,000 people lined the streets of Waitsfield, and several people skiing alongside Vance on the mountain brought signs and yelled at him when they got the chance. Enough people were annoying or troublesome enough that the Vance family moved their planned stay from a resort to a private residence and eventually cut short their planned four-day trip.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Society Can’t Quit The Oscars]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182899</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/society-cant-quit-the-oscars"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T19:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Academy Awards are goofy. Always have been. A combination of theater-kid pageantry overload and an earnest celebration of Hollywood, or maybe just of the people working in Hollywood. The show has never had its finger on the pulse of the art form, settling instead on keeping its foot on the sternum, and the movies that lose usually say more about the state of the medium than the movies that win.
This year's slate of nominees featured very few truly great movies, but also very few truly bad ones. So a lukewarm Oscars telecast is exactly what everyone should've expected. A few laughs, a couple surprises, and no one walks away feeling particularly good or bad about any of it in totality. Good work!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Leopards Are Getting Fat]]></title>
        <id>67c5d7bc4d6c7b0001e1b60d</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/the-leopards-are-getting-fat/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T19:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's fun to pretend elected leaders in charge of a nation of 350 million people can handpick who suffers and who does not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking The Life Out Of “Day In The Life”]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182875</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/taking-the-life-out-of-day-in-the-life"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T17:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[11:59 a.m. The tiny clock at the bottom of the screen counts down to the top of the hour, and like a bizarre bell chime from a digital clocktower, large pink text overtakes the Whitney Museum’s website. 
"A quick bus ride and transfer to the F gets us into the city nice and swiftly at noon, where I’m greeted by this food truck."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pete Rose Will Spend The Afterlife As A Cudgel]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182888</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/pete-rose-will-spend-the-afterlife-as-a-cudgel"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T16:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On an otherwise calm day for the president (only blaming one country for being invaded is a light day by his standards), he announced his intention to pardon Pete Rose. For what, we're not sure, and with jurisdiction he does not have, he has decided that Rose needs to be reintegrated into America's good graces in the way Rose expressly said he didn't want it: posthumously.
But as the master of the grand and clumsy gesture, the Snickers-bar-in-chief said he was going to pardon him anyway, claiming with syntactical shoes-on-the-wrong-feet grace that Rose "never betted against himself, or the other team. He had the most hits, by far, in baseball history, and won more games than anyone in history." How Rose's betting slips or his Baseball Reference page covers his conviction for tax evasion is hard to parse, as is the claim that he "never betted against himself or the other team" unless he was trying to middle every bet he ever made by betting both ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, March 3: Think Again (Themeless)]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182870</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-march-3-think-again-themeless"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They say March comes in like a lion, which is why we thought it appropriate to BEGIN the month with a challenging themeless. That is the reason you are getting a themeless puzzle this week and did not get one last week to end the month as you normally do! It has nothing to do with a total puzzle post scheduling mistake on my part, for which I am very sorry. This week's puzzle was constructed by Trent Evans and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Trent has been constructing crossword puzzles since 2018. His work has appeared in the New York Times, Los Angeles Times, Wall Street Journal, and other major publications and independent puzzle venues. He publishes free puzzles at gridtherapy.com. He is a clinical psychologist in private practice in Catonsville, Md., where he lives with his wife Beth and their dog Donut. A rotating cast of five young adult children breeze in and out at their leisure, much to Trent and Beth’s delight. 
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deebo Samuel And The Offensive Revolution That Never Was]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182857</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/deebo-samuel-and-the-offensive-revolution-that-never-was"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T14:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three years ago, Deebo Samuel changed the nature of offensive football. This weekend, he was traded from San Francisco to Washington for a fifth-round draft choice, not long after his 29th birthday. In the NFL, life comes at you fast and aims for your legs with a pipe wrench.
Samuel was the signature piece at the zenith of the Kyle Shanahan Experience, the 49ers' ringless dynasty that looks like it might be ninja-stalking its sell-by date. He was the intriguing pass-catcher who became significantly more when he was unleashed as a running threat from the wideout position midway through the 2021 season. They solved their average-but-not-much-more-than-that quarterbacking problem, code-named Jimmy Garoppolo, by doubling down on an already run-dependent offense (they won the NFC championship game two years earlier by deliberately throwing only eight passes) with Samuel breaking down defenses by attacking with verve and sparkle from the outside back toward the maelstrom of the tackle box. He was named All-Pro, and teams across the league started thinking about wide receivers as running backs waiting for their moment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Big Can Big Air Go?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182513</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-big-can-big-air-go"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T13:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There can be many nuances to ski, snowboard, and skateboard tricks that are lost on the average viewer. Was that a mute grab or an indy grab? What’s the difference? Which one is harder? Most of us will never know. Pure rotation, however, is easy to grasp. That's why during this year’s Winter X Games in Aspen this past January, everybody lost their minds when Japanese 19-year-old Hiroto Ogiwara pulled off the world’s first 2340 on his snowboard.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DNlPnAnWvq0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brent Rose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please Do Not Lie To Me About Hockey Butts]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182818</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/please-do-not-lie-to-me-about-hockey-butts"/>
        <updated>2025-03-02T23:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As an ass-appreciator, certain sports carry more intrigue than others. The benefit of baseball is the pants, which are tight and stretchy. The benefit of football is that sometimes they are pushing each other's tushes. The benefits of soccer and basketball are currently unknown to me, but I am willing to learn. But of all the sports, it is hockey which rewards the ass appreciator the most.
Hockey players are known to be unbelievably jacked in their lower body. Their quads are huge! Their hamstrings are made of steel! Their calves are as big as my thigh! The effort of pushing yourself around on skates for your entire life is a perfect formula for building a beautiful, ginormous butt. One of my favorite hockey articles of all time is an ESPN The Magazine story where Emily Kaplan interviewed a bunch of NHL players about how hard it is for them to buy jeans. Which is why I was stunned, horrified even, to see my king the menswear critic Derek Guy calling this butt a "prominent seat."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe Trading Childhood Memories For Profit Is Not A Market Advantage]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182813</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/wemby-jersey-auction-dispute"/>
        <updated>2025-03-02T19:38:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As far as memorabilia auctions go, a Victor Wembenyana jersey selling for $73,200 is a modest, if unremarkable sum. Granted, it's better than, say, a Malachi Flynn in-season tournament jersey going for the cost of a nightstand at Crate & Barrel, but already in his early career Wembenyama's jerseys have cleared $700,000 in the sports trinket market. 
But the reason this is notable is because the jersey in question was at the center of a bit of fan theater that went viral and subsequently boomeranged faster than anyone could have guessed. No sooner had Wembenyama swapped jerseys with a kid—Comme c'est merveilleux! It looks like Wemby's uni got left in the dryer too long—than it wound up for auction, finally ending in a sale on Feb. 22.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Don’t Have To See Everything In The Museum]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182806</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/you-dont-have-to-see-everything-in-the-museum"/>
        <updated>2025-03-02T18:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was in Chicago for a book event this weekend with some time on my hands in the space between doing some publicity things and preparing for an event. After stopping for Cuban sandwiches with my publicist Brittani, we decided to pop into the Art Institute of Chicago for a hot second.
Most museums are very large. There are so many things in there, and most of them you won't care about at all. Many people view excursions to see art as a chore that must be completed the way homework must be completed. You have to see everything. You have to read all the plaques. You have to appreciate that which you do not and cannot understand. This, I think, is stupid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A sound faintly like Seth Rogen laughing]]></title>
        <id>67c21363fd76390001aa4a1b</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-267/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T21:35:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amy Chu considers the future]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Worst Case Scenario]]></title>
        <id>67c1f8e2fd76390001aa496f</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-best-worst-case-scenario/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T21:31:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Amy Chu
The time has come for us to reimagine everything. We have to reimagine work and go away from labor. We have to reimagine revolution and get beyond protest. We have to think not only about change in our institutions, but changes in ourselves. We are at the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Chu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Out Of Options Players To Watch This Spring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=842980</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/10-out-of-options-players-mlb-spring-training.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T20:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most interesting elements of spring training every year, at least for those of us who feast on roster construction minutiae, is the collection of players who are out of minor league options. MLBTR just released a full list of such players earlier today. In many instances, a player being out of minor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Gottlieb Is Immersed In The Grim Men’s Lifestyle]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182748</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/doug-gottlieb-is-immersed-in-the-grim-mens-lifestyle"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T19:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[National radio host and beleaguered basketball coach Doug Gottlieb is living a life full of grim men's evenings, based on two well-written profiles published recently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Will Take An Annoying World Over A Sterile One]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182768</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-will-take-an-annoying-world-over-a-sterile-one"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T19:26:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we're running a small package of essays on the topic of nuisances. Why? That's an annoying question.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Jensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emma Hayes Shows Us The USWNT She Believes In]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182750</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/emma-hayes-shows-us-the-uswnt-she-believes-in"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T18:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In January, Emma Hayes called in 50 players to train with the USWNT. Twenty-six were with the senior national team, and the rest were part of a Futures camp, which was meant to develop and scout young prospects. It was all part of Hayes’s mission to revamp the American women’s soccer system at all levels. Since then, she’s laid out a far-reaching plan that details how she hopes to push the American soccer world to reframe its goals from matching the men’s game to doing instead whatever is best for female players specifically. The effects of that blueprint, or “The WNT Way” as she calls it, will only be evident years down the line. But where Hayes does have total control, and where results are more prompt, is with the senior national team. Most immediately, she would have to select a 23-player roster for the SheBelieves Cup.
U.S. Soccer created the poorly named tournament in 2016 as an alternative to the Algarve Cup. It’s not a tournament that means much on its face, other than being a guaranteed three games against strong opposition at a regular lull in the international soccer calendar. With more than two years to go before the next major tournament, this SheBelieves Cup provided a good opportunity for the USWNT to tinker with its roster and tactics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abigail Segel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High School Basketball Team Forfeits Season Over Violation, Is Still Eligible For State Championship]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182714</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/maryland-high-school-boys-basketball-scandal"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T18:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top public school boys basketball program in Prince George’s County, Md., which by any objective measure (or if you just ask me) is the best basketball county in the country, went 0-20 this season. Or anyway the official record book says so now, thanks to punishments doled out in yet another high school sports cheating scandal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steph Curry Still Has The Nuclear Button]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182725</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/steph-curry-still-has-the-nuclear-button"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T17:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Magic are a fun, flawed team. Evidence of both attributes could be seen on Thursday night, when, after leading by 17 at one point in a game against Golden State, Orlando looked poised for a statement win against a surging Warriors squad. But God had other plans, and by God I mean the 6-foot-2 demon with No. 30 on his chest who goes by the name Steph Curry.
Curry scored a personal season-high 56 points on 16-of-25 shooting, 12 of those makes coming from three-point range. He hit one shot from well behind the half-court line shot to end the first half, and scored 22 points in the third quarter alone, outscoring the entire Magic team in that period. Whether it's invigoration from the arrival of Jimmy Butler (the Warriors have won seven of their last eight), or if he just had the juice flowing last night, Curry put on a prime performance, the likes of which we haven't often seen from him this year. The Warriors needed every bit of it to overcome Butler's off night and the aforementioned double-digit deficit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Nickel Boys’ Deserves Best Picture]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182730</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nickel-boys-deserves-best-picture"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T16:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Emilia Perez star Karla Sofía Gascón’s racist tweets, and blackface allegations related to I’m Still Here lead actress Fernanda Torres have been grabbing headlines, the more overlooked 2025 Oscars scandal continues to be egregious nomination snubs for Black-led performances. The most notable omissions were Marianne Jean-Baptiste for Mike Leigh’s Hard Truths, Danielle Deadwyler for Malcolm Washington’s The Piano Lesson, Clarence Maclin for Greg Kwedar’s Sing Sing, and Aunjanue Ellis-Taylor for RaMell Ross’s Nickel Boys. And while Nickel Boys did receive Best Picture and Adapted Screenplay nominations, the most baffling Oscar oversights were in the technical categories: Jomo Fray for Nickel Boys' cinematography and RaMell Ross for directing and film editing. Nickel Boys is a masterpiece, and it’s here where the film is the most experimental, inventive, and alive to the possibilities of cinema. 
Ross's 2018 debut feature, the unconventional, Oscar-nominated documentary, Hale County This Morning, This Evening, follows the life of two Black high school students from Hale County, Ala., where the documentarian and visual artist spent five years immersed in the rural Black communities as a photography teacher, capturing footage. The film bends time and linearity to craft a communal tapestry of the banality and nuance of life in the Black Belt region, as well as early Black cinema (e.g., Lime Kiln Club Field Day). Ultimately, what emerges is what Ross names his “source code” for the recordkeeping of Black southern life liberated from the dominant ways of seeing. Ross’s second feature builds upon the “empowered black data” laid forth in the contemporary through Hale County to attend to the forgotten Black boys of the Jim Crow South and its afterlives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matene Toure</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clownfish Fatten Up Their Best Buddies To Upgrade Their Homes]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182571</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/clownfish-fatten-up-their-best-buddies-to-upgrade-their-homes"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T15:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The clownfish spawn in the anemone, and their feces fertilize their host with ammonia. The fish also aerate the anemone at night, offering their hosts fresh oxygen. They remove waste and other unwanted materials. And in certain situations, they deliver tasty meals right to the anemone's door.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NIH Cuts Are Part Of An All-Out War On Higher Education]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182652</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-nih-cuts-are-part-of-an-all-out-war-on-higher-education"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T15:28:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a presidential administration with an unlimited capacity for chaos, colleges and universities have become targets of this early phase of right-wing assault. This is not so surprising: Many of the key political threads that comprise today’s Trumpism share an opposition to the academy and all it represents. Chris Rufo has presided over the dismantling of New College of Florida and succeeded in smuggling his bespoke interpretations of concepts like “DEI” and “critical race theory” into state law and now federal policy. JD Vance has appeared at gatherings of national conservatives to say that “professors are the enemy.”
Trump’s newest allies in Silicon Valley may worship a narrow idea of intelligence, but they view the long apprenticeship, not to mention the still-broad education required of the traditional college student, as a waste of time. And then there is Trump’s traditional base, which splits decisively along educational lines: educational attainment now reliably predicts support for the Democratic Party. Trump, for his part, has said that he loves “the poorly educated”—and they love him back! From another quarter, the battle is joined by MAHA types, COVID skeptics, and Big Pharma truthers who see the country’s medical research apparatus as a machine for laundering money into dubiously valuable experiments that make Americans sicker and the pharmaceutical companies that sell medical remedies richer. What Americans really need, in their view, is raw milk, beef tallow, and a few weeks on the happy farm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dennis M. Hogan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Tale Of The Early-Round KO Of Muhammad Ali’s Champburger]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182304</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-tale-of-the-early-round-ko-of-muhammad-alis-champburger"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T14:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ali's stint in a Miami jail was also part of a promotion for his new hamburger joint, Champburger, which was set to open its first location at the end of the the month. “To his credit,” the Miami Herald’s Ray Crawford wrote, “he didn’t try to snow the press. He admitted he was looking for publicity.” Indeed, Ali was quite direct: “My main reason for coming here is to open our new Champburger headquarters here.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We'll Never Be The Same': The Victims Of Elon Musk's Unreality]]></title>
        <id>67c1b09fe121bc0001a107af</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/elon-musk-unreality/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T14:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['A clownish South African reaper figuratively chainsaws me, a human being, to cheers from a rapturous crowd.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Are Other People In The World]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178653</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/there-are-other-people-in-the-world"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T14:21:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pay attention to the things around you! Be aware of the space you take up, and the space other people take up, and when those two things might come into conflict!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>