<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-02-13T01:13:14.824Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dippi – calculate display info like DPI and aspect ratio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142178</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/dippi-calculate-display-info/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T23:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dippi is a tool which can analyze any display. Input a few details and figure out the aspect ratio, DPI, and details of a particular display.
The post Dippi – calculate display info like DPI and aspect ratio appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[termv – terminal iptv player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142262</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/termv-terminal-iptv-player/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T20:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[termv is a small bash script that allows you to select an iptv stream using fzf and play it using mpv.
The post termv – terminal iptv player appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Béty Lê Shackelford champions marginalized communities through good eats and good deeds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=868710</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/bety-le-shackelford-champions-marginalized-communities-through-good-eats-and-good-deeds/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T20:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Phon Wills If you’ve followed trends of motivation and self-betterment over the years, you may have encountered the Japanese idea of ikigai. Ikigai literally refers to the idea of “the meaning of living,” and it is the search to find a passion that makes your life and the world a better place. Béty Lê Shackelford—the founder and executive...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Baranowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ridiculous Timberwolves Ownership Saga’s End Is In Sight]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181259</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-ridiculous-timberwolves-ownership-sagas-end-is-in-sight"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T19:13:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost four years after agreeing to buy the Minnesota Timberwolves from Glen Taylor, Alex Rodriguez and Diapers.com tycoon Marc Lore have won an arbitration case that will allow them to finally take control of the team. A three-person arbitration panel issued its ruling on Monday, voting 2-1 to let them advance to the final steps of seeing out a contract they agreed to, which Taylor was trying to wriggle out of. The mechanics of that vote, and the process it guaranteed, are far more arcane than simply and immediately transferring ownership, but the upshot is that Taylor is out and the Business Boys are in. It's the story of NBA ownership over the past two decades in miniature.
Taylor has always been a bad owner. This is not always the simplest thing to judge, as a team's performance in the short and even medium term can exceed the willingness of its ownership group to do the two things that distinguish a "good" owner: pay the luxury tax for a good team and, most importantly, shut up and get out of the way. You can't always get both, and many fans would settle for one or the other. Marc Cuban, former Dallas Mavericks majority owner and now Mavericks minority owner, was never willing to abide by the latter clause, though he regularly paid the tax when his teams were in contention. Memphis Grizzlies owner Robert Pera has learned to keep himself out of the public eye—after Sports Illustrated reported that he wanted then-coach Dave Joerger to wear a headset so Pera could personally call in plays—though he is staunchly unwilling to pay the luxury tax.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Manchester City And Real Madrid Defenses Barfed All Over Themselves]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181232</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-manchester-city-and-real-madrid-defenses-barfed-all-over-themselves"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T18:57:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester City and Real Madrid are arguably the two defining clubs of the past decade. Both have reigned over their respective domains—the Premier League and the Champions League—with unprecedented supremacy. Clashes between the two have become annual rituals that determine which one can claim the title of the best team in the world. But while most of the the names and faces of the current City-Madrid tie are familiar from those iconic matches of the recent past, if Tuesday's first leg of their UCL knockout playoff reminded us of anything, it's just how far below their usual standard these teams have been this year, specifically at the back.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Do-C4u_7vZs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals’ James McArthur Recovering From Elbow Surgery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=841359</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/james-mcarthur-elbow-surgery-royals.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T18:26:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Royals right-hander James McArthur underwent surgery to repair a fractured olecranon in his right elbow and is behind schedule this spring, per Jaylon Thompson of the Kansas City Star. McArthur, who had two screws installed in his pitching elbow, is just now beginning to throw. It’s not clear exactly when McArthur had the procedure, but…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSwoole – programmatic platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142119</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/openswoole-programmatic-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T18:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Openswoole aims to  power the next-generation micro-services and application.
The post OpenSwoole – programmatic platform appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If You Ever Stacked Cups In Gym Class, Blame My Dad]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181093</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/if-you-ever-stacked-cups-in-gym-class-blame-my-dad"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T17:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The boxes came from Tokyo: first by tanker, then overland via container truck from a Pacific port, across the Continental Divide, and finally backed into a driveway at the end of a cul-de-sac in a south Denver suburban enclave. This was a neighborhood with Razor scooters dumped in trimmed front lawns. Where family walks with leashed dogs happened down the middle of intentionally curved streets named after long demolished natural landmarks like "Timbercrest" and "Forest Trails." Where the HOA (because of course there was an HOA) banned the installation of driveway basketball hoops.
Receiving industrial freight deliveries, freshly cleared through international customs, probably wasn't explicitly prohibited in the homeowner's handbook. But then, why would it need to be? Nobody would think to bring that kind of commercial chaos into the burgeoning middle-class peace of Castle Pines North in 1998.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kit Fox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Butler – companion for Home Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142175</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/butler-companion-for-home-assistant/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T17:07:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Butler is a hybrid native and web app for Home Assistant. Butler is designed and developed on and for GNOME. 
The post Butler – companion for Home Assistant appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Civilization VII’ Takes A Bumpy Road Toward Immortality]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181096</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/civilization-vii-takes-a-bumpy-road-toward-immortality"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T16:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Civilization series has been a load-bearing pillar of the video game industry dating back to 1991, and though the series has gone through many changes throughout its history, the core gameplay has generally stayed the same. Players pick a civilization with an attached leader, then guide it from the early stages of humanity into the near future. It's a tried-and-true formula that has had enough wrinkles to not just thrive for 34 years, but also inspire enough passion in its different iterations to have rabid fanatics of each game. (For my money, Civilization V is the best one, even though I played VI the most.) Civilization VII tries something new, something so fundamentally different that at times it feels like a Civ competitor more than a proper new entry in the series. It shouldn't work, and it often doesn't, but the evolution, really the revolution, that comes with the seventh installment of this long-running series is thrilling even in its flaws.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gV0waX2uPLg]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Reads A Book Is Going To Reap What Octavia Butler Sowed]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181166</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-reads-a-book-is-going-to-reap-what-octavia-butler-sowed"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T16:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1992, while Octavia E. Butler was writing her novel Parable of the Sower, Los Angeles was hitting bottom. The acquittal of the police officers filmed brutalizing Rodney King triggered a paroxysm of riots and violence in the city. To Butler and many others, it felt like the apotheosis of a number of untenable realities. As a writer of science fiction, Butler took the anxieties she felt—about social rot and political atrophy, about a vision of capitalism poised somewhere between merely dehumanizing and actively anti-human, about climate collapse and social collapse—and turned them into a story that was both more speculative and more full of possibility than the news. Parable of the Sower, which was published in 1993, begins in the year 2024.
The book tells the story of Lauren Oya Olamina, a brilliant and supernaturally sensitive 15-year-old growing up in a town that sits on the outskirts of a collapsing Los Angeles, and in every way on the verge of a deep abyss. Her experience of the dying world around her fuels a vision of a new faith, called Earthseed; when circumstances force Lauren out into that world, she and that faith are tested over and over again as she and a collection of fellow travelers look for safety in a very dangerous country. It's not any more uplifting or much less harrowing than it sounds—I haven't finished reading it yet, but I'm not expecting a big comeback for Society—and the many ways in which it has proved prescient do not make it any easier to take. But it did give the book, which was well-reviewed in its time and became a cornerstone of Butler's legacy, a long and uneasy second life. In the fall of 2020, at what felt like the bottom of the pandemic, 27 years after it was first published, and 14 years after Butler's death, Parable of the Sower became a New York Times bestseller.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Onto the next storm (WED 2/12)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3822637</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-onto-the-next-storm-wed-2-12/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T15:26:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Occasional snow showers and bitter cold temperatures prevail on Wednesday before Kansas City's next winter system arrives this weekend]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joel Embiid Is Creaking Through It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181228</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/joel-embiid-is-creaking-through-it"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T15:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Philadelphia 76ers star Joel Embiid returned from his latest injury-related absence on Feb. 4, and if you were to look at his statistics across the four games he has played this month, you might get the impression that he's right back in the groove. He's averaged 26 points, 10 rebounds, and six assists in those games, and he's gotten to play three of them alongside Tyrese Maxey and Paul George. Embiid's on the floor and the Big Three is finally reaching an operational state; things are finally starting to turn around in Philadelphia, right?
The Sixers are 1-3 since Embiid returned to the lineup (George did not play in the game they won), and each has produced footage of Embiid that one might describe as "alarming." He shot 38 percent from the field in last Friday's loss to the Pistons, and in 30 minutes of action was able to put together a highlight reel of awkward flailing. Last night's game against the Raptors produced what might be a new low point in Embiid's season. Down two with 16 seconds left, Embiid set a screen for Maxey at the top of the three-point line and then popped into space. Maxey zipped the ball to his wide-open big man, who lined up a potential game-winning three, hesitated, awkwardly drove into the defense, and then just kind of ... dribbled the ball off the back of his own head?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SonicRadio – stylish TUI radio player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142315</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/sonicradio-stylish-tui-radio-player/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T14:41:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SonicRadio is billed as a stylish TUI radio player making use of Radio Browser API and Bubbletea.
The post SonicRadio – stylish TUI radio player appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s Always Room For More Merritt Wever]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181107</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/theres-always-room-for-more-merritt-wever"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T14:02:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was sleepwatching through the first two episodes of Severance. It’s not an easy show to get into. It’s sterile because it’s supposed to be—it’s a show about a biotech company called Lumon whose employees have the option of severing their brains so that one version of them goes to the office (the “innie”), while the other (the “outie”) can just live their life. Neither of them ever has to meet—they do not share a consciousness. It’s a clear indictment of corporate culture and the modern workplace in general, the soulless bullshit jobness of it all, but that can almost make it a little hard to stay with it because it can be alienating. The first season has Mark (Adam Scott) leading his co-workers, including game new hire Helly (Britt Lower), award-driven Dylan (Zach Cherry) and company man Irving (John Turturro) on a mutiny. The second season brings them back, with Lumon clearly attempting a pivot to various superficial perks in order to lull the team back into sedation. And this is where we are in the third episode, with a confused Dylan being led to Lumon’s security room. 
When he arrives, it’s an eerie scene, like all the scenes in the series where some form of real-life attempts to invade the corporate space. A wall of screens shows a disarmingly mall-grade portrait of Dylan and a woman who appears to be his wife. That woman appears to be Merritt Wever, who just might be my favorite actress in the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Good mornings at Two Sugars Coffee and Westside Local]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=871139</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-good-mornings-at-two-sugars-coffee-and-westside-local/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T14:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two Sugars Coffee // Photo By Tiffany Watts As a food writer and content creator, I’m always on the hunt for new coffee spots where I can park myself between meetings and power through some work. This time, my search led me to Two Sugars Coffee, a centrally located café that checked all the right boxes: ambiance, aesthetics, and—of course—good...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Best Free and Open Source Email Servers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=68007</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-email-servers/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T11:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's our verdict on free and open source email servers. We recommend Exim, OpenSMTPD, mox, DBMail, and WildDuck.
The post 15 Best Free and Open Source Email Servers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZnapZend – ZFS centric backup tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142151</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/znapzend-zfs-centric-backup-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T11:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ZnapZend is a ZFS centric backup tool to create snapshots and send them to backup locations.
The post ZnapZend – ZFS centric backup tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ambient Country Episode 41: Stelth Ulvang (from The Lumineers)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/ambient-country-episode-41-stelth</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/ambient-country-episode-41-stelth"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T08:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On today’s episode of Ambient Country, Bob Holmes of SUSS is joined by co-host Stelth Ulvang of The Lumineers and Heavy Gus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MystiQ – GUI for FFmpeg]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142218</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/mystiq-gui-ffmpeg/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T07:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MystiQ is a GUI for FFmpeg, a powerful media converter. MystiQ features an intuitive graphical interface and a rich set of presets.
The post MystiQ – GUI for FFmpeg appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atom]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3050/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3050/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Hire Ned Yost As Senior Advisor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=841312</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/royals-hire-ned-yost-as-senior-advisor.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-12T02:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced this afternoon that they’ve hired Ned Yost as a senior advisor to general manager JJ Picollo. Yost, the winningest manager in franchise history, returns to the organization six years after retiring as skipper. “My deep love for the Royals, for Kansas City and for the people there never left,” the 69-year-old said…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plausible – web analytics software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142181</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/plausible-web-analytics-software/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T23:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plausible Analytics is an easy to use, lightweight, open source and privacy-friendly alternative to Google Analytics.
The post Plausible – web analytics software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Artist’s Way’ Week 5: Looking For Small Evolutions]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181084</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-artists-way-week-5-looking-for-small-evolutions"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T21:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five weeks is a long time to spend doing something. After five weeks, your excitement has probably worn off and you've probably had a share of good and bad days to muddle through. Your Defector pals have just finished their fifth week of The Artist's Way, a 12-week course on creativity created by Julia Cameron, and the novelty has certainly worn off for a lot of us. But that doesn't mean there weren't little breakthroughs along the way. It's tempting to think of something like The Artist's Way as a quick(ish) fix for any and all creative and existential woes, but the kinds of changes many of us are hoping for happen incrementally. The Artist's Way, and these weekly check-ins, are useful ways to stop and notice those incremental changes. 
How many days this week did you do your morning pages? How was the experience for you?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gossip Queen Kelsey McKinney SPILLS EVERYTHING In This SHOCKING Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180937</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/gossip-queen-kelsey-mckinney-spills-everything-in-this-shocking-interview"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T20:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When our brilliant, inquisitive colleague Kelsey McKinney last participated in the Defector staff author interview series, she was here as a novelist. Her debut, God Spare The Girls, came out in 2021. In those pages, you can already sense her interest in rumors and secrets, the way they structure our communities. Six months later, she and Alex Sujong Laughlin dropped the first episode of Normal Gossip, the instant mega-hit podcast serving up “juicy, strange, funny, and utterly banal gossip about people you'll never know and never meet.” After seven seasons, Kelsey and Alex have left the show in the hands of an amazing new host-producer duo in Rachelle Hampton and Se'era Spragley Ricks, but Kelsey has distilled all the years she’s spent telling, listening to and thinking about gossip into a new book, You Didn’t Hear This From Me: (Mostly) True Notes On Gossip, which is out today.
“At its most basic, gossip is just one person talking to another about someone who isn’t present,” Kelsey writes. She swallows up all these disparate categories of story—rumor, conspiracy, legend—and cleverly digests them. In some essays, she re-examines familiar places to see how gossip functions—in religious communities, on reality TV sets. In others, she’s concerned with the systems that accelerate gossip, like the norms of the internet and the anatomy of the ear. By the time you finish this book, you will have traveled in so many strange and enriching directions. Take this sampling from the "D" section of the index: defamation; Deuxmoi; Diana, Princess of Wales; Dickinson, Emily; Disney, Walt; Doja Cat; Donegan, Moira; dopamine; Dostoevsky, Fyodor; drag queen terminology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Remember Some Movie Characters Saying, “Fuck!”]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181122</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lets-remember-some-movie-characters-saying-fuck"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T20:23:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about dipshits, friends who are way too into pro wrestling, disposable football helmets, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nike Triumphantly Agrees To Fix The MLB Uniforms It Ruined, Eventually]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181137</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nike-triumphantly-agrees-to-fix-the-mlb-uniforms-it-ruined-eventually"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T19:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Los Angeles Dodgers' spectacular and mostly uncontested offseason binge buy has provided for conspiracy theorists just as surely as it has for Dodgers fans. The benefit to the latter, who have seen the defending champs add a two-time Cy Young Award winner and a vaunted international free agent, among many others, is not hard to figure. Conspiracy types, for their part, can look at the Dodgers’ power moves and see the angle that MLB owners will play in their next attempt to finally install a salary cap. Their historic outlay for Shohei Ohtani a year ago made perfect sense because they just won the World Series; that they would continue trying to get better seems, to some, uncouth. In raising their tax payroll by $110 million in two years the Dodgers are now raising suspicions that they are cravenly buying up all the people there are in the game, and ruining baseball, and blah blah blah.
Well, maybe, but what if all this is actually a move toward legitimizing the Dodgers' recent history? Even allowing for their dominance in the marketplace and their roll to victory in October, the Dodgers have not yet won a championship 1) in a complete season (they won the 2020 bubble title), or 2) while wearing actual major league uniforms since 1988.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Sale: The End, And The Means To Wait For It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180874</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/for-sale-the-end-and-the-means-to-wait-for-it"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T18:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In one Super Bowl commercial, an octogenarian actor waxes lacrimal about freedom, a privilege bought for you with the blood of troops 80 years ago, a privilege whose outer bound and cleanest expression is the freedom to buy different kinds of trucks. A direct-to-consumer pharmacy vaguely refers to inadequacies in the healthcare system—inadequacies you allay by buying its products. The Fox network advertises a new show in which Americans live out post-apocalyptic survivalist fantasies in the woods while their families watch them experience pain and suffering, which they can end at the cost of pulling from the game and ending their chance of winning a cash prize. An artificial intelligence firm positions its core product as the logical endpoint (and end) of human evolution. Every single other ad asks, Do you remember these celebrities? Do you know that they're doing a Super Bowl ad for you right now? The unified message I took away from the ads was that the time of new ideas is receding, and society along with it. The theme was the soft acceptance of a comfortable death.
If you can learn anything of value from a year's crop of Super Bowl commercials, it is not in the products being sold to you, but rather in how they are being sold. Think of an advertisement as a mirror: The way that mirror reflects and distorts a vision of reality, a reality that can be confirmed or avoided by purchasing the correct product, tells you both what the advertiser sees as vital or interesting about culture and what they think you want to see.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tally – hybrid native and web app for Plausible Analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142186</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tally-hybrid-native-web-app-plausible-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T17:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plausible is a privacy-friendly alternative to Google Analytics. Tally wraps the Plausible web app in a native UI.
The post Tally – hybrid native and web app for Plausible Analytics appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every Mavericks Home Game Is Now A Mutiny]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181101</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/every-mavericks-home-game-is-now-a-mutiny"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T16:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is time to become acquainted with that face up there. It belongs to Patrick Dumont, son-in-law of Miriam Adelson and newly appointed governor of the Dallas Mavericks. It's a bad face: pink, shiny, weirdly cartilaginous, unpleasantly suggestive of something that emerged recently from a long sous vide, or that bobs up in a stock pot, leached of nutrients. Up there it is affecting an expression of grim disappointment. Here is that same face, in somewhat happier times. Terrible face!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Did She See, At The End?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180875</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-did-she-see-at-the-end"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T15:16:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[She does not fear the darkness. She does not love it, either, mind you; may as well ask her to have an opinion on water! The darkness is all she knows, all she has ever known, all she might have ever known. It is home. If you can see her, it is too late for you. Or, on her final journey, just in time.
She is Melanocetus johnsonii, the humpback anglerfish, the black seadevil. She appears demonic enough to deserve the nickname: a gaping maw that opens almost fully vertically; jagged, needle-sharp teeth, like something out of an ancestral nightmare; the instinct and the appetite to attack and consume anything unfortunate enough to fall into her trap, even if it is larger than she is. But she is no devil. She is a living thing, one that like any other has carved out a way to survive, in a place you might think nothing could. She is a marvel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything I Would Eat With The Spoon Inside My Brain]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180991</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/everything-i-would-eat-with-the-spoon-inside-my-brain"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T14:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every month, it seems, a new paper comes out declaring that microplastics have invaded another realm of our body: They're in our hearts, our livers, our kidneys, our lungs, our intestines, our testicles, our placentas, our breast milk, our blood, and our brains.
This slow suffusion should come as no surprise. Knowingly, we wear plastics, we drive in them, we unwrap them, and we smear them on our faces. Unknowingly, we eat plastics, drink them, breathe them in. We live our lives surrounded by plastics both macro and micro—meaning a shard narrower than 5 millimeters across. There is also the even subtler, more elusive risk of nanoplastics—a flake narrower than 1 micrometer. Just as plastics degrade into microplastics, microplastics degrade into nanoplastics, and all of this plastic refuse becomes less like an object and more like an atmosphere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Heavier snows trending down a bit (TUE-2/11)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3821392</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-heavier-snows-trending-down-a-bit-tue-2-11/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T14:38:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are still looking at impactful snow, but it should be a bit more manageable for snow clearing, and while schools will likely close tomorrow, the road crews may be able to keep up with things during the afternoon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xjadeo – the X JACK video monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142214</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/xjadeo-x-jack-video-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T14:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xjadeo is a standard for video-monitoring with the Ardour Digital Audio Workstation and used by a variety of projects, predominantly on Linux.
The post Xjadeo – the X JACK video monitor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confused Brits Cause Severe Damage At The Donald Trump Propaganda Factory]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181049</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/confused-brits-cause-severe-damage-at-the-donald-trump-propaganda-factory"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T14:09:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are reasons to envy people who work in conservative media and reasons to pity them, but there's an element of abstraction to that ecosystem and its native bog critters that makes either response seem insufficient. For those stuck working at outlets supported by subscribers or advertisements, and not by the rounding-error subsidies of half-literate box magnates and the heirs to electronics fortunes, some envy is natural. Those jobs mashing away at the reactionary soundboard on behalf of a seething and reclusive Wisconsin billionaire, who will not and quite possibly cannot read anything you write, are easy and secure relative to ones that exist in the free-market media environment. The pity comes from the same place—these aren't real jobs, really, and the work of hunching over the ROFL…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eat This Now: Injera and all at Abol Ethiopian Restaurant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=870377</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/eat-this-now-injera-and-all-at-abol-ethiopian-restaurant/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T14:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doro Tibs and Vegetarian Combo at Abol Ethiopian Restaurant // Photo by Sarah Sipple Abol Ethiopian Restaurant is nestled among gift shops, salons, boutiques, and the award-winning Overland Park Farmers’ Market. The lunch and dinner spot, formerly named Elsa’s, introduced an expanded menu and hours of operation early in 2024 under new management. On a wintery lunch date with friends,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Best Free and Open Source Snippet Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142204</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-snippet-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T12:47:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A snippet tool is utility software that can boost your productivity. They are especially useful to save complex commands
The post 9 Best Free and Open Source Snippet Tools appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AR Tag Placement and Finder Tool – minimalist image editor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142164</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ar-tag-placement-finder-tool-minimalist-image-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T11:34:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AR Tag Placement and Finder Tool is a minimalist image editor designed for placing augmented reality (AR) tags and QR codes, into images.
The post AR Tag Placement and Finder Tool – minimalist image editor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chirurgien – hex editor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142126</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/chirurgien-hex-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T09:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chirurgien is an hex editor and a tool for reverse engineering, analyzing, and carving binary file formats.
The post Chirurgien – hex editor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flow State Episode 264]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-episode-264</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-episode-264"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T08:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s mix opens with the “Music of Wellness” track from the TV show Severance. We play some other gentle ambient pieces by Zane Trow, Sgarz, David Bowie (produced by Brian Eno), and Yumiko Morioka. We play through recent instrumental discoveries from Rubey Hu (h/t]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Best Free and Open Source Photo Metadata Editors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=5653</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/photometadataeditors/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T07:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A metadata editor is computer software which allows users to view and edit metadata tags interactively and save them in the graphics file.
The post 7 Best Free and Open Source Photo Metadata Editors appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coulomb –  simple and elegant circuit simulator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142271</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/coulomb-simple-elegant-circuit-simulator/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T07:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coulomb is billed as a simple and beautiful circuit simulator app for Linux.
The post Coulomb –  simple and elegant circuit simulator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GopherDrop – Secure One-Time Secret Sharing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142156</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gopherdrop-secret-sharing/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T23:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GopherDrop is a secure, self-hostable REST API and UI for sharing encrypted one-time secrets and files.
The post GopherDrop – Secure One-Time Secret Sharing appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland Continues Moving Toward Historic Rugby Threepeat With Assist From Failed Imperialist Nation Where Game Was Invented]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181055</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ireland-six-nations-threepeat"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T21:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland came out strong and finished stronger while defeating Scotland, 32-18, in a Six Nations rugby tilt Sunday evening in Edinburgh. Ireland, the tournament's two-time defending champs, came out of the weekend as the only remaining undefeated side after only two rounds.
Ireland struggled to get going last week in Dublin in its Six Nations opener before blitzing England with 22 unanswered points to put the match away in the second half. There was no such slow start against the Scots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[qr-rs – encode URLs or text into QR codes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142170</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/qr-rs-encode-urls-text-qr-codes/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T21:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[qr-rs is a command line interface utility to encode URLs or more generally text into QR codes in various file formats and colors.
The post qr-rs – encode URLs or text into QR codes appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scenes From Broad Street And Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180971</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/scenes-from-broad-street-and-beyond"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T19:53:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA — The Philadelphia Eagles are Super Bowl champions once again. After whomping the Kansas City Chiefs 40-22, the Eagles join the ranks of teams with multiple title wins, a list that had felt incomplete without this most rabid of fanbases. While fans' celebrations for Super Bowl 59 were missing the first-time-winner chaos of the 2018 victory, there was plenty of screaming and mirth in the immediate aftermath of this one-sided ass-beating.
Following the Eagles' win, Defector Philadelphia Bureau members Kathryn Xu and Luis Paez-Pumar filtered out onto the streets of the city to capture the delight of a city in the thralls of Birdsmania. The results weren't quite as blissful or picturesque as either hoped, but one thing rang true for our intrepid reporters: Philadelphia had itself a party for the ages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Want To Go To The Wet, Empty Alley Where Kevin Burkhardt And Tom Brady Called Last Night’s Game]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181007</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-want-to-go-to-the-wet-empty-alley-where-kevin-burkhardt-and-tom-brady-called-last-nights-game"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T19:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last night Fox Sports unveiled a new graphics package, as companies tend to do for the Super Bowl, and I pretty much liked it. The main thing to notice was the score box—minimalist, clean, not too distracting. Sports broadcasts tend to clutter up the screen, and this was a nice change in my opinion. It did clash with the maximalist Super Bowl graphics, but I will be happy if that’s the route Fox is going with next season.
I will admit that it is at least a little bit sad that I care about this. Time to make things even sadder: I have one massive complaint about the Super Bowl graphics package, and I want to share it with you here. A few times per game football broadcasts will throw to the announcers in the booth, where they will deliver analysis, convey game storylines, or just yuk it up a bit on camera. With the game itself being a blowout pretty much straight through, last night's broadcast went to Kevin Burkhardt and Tom Brady multiple times. They were shown not in the booth, but in front of a green screen. More to the point, Burkhardt and Brady were in front of a green screen depicting a completely empty alleyway that had apparently just been soaked by rain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tanks of Freedom II – Indie Turn Based Strategy Game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142160</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tanks-of-freedom-ii-indie-turn-based-strategy-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T18:50:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tanks of Freedom II is a classic, turn-based strategy game with up to four armies fighting against each other. 
The post Tanks of Freedom II – Indie Turn Based Strategy Game appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kendrick Lamar Did The Super Bowl Halftime Show His Way]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180955</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/kendrick-lamar-did-the-super-bowl-halftime-show-his-way"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T18:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kendrick Lamar capped off the greatest year a rapper has had in quite some time with a Super Bowl halftime show designed specifically to piss off Drake, his fans, and Fox News conservatives alike. A week after winning five Grammys for "Not Like Us," it was pretty obvious that the smash hit was going to make an appearance, despite Drake's dogged attempts to sue damn near the entire music industry over the song. And Kendrick clearly had fun with that fact, repeatedly teasing the record at various points during the show until eventually performing it. At the song's telling moment, with a mischievous grin, Kendrick called out Drake right to camera before deftly declining to say the word "pedophile" on national TV.
"Not Like Us" quickly transcended its original context within the beef, and has since become an anthem like The Killers' "Mr. Brightside" or The White Stripes' "Seven Nation Army." It helps that its message is easily refashioned into a generalizable sentiment: THEY are not like US, whoever "they" or "us" might be. Kendrick himself has encouraged this broadening of the song's scope. "Not like us is the energy of who I am, the type of man I represent," he said in an interview with SZA in Harper's Bazaar. "This man has morals, he has values, he believes in something, he stands on something. He’s not pandering. If I’m thinking of 'Not Like Us,' I’m thinking of me and whoever identifies with that." Sure. Fine. But there is a context to it, and a fallout from it, and Kendrick brought it all up there with him on the Super Bowl stage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Scorebug Snuggery: Super Bowl 59 Goes Big And Brutalist]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180935</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-scorebug-snuggery-super-bowl-59-goes-big-and-brutalist"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T18:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Scorebug Snuggery, that place we all know of and recognize, where we discuss the artistic merit of scorebugs on sports television broadcasts. Today, we look at the Fox network's new scorebug. 
Sunday night's Big Game was one of the least suspenseful Super Bowls of the 21st century, and thus, while watching, I had plenty of time to contemplate the scorebug. Debuting on Fox was the design seen in the screenshot above, replacing the old model, displayed below in the NFC Championship Game:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Luka Doncic Trade Needed Just Three Quarters To Go From Bad To Worse]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180969</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-luka-doncic-trade-needed-just-three-quarters-to-go-from-bad-to-worse"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T17:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Relying on Anthony Davis's availability is like setting foot on a rotted, rickety trapdoor and believing you'll be able to take another step. Beneath the trapdoor, in this analogy, is hell. Nico Harrison and Mavericks owner Patrick Dumont arranged it this way: By making it about a championship window, by calling their popular world-beating superstar an unreliable toxic fatso on his way out, by shrinking the period of observation down to the near term, the Mavericks all but announced This has to work right away. It became a piece of basketball wisdom so cheap and obvious that bothering to articulate it aloud had the ironic effect of making the speaker look somehow less knowledgeable about the sport: All of whatever they imagine makes Davis more valuable than Doncic to the present-day Mavericks relies upon Davis being upright. Davis does lots of things, many of them great and wonderful, but one of the things he does a lot is get hurt. And after not even three quarters of basketball in a Mavericks uniform, Davis got hurt.
He was playing very well Saturday, dominating the Houston Rockets and helping the Mavs to a 17-point halftime lead. Davis's skill and versatility popped immediately. He opened the game with a post touch against a positional mismatch, pulled in a help defender, scanned the court, and threw a perfect lob pass to Daniel Gafford for an alley-oop. Seconds later he swatted a layup from Alperen Sengun, gathered the rebound, led the break, and dished ahead to P.J. Washington for a transition dunk. Minutes later Davis dribbled the ball into the front court, sized up another mismatch, backed his defender into the paint, and turned over his shoulder for a calm jump hook. By halftime, Davis had 24 points, 13 rebounds, five assists, and three blocks, and the Mavericks had won his 21 minutes by a convincing 17 points. Harrison, who'd relinquished his seats in the arena due to the intensity of fan backlash, was for sure hearing the swelling music, if not the actual sounds of the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Eagles Were Just So Cool]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180931</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-eagles-were-just-so-cool"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T16:22:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ron Jaworski made a great throw, and Charlie Smith was open in the end zone. The Eagles had a first-quarter touchdown—until the refs threw a flag. Harold Carmichael, who would become a Hall of Famer, went in motion before the snap. He’d left too early. The play was called back, the Eagles punted, and three plays later Oakland Raiders quarterback Jim Plunkett hit Kenny King for an 80-yard score. The Eagles lost the Super Bowl, 27-10.
That was Super Bowl 15, which was played in 1981, in New Orleans. I thought about that play during the first quarter of the Eagles’ absurd 40-22 blowout over the Chiefs last night in Super Bowl 59. I’d been thinking a lot about Super Bowl 15, the Eagles’ first and only previous New Orleans Super Bowl appearance. Never mind that it happened before I was born; oldheads in my neighborhood who had attended the game filled me in during my childhood. They talked about that Eagles Super Bowl trip as if they’d made a medieval pilgrimage to the Abbey of Saint Gall (patron saint of birds). They also complained about the penalty, still, a decade-plus after the fact. It was bullshit, they’d say, not pausing to apologize for the word. They believed that the Eagles could’ve won if they’d just been able to tie the game at 7 there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Feb. 10: Telework]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180939</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-feb-10-telework"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's no puzzle like our Monday crossword. This week's puzzle was constructed by Kate Hawkins and Rachel Fabi, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Rachel and Kate went to the same college at (mostly) the same time and then worked for the same educational nonprofit but didn't meet each other until they started making crosswords nearly a decade later. They have since met J. Smith Cameron.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Best Free and Open Source Cheatsheet Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142191</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-cheatsheet-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T15:40:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cheatsheet is a concise set of notes used for quick reference. We recommend the best cheatsheet tools for Linux.
The post 6 Best Free and Open Source Cheatsheet Tools appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sled – embedded database]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142154</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/sled-embedded-database/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T15:32:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sled is an embedded database that's written in the Rust programming language.
The post sled – embedded database appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Win The Draft And You Can Beat Everyone’s Ass]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180932</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/win-the-draft-and-you-can-beat-everyones-ass"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T15:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Philadelphia Eagles are your decisive Super Bowl champions, and I could interpret their victory through a whole host of choices on the narrative play sheet. Jalen Hurts, the most serious person who has ever lived, finally getting the recognition he deserves as a fully-rounded quarterback. Eagles defensive coordinator Vic Fangio ruining Patrick Mahomes’s shit without having to call a single blitz. Kansas City’s atrocious pass protection finally catching up with them, same as in 2020. GOAT coronations withheld. Cooper DeJean’s pick-six. Saquon. The power of Italian thinking. Whatever take greases your pole, you can have at it.
So here’s mine: the Eagles won this title because they draft out of their fucking minds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Winter storm watch in effect (MON-2/10)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3820188</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-winter-storm-watch-in-effect-tue-2-10/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T14:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More winter weather is hitting the metro this week with high snow totals and a winter storm watch issued for the region.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick Mahomes Was In Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180909</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/patrick-mahomes-hell-eagles-chiefs-superbowl"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T14:02:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick Mahomes, the best quarterback in the world, spent Super Bowl Sunday being ground into a fine paste by the Eagles' pass rush, and then for good measure, jarred and preserved. Pressured on 38 percent of his snaps, Mahomes was hit 11 times, sacked six times, forced into a pair of picks, and fumbled the ball away once. In one of the more stunning stats in NFL history, the Eagles did all that without blitzing a single time. That trickles down—because they never had to send help, Philadelphia was able to stay in Cover 4 all game long, cutting off deep balls and quickly smothering anything underneath. "In order to make a team blitz, you have to be able to beat what they're showing." Mahomes said." And that's what we didn't do." 
Patrick Smith/Getty Images]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ExTiX – Ubuntu-based Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141010</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/extix-ubuntu-based-linux-distro/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T11:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ExTiX is a Linux distribution based on Ubuntu. 
The post ExTiX – Ubuntu-based Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Apple AirDrop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142236</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-apple-airdrop/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T11:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple AirDrop is a proprietary wireless ad hoc service. We recommend the best free and open source alternatives for Linux.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Apple AirDrop appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blanket Swimming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/blanket-swimming</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/blanket-swimming"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T08:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Blanket Swimming, an American electronic musician based in Kansas City.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlsaPlayer – heavily multi-threaded PCM player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142147</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alsaplayer-heavily-multi-threaded-pcm-player/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T07:03:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AlsaPlayer is a type of PCM player. It is heavily multi-threaded and tries to excercise the ALSA library and driver quite a bit. 
The post AlsaPlayer – heavily multi-threaded PCM player appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incoming Asteroid]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3049/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3049/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Eagles So Humiliated The Chiefs That Even Philly Fans Have To Believe]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180894</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-eagles-so-humiliated-the-chiefs-that-even-philly-fans-have-to-believe"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T03:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kansas City Chiefs did the sensible, defensive, and very orthodox thing when they won the opening coin flip of Super Bowl 59—they deferred possession until the second half. It was the last thing they controlled the entire evening.
The team that rope-a-doped their way to almost incandescent glory in 2024 instead found out that, sometimes, you just can't slip the punch. It wasn't the third-time's-not-the-charm jinx that did them in, it was the Philadelphia Eagles. And more decisively, it was the Eagles with only some Saquon Barkley, an entirely different M.O. That meant the Chiefs weren't undone by a single player but a smothering collective impervious to even Patrick Mahomes's multileveled sorceries. The final score of 40-22 grossly flattered the Chiefs and barely explained Philadelphia's dominance. It's as if the "GAME OVER" legend at the end of Kendrick Lamar's halftime show had been frantically cobbled together after Zack Baun's second quarter interception.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slint – blind-friendly Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142111</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/slint-blind-friendly-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T23:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slint is an easy-to-use, versatile, blind-friendly Linux distribution for 64-bit computers. It's based on Slackware.
The post Slint – blind-friendly Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Could Only Be One Hubie Brown]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180865</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/there-could-only-be-one-hubie-brown"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T23:12:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be wrong to say that Hubie Brown deserved a better sendoff than Bucks 135, Sixers 127 on Super Bowl Sunday because Hubie Brown was perfect for Bucks 135, Sixers 127. He would have bunny-hopped across an eight-lane highway for Bucks 135, Sixers 127 because for him—the last true basketball lifer—it wasn't the 135 or the 127 that moved him. It was the Bucks and Sixers part, and it would have been the same had he been given Pistons 112, Hornets 102, or Rockets 94, Raptors 87, or even anything involving the freshly re-deadified Wizards. Hubie was there unapologetically for The Game before him and only The Game before him. If you would have preferred Rockets-Raptors because it featured 81 points of better defense, you would have been wrong because every games was equal in his eyes— a chance to explain what was before him to people wanting to learn.
Hubie Brown is 91, and he looked and sounded every day of it 20 years ago when his coaching career ended. He coached somewhere for 30-some-odd years (even Wikipedia doesn't have firm dates for two of his high school jobs) and broadcasted somewhere for 29. He coached forever the same way, and he told the stories of the game the same way. He knew what he believed to be important, and walked and talked with that central precept for the entirety of his public life. He did it for so long and so unabashedly his way that he managed, somehow, to never fall out of fashion while anyone who came after him trying it Hubie's way was out of fashion immediately. The closest anyone came to doing Hubie was the much younger but no less self-assured JJ Redick, and he got in two years and change before he was hired to Hubie-up the Los Angeles Lakers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers’s Jets Tenure Ended In True Jets Fashion]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180859</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/aaron-rodgerss-jets-tenure-ended-in-true-jets-fashion"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T21:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brick Johnson wields a sure, swift sword, and even if he didn't wield this one, it's nice to think he did without even looking up from his Fortnite screen. This might just be a sins-of-the-father vehicle, but when the New York Jets make news, his name will be invoked because they are the Jets constantly doing Jets things.
If we are to trust Jay Glazer, and let's face it, he's no less trustworthy than any of the other sneaks who pull news out of the NFL before it can type up a release, Rodgers flew to New York last week to learn about his future with the Jets only to discover that he'd already had it. The Jets were, as they say, moving on to their next stupid idea, and their 19th starting quarterback since 2010, the last time they played more than the minimum allotted games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Hip Stretch To Help You Stay Sane]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180833</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-hip-stretch-to-help-you-stay-sane"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T19:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news is all shit right now. Sure, there are more artful, creative, and writerly,  ways to say that, but time is precious and writing something like that would prove nothing more than ownership of a thesaurus. 
If you're like me and millions of others, you are absorbing all this and wondering, "What can I do?" You can subscribe to journalism (which you probably already do! Yay!), donate money, volunteer, show up for your family, friends, and neighbors, and then what? That's the thing about the battle for a real democracy—it is not won in flashy, Hollywood fight scenes, though those do make for excellent inspirational images for sharing amid said battle for democracy. It's won in federal workers showing up to do their jobs. It's won in reporters showing up to do their jobs. It's won in a lot of us, in our own ways, showing up, doing our jobs, and not being assholes, even to the person who irritates you—and they are so, so annoying—but dammit we'll deal with that after we make sure there's still a republic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Superb Owl Lead Up That Never Was]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180851</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-superb-owl-lead-up-that-never-was"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T19:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This has not been a terribly memorable walk up to the Superb Owl, not in New Orleans, not across America, not even in Australia, where the NFL is staging a regular season game in 2026 as a very belated punishment to the Los Angeles Rams for those uniforms. And if you can't be weird in Louisiana, well, what exactly is the point?
When your biggest moment of the week, after all, is Roger Goodell leaning hard into an 18th game, you have a serious cultural dud on your hands. The football will be the football, of course, and as matchups go Eagles-Chiefs is not far from the best you can do. But New Orleans might be the last bastion of the pre-corporate days when the town created the atmosphere and it was up to the visitors to keep up. This time, the weirdest thing we got will be something we have to conjure in our own minds—the big game with a sitting President (Uncle Dismal) and a potential rival in 2028 (Stephen A. Smith). Neither is qualified to do the job, as one has proven and the other certainly would if given the chance, but the moment Smith's name appeared on a poll listing potential Democratic candidates and garnering 2 percent, we took an irrevocable turn toward a world in which Prince Andrew seems leaderly. All that is left for the rest of us is to find a country without an extradition treaty out of the way of the nuclear winds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickgui – virtual machine manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142101</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/quickgui-virtual-machine-manager/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T18:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quickgui is a graphical user interface for the Quickemu virtual machine manager.
The post Quickgui – virtual machine manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Snowstorm(s?) likely in KC (SUN-2/9)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3819475</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-snowstorms-likely-in-kc-sun-2-9/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T17:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Super Bowl Sunday, and New Orleans yesterday hit a record 85° at the airport. Here in Kansas City, we've dumped back into the colder air today and this cold will be with us for a while it appears. It's one ingredient to the set-up for multiple snow chances into next weekend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Snowstorm(s?) likely in KC (SUN-2/9)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3819475</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-snowstorms-likely-in-kc-sun-2-9/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T17:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Super Bowl Sunday and while New Orleans yesterday hit a record 85° at the airport...here in KC we've dumped back into the colder air today and this cold will be with us for awhile it appears. It's one ingredient to the set-up for multiple snow chances into next weekend. There will be a more [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BinEd – binary / hex editor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142123</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/bined-binary-hex-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T16:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BinEd is an editor for binary data (hex viewer/editor). It's written in Java so runs under a wide range of platforms.
The post BinEd – binary / hex editor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart.Framework – PHP and JavaScript web framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142066</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/smart-framework-php-javascript-web-framework/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T16:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart.Framework is a practical, modern and high performance PHP / JavaScript Framework for Web featuring Middlewares and MVC.
The post Smart.Framework – PHP and JavaScript web framework appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[19 Best Free and Open Source Linux Astronomy Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=4452</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/astronomy/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T15:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article focuses on selecting the best free astronomy software available for Linux.
The post 19 Best Free and Open Source Linux Astronomy Apps appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TiMidity++ – MIDI to WAVE converter and player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142143</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/timidity-midi-wave-converter-player/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T13:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TiMidity++ is a software synthesizer. It can play MIDI files by converting them into PCM waveform data.
The post TiMidity++ – MIDI to WAVE converter and player appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Best Free and Open Source CLI Tools to Find and Delete Duplicate Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139565</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-cli-tools-find-delete-duplicate-files/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T13:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This roundup focuses on free and open source command-line tools that help you find and remove duplicate files.
The post 15 Best Free and Open Source CLI Tools to Find and Delete Duplicate Files appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kinship Cafe is leaving Kansas City, Kansas. But the coffee shop isn't closing for good]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-02-09/kinship-cafe-strawberry-hill-independence-overland-park</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-02-09/kinship-cafe-strawberry-hill-independence-overland-park"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TJ Roberts first opened Kinship Cafe in 2021 in Strawberry Hill. After a lease deal fell through with his property owner, Roberts is leaving his original location behind for new shops in Independence and Overland Park.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Wilmore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glow – render Markdown on the command-line]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142081</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/glow-render-markdown-command-line/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T08:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glow is a terminal based markdown reader designed from the ground up to bring out the beauty—and power—of the CLI.
The post Glow – render Markdown on the command-line appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tyler Beede Holds Showcase For Interested Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840977</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/tyler-beede-holds-showcase-for-interested-teams.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T03:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right-hander Tyler Beede threw for teams held a pro day for interested teams on Friday, per a report from Ari Alexander of KPRC2. Alexander adds that Beede’s fastball was in the range of 93-95mph and that the Astros and Royals both were represented at the righty’s showcase. Beede, 32 in May, was selected in the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terrapin Vulnerability Scanner for the Terrapin attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142076</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/terrapin-vulnerability-scanner-terrapin-attack/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T23:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terrapin Vulnerability Scanner  can be used to determine the vulnerability of an SSH client or server against the Terrapin Attack.
The post Terrapin Vulnerability Scanner for the Terrapin attack appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[J.J. Picollo Discusses Royals Offseason Pursuits, Outfield Mix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840961</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/j-j-picollo-discusses-royals-offseason-pursuits-outfield-mix.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T21:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A year ago, the Royals had just put the finishing touching on an extension with budding superstar Bobby Witt Jr. that served as a capstone on the busiest and most aggressive offseason the club had put together in years. That strong offseason effort led to an 86-win season and a trip to the NLDS, where…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pop PHP Framework – toolkit for rapid application development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142062</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pop-php-framework-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T21:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pop PHP Framework contains a group of core components and an additional 30+ components that serve as a toolkit.
The post Pop PHP Framework – toolkit for rapid application development appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bochs – IA-32 (x86) PC emulator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142094</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/bochs-ia-32-x86-pc-emulator/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T20:39:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bochs is a highly portable IA-32 (x86) PC emulato, that runs on most popular platforms. 
The post Bochs – IA-32 (x86) PC emulator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Melt – backup and restore SSH private keys using memorable seed phrases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142085</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/melt-backup-restore-ssh-private-keys/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T19:38:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Melt is a utility that lets you backup and restore SSH private keys using memorable seed phrases.
The post Melt – backup and restore SSH private keys using memorable seed phrases appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cassowary – run Windows virtual machine on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142098</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/cassowary-windows-virtual-machine-linux/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T16:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cassowary lets you run a Windows virtual machine and use Windows applications on Linux as if they were native applications.
The post Cassowary – run Windows virtual machine on Linux appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Best Free and Open Source Media Players]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=70925</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-media-players/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T16:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A media player is software that lets you watch video and listen to music on your computer. We cover the best free and open source options.
The post 16 Best Free and Open Source Media Players appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>