<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-10-02T16:20:07.421Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World’s Richest Biglaw Firm Announces Another HUGE Partnership Class]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075741</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/worlds-richest-biglaw-firm-announces-another-huge-partnership-class/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T16:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With 200 new partners, how many of them will enter the firm's equity ranks?
The post World’s Richest Biglaw Firm Announces Another HUGE Partnership Class appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Main Street Saints’ lone full-length album gets wax treatment for 25th anniversary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850647</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/just-like-heaven-main-street-saints-lone-full-length-album-gets-wax-treatment-for-25th-anniversary/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Main Street Saints In the ‘90s, few genres of music were as omnipresent in Kansas City as punk rock. Thanks to places like Fred P. Ott’s, The Pub (now The Brick), and Davey’s Uptown, along with all-ages venues like The FuseBox, The Daily Grind, El Torreon, and Gee Coffee, you could step out to hear loud, fast,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Borussia Dortmund’s Newest Star Is Born]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169005</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/borussia-dortmunds-newest-star-is-born"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Borussia Dortmund is famous for something, it is for being the most consistent, and so far the most successful, challenger to Bayern Munich's Bundesliga supremacy in the 21st century. If Borussia Dortmund is famous for something else, it is for being Europe's premier finishing school for young talents destined for bigger and better salaries and transfer fees upon graduation. Here's a short list of players who have passed through Dortmund in the last 15 years or so, in no particular order: Robert Lewandowski, Ousmane Dembélé, Jadon Sancho, Ilkay Gündogan, Mario Götze, Christian Pulisic, Jude Bellingham, Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang, Erling Haaland, Mats Hummels ... Ok, maybe the list isn't so short, and not all of those players starred upon leaving Dortmund. However, the impressive history of talent detection and refinement is there, and that list is about to get a little bit longer, now that Karim Adeyemi appears to be hitting a new level of excellence.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lv1mY5JAzyo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gen AI + Law Firm Data: Gaining A Key Competitive Edge [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075723</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/gen-ai-law-firm-data-gaining-a-key-competitive-edge/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join this webinar on October 30th to learn how your firm can deliver better client service, improve case outcomes, and empower its teams. 
The post Gen AI + Law Firm Data: Gaining A Key Competitive Edge appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Litera and Above The Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create A Fulfilling Law Practice]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075735</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/how-to-create-a-fulfilling-law-practice/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These lawyers align their skills with their passions.
The post How To Create A Fulfilling Law Practice appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: A taste of summer with no rain (WED-10/2)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3682930</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-a-taste-of-summer-with-no-rain-wed-10-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a crisp morning in the area with lows down into the lower 40s with mid 30s is some of the outlying areas, and if there was some frost out there somewhere, I wouldn't have been shocked. This cooler weather will moderate today thanks to south winds this afternoon and tomorrow looks to be [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personalize Patient Care With Confidence Through Efficient, HIPAA-Compliant Data Usage]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075738</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/09/personalize-patient-care-with-confidence-through-efficient-hipaa-compliant-data-usage/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:03:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible procurement and handling of data and digital marketing insights by hospitals can generate useful information to improve patient wellness and operational efficiency without compromising compliance.
The post Personalize Patient Care With Confidence Through Efficient, HIPAA-Compliant Data Usage appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WENDY ERTERR via MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fat Bear Week Delayed By Bear Killing Bear]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168970</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/fat-bear-week-delayed-by-bear-killing-bear"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T13:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My first pets were a pair of hamsters, sisters from the same litter. I was surprised that such tiny little brains could hold such distinct personalities: Harley, golden and white, was more athletic, more aloof, notably smarter, happy to play by herself; Yankee, a chubby cream-colored meatball, craved human touch—she'd run to the door at the top of her cage and stare up, unable to see much with a hamster's terrible eyesight but secure in the knowledge that I'd soon come to scoop her up. All she wanted was to be held and petted. She was the biggest little sweetie on god's green Earth. The sisters got along grandly in their shared, three-tiered cage. And then one day out of nowhere, and for reasons I never understood and I suspect they didn't either, Yankee starting beating the shit out of Harley every time they'd cross paths—biting her, scratching her, screaming with fury at the mere sight of her previously beloved sister. We separated them, giving each their own cage, and they each lived out their long happy hamster lives in solitary. But it was a good lesson for young me. No matter how fuzzy or friend-shaped, creatures are not simply furry people and can't be viewed or treated as such. Animals are animals.
Grizzly bears, despite looking an awful lot like thousand-pound hamsters, are ur-predators. They are secretive, unknowable, capable of tremendous acts of strength and violence. Our ancestors knew this: The word "bear" was originally a euphemism, invented by our Germanic-speaking predecessors afraid to use the animal's true name, made taboo out of a superstitious fear that speaking it would cause them to meet one. Our Enlightenment-era men of science were no less intimidated—it was designated Ursus arctos horribilis for a reason. This week in Alaska, nature provided a morbid and useful reminder that bears are bears, with all that entails.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.02.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075742</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-02-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T13:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Former Jaguars financial administrator in jail for embezzling millions in team funds for his own gambling suing FanDuel accusing the app of exploiting his addiction. Somewhere Diddy is preparing a filing against baby oil manufacturers. [Law360]
* Fifth Circuit stops Amazon case to consider whether the NLRB has secretly been unconstitutional for the last 90 years and they're the first ones to notice. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Record labels suing the internet archive over old recordings, draping themselves in concern for the rights of the artists hoping no one ever notices that the labels routinely and aggressively rip off artists, especially artists of color. [Rolling Stone]
* California plan to break with the NCBE monopoly sent to the state supreme court. [ABA Journal]
* Lawyers often victims of workplace bullying. [Reuters]
* Profile of the law school dean who helped push Trump's election denial efforts. [The Intercept]
* New tax hypo just dropped: "it's not a vacant commercial property, it's a snail farm." [Lowering the Bar]
The post Morning Docket: 10.02.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Shambling, Half-Dead Braves Have Gone Far Enough]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168968</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-shambling-half-dead-braves-have-gone-far-enough"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T13:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Atlanta Braves will play their second elimination game in three days Wednesday afternoon, when Max Fried leads them against Joe Musgrove of the San Diego Padres in Game 2 of their National League Wild Card series. With all due respect to Atlanta's handful of healthy players, the Braves are not wanted here! Four of their, what, six best players are out; the team only nosed into the Wild Card at all because of a preposterous first-in-history gap-day doubleheader, where everyone knew going in that both teams could advance with a split. It's hard to imagine a less legitimate playoff berth than one earned in the second of these two games, after your opponent has already lost all motivation.
It's clear that God has seen enough of the Braves. Three road teams won on Tuesday, including the even more road weary New York Mets, who haven't played a game at home since Sept. 22 and who failed America by going hangover mode in Monday's late game and allowing Atlanta to shamble onwards. The Braves, meanwhile, advanced one single runner to third base in nine innings Tuesday night, struck out 15 times, and were ruthlessly blanked by playoff debutante Michael King and a pair of Padres relievers. For lack of anything even vaguely resembling a suitable alternative, Atlanta manager Brian Snitker handed the ball to A.J. Smith-Shawver, a 21-year-old prospect with fewer than 30 total innings of work in the majors, who threw 87 pitches for the big club this year, all of them back on May 23. Smith-Shawver watched his team squander a first-inning scoring opportunity, then took the mound in a Braves uniform for just the second time in 2024. Seven pitches later, this happened:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Black Feast Week and flavor-packed aguachiles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853320</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-black-feast-week-and-flavor-packed-aguachiles/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T13:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matties Food // Photo By Tiffany Watts Mattie’s Foods for Black Feast Week As Kansas City celebrates its first-ever inaugural KC Black Feast Week, hosted by The Kansas City Defender, there’s no better time to spotlight the city’s extraordinary Black culinary talent. From October 1st to October 14th, Black Feast Week highlights nearly every major Black-owned restaurant in Kansas City....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is Why You Get an Ace: Royals Win Series-Opening Pitchers’ Duel]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=447695</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/this-is-why-you-get-an-ace-royals-win-series-opening-pitchers-duel/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T01:45:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“As Tommy Pham says, whenever you allow the other team to score zero runs, you have a 99.999% chance to win that game."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Baumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Trump Judge Is The Cream Of The Crap — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075732</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/this-trump-judge-is-the-cream-of-the-crap-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now That's A Really Big What If: Legal mastermind finds clearly established legal concept unconstitutional.
Straight From The Mouths Of Summer Associates: These are the top Biglaw firms to work for!
What Happened To Neutrality?: Judge steps down after getting caught in the Jan. 6th crowd.
Dude, Where's My Helicopter: Negligent parking job costs the Army millions.
The post This Trump Judge Is The Cream Of The Crap — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Defense Lawyer For ‘El Chapo’ To Successful Ranchera Singer]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075698</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/from-defense-lawyer-for-el-chapo-to-successful-ranchera-singer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T22:18:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lawyer says she sang for 'El Chapo,' and now she's singing for her fans.
The post From Defense Lawyer For ‘El Chapo’ To Successful Ranchera Singer appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Lawyers Discover Abiding Concern For Witness Safety And Sanctity Of Jury Pool]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075721</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/trump-lawyers-discover-abiding-concern-for-witness-safety-and-sanctity-of-jury-pool/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T21:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You bet.
The post Trump Lawyers Discover Abiding Concern For Witness Safety And Sanctity Of Jury Pool appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recs with Merritt turns through some of hottest vinyl releases of October 2024, including Leon Bridges, Samara Joy, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853241</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/recs-with-merritt-turns-through-some-of-hottest-vinyl-releases-of-october-2024-including-leon-bridges-samara-joy-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T21:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recs With Merritt. // Art by Cassondra Jones Records with Merritt is Marion Merritt’s vinyl store in Westport with partner Ann Stewart. As a staple in our community for nearly a decade, we’ve partnered with Merritt for a monthly column, where the tastemaker shares her picks for the best wax releases to look forward to grabbing, divided by release date. Here’s Marion Merritt’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marion Merritt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holy Intellectual Property Defeat!]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075727</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/holy-intellectual-property-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T20:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He even told them his whole plan...
The post Holy Intellectual Property Defeat! appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ferocious feline felony body-horror flick Booger marks the revenge of childless cat ladies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=843382</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/feline-felony-booger-is-the-dark-body-horror-comedy-that-2024-deserves/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T20:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cat is outta the bag on this year’s most slept-on indie horror flick. I’d apologize for the terrible pun, but I’m fairly certain its right in line with what the filmmakers set out to achieve here. Booger follows Anna (Grace Glowicki) from NYC, whose best friend and roommate Izzy unexpectedly shakes off this mortal coil. Anna’s attempts to regain...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Julius Randle’s Knicks Tenure Was Exhilarating And Infuriating]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168780</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/julius-randles-knicks-tenure-was-exhilarating-and-infuriating"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T20:17:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Behind Randle's brilliance lurked many mysteries. He's an elite athlete by NBA standards, conditioned to the max, with rare agility to his size; somehow this never translated into even average defense. One night he'd give everything for 40 minutes and end in sweat-soaked triumph; the next game, he'd give up on the team in a thousand tiny ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Court Dismisses ROSS Intelligence’s Remaining Antitrust Claim Against Thomson Reuters]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075697</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/09/federal-court-dismisses-ross-intelligences-remaining-antitrust-claim-against-thomson-reuters.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T20:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Still to be decided in the case are TR’s claims that ROSS violated its copyrights by unlawfully copying TR’s legal materials in order to use them to train its own AI-driven legal research platform.
The post Federal Court Dismisses ROSS Intelligence’s Remaining Antitrust Claim Against Thomson Reuters appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHL’s Moose Jaw Warriors Keep Red in Rotation With New Third Jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82457</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/01/whls-moose-jaw-warriors-keep-red-in-rotation-with-new-third-jersey/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After ruby red 40th anniversary jersey proved popular last season, Warriors have unveiled new red alternate jersey that follows striping pattern of regular home, road jerseys]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dangerous Parking Job Costs Army $3.3M]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075714</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/dangerous-parking-job-costs-army-3-3m/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T19:15:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No wearing shades in the dark, and no parking a darn helicopter in people's path. 
The post Dangerous Parking Job Costs Army $3.3M appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kon Tiki and Conchita Tacos blend island-style booze and bites to the Crossroads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850628</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/rum-dont-walk-kon-tiki-and-conchita-tacos-blend-island-style-booze-and-bites-to-the-crossroads/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T19:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Kon Tiki and Conchita Tacos When it comes to nailing a Tiki concept, having positive energy is every bit as important as having good rum behind the bar. That’s what brought about the unofficial slogan for Kon Tiki, which recently opened its doors next to Up-Down in the Crossroads Arts District. For Chad Troutwine and Chris Seferyn—the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Baranowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Sense Passwords Coming To Law Firms Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075680</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/common-sense-passwords-coming-to-law-firms-soon/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T18:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Be open to changing the way you protect your data.
The post Common Sense Passwords Coming To Law Firms Soon appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharon D. Nelson, John W. Simek, and Michael C. Maschke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Judge Proves Again That She’s One Of America’s Least Qualified Jurists]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075706</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/trump-judge-proves-again-why-shes-known-as-one-of-americas-least-qualified-jurists/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T17:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Judge declares that 'Lincoln's Law' has been unconstitutional for over 160 years.
The post Trump Judge Proves Again That She’s One Of America’s Least Qualified Jurists appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Yourself A Mate Who Will Be Your Sex Umbrella]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168761</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/get-yourself-a-mate-who-will-be-your-sex-umbrella"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T17:36:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Desert locusts are pests of biblical proportions, devastating crops and the communities that depend on them. Left to their own devices, the locusts are solitary and greenish, mostly indistinguishable from any other grasshopper. When the environment is right and the insects' populations begin to grow, however, the locusts can sense their growing numbers and undergo a dramatic transformation into their gregarious phase. They change their color, their body size, and even their brain. And then the locusts begin to swarm, flying in groups of tens of billions that can reach up to 100 square miles, all in search of food.
Although Schistocerca gregaria is one of the world's most devastating pests, "the desert locust has been little studied in the field, and much of its ecology is still unknown," said Koutaro Ould Maeno, a locust expert at the Japan International Research Center for Agricultural Science.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I Would Do It Over Again’: Judge Resigns Amid Probe Into His Attendance At January 6 Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075709</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/i-would-do-it-over-again-judge-resigns-amid-probe-into-his-attendance-at-january-6-rally/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T17:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['Yeah, I went to Trump's rally,' the judge said -- and he has no regrets about doing so.
The post ‘I Would Do It Over Again’: Judge Resigns Amid Probe Into His Attendance At January 6 Rally appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Odie Leigh’s Monday Bottleneck show was a glimpse into a secret ultimate fandom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853232</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/odie-leighs-monday-bottleneck-show-was-a-glimpse-into-a-secret-ultimate-fandom/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T17:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Odie Leigh // Photo by Nick Spacek Odie Leigh w/ Valley James The Bottleneck Monday, Sept. 30 Sometimes, you get an email about a show you’d forgotten you expressed interest in, so you take a shower, grab your camera, and head out. I wasn’t that familiar with either artist performing Monday night at the Bottleneck. Odie Leigh was one of those...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024-25 NHL Team Twitter (or X) Logo Hashtags]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82467</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/01/2024-25-nhl-team-twitter-or-x-logo-hashtags/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T16:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The full list of custom NHL team logo hashtags dropped on Twitter/X this morning. Most of the clubs kept things the same as in previous years—consistency is good for familiarity, after all. The Ducks and Kings have their new logos added to their tags, while we’ve got a new one]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Creamer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything We’re Looking Forward To In The 2024 MLB Playoffs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168849</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/everything-were-looking-forward-to-in-the-2024-mlb-playoffs"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T16:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Baseball is good right now, and it's going to get better in a few hours, when the playoffs begin. To celebrate, we put together a list of things we're excited to see and experience this postseason. If you're looking for your own reasons to get locked in for the playoffs, or if you'd just like to read about a long-lost ritual in which a Defector staffer tried and failed to get his small sons to kiss a photo of Bryce Harper, then please read on.
A Resurgent Giancarlo Stanton]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How To Make A Difference For Survivors Of Intimate Partner Violence [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075408</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/learn-how-to-make-a-difference-for-survivors-of-intimate-partner-violence/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T16:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build your skills and knowledge to better advocate for intimate partner violence survivors who need legal assistance.
The post Learn How To Make A Difference For Survivors Of Intimate Partner Violence appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Practising Law Institute</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 81-81 Red Sox Weren’t The Most Mediocre Team Of The Season]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168855</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-81-81-red-sox-werent-the-most-mediocre-team-of-the-season"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T16:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Boston Red Sox have obtained what many would consider the ultimate in mediocrity: a final record of 81-81. Though they got off to a strong start of winning a game and then losing a game, or vice versa, they performed too well during the rest of the season to achieve what I would consider historic mediocrity: the highest percentage of games that ended in a .500 record. Their superior competition ended up being their divisional rival.
The last time we checked in with the Red Sox in the race to .500, in the middle of June, the live standings had them at second all-time behind this year's San Diego Padres. While the Padres' second-half surge completely shed any accusations of mediocrity en route to the playoffs—23 out of their 26 games finished at .500 happened within the first 72 games of the season—the Red Sox gave their fans just a little more hope with an 81-81 finish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: A Kansas tale from Paul Koudounaris’ new book Faithful Unto Death]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853190</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/exclusive-a-kansas-tale-from-paul-koudounaris-new-book-faithful-unto-death/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T16:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Private Scott and Laddie. // photo from the collection of Paul Koudounaris Out this week from Thames & Hudson, author Paul Koudounaris’ new book, Faithful Unto Death, tells the history of “Pet cemeteries, animal graves, and eternal devotion” with emotional heft and an eye for detail. From Mr. Winbridge’s burial of a dog named Cherry at London’s Hyde Park to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen Sanchez was a blast from the past with vintage radio show framing at Madrid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853060</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/stephen-sanchez-was-a-blast-from-the-past-with-vintage-radio-show-framing-at-madrid/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T15:36:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Sanchez & The Moon Crests. // photo by Haley Mullenix Friday night, the fine folks of Kansas City pulled out their best dresses, slacks, and hairdos and made their way to The Midland Theatre where Steven Sanchez & The Moon Crests, along with support from The Brook & The Bluff, set the stage for a night of revelry. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haley Mullenix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 More Questions For A Patent Podcast Pro (Part II)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075486</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/3-more-questions-for-a-patent-podcast-pro-part-ii/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T15:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Considering its importance to today's IP-driven economy, it is surprising that there is not more coverage of USPTO goings-on.
The post 3 More Questions For A Patent Podcast Pro (Part II) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaston Kroub</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHL’s Calgary Hitmen Unveil 30th Anniversary Logo, Jersey]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82449</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/01/whls-calgary-hitmen-unveil-30th-anniversary-logo-jersey/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anniversary logo takes team's primary logo and switches almost all details to copper, adds "XXX" on stick tape to denote 30th anniversary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Biglaw Firms, Ranked By Summer Associates (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075677</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-best-biglaw-firms-ranked-by-summer-associates-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T14:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What matters most to summer associates? Here are the Top 10 Biglaw firms, in their eyes.
The post The Best Biglaw Firms, Ranked By Summer Associates (2024) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Activate Vinnie Pasquantino For Wild Card Series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=826104</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/royals-activate-vinnie-pasquantino-for-wild-card-series.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T14:14:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced their Wild Card Series roster this morning, revealing within that first baseman Vinnie Pasquantino is being reinstated from the injured list. He’ll be back in the middle of the Kansas City lineup taking on Orioles ace Corbin Burnes in today’s Game 1 matchup. It’s a rapid return for Pasquantino, who suffered a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FTC Is Suing PBMs Over Insulin Prices. Will It Be Successful?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075681</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/09/ftc-sue-pbms-insulin/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T14:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Trade Commission has sued CVS Caremark, Express Scripts and Optum Rx, alleging that they engage in 'anticompetitive and unfair rebating practices' as it relates to insulin. One legal expert believes the FTC might win this legal battle.
The post The FTC Is Suing PBMs Over Insulin Prices. Will It Be Successful? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MARISSA PLESCIA - MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pete Rose, All-American]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168841</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/pete-rose-all-american"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T13:52:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Pete Rose's death was announced on Monday night, a lot of clever microphone addicts opened their obligatory thumbnail summaries of him by explaining that he was "a complicated figure." It’s the sort of thing people say about people when they can’t believe that the person they're describing is really just what they appear to be. Nothing could have been more obviously wrong, in this case, including the concept of hitting on 17. The last thing in the world Pete Rose ever was, for all the things he was or purported to be, was complicated.
He wasn't complicated as a player, a manager, or in the end, as a self-parodic martyr. Rose had smaller measures of the skills that great ballplayers have but a greater capacity to employ them tirelessly, which is what his admirers always admired. He had one overarching gift, though, that covered by the play and the player—the determination and ability, through sheer persistence, to make you make a stand about him. His was the purest kind of narcissism, one so utterly naked that it never needed a second level. He knew that you were only interested in hearing him speak on the subject of him, and that became increasingly true as he grew from boyhood to late boyhood to middle-aged boyhood to octogenarian boyhood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mets And Braves Played All Summer In A Day]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168835</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-mets-and-braves-played-all-summer-in-a-day"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T13:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were various scenarios involving the three teams competing for the last two NL Wild Card spots—the Mets, the Braves, and the rapidly deflating Arizona Diamondbacks—that might have made Monday's doubleheader, which made up two games that the NL East rivals were unable to play while Hurricane Helene drenched greater Atlanta, less meaningful. There were some scenarios that might have led the league to remove the games from the schedule entirely for reasons of competitive hygiene. None of those came to pass. The Mets and Braves were more likely to claim those last two spots than the Diamondbacks, but both would be worse off for the labor of earning it—only getting swept would let Arizona ace either one out of the last spot, but a hard-fought split would leave both at a significant disadv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from the Editor: Diagrams and charts mending broken hearts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850619</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/letter-from-the-editor-diagrams-and-charts-mending-broken-hearts/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T13:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Welcome, dearest readers, into the fold of the October 2024 issue of The Pitch—a product homegrown right here in KC. As you can tell from our cover story, homegrown is certainly a theme for this month’s issue. The narratives you’ll find us tackling in these pages all share a common thread of who in the metro...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.01.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075704</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-01-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T12:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Judge reassigned after mining In Living Color for the jokes best left in the 90s during a whole day of inappropriate remarks because, to put it in terms he might understand, "the court system don't play that." [ABA Journal]
* Big win for legal reporting in Idaho, where the top court official had been holding pleadings back in an effort to keep them from making the news. [Courthouse News Service]
* El Chapo lawyer launches music career. [AP]
* Blame US Trade laws for fentanyl.  [Reuters]
* Alaska's taxing AI and they've got a pretty good plan. [Law360]
* It's not really an answer to antitrust to spin off stores into a new competitor... and then immediately shut down that competitor. [Law360]
* Lawyer cops to fraudulent Iraq war claims. [Guardian]
The post Morning Docket: 10.01.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: M. Ward brought soothing soul (and Leslie Stevens) to The Madrid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853062</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-m-ward-brought-soothing-soul-and-leslie-stevens-to-the-madrid/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T12:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[M. Ward. // photo by Whitney Young M. Ward with Leslie Stevens The Madrid Tuesday, September 24 Last Tuesday, indie rocker M. Ward came to Madrid in support of last year’s Anti Records release, Supernatural Thing, with fellow singer-songwriter Leslie Stevens in tow. Our photographer, Whitney Young, was there to capture it all. M. Ward M. Ward setlist Never Had...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Whitney Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Potential Big Change To The U.S. News Law Rankings! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075689</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/potential-big-change-to-the-u-s-news-law-rankings-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T23:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yale Hits Historic Low In Rankings Prediction!: Will it ever manage to recover?
Bigger Plans? Big Apple: This Biglaw firm sets its sights on New York and North America.
Look Out, Doc Reviewers: AI is coming fast for the first pass. 
Women Making History: Davis Wright Tremaine announces its first female firmwide managing partner.
The Crimes Are Coming From Inside The House: Former DA employee accused of making a bomb threat.
The post Potential Big Change To The U.S. News Law Rankings! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Democratic Proposal To Expand The Supreme Court]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075670</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/the-democratic-proposal-to-expand-the-supreme-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T23:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Faith in the Supreme Court is at a low, and this Senator thinks reform is the way to go.
The post The Democratic Proposal To Expand The Supreme Court appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alabama Purges Voter Rolls, VRA Be Damned]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075687</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/alabama-purges-voter-rolls-vra-be-damned/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T22:18:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alabama SOS Wes Allen might not have consulted a lawyer about the latest voter purge. But he's definitely going to need one now.
The post Alabama Purges Voter Rolls, VRA Be Damned appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is It Time For Joe Biden To ‘Dissolve’ The Supreme Court?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075650</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/is-it-time-for-joe-biden-to-dissolve-the-supreme-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T21:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After all, the high court is nothing more than 'Trump's harem,' the prolific author said.
The post Is It Time For Joe Biden To ‘Dissolve’ The Supreme Court? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alyssa Thomas Knows Only One Way To Hit A Dagger]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168753</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/alyssa-thomas-knows-only-one-way-to-hit-a-dagger"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T21:06:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daggers don’t really belong on a spectrum. They matter so much more for their result—finality, punctuation, hope extinguished—than for their means that it’s kind of silly to compare one to another. Even so, there was something especially vicious about the last shot Alyssa Thomas took Sunday in Game 1 of the Sun-Lynx semifinals. It was the dagger-iest dagger you’ll ever see.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black-owned eateries launch extensive food week benefiting Missouri’s longest-standing Black-owned bookstore]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851410</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/a-new-food-week-highlights-kansas-citys-black-owned-eateries/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T21:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new type of food week has pulled up a seat in Kansas City. From October 1 – 14, Kansas City Defender is hosting the first-ever KC Black Feast Week. Kansas City Defender is a youth-led Black media and community organization.  With a goal of highlighting KC’s Black culinary talent as well as uplifting Black-owned businesses, the two-week event will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congress To Federal Judges: You Are Not Above The Law]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075660</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/congress-to-federal-judges-you-are-not-above-the-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T20:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, Congress reintroduced legislation that will extend federal anti-discrimination protections to more than 30,000 federal judiciary employees, including law clerks and federal public defenders.
The post Congress To Federal Judges: You Are Not Above The Law appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aliza Shatzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Adams Argues That Turkish Delights Slipped Into His Pasties Were Tips, Not Bribes]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075678</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/eric-adams-argues-that-turkish-delights-slipped-into-his-pasties-were-tips-not-bribes/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T20:02:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks, Chief Justice Roberts!
The post Eric Adams Argues That Turkish Delights Slipped Into His Pasties Were Tips, Not Bribes appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[League One Volleyball Unveils Jerseys For All 6 Teams in Inaugural Season]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82423</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/09/30/league-one-volleyball-unveils-jerseys-for-all-6-teams-in-inaugural-season/other/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teams based in Atlanta, Austin, Houston, Madison, Omaha and Salt Lake will take the court for LOVB's inaugural season in January 2025]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clippers Fans, And Only Clippers Fans, Can Now Buy Alcohol At 3:17 In The Morning In California]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168765</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/clippers-fans-and-only-clippers-fans-can-now-buy-alcohol-at-317-in-the-morning-in-california"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T19:43:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For too long, as they suffered under a purple-and-gold yoke, Los Angeles Clippers fans were familiar with a very particular sort of pain: The arena stopped serving alcohol at the end of the third quarter, meaning anyone seeking a premium-style VIP luxury bar experience in the dreary confines of an NBA arena during the fourth quarter was out of luck. The thrill of watching James Harden take his 13th and 14th free throws of the night as the Clips try to overcome a late 11-point deficit just doesn't hit the same without a $22 domestic draft. The experience of recounting said free throws five hours later over a $31 gin and tonic is equally paltry if you can't share it with fellow VIPs in the arena where Harden shot those free throws.
Thankfully, California governor Gavin Newsom has solved this pressing problem. On Sunday, Newsom signed AB-3206, an extremely specific bill that will allow alcohol sales to continue until 4:00 a.m. in VIP areas of the new Clippers arena in Inglewood until Jan. 1, 2030. California state law otherwise prohibits alcohol sales between 2 a.m. and 6 a.m.; now, thanks to the state legislature, an arena that has yet to host its first NBA game can boast of the first exception. The bill does not name the Clippers arena specifically, though its carve-out in state liquor law applies strictly to vendors operating in a "fully enclosed arena with a seating capacity of at least 18,000 seats located in the City of Inglewood," and only within a "private area in the arena no larger than 2,500 square feet" after events.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Well-Known Midsize Boston Firm Shutters After Biglaw Firms Poach Half Its Lawyers]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075652</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/well-known-midsize-boston-firm-shutters-after-biglaw-firms-poach-half-its-lawyers/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T19:12:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The longtime midsize firm was unable to find a suitable merger partner to save it from closure.
The post Well-Known Midsize Boston Firm Shutters After Biglaw Firms Poach Half Its Lawyers appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLB, Nike to Fix Most 2024 Uniform Issues in 2025-26]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82445</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/09/30/mlb-nike-to-fix-most-2024-uniform-issues-in-2025-26/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T19:10:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is why pencils have erasers! This afternoon, Major League Baseball announced a series of changes to their on-field Nike uniforms following the disastrous rollout of the new Vapor Premier line before the 2024 season. The decision was finalized following discussions between MLB, Nike, Fanatics, and the Major League Baseball]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Creamer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Megalopolis’ Is Both Ingeniously Stupid And Stupidly Genius]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168693</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/megalopolis-is-both-ingeniously-stupid-and-stupidly-genius"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T19:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most honest Francis Ford Coppola has ever been on celluloid isn't present in any of his own movies. Rather, it can be found in a 1991 documentary shot by his wife, Eleanor. Hearts of Darkness, a project started by Eleanor and later finished by co-directors George Hickenlooper and Fax Bahr, tells the story of Francis’s travails while making Apocalypse Now, a movie that was already considered a canonical classic of the New Hollywood era by the time the documentary was released. But at the time of filming, the infamously beleaguered production of Apocalypse Now was just another example of FFC’s limitless, egomaniacal ambition to achieve the ultimate spectacle-as-political-statement, that would speak to something profound about Vietnam, about America, about mankind.
Coppola at that point in time was one of the biggest directors in the world, coming off his two enormously successful Godfather movies and the critically beloved The Conversation. He had long planned to adapt Joseph Conrad's 1899 novel Heart of Darkness, turning it into a story of the Vietnam War that journeyed into the dark night of the human soul. Eleanor’s documentary is about the dark night of Francis’s soul. At times, he is the picture of the overindulged, male auteur full of grandeur and vanity, holding court on the importance of cinema and art and ambition and himself. At other times, he is a ball of exposed nerves, full of anxiety about the difficulty of the production, about the personal wealth he has poured into the film when outside funding ran out, and, worst of all, about the prospect of failing to make a good movie. At one point, he talks about the sin of pretentiousness, about how every artist is terrified of being seen as pretentious, so much so that they pull back or play safe in detrimental ways. He tells his wife that he cannot allow himself to be afraid to be seen as pretentious, as it’s the only way to really go for it. It is a risk worth taking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In failing to protect voting rights, the Kansas Supreme Court reserves the right to be wrong.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=852977</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/in-failing-to-protect-voting-rights-the-kansas-supreme-court-reserves-the-right-to-be-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T18:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elisabeth Frost, representing League of Women Voters, gives a rebuttal to a question in her Kansas Supreme Court argument during the hearing of League of Women Voters, et al v. Schwab in 2023. (Pool photo by Evert Nelson/Topeka Capital-Journal) One hundred and sixty-five years ago come Friday, the Kansas Constitution was adopted by voters. The document had been framed the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max McCoy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bomb Threat Alleged To Have Ties To District Attorney’s Office]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075679</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/bomb-threat-alleged-to-have-ties-to-district-attorneys-office/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T18:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who hired this guy?
The post Bomb Threat Alleged To Have Ties To District Attorney’s Office appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Mr. McMahon’ Is An Incomplete Portrait Of Wrestling’s Reprehensible Kingpin]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168555</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mr-mcmahon-is-an-incomplete-portrait-of-wrestlings-reprehensible-kingpin"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T18:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How will Vince McMahon be remembered? That question drives the new Netflix documentary on wrestling's most famous promoter. Mr. McMahon is named for the character that the real-life McMahon portrayed on TV starting in the late '90s, and the documentary tries to untangle the fiction of that character from the reality of the man—a reality that is oftentimes more repugnant than any wrestling angle could dare to be. It succeeds, to an extent, thanks to the shocking behavior of its subject, but there is a lack of understanding that what made Vince McMahon successful at all costs is also what made him reprehensible.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fwKm7WM_P8E]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If Harris Wins, Will The Economy Collapse? We’ve Heard This Stuff Before.]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075655</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/if-harris-wins-will-the-economy-collapse-weve-heard-this-stuff-before/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T17:42:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Trump is again in an election season, he's again saying crazy things.
The post If Harris Wins, Will The Economy Collapse? We’ve Heard This Stuff Before. appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Herrmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Jets Feel Forever One Poke Away From Collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168750</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-jets-feel-forever-one-poke-away-from-collapse"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T17:35:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are NFL teams that project enough strength and resilience that they can shrug off a miserable 10-9 home loss in the rain. And then there are the New York Jets. Taking a soggy field for their contest against the Broncos after a solid 2-1 start, head coach Robert Saleh's boys delivered the kind of performance that makes fans in the stands swear off football for life and turns a star quarterback into a sour prig—well, OK, Aaron Rodgers was already that, but he's aiming it more pointedly at his own guys now.
Everyone can agree on this: It was not the defense's fault. After holding the Patriots to three points last week, they shut down the pass and only really slipped up on one Denver touchdown drive. Even late in the game, when they could have pleaded exhaustion, they stiffed the Broncos on key plays and put their offense in position to win. They also helped produce this bleak QB stat graphic:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[American League Wild Card Preview: Baltimore Orioles vs. Kansas City Royals]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=447520</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/american-league-wild-card-preview-baltimore-orioles-vs-kansas-city-royals/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T17:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals and Orioles are each led by their star shortstops, but the similarities end there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Clemens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Biglaw Firm Announces Its First Female Firmwide Managing Partner In History]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075653</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/top-biglaw-firm-announces-its-first-female-firmwide-managing-partner-in-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T17:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[She hopes to successfully guide the firm into the future.
The post Top Biglaw Firm Announces Its First Female Firmwide Managing Partner In History appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLB Announces Usual Team Uniforms Returning for 2025 All-Star Game]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82425</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/09/30/mlb-announces-usual-team-uniforms-returning-for-2025-all-star-game/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T16:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fans of Major League Baseball’s All-Star Game, I have some news for you. Starting with next year’s Mid-Season Classic, players will wear their usual team uniforms again during the All-Star Game (still paired with a special cap) MLB’s All-Stars wore their standard team uniforms right up until 2019, with a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Creamer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mise en Place: Fresh takes and Asian influences guide Mari Matsumoto’s cocktail creations at Goat & Rabbit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=852871</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/mise-en-place-fresh-takes-and-asian-influences-guide-mari-matsumotos-cocktail-creations-at-the-goat-rabbit/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T16:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Mari Matsumoto In the bar scene of Kansas City, few stories are as captivating as that of Mari Matsumoto, a seasoned bartender whose journey began in the quiet farmlands of Japan. With family in the restaurant industry and farming, Matsumoto’s path has been one of passion and resilience. From bussing tables and decorating cakes to becoming a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ellen Beshuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFL Teams Show Support for Truth and Reconciliation With Indigenous-Themed Logos in Week 17]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82352</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/09/30/cfl-teams-show-support-for-truth-and-reconciliation-with-indigenous-themed-logos-in-week-17/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T16:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Montreal, Saskatchewan and Toronto round out Indigenous logos across the league; Calgary Stampeders wore theirs in Week 15 against Alouettes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIP To Human First Pass Document Review?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075666</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/rip-to-human-first-pass-document-review/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T16:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using actual humans to perform an initial review isn't gone yet, but the days are numbered.
The post RIP To Human First Pass Document Review? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tangled Up In Blue: Dems down the ballot push against unbeatable odds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850610</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/tangle-up-in-blue-dems-down-the-ballot-push-against-unbeatable-odds/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T16:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Barbara Shelly About 20 people gathered on a Saturday morning in a strip mall storefront that operates as the office of the Platte County Democrats. Some are fresh faces but most are core volunteers who understand that, in Missouri, the surest way to make a difference in politics is to bolster Democratic representation in the state legislature. This...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barbara Shelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NHL Honours Gaudreau Brothers with Helmet Decal]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82353</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/09/30/nhl-honours-gaudreau-brothers-with-helmet-decal/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T15:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All 32 NHL teams will honour the memory of Johnny and Matthew Gaudreau by wearing special helmet decals to begin the 2024-25 season. The tribute will run league-wide through October 24, when the Los Angeles Kings host the San Jose Sharks in their final home opener and be worn on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Creamer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: NASCAR weekend zoomed through the Kansas Speedway this past weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851603</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-nascar-weekend-zoomed-through-the-kansas-speedway-this-past-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T15:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NASCAR Weekend at the Kansas Speedway on Sept. 27-29. // Photo by Tarik Sykes The Kansas Speedway hosted a weekend full of throttles and turns as NASCAR came through town. The weekend began on Friday with the Reese’s 150, won by Tanner Gray, and the Kubota Tractor 200, won by Corey Heim. Saturday was all about the Kansas Lottery 300,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarik Sykes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mega Biglaw Firm Plans To Get Even Bigger, Focuses On New York]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075669</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/mega-biglaw-firm-plans-to-get-even-bigger-focuses-on-new-york/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T15:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm is already big, but it wants to become more profitable.
The post Mega Biglaw Firm Plans To Get Even Bigger, Focuses On New York appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Sept. 30: Who Do You Think You Are? We Am (Themeless)]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168732</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-sept-30-who-do-you-think-you-are-we-am-themeless"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As always, we're ending the month with a challenging themeless. This week's puzzle was constructed by Greg Snitkin and Glenn Davis, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Greg is a dad with three small kids and a hedge fund accountant from South Orange, N.J. He famously refers to changing diapers as “batting clean-up” (after his kids have “loaded the bases”). His puzzles have appeared in The New York Times, Wall Street Journal, and Universal. He’s thrilled to see his lifelong friend Glenn make his puzzling debut! Glenn is a reformed sports blogger now working in the nonprofit sector. He hopes this collaboration with Greg is better received than the biology lab report in high school their teacher took them to task for writing too informally.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Country artist Evan Honer stuns in his honky tonk KC debut]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851427</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-country-artist-evan-honer-stuns-in-his-honky-tonk-kc-debut/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T14:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evan Honer // Photo by Allison Scavo Evan Honer w/ Thomas Rowland recordBar Thursday, Sept. 26 Touring in support of his latest full-length, Fighting For, Evan Honer erupted his very first Kansas City show with “Going Nowhere Fast” and introducing us to his explosive live honky tonk ways on Thursday, Sept. 26. As he showcased songs from his recent album...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Scavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. News Law School Rankings Prediction Sees A Huge, Historic Change At The Top]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075651</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/u-s-news-law-school-rankings-prediction-sees-a-huge-historic-change-at-the-top/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T14:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will a new law school be able to take the No. 1 spot away from Yale? We'll have to wait and see in the real U.S. News law school rankings.
The post U.S. News Law School Rankings Prediction Sees A Huge, Historic Change At The Top appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brass Balls In Beijing]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075644</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/09/brass-balls-in-beijing"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T14:03:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Tepper is buying what Xi Jinping is selling.
The post Brass Balls In Beijing appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Side Stand Up: Your Owner’s Open Letter Wasn’t The League’s Worst]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168702</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/south-side-stand-up-your-owners-open-letter-wasnt-the-leagues-worst"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T13:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It could be worse, White Sox fans. You could be Pirates fans, trapped in a cycle of losing by the caprices of your cheapskate organization, which by releasing one fan-favorite player four plate appearances shy of a contract bonus and benching another, did its part to warn off future free agents. You could be Angels fans, who ever so briefly were allowed to believe they would be free of Arte Moreno's reverse Midas touch, and instead just witnessed the team's losingest season in franchise history, has no future prospects, and spent last week making your White Sox look like world-beaters. You could be A's fans, who on Sunday received one last kick in the crotch after 20 years of it, when the final postgame show of Oakland's season and existence was, for unclear reasons, recorded before game 162 was actually played. "We don’t even know the result of today’s baseball game," studio host Brodie Brazil told viewers trying to prolong the last hours of the Oakland Era—a fitting and final fuck-you to a fanbase that's used to them.
Cheer up, White Sox fans! You ended your season with a win on Sunday, something 11 of the 12 playoff teams won't be able to say. It was your fifth win in six games to close the season and avoid passing the '62 Mets for the worst record in the modern era. Sure, OK, maybe a lot of you were hoping for a loss—hoping that each of your 121 losses could at least be in service of history. That might at least have made the losses teleological and thus more bearable, but they must instead stand on their own as the droppings of an epically but not quite historically bad team. Shit for shit's sake.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Stuck in a dry pattern (9/30)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3680196</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-stuck-in-a-dry-pattern-9-30/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T13:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month will be ending on a dry note, and if it wasn't for the 2 days or so of some rain a couple of weeks ago, there wouldn't have been a drop of rain either. Thank goodness we got what we did then because we'd be in a world of hurt for moisture. As [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shohei Ohtani Ends His Season Dismantling The Entire Concept Of The Decimal System]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168397</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/shohei-ohtani-ends-his-season-dismantling-the-entire-concept-of-the-decimal-system"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T13:16:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The collective agreement on what to do after catching a historic baseball is very fiscally responsible, like a financial literacy course titled "So You Just Won The Lottery." The man who caught Shohei Ohtani's 50/50 home run ball would receive full marks: He declined an initial offer—reportedly $300,000—from the Dodgers and contacted an auction house, Goldin, the next day. Seeing as the current highest bid for the ball sits at $1.2 million with over 16 days to go, it was pragmatic and well-executed, if unsentimental, decision-making. As the seller wished to remain anonymous, the ESPN article on the auction instead quotes Goldin CEO and founder, Ken Goldin, and Goldin seizes upon the opportunity to mete out some uncensored self-advertising: "This is one of those cases where our reputation for getting the absolute highest price on hot-market items [came] into play ... honestly, we had no competition at all."
This is not moral judgment on the man who caught Ohtani's baseball. Imagine being so composed if a house were to fall into your lap; chance would be a fine thing. Ultimately the point of any item of sports memorabilia is to own it or sell it, and to own a baseball of Ohtani's worth is synonymous with being extremely wealthy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eureka Springs projects new screams on screen at ‘Nightmare in the Ozarks’ film fest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=849064</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/eureka-springs-projects-new-screams-on-screen-at-nightmare-in-the-ozarks-film-fest/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T13:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever been to Eureka Springs, Ark., you know it’s a perfect place to get in the mood for Halloween. The picturesque, artsy Ozarks town is packed with antique stores, historic buildings and boutiques specializing in magic supplies, crystals and new age healing. The town is probably most famous for the Crescent Hotel, which bills itself as “America’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 09.30.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075659</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/morning-docket-09-30-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T12:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Eric Adams top aide served federal subpoena and has her phone seized by the DA. So, welcome NY state prosecutors to the Adams show! [Gothamist]
* "Negligently parked helicopter" isn't a phrase you see often. [ABA Journal]
* Judge tells woman who owes over $50K in contempt that her lawyers aren't helping. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Lawyer taking on over 50 clients to go after Diddy. [Houston Public Media]
* Devastating hurricane causing courthouse disruption. [Law360]
* New leadership at Davis Wright Tremaine. Our friends over at Law.com are experiencing some technical issues, so if this doesn't open, just try again. [Law.com]
* Wyoming wants to make it easier to do drivebys on wolves. People firing from moving vehicles... what could possibly go wrong? [CBS]
The post Morning Docket: 09.30.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantastic Fest 2024: Detention’s manic master Joseph Kahn brings us his most accessible movie yet with Ick]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851581</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/fantastic-fest-2024-detentions-manic-master-joseph-kahn-brings-us-his-most-accessible-movie-yet-with-ick/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T12:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Fantastic Fest This is part of our coverage from Fantastic Fest 2024 in Austin, TX where genre films are debuting before they get wider release. Check out all of our coverage here.  No one makes movies quite like director Joseph Kahn. He’s the kind of visual Tasmanian devil who people stop short of calling an auteur because of his chaotic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Torres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rory Dames Disappeared From The SafeSport Database And SafeSport Isn’t Saying Why]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168616</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rory-dames-disappeared-from-the-safesport-database-and-safesport-isnt-saying-why"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T00:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At one point in time, Rory Dames was mostly known as a longtime women's soccer coach, leading the NWSL's Chicago Red Stars for about a decade as well as overseeing Chicago-area youth powerhouse Eclipse. But more recently, he's become known as a coach whom players repeatedly reported for emotional abuse and manipulation. Those reports by players did not immediately diminish Dames's power; he only resigned when those accounts began becoming public. The ensuing 234-page Yates report into systemic abuse across women's soccer included his name hundreds of times. 
U.S. Soccer, which oversees the U.S. Women's National Team as well as sanctioning the NWSL, suspended Dames's coaching license and, per USA Today, the federation reported him to the U.S. Center for SafeSport, the organization created by Congress to investigate sexual abuse across Olympic sports. SafeSport doesn't have any jurisdiction over the NWSL, but Dames's presence in the database still mattered, especially given his continued prominence in Chicago-area youth soccer. (The NWSL also banned Dames for life.) SafeSport opened an investigation into Dames, and anyone who searched its database would have found his name.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Darnold?!? Uh. Yeah. Sam Darnold]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168677</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/sam-darnold-uh-yeah-sam-darnold"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T22:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news from Green Bay is this: Sam Darnold hasn't turned into San Darnold just yet, and the possibility that he actually isn't Sam Darnold anymore remains more than zero.
The phrase "Sam Darnold" here is meant as the pejorative everyone who pays attention to these things has always meant it to be, but the Darnold in this dimension continues to defy the common usage. He isn't the central reason the Minnesota Vikings have won their first four games, which puts them in approximately the 95th percentile of all NFL teams in the last decade, but he has been more than just "not an impediment." I mean, 4-0 is its own answer to any question you have.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flávia Saraiva Remains A Star]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168657</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/flavia-saraiva-remains-a-star"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T20:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jade Barbosa and Flávia Saraiva, teammates on the Brazilian women's national gymnastics team, reunited this weekend to celebrate the former's nuptials. In a video posted Saturday to both of their Instagram accounts, Barbosa is seen preparing to throw her bouquet. Saraiva's in the background, her heels exchanged for slides and a drink in hand. Her other hand is on her hip as she gazes toward the scrum ensuing over the tossed flowers. As the lucky recipient cheers and hugs Barbosa, Saraiva raises her glass, looks dead into the camera and smirks.
They captioned the video, "Enquanto umas caçam…" which roughly translates to "while some go hunting..."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cruelest Part Of Sports Are The Trades]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168587</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-cruelest-part-of-sports-are-the-trades"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T19:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My father and two brothers are dedicated Chicago Bears fans; the cacophony of halftime analysis, both professional and amateur, soundtracked most of my Sundays until I left for college. Football isn't their only sport of choice though its arguably the one I understand the most, having spent my adolescent years in the suburbs of Dallas-Fort Worth, where high school football is famously a way of life more than anything else. So while I do not consider myself deeply knowledgeable about professional sports, some crucial information has managed to lodge its way into my brain over the years spent idly on the couch or the bleachers while sports happened in the background.
Offensive and defensive lines, interceptions and sacks: These are all terms that, for me, possess a paradoxically equal amount of familiarity and mystery. Instead, the parts of the game that tended to pique my interest happen off the field in the swirling rumors and gossip that my brothers and father pored over during commercial breaks. Rumors of trades were the most frequent topic of conversation, or at least the ones I cared about the most. Of all the regularly inconvenient features of professional sports—injuries, drafts, post-game interviews—the concept of being traded away at a moment's notice was the one that struck me as the most casually devastating.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Trade Is The Cruelest Thing In Sports]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168587</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-trade-is-the-cruelest-thing-in-sports"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T19:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My father and two brothers are dedicated Chicago Bears fans; the cacophony of halftime analysis, both professional and amateur, soundtracked most of my Sundays until I left for college. Football isn't their only sport of choice though its arguably the one I understand the most, having spent my adolescent years in the suburbs of Dallas-Fort Worth, where high school football is famously a way of life more than anything else. So while I do not consider myself deeply knowledgeable about professional sports, some crucial information has managed to lodge its way into my brain over the years spent idly on the couch or the bleachers while sports happened in the background.
Offensive and defensive lines, interceptions and sacks: These are all terms that, for me, possess a paradoxically equal amount of familiarity and mystery. Instead, the parts of the game that tended to pique my interest happen off the field in the swirling rumors and gossip that my brothers and father pored over during commercial breaks. Rumors of trades were the most frequent topic of conversation, or at least the ones I cared about the most. Of all the regularly inconvenient features of professional sports—injuries, drafts, post-game interviews—the concept of being traded away at a moment's notice was the one that struck me as the most casually devastating.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Knicks And Wolves Made The Confusing Trade We Expect From Them]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168652</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-knicks-and-wolves-made-the-confusing-trade-we-expect-from-them"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T18:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is difficult to conjure a happier development for those addicted to low comedy than the phrase "Timberwolves-Knicks trade," so to them we bequeath the Friday night news that these two deeply and persistently weird franchises completed the most inexplicably timed big trade in recent league history. Put another way, while everyone else was doing their preseason media fun fairs, the Knicks and Pups were frantically scrubbing their rosters for wildly differing reasons. The Knicks needed a center because they had none, and the Wolves needed Julius Randle because how better to clog the traffic in front of Anthony Edwards?
Both teams seem to be on the rise, at least superficially, and positioned themselves to make a blockbuster deal each can claim unconvincingly puts them over the top. The Knicks get Karl-Anthony Towns, the beetle-browed post who has frustrated as much as he has entranced because he is capable of such grand levels of enchantment, and can complete the task of making this Jalen Brunson's team. The Wolves get some cash and cap relief and a player looking for a new contract who holds the ball enough to frustrate their newfound franchise face. The new blood on both ends suggests that Minnesota's conference finals appearance and the Knicks' continued slow boil are ready for enhancement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vinnie Pasquantino Ahead Of Schedule, Could Return For Wild Card Series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=825900</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/09/vinnie-pasquantino-ahead-of-schedule-could-return-for-wild-card-series.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T18:03:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Royals first baseman Vinnie Pasquantino saw his regular season come to an end a month ago when he suffered a broken right thumb. It was a devastating blow to Kansas City’s offense, and the initial timeline provided at the time left him set to miss the next six-to-eight weeks, not only ending his regular season…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best College Football Game Of The Year Has Happened]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168634</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-best-college-football-game-of-the-year-has-happened"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T16:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a half, the highest profile college football game of the year—and therefore the most hysterically overhyped—was a letdown of Megalopolis-level proportions. Alabama, ranked fourth in the nation by people who are permitted to guess at such a thing and have their votes counted, was stomping Georgia, ranked second by those same people. Watched in person by High Lord Emeritus Saban and his consort Terry, plus the full ESPN panoply of hyperkinetic parrots called College GameDay, the Crimson Tide scored four touchdowns in 17 and a half minutes, along with forcing a safety and two turnovers, for a 30-7 halftime lead that also included this play from Ryan Williams, effectively spurring what we will be told was a massive national television audience of megatybillions to cry out at once, "What else is on?"

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=efSIxPPonIM&ab_channel=AlabamaCrimsonTideonAL.com]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL Week 4 Uniform Schedule: Lions Debuting New Black Jerseys, Blue Helmets While Browns, Falcons Wearing Throwbacks]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82340</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/09/29/nfl-week-4-uniform-schedule-lions-debuting-new-black-jerseys-blue-helmets-while-browns-falcons-wearing-throwbacks/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T15:53:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our new weekly series that looks at every uniform matchup across the NFL is headlined by the debut of the Detroit Lions' black alternate uniforms and throwback threads for the Atlanta Falcons and Cleveland Browns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday Notes: All Hail the Detroit Tigers (and Kudos AL Central)]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=447446</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/sunday-notes-all-hail-the-detroit-tigers-and-kudos-al-central/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T11:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus Matt Quatraro on leadoff hitters, Paul Skenes's availability, Luis Arraez's batting titles, Kirby Yates's ERA, facts and stats galore, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Laurila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Ducks’ New White, Yellow “Generation O” Jerseys Leak On Social Media]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82324</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/09/28/oregon-ducks-new-white-yellow-generation-o-jerseys-leak-on-social-media/college/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T17:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both the white and yellow versions of Oregon's new "Generation O" uniforms were leaked on social media on Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>