<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-04-22T14:17:14.934Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Rocks When A Hockey Game Is Funny]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187559</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/kings-oilers-wacky"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T13:47:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is, I insist, cool and good that one of the wildest and most intense playoff games in a while ended so stupidly. It rules, quite frankly, that a game which saw the Kings seemingly exorcise their Oiler-matchup demons, then collapse in the face of a sudden Edmonton onslaught, was ultimately decided by a blooper-reel goal. Hockey is a ludicrous sport sometimes, and puck often lies, and had Phillip Danault taken a normal shot, Stuart Skinner probably would have stopped it easily and Game 1 would've headed to overtime, the Oilers carrying all the momentum after erasing a four-goal deficit. But Danault fanned, and fluttered the puck with comical slowness past Skinner, who saw neither hide nor hair of it.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TwyDSh7YJLo&ab_channel=SPORTSNET]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kawhi Leonard Is Just Living With It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187560</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/kawhi-leonard-is-just-living-with-it"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T13:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A closely contested NBA playoff game is an insanity device. Every turnover is a rake across the brain, every missed free throw a boil on the soul. Each second of game time that passes is designed to pull the contents of your guts closer and closer to the edge of your throat. If that is what it feels like to watch it, I can't imagine what it must be like on the court.
None of this applies to Kawhi Leonard. Despite his close proximity to the action, I spent most of Monday night's Game 2 clash between the Nuggets and Clippers wishing I could trade places with him. Even when he had the ball in his hands with under a minute left, readying himself to take what would be the deciding shot in L.A.'s 105-102 victory, it was impossible to imagine anyone, anywhere, more at peace than Kawhi Leonard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White fangs]]></title>
        <id>680697fc105fa700014c04e3</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-303/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T23:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maria Bustillos on 'Sinners']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Music in the Blood]]></title>
        <id>680654e1105fa700014c0360</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/music-in-the-blood/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T23:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sinners, the new vampire horror movie directed by Ryan Coogler and starring Michael B. Jordan, opened this weekend to boffo reviews and impressive global box office receipts of $61 million. Coogler’s films have made more than $2.4 billion at the box office, according to Variety, giving him]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Bustillos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kerry And Cork Redeemed A Dour Season Of Gaelic Football With One Great Game]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187537</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/kerry-and-cork-redeemed-a-dour-season-of-gaelic-football-with-one-great-game"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T19:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pope died on Sunday. Here’s hoping his holiness got to see the Kerry–Cork football match first. To call it the greatest Gaelic game of the millennium would be an understatement of Irish proportions. Or something. But as GAA+ play-by-play man Liam Aherne gushed within seconds of the game’s end: “My god!”
On a rain-soaked pitch at regal Páirc Uí Chaoimh in Cork on Saturday evening, the Kingdom advanced in the Munster Championships—one of the provincial tournaments that determines seeding for the All-Ireland Championship—by outlasting the underdog squad from the Rebel County in overtime, 3-21 to 1-25. The back-and-forth contest climaxed on a shocking goal from Kerry midfielder Joe O’Connor, who blasted a ball from 20 meters out in traffic into the Cork net late in the second extra period. The action gave fans, players, and even broadcast commentators no time to breathe from halftime to the final horn (or “hooter” in GAA parlance).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WrestleMania 41’s Two Main Events And The Risks Of Getting Epic]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187475</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/wrestlemania-41s-two-main-events-and-the-risks-of-getting-epic"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T18:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the WWE house style there are many archetypes, but nothing is more tried-and-true—or, in some cases, tired and false—than the WWE Epic Main Event. As the saying goes, you know it when you see it, but the Epic Main Event is easy enough to break down into its component pieces. An EME will have a lot of cinematic spots, usually involving weapons or the environment around the ring—tables being the main one, but oftentimes the crowd areas come into play as well. It will be a bit on the slower side, for one of two reasons, with the choice between the two depending upon how generous you want to be. Either the EME will be slow to build up the drama until it bubbles over, or it will be sluggish because WWE's main event wrestlers are generally more on the methodical side. Most relevant to WrestleMania 41's double main events is that these matches are usually over-stuffed with outside interference and mechanics that go beyond the simple foundation of wrestling, in which a wrestling match can be boiled down to some amount of performers fighting each other to prove who is best. The Epic Main Event exists because of WWE's longstanding suspicion that that isn't enough.
With that in mind, the respective main events for the two-night marathon that was WrestleMania 41 were predictably both in that WWE Epic Main Event style. Taken together, they do a rather neat job of encapsulating the good and the very bad of what that style can bring. If last year's night two main event was WWE at its most giddily excessive, this year's show offered two more measured scoops of melodrama that went down easily when they worked, and crashed and burned almost impossibly hard when they didn't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oscar Piastri Seizes The Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187465</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/oscar-piastri-seizes-the-lead"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T17:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before the third session of qualifying, Lando Norris was the fastest man at the Saudi Arabian Grand Prix. Other drivers beat him on one-off occasions—Max Verstappen in Q1, and, somehow, Pierre Gasly in FP1—but notably and most importantly, neither of those drivers were his teammate and championship rival Oscar Piastri. The Saudi Arabian GP was shaping up to be a bounce-back race for Norris across Formula 1's midseason oil-money double-header, after his comparatively disastrous P3 finish at Bahrain.
Then Norris clipped a curb on a flying lap, unsettled his car, and crashed into the left-side wall, red-flagging the session. Norris let his race engineer know that he was fine, before following up with a characteristically self-critical, "Idiot." As much as McLaren professes its car the best on the grid, it doesn't have quite the pace of the early hybrid-era Mercedes or rocket Red Bull, where, with the right driver at the wheel and right teammate up ahead, a P10 in qualifying could easily convert to a race win. And with that one mistake, Norris's race goal shifted from a win, cementing his Drivers' Championship lead, to a decent recovery drive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bud Black Has Either The Best Or The Worst Job In Baseball]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187525</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bud-black-has-either-the-best-or-the-worst-job-in-baseball"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T17:11:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of all the odd moments of a well-packed sports weekend, maybe the oddest was the debate between what is more unusual, one MLB team beating another 24-2, or an accomplished professional basketball team beating a slightly less accomplished one, in the playoffs, by 51 points. If it helps, it's about a tie.
But the sneaky third option might have been the Colorado Rockies winning the second game of their punishment doubleheader with the Washington Nationals. Here was one team with an excruciatingly bad bullpen facing a team with an excruciatingly bad everything else; by rights such a match-up should end up with each team losing once, and it did. But putting it like that diminishes the Rockies' status as an all-time cornea-searing disaster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brewers Acquire Cesar Espinal To Complete Mark Canha Trade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=849164</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/brewers-royals-mark-canha-trade-ptbnl-cesar-espinal-pitcher.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T16:51:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced Monday that minor league righty Cesar Espinal has been traded to the Brewers. He’s the player to be named later from the swap that sent Mark Canha from Milwaukee to K.C. late in spring training. Espinal is just 19 years old, but this is already the second time in his career that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O’s, No!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187455</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/os-no"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T16:44:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because it is a long enough regular season to test and re-test just about every variable, every team in baseball is going to have their wieners mangled in at least one game. Even the mighty zillion-dollar Los Angeles Dodgers recently had their tender bits forcibly run through a cheese-grater by the Chicago Cubs. It happens! Still, it's hard not to feel a little bit uneasy about the suffering delivered to the Baltimore Orioles Sunday, at home, in the rubber match of a weekend series against the Cincinnati Reds. The O's put 41-year-old Charlie Morton on the mound to start the contest, and the Reds lifted him by his ankles and drowned him in a toilet, and then spent the rest of the game mercilessly bullying an increasingly ridiculous sequence of relief pitchers, rudely flaunting MLB's lack of a mercy rule, to the tune of a 24–2 final score.
Things didn't turn fully gruesome on Morton until the third inning, when Elly De La Cruz (who also made several eye-popping plays up the middle during the very brief period when this game could be described as "competitive") socked a high heater into the stands in right field to lead off what would soon become a "Baseball Bugs" conga line for the Reds. Minutes later, struggling with command, amassing a nightmarish pitch count, having already used a mound visit, and desperate for an out by any means, a sweaty and flustered Morton attempted a pickoff move to first, missed wide, and allowed an unearned run to scamper home, the fourth of the inning. Reds catcher Austin Wynns then punched a Morton 2–2 changeup into center field to drive home another run, and Orioles manager Brandon Hyde decided to put his bumbling pitcher to bed. Reliever Cody Poteet came on and hung a 3–2 slider to TJ Friedl, who socked it deep to right; Ryan O'Hearn, who is defensively out of position at every position but especially in right field, made a hilariously feeble effort to catch the ball on the warning track, and now the flood gates were not just open but entirely gone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please Enjoy These Images Of The 2025 Corgi Derby]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187482</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/please-enjoy-these-images-of-the-2025-corgi-derby"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T15:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday was the third annual Corgi Derby, a tribute to Queen Elizabeth held at the Musselburgh Racecourse in Scotland. The little dogs that the queen loved most race each other around a 230-foot course, with the winner getting a trophy and treats delivered by Judy Murray, Andy’s mom. The winning dog's name is also printed in publications around the world. This year’s winner was named Juno. See! All you need to do to get your dog’s name in Defector is to have it win a corgi race in front of Andy Murray’s mother, and for there to be lots of cute photos on the wire. Of course your dog will never know that its name was published on Defector, but it might be nice for you.
Which reminds me: Defector has access to a lot of these cute photos, and we’d like to share them with you now. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, April 21: Happy Arbor Day]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187464</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-april-21-happy-arbor-day"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why not branch out and try our Monday crossword? This week's puzzle was constructed by Sala Wanetick and Emily Biegas, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Sala is a crossword constructor and cheesemonger based outside of Detroit. Her sports knowledge specialty areas include reality stars' romantic partners, and common crossword clues (shoutout to Mia Hamm, Pele, and Epee.) She would love to connect with solvers and constructors—Sala Wanetick on all platforms, she is the only one. Emily started constructing crosswords with Sala in 2023; they have had puzzles published in the Los Angeles Times, USA Today, and Universal. Besides crosswords, her other passion is music (shoutout to the three-letter king, ENO!) A corporate girlie by day, by night Emily plays guitar in a garage rock trio called ZEM that plays shows in and around Detroit. 
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[See What Makes The Cavaliers Special Through The Ty Jerome Game]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187451</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/see-what-makes-the-cavaliers-special-through-the-ty-jerome-game"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T14:29:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The theory of the Cleveland Cavaliers is that by virtue of being able to play at least one of Donovan Mitchell and Darius Garland at all times, they are guaranteed 48 minutes of all-star–level shot creation. That allows them to play a bunch of incredible play-finishers, like Jarrett Allen and Max Strus, who don't need to worry about dribbling the basketball unless it's into an advantage presented to them by one of their genius operators and can otherwise stick to jamming huge dunks and nailing open threes. Everything on offense is fast and so much of it easy, which starts at the top. So naturally, a point guard's big game tells the story of Cleveland's 121-100 playoff-opening win over the Miami Heat. That's right: Ty Jerome.
The little point guard has had an incredible season for the Cavs, averaging a hair over 12 points per game on 63-percent true shooting in just under 20 minutes per game for the best offense in the league. When a mildly undersized guard averages those sorts of numbers in that sort of role, you might expect their game to be built around nailing catch-and-shoot threes, attacking closeouts, and running vanilla pick-and-rolls. You know, responsible offense. Jerome is great at all of those things, but what really makes him great is his floater. There's nothing complex about it: Jerome is a floater maestro, with an uncanny sense of timing, enviable balance, and eiderdown touch. If he gets his defender on his hip, he knows exactly how to lathe out an extra six or seven feet of space, and he knows exactly when the low man is either committed to blocking his shot or too terrified of an alley-oop, and thus content to watch Jerome sail it in over his head.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Warriors And Rockets Know Each Other’s Weaknesses]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187458</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-warriors-and-rockets-know-each-others-weaknesses"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T13:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Occasionally, and by occasionally we of course mean rarely, the dumb luck of the NBA standings will create an early-round playoff series in which each team is somehow a bad matchup for its opponent. The force of the postseason naturally tends to create these as the process grinds on; to get one before things otherwise get interesting is both a gift from the universe and a pain in the ass for the teams involved. You think about a series like this, you watch it and rewatch it, and all you come away with is the brain-bending realization that the teams involved are not playing against each other so much as they are playing against their own capacity for discomfort.
And with that, we present to you Rockets-Warriors, or based on the result in Game 1 of this series, Warriors-Rockets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AL Central Notes: Carpenter, Erceg, Meidroth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=849119</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/al-central-notes-carpenter-erceg-meidroth.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T03:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With four outfielders already on the injured list, the Tigers might’ve lost another key contributor when Kerry Carpenter left today’s 4-3 loss to the Royals with what manager A.J. Hinch described as right hamstring soreness.  As Hinch told the Detroit News’ Chris McCosky and other reporters, Carpenter suffered the injury while running out an infield…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Knicks Gave The Pistons A Lesson In Playoff Entropy]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187437</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-knicks-gave-the-pistons-a-lesson-in-playoff-entropy"/>
        <updated>2025-04-20T16:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Detroit Pistons roster a bunch of rowdy youths fresh to a playoff atmosphere, with all that entails—good and bad. They don't know what they don't know, which is often a successful mindset: Many a game has been lost by knowing you're supposed to lose it, and many a game won by the weightlessness of happy ignorance. Expectations, too, can be a burden. But gravity-free hoopage only lasts so long. Eventually, especially on the road, the noise builds and the pressure increases and more seasoned opponents are braced against wilting, and suddenly, unawareness of "what's supposed to happen" stops working, because the thing starts happening anyway. Over a 21-0 fourth-quarter run that led to a 123-112 New York victory, the Knicks offered the Pistons a corrective for the first three quarters, a demonstration of postseason basketball's unpredictability, and a lesson that not all 48 minutes are created equal.
The Knicks' defensive strategy was obvious from the get-go: make life difficult for Cade Cunningham. The Pistons have a dearth of ways to beat teams, and the Knicks were intent with shutting down their 26-ppg primary weapon, with OG Anunoby getting frequent help from Karl-Anthony Towns whenever Cunningham broke through on a screen. But Cunningham was generally content with passing out of pressure, because his mates were hitting their shots. Tobias Harris, Tim Hardaway Jr., and Malik Beasley—the veterans on the team, probably not coincidentally—were 20-of-33 from the field after three quarters, and hitting better than 50 percent of their threes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Lakers Have Bigger Problems Than Luka Doncic Can Fix]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187433</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-lakers-have-bigger-problems-than-luka-doncic-can-fix"/>
        <updated>2025-04-20T14:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NBA is an odd amalgam of friendships and enemies' lists, alliances and rivalries, defenders and critics—all under the same jiggling tent. Thus, it should have come as little surprise that the Minnesota Timberwolves fought so brilliantly for Nico Harrison's honor when the people currently paying him are not only letting him twist in the breeze but aiming the wind machine at him to make the spinning more painful.
This is not, of course, Minnesota's prime intention. The Wolves beat the Los Angeles Lakers 117-95 Saturday night for their own glory, honor and self-esteem. They spotted the Lakers a 28-21 lead, took it away two minutes into the second with a 14-2 run, then reinforced it with a 21-6 burst to start the third. If it wasn't Jaden McDaniels crushing all before him, it was Anthony Edwards at his cheeky best, with sides of Julius Randle and Naz Reid scattered about the landscape, while the Lakers had LeBron James, Luka Doncic, and crickets. The final buzzer was an act of mercy, as was the you-can-go-to-sleep blowout at the end of a 10-hour hoopathon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That’s About As Hot As It Gets In Winnipeg]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187410</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/thats-about-as-hot-as-it-gets-in-winnipeg"/>
        <updated>2025-04-20T13:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It feels almost unfair that the Winnipeg Jets, with their all-universe goalie and their league-fewest goals allowed, are also constructed to be able to win a slugfest if necessary. Third-most goals in the NHL this year, paced as always by the dynamic Kyle Connor–Mark Scheifele duo, the Jets are very much unlike some of the defense-first rosters out there in that they can and will happily absorb a haymaker or two and answer in kind. That came in handy on Saturday, as a white-hot crowd watched the Jets trade goals with the Blues in a wild first period, only to asset their dominance as the game wore on.
The final score read 5-3 Jets, but after a 2-2 first period, it felt like it might be one of those very silly playoff openers where the combination of nerves, an extended feeling-out period, and the small sample size add up to a game with no particular contextual anchor, where everyone kind of agrees to pretend it was an anomaly that just sort of happened. "That first period it was kind of a little bit wacky and we were a little bit sloppy," Jets coach Scott Arniel said. But when Jordan Kyrou scored on the power play just 1:13 into the second to give St. Louis the lead, it was hard not to wonder if this was the return of Playoff Helle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is No Getting Off The Russell Westbrook Rollercoaster]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187404</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/there-is-no-getting-off-the-russell-westbrook-rollercoaster"/>
        <updated>2025-04-20T13:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russell Westbrook being a man in a hurry and all, he has needed only four games to show his newest coach, David Adelman, what the full Russ Experience entails. It is, as the nine coaches before him have learned, a flight to a tropical paradise through six hours of turbulence and which may at any moment be rerouted to Gary, Indiana.
Saturday, though, it was paradise after all. Westbrook made enough superb and silly plays in tandem, including a few of each in overtime, to guide the Denver Nuggets to a 112-110 victory that was, as the Brits like to say, very much "against the run of play." Westbrook's damp dynamite stylings have led people to consider him hyperwashed for several years now because he is capable of such seismographically comedic highs and lows, and yet Adelman has come to rely upon (if not entirely trust) Westbrook. Westbrook played 34 minutes Saturday, including the final 23 minutes that encapsulated half the third quarter and all of the fourth and overtime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Busy In The NBA Playoffs Open Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187401</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/get-busy-in-the-nba-playoffs-open-thread"/>
        <updated>2025-04-19T16:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lotsa games today! Lotsa games tomorrow, too. Feel free to hang out here and chat while you binge on all that spectacular hoops action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Option MJ Melendez To Triple-A, Activate Mark Canha From 10-Day IL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=848937</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/royals-option-mj-melendez-to-triple-a-activate-mark-canha-from-10-day-il.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-19T14:07:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that outfielder MJ Melendez has been optioned to Triple-A Omaha.  The move opens up a roster spot for Mark Canha, as the veteran outfielder/first baseman was reinstated from the 10-day injured list. More to come…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Player Option/Opt-Out Update: April Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=848721</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/player-option-opt-out-update-april-edition.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-18T23:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The increasing popularity of opt-outs/player options as a means to close the gap in free agent signings and extensions has changed the face of free agency entirely. Not long ago, opt-outs were perks reserved for the game’s truly elite stars — a benefit to help differentiate nine-figure offers and secure the game’s top stars. In…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy listening]]></title>
        <id>680294b3105fa700014bef72</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-302/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-18T21:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jennie Rose Halperin on the life and work of Michael Hurley]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye to the Godfather of Freak Folk]]></title>
        <id>6802b4ed105fa700014befdb</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/goodbye-to-the-godfather-of-freak-folk/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-18T21:48:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YOU CAN SHARE THIS POST ON BLUESKY THANK YOU
I first heard Michael Hurley play in a small, mostly empty venue in Berlin in 2013. It was an early set; the bar was muted, brown, and dingy in dusty late spring light, but when he came in he lit up]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennie Rose Halperin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine A Pro-Democracy Supreme Court – If You Can]]></title>
        <id>68028ec00951470001ef0769</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/imagine-a-pro-democracy-supreme-court-if-you-can/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-18T18:51:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States can't be saved unless SCOTUS is saved first]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silence! You Are Summoned To Read A Preview Of The 2025 NBA Playoffs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187330</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/silence-you-are-summoned-to-read-a-preview-of-the-2024-25-nba-playoffs"/>
        <updated>2025-04-18T17:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you seen this? Are you aware of this? The NBA playoffs are about to begin! This is real. I would not lie to you.
This means that the time has come for you, the casual basketball fan, the dunce that you are, the grime on the bottom of a true basketball-knower's shoe, to begin scrambling around for information about this so-called "NBA postseason." There are 16 damn teams in the field, and you need to know stuff about all of them, lest you be driven from the village for your foolishness!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case For A New MTV]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187214</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-case-for-a-new-mtv"/>
        <updated>2025-04-18T15:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Listening Habits, a column where I share the music I’ve been fixated on recently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired CDC Health Communications Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187190</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-cdc-health-communications-manager"/>
        <updated>2025-04-18T14:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After weeks of receiving insulting emails from the federal government, Sarah Boim learned she was fired from her dream job at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention at 8 p.m. on a Saturday. The email, which adhered to a template sent to all probationary workers, cited Boim's performance as the reason she was being let go. "That was devastating to me to read, even though I knew that it wasn't true," Boim said, adding that she had received a 4.66 out of five on her last annual performance review. Boim was overwhelmed with feelings from shock to depression. "I basically went through the stages of grief," she said. Then she arrived on a more galvanizing emotion: anger.
Boim and other probationary employees fired from the CDC scrambled to get more information about their situation. "Everybody was so scared, first of all that we were being spied on, which I'm sure we were," she said. They created a Signal chat and crowdsourced information, but they found a thicket of misinformation. "So a small group of us decided to start a newsletter to cut through some of that noise and increase access to facts," Boim said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Stanley Cup’s Got To Return To Canada Sometime, Right?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187308</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-stanley-cups-got-to-return-to-canada-sometime-nhl-playoffs"/>
        <updated>2025-04-18T12:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NHL postseason stands in the exalted place it does because of two counterintuitive yet almost inviolable truths: that the regular-season standings and the achievements attached therein are an utter lie, and that the most fun is always found in the first round, when even the unworthy teams offer delicious levels of entertainment.
Proof of Truth 1: The last time the team with the best regular season record won the Cup in a regulation-length season was 2008.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trouble at home]]></title>
        <id>680180bd105fa700014bddd3</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-301/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T23:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arwa Mahdawi nears the end of an investigation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Solve a Murder: Part Five]]></title>
        <id>68017557105fa700014bddaa</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/how-to-solve-a-murder-part-five/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T23:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 1996, 36-year-old Susan Walsh supposedly left her house in New Jersey and never came back. She is presumed dead but a body has never been found. This is Part Three of a series on my five-year investigation into her unsolved disappearance.
To catch up, here are Part One]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arwa Mahdawi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Beautiful Mount Airy Lodge]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187242</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/at-beautiful-mount-airy-lodge"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T19:36:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not quite a large enough sample to be significant, and too inherently insignificant to really be worth the sampling, but we've done enough Drew Is About To Go On Vacation episodes of the podcast by now that I can detect their specific vibrational energy. Drew is both a little bit more eager than usual to wrap things up and just absolutely relaxed; I am maybe a bit more inclined to wander afield and go long and as close to absolutely relaxed as I get, as if I was getting some sort of residual contact high from the vacation that the big fella is about to take. It is not quite the episode that would be recorded from a vacation—we've done some of those, too, and likely will do some more—but it has all the energy of having more or less wrapped up work. All of which is to say that, at this anxious and ominous broader moment, I found this week's episode to be kind of a relief, and to reiterate I am not even going on vacation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I Keep Masking]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187293</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-i-keep-masking"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T19:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the earliest photos of me features my grandfather, a doctor from the Philippines, cradling me as a newborn while wearing a face mask. He had a cold at the time and I was as vulnerable as a human being can be. That photo didn’t normalize the idea of wearing face masks for me, though I did feel comparatively inured to the sight as I grew up. Relatives would show up to gatherings wearing them and, in a family of medical professionals, all manner of PPE was unremarkable. I’d be lying if I said there wasn’t a cultural element to this as well. Up there with that common, meme-ified image of an elderly Asian man out for a leisurely, inquisitive stroll with his hands clasped behind his back is the image of an elderly Asian person out in public with a face mask on. Sometimes, the images are o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Don’t Put Poison In Your Mouth,” And Other Great Tips From ’80s And ’90s Trading Cards]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183012</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dont-put-poison-in-your-mouth-and-other-great-tips-from-80s-and-90s-trading-cards"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T17:57:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A player can look good on the front of his card, but it's what’s on the back that matters. That's where the player's stats and accomplishments appear, and where the bigger story of their career really rounds into shape: what they've done and where they've done it, how well and for how long. The photo on the front might show a guy's only home run all season; if so, the back of the card will tell you.
Because they're all grounded in the same categories and expressed in similarly shaped statistics, the numbers on the backs of all those cards can blur together somewhat; they are all different, but they don't really look that different. For instance there is Bill Hanzlik, who averaged 7.2 points per game during his 10 years in the NBA, spent mostly with the Denver Nuggets. The 6-foot-7 small forward was mostly known for his defense, which means that a lot of what he did best didn't show up on the back of his trading cards. But he was there, and the proof is in the 12-card set of Nuggets trading cards that the Denver Children's Hospital released for the 1989–90 season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Dangerously Bad Bullpen Is Everyone’s Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187261</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-dangerously-bad-bullpen-is-everyones-problem"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T17:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Washington Nationals reliever Jorge López was tossed from a game Wednesday night. He came on in relief in the seventh inning and—in the fashion preferred by members of this insanely terrible bullpen—immediately immolated his own team's chances of winning what had been a one-run game. First he allowed two singles and an RBI-groundout; then with two outs, he threw a first-pitch sinker up and in and plunked Bryan Reynolds. Three pitches later, López fired a fastball at the ear of Andrew McCutchen, which McCutchen avoided only by throwing himself onto the ground. While the umpires conferenced, López and McCutchen began to shout at each other, and soon the benches emptied.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ehyFBlpWcSI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone Can Do That]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187268</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/everyone-can-do-that"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T15:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Listen, I will happily devour any article about Nikola Jokic. He's my big special guy and every anecdote that gets published about him keeps a place in the most lovingly curated segment of my mind. So it is with great sadness that I am forced to issue a yellow card on this simile from The Athletic's recent story on Jokic, written by Fred Katz:
Early in Brown’s season in Denver, the guard went into a handoff play with Jokić. Once the MVP received the basketball, both his defender and Brown’s followed him, which left Brown open. Brown screamed out the proper terminology.
“Wolf! Wolf!” he yelled, the Nuggets’ alert that a double team was coming.
With no one on him, Brown then cut to the basket, figuring Jokić could hit him for an easy layup. Instead, Jokić tossed a no-look pass far behind him and out of bounds. Later in the game, Jokić explained why.
“Don’t cut,” he told Brown. “I’m listening to your voice.”
Jokić, like a bat, can tell where people are just by where sound waves originate. From that point on, Brown never cut after yelling for the ball; Jokić hit him with no-look dimes constantly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need A New Concept Of Free Speech, And We Need It Now]]></title>
        <id>680118e20951470001ef01a7</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/we-need-a-new-concept-of-free-speech-and-we-need-it-now/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T15:32:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rejecting the civil libertarian interpretation of the First Amendment is more important than ever]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal Was Perfect When It Had To Be]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187256</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/arsenal-was-perfect-when-it-had-to-be"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T15:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite a comfortable 3-0 home victory in the first leg of its Champions League quarterfinal against Real Madrid, Arsenal must have still felt in danger on Wednesday. Call it the Real Madrid Effect, or call it the Arsenal Had Only Been To Two Champions League Semifinals Ever Conundrum, but nothing felt safe as the Gunners tried to build on their monumental win last week in hopes of advancing. They needn't have worried, though. Despite a couple of ominous mistakes, Arsenal continued to prove that it was just the better team in this match-up, and one that can not only make a semifinal but actually win the whole tournament. The Gunners left the Estadio Santiago Bernabeu with a 2-1 victory, and a 5-1 aggregate romp, that felt as fair as any Real Madrid loss can.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hEZDGBlptss]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘North Of North’ Is An Arctic Comedy That Will Warm Your Heart]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187051</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/north-of-north-is-an-arctic-comedy-that-will-warm-your-heart"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T14:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I am a modern Inuk woman,” says the actress Anna Lambe, in the opening moments of her new sitcom, North of North. “…Whatever that means.” Lambe plays Siaja, a twenty-something undergoing a quarter-life crisis in her tiny Arctic hometown: Ice Cove, a fictional place built on the realities of life in Nunavut’s two dozen far-flung hamlets. 
As the pilot episode unfolds, Siaja decides that she’s spent too much time putting other people first. She was forced to self-parent during the years before her single mom, Neevee, got sober; then she married right after high school and had a daughter soon after. Now she’s a stay-at-home mother, the wife to an oblivious husband, and she desperately needs a change. Across the eight short episodes of the show’s first season, Siaja tries to remake her life—often while spinning from one awkward disaster into another.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eva Holland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extinguish The Beam]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187252</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/extinguish-the-beam-sacramento-kings"/>
        <updated>2025-04-17T13:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the play-in tournament is good for anything, it's throwing an annual spotlight on some of the NBA's most stuck-in-the-mud franchises. Whereas 9- and 10- seeds used to be able to slink into the offseason in relative anonymity, they are now dragged into the light for one more nationally televised, win-or-go-home game that is sure to leave everyone who watches muttering something like, "Oh boy, this is a mess."
This year, it's the Sacramento Kings whose asses are in the jackpot. This is thanks to the humiliating 120-106 loss they suffered to the post-Luka Mavericks on Wednesday night, bringing an end to a season in which the Kings went 40-42, fired their coach, and traded their best player. A casual observer tuning into last night's game, checking in on the Kings for maybe the first time all season, would have been confronted with some alarming developments: DeMar DeRozan needed 28 shots to score his 33 points; Domantas Sabonis could muster only 11 points while committing five turnovers; Zach LaVine is on this team now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Film a hand / Break a leg]]></title>
        <id>68001b35105fa700014bcac0</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/film-a-hand-break-a-leg/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T22:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nathan Munn on Canadian medicine, and Hollywood gossip on the road with Jack Pendarvis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ace Goes to Hollywood: Episode 4]]></title>
        <id>67ffcf22105fa700014bc9bc</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/ace-goes-to-hollywood-episode-4/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T22:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ace Goes to Hollywood is a continuing transcript of a ride from Oxford, Mississippi, to Memphis, Tennessee, during which Jack Pendarvis interviewed Ace Atkins about his work on the Pauly Shore film Jury Duty.
Episode 4: Bring Me the Hands of Abe Vigoda
Ace has just answered his phone, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Pendarvis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Health Care You Can Trust]]></title>
        <id>680007dd105fa700014bca4e</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/health-care-you-can-trust/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T22:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you, a Canadian, should catastrophically break your femur and dislocate your hip doing something stupid, as I did 20 years ago, you’ll quickly find your screaming, shivering form scooped up by friendly paramedics, delivered to hospital, triaged, X-rayed, repaired by world-class surgeons (alongside radiologists, nurses, anaesthesiologists, etc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Munn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dominique Malonga Is Ready To Light Up The WNBA]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186982</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dominique-malonga-is-ready-to-light-up-the-wnba"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T20:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the morning of the WNBA draft, Dominique Malonga stepped out onto the observatory deck of the Empire State Building, sporting a huge, winsome smile and a tiny camcorder in her hand. Against a canvas of groggy faces in matching hoodies, Malonga’s own bright face stood out. She and her fellow draft prospects were midway through a tiring multi-day circuit of media engagements and rookie orientation meetings. (At the draft that night, the writer Mel Greenberg called this procession “the car wash.”) So you could forgive them all for looking less than enthused to ceremonially “light” a building that would not actually be lit for many more hours because it was 9:00 a.m.
Maybe it was the smile that won me over. Maybe it was the tiny camcorder. Maybe I felt some extra affection on account of Malonga’s youth. International pros are subject to looser age restrictions than players drafted from the NCAA. At 19, the French center is one of the youngest members of this rookie class. Someone from the league’s in-house media staff asked Malonga a few questions about her game and her WNBA goals for a video. With the city skyline behind her, the 6-foot-6 Malonga spoke about her versatility and said she was most excited to discover American culture. (I have some bad news, Dominique.) She was then asked what she wanted fans to know about her. “That I’m, like, a smiley person,” she said—how else?—smiling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angry Interjections From Chuck Grassley’s Chippy Town Hall Meeting, Ranked]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187196</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/angry-interjections-from-chuck-grassleys-chippy-town-hall-meeting-ranked"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T18:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chuck Grassley, Iowa's 91-year-old Republican Senator, held a town hall with some of his constituents yesterday in Fort Madison, Iowa. After reviewing eight minutes of footage from the meeting, I have to say that the people of Fort Madison were really getting Chuck's ass.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gbfPt8o8h5A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The DOGE Fencing Hearing Reveals The Latest In Anti-Trans Grift]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187154</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-doge-fencing-hearing-reveals-the-latest-in-anti-trans-grift"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T17:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On March 30, fencer Stephanie Turner was disqualified from the Cherry Blossom Open, a minor Division I-A tournament in Maryland, for kneeling and refusing to compete against her opponent, college fencer Red Sullivan, who is a trans woman. The incident was recorded and immediately posted to Twitter; shortly afterward, Turner participated in an interview with Fox News, stating, "I looked at the ref and I said, 'I'm sorry, I cannot do this. I am a woman, and this is a man, and this is a women's tournament. And I will not fence this individual.'" The referee then gave Turner, who is 31 years old, a black card for refusing to fence, in accordance with the International Fencing Federation rules, which was later upheld by USA Fencing. Sullivan, who is 19 and a self-described "mid" competitor, went on to place 24th out of 39 fencers at the competition, winning two out of her six bouts.
The incident has predictably ballooned far outside of the original event's scope or results. J.K. Rowling, whose primary vocation nowadays is spamming posts about trans issues on Twitter, quote-tweeted the video with "What a heroine looks like." After stating that her stunt would temporarily ruin her life, Turner received a $5,000 "Courage Wins Champions" prize from XX-XY Athletics, a sportswear brand centered around "protecting women's sports." Most eye-wateringly, on Tuesday, Congresswoman and DOGE subcommittee chair Marjorie Taylor Greene announced a hearing on USA Fencing's policy allowing trans women to compete in women's events, and invited Turner to testify. The hearing is scheduled for May 7.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zach Edey Is A Force]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187156</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/zach-edey-is-a-force"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T17:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The competitive dynamic of Tuesday night's Grizzlies–Warriors play-in was brutally simple: The Warriors were more skilled and generally better, but the Grizzlies were bigger, more athletic, and nastier. The winner would be the team that could enforce its style of play, and while Golden State eventually did so, there was a solid 24 or so minutes spanning the back half of the second quarter through most of the fourth when they couldn't do a thing against Memphis's physicality. I was particularly enamored of—and the Warriors were particularly plagued by—Zach Edey.
Edey is a curious player. His considerable strengths (vertical) and weaknesses (horizontal) are evident to anyone who watches him move around the court for one single play, and the Warriors made hay early by repeatedly isolating him and having Jimmy Butler and Steph Curry attack him in space. That was often the right play, though Edey is so huge and so rugged that he warps the space on the court in a way no other player in the league does. Butler would feint and flex his way into the paint, beating Edey to the spot, or Curry would drive past an overplaying defender and into the paint, and neither superstar would convert on the sort of easy opportunity they have for a collective 30 seasons, due to Edey forcing a miss. Curry destroyed the Kings for 50 points in 2023 with these sorts of drives, but Edey, slow as he is, is just too big.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Became Highly Educated Grist For The AI Mill]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187101</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-i-became-highly-educated-grist-for-the-ai-mill"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T16:43:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was actually having a pretty good conversation with the avatar interviewer. We had discussed my current work, my PhD thesis, and recent research developments I found compelling. It only took a few seconds to adjust to the reality: that this was the interview, that I would talk only to this avatar, that this avatar had accurately regurgitated some of the more arcane phrases related to particularly new research techniques that it probably hadn't heard before, that this avatar was steering this conversation in predetermined directions about as well as some human "recruiters" I'd spoken to. I thought back to previous conversations I'd had, at similar phases of similar job applications, and, honestly, this wasn't so different. "There's a formula," I'd been told, and it pretty much was that way. Now it had been formalized, finalized, and rendered.
And then it asked me some questions I hadn't gotten before in an interview like this: What made a good multiple choice question? And if I were to write a multiple choice question, what would make for a difficult incorrect answer?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Post-Postdoc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paris Saint-Germain Escaped Its Past, For Now]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187114</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/paris-saint-germain-escaped-its-past-for-now"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T15:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last 10 years or so, no team has suffered more heartbreaking collapses in the Champions League than Paris Saint-Germain. The Ligue 1 monolith has, on three separate occasions, held a two-goal advantage at some point in the second leg of a tie, only to lose in demoralizing fashion. The list doubles as a horror story for PSG fans: First was the famous Barcelona comeback in 2017, in which PSG blew a four-goal lead, then came a two-goal disintegration by Manchester United two seasons later. Finally, in 2022, PSG gave up a hat trick to Karim Benzema and Real Madrid in 17 minutes, turning a 2–0 overall lead into a 3–2 aggregate defeat.
Given all that history, there's no way PSG should have felt comfortable heading into Tuesday's second leg of the Champions League quarterfinals against Aston Villa with a 3–1 lead. Something like comfort may have started to creep in after PSG scored the first two goals of Tuesday's game, giving them a 5–1 lead on aggregate. After all, the Parisians trounced Liverpool in the previous round, and Aston Villa is, on paper, no Liverpool. And yet, fear and panic arrived right on schedule, and it took every single bit of resilience PSG had, along with a healthy dose of Gianluigi Donnarumma goalkeeping heroics, to hang onto narrow a 5–4 aggregate victory.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lit Up On Bleep Island]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187141</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lit-up-on-bleep-island"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T15:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Much has been said about small towns. As someone with the dubious pleasure of living in a small town from birth to college, I think small towns have earned every aspect of their reputation. But when you’ve got a small town on a remote island, all those pressures double. Everyone knows everyone else’s business, and it’s harder to escape! Hell is even more hell and other people are even more other people. 
This week, we’ve brought you a story from the beating heart of one such island town: the volunteer firefighting squad. Get ready for a juicy power struggle featuring nepotism, inept boyfriends, and goji berries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired USAID Education Officer]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186894</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-usaid-education-officer"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T14:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Joel Runnels graduated from college, he followed the age-old tradition of young people who don't quite know what they want to do with their lives, which is to say he applied to the Peace Corps. Runnels had studied American Sign Language in college and, as someone who grew up with a speech impediment, he also had a lifelong affinity for working with people with disabilities. The Peace Corps, under the mistaken impression that there's one universal sign language, invited him to pioneer their Deaf Education Program in Kenya. Runnels only knew ASL, so he had to learn Swahili and Kenyan Sign Language as well.
In Kenya, Runnels's students kept asking him if he'd heard of an African-American educator and missionary named Andrew Foster, who is often called the father of Deaf education in Africa. Runnels hadn't, and back in the U.S. he found no books about Foster's life or legacy. "I thought, if I want to read the book, I have to write it," he said. Runnels ended up getting a PhD so that he could write a biography of Foster as his dissertation. "I felt, if he has served as a bridge between America and Africa for 30 years, I can give up a few of my years to give his life and legacy a scholarly treatment," he said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Warriors Really Had To Work For It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187117</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-warriors-really-had-to-work-for-it"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T13:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a game with a hundred turning points, each more compelling than the one before it, building to a crescendo that ended with…an inbound violation? Well, that's something else for the Memphis Grizzlies to work on before Friday, we suppose.
In a mesmerizing yet jagged game to determine which of the two top play-in teams was better suited to deal with the precocious Houston Rockets this weekend in the first round of the actual Western Conference playoffs, the Golden State Warriors out-experienced the Grizz, 121-116. That experience and the steady relentlessness it made was the one thing Memphis could not overcome. They refused to take the knee after a befuddled start and then just kept on refusing, forcing the Warriors to draw 75 points from Jimmy Butler and Stephen Curry in order to survive the kind of scare they are both too old to endure too often. The correct team won, but only after working far harder than they either had meant to or logically can be expected to do repeatedly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Last Nice Moment For Marc-Andre Fleury, Who Deserves Them All]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187081</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/one-last-nice-moment-for-marc-andre-fleury-who-deserves-them-all"/>
        <updated>2025-04-16T13:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Objectively speaking, the Minnesota Wild's final regular-season game against the Ducks Tuesday was a crucial one. They needed to gain a single standings point, by hook or by crook, to clinch one of the West's suddenly competitive wild card spots. The Blues won their game, clinching their own spot, and a regulation loss for the Wild would've left their fate in the hands of the pursuing Flames, who have one more game left. Subjectively speaking, it was even more important for everyone involved that the Wild lock down that point so that Marc-Andre Fleury could get a proper home send-off.
Fleury, 40 years old and playing his 21st and final season, has been on something of a farewell tour as Minnesota's backup. He's been honored in every city, and opponents have formed handshake lines just for him. He's a one-man NHL institution, the rare first-overall goaltender pick way back in 2003, and one of just two players left who played before the lockout. He's been a rock: second all-time in wins and games played. He won three Cups with the Penguins, though, for my money, his most impressive feat was having a career year at age 36 with Las Vegas, winning his first Vezina after most of his contemporaries had already hung up their pads. He's also (and this is a technical term) a good dude, beloved by teammates, fans, and media. He was never truly a dominant netminder, and I think that humanity only made him more endearing as he handled various goaltender controversies and benchings and one unceremonious Vegas eviction with nothing but equanimity. He easily could have retired then, but he still enjoyed playing hockey and so put in the work for a woeful Chicago team, and was rewarded with a third lease on life in Minnesota. The Twin Cities embraced him, as had all his previous homes, and it was as good a situation as any to go out on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New life / Aging legs]]></title>
        <id>67fead90b249b300019cbb7b</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-299/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T23:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Ehrenreich sweeps forward; dance class with Amy Chu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adult Ballet Class]]></title>
        <id>67febb68b249b300019cbbd9</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/adult-ballet-class/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T23:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a collective of 60 writers, on fire and hard to kill]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Chu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soon]]></title>
        <id>67fe93d9b249b300019cbb3c</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/soon/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T23:14:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At some point in the next few days or even hours, my partner will give birth to a child. Her delivery date came and went earlier in the week, but with so much going on and the markets all yippy, who has time for the miracle of life? I’]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Ehrenreich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nico Harrison Picks Ideal Moment To Piss Off Everyone Again]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187061</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nico-harrison-picks-ideal-moment-to-piss-off-everyone-again"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T21:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tomorrow, the Dallas Mavericks will be tipping off a play-in game against the Sacramento Kings. Win, and their hopes of making the postseason stay alive. Lose, and their season ends. Obviously, today was the perfect day for the front office to orchestrate a strange, semi-secretive sit-down with selected members of the local media, the purpose of which seems to have been getting everyone really agitated about the Luka Doncic trade again.
The meeting was organized by Mavs general manager Nico Harrison and CEO Rick Welts. According to DLLS Sports reporter Tim Cato, there were about 15 people present at the meeting, including several Mavericks staffers. The reporters who attended the meeting had to agree not to record any audio, and were told that no video cameras would be allowed into the room. Surely these restrictions were put in place because Harrison and Welts had something new to say to the media, perhaps even a piece of information so explosive that it could not be appropriately revealed without strict messaging controls in place. Surely these two bozos did not drag a dozen or so reporters down to the team facility this morning so that they could sit there and say "Defense wins championships" over and over again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Thing I Own Is My Tiny TV/VCR]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186041</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-best-thing-i-own-is-my-tiny-tv-vcr"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T19:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The idea came in a flash while I was on a barstool in Bed-Stuy’s Do Or Dive. The bartender snapped off the music to swap in the Jeopardy! theme, but I couldn’t find Trebek until I followed my fellow bargoers' gaze to the top of a fridge, where the smallest black and white TV I’ve ever seen rested. In no way was it an appropriate size to show anything, but for a show based mostly in audio it worked fine enough. I wanted my own right away. 
I went to eBay, steering clear of those with DVD players because they felt wrong, and eventually finding one with a VCR built-in because that felt right. It was from Sylvania, with a whopping 9-inch screen, and came with a power source that hooks up into your car’s cigarette lighter for when the grid goes down and we’re fucked. It cost me $120, and it’s the best thing I’ve ever purchased.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Paulas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At What Point Has One Actually “Been To” Space?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186986</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/at-what-point-has-one-actually-been-to-space"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T18:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Monday, the singer Katy Perry, the TV personality Gayle King, Fight Club star Lauren Sánchez, and a few others took a 10-minute, 21-second ride aboard the New Shepard rocket operated by Jeff Bezos's Blue Origin aerospace company. For some brief period of time—a mere fraction of the flight's overall duration—the rocket and its inhabitants reportedly reached or exceeded 330,000 feet of altitude, or what is known as the Kármán Line, a popular but by no means universally agreed-upon definition of the "edge of space." Bezos himself has made this trip before, as have a few others with his Blue Origin company or with competing outfits; each time, the press deferentially reports that the travelers went "to space" or "to outer space."
Charitably, let's grant that the Kármán Line does in fact represent the edge of space. The line's namesake, scientist Theodore von Kármán, chose it as a rough estimate of the altitude at which a vehicle in flight would no longer be kept aloft by aerodynamic lift, but rather entirely by inertia. OK! Fine. Works for me. Grant that the Kármán Line really is a line, and is the edge of space, and grant that the vehicle bearing Katy Perry, Gayle King, et. al. traveled to and possibly past it. Have they "been to space"?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Belichick’s Girlfriend Asks That Her Boyfriend’s Son Receive The “Upmost Respect”]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186985</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bill-belichicks-girlfriend-asks-that-her-boyfriends-son-receive-the-upmost-respect"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T18:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Belichick's University of North Carolina football team, college sports' strongest argument for open records laws, began spring practices this past weekend. As the 72-year-old head coach sorts through position battles and figures out who's going to play quarterback, the real fun for outside observers is in getting a sense of how much Jordon Hudson, his 24-year-old girlfriend, will be doing for the program.
Belichick stocked his coaching ranks with various unsuccessful friends and associates, all of whom seem to understand this might be their final opportunity to harvest a salary from the putrescent corpse of the ex–New England Patriots coach's legacy. According to emails uncovered by The Assembly in March, Belichick is farming out correspondence duties to Hudson, asking a UNC administrator to copy her on all emails sent to him. This week, the Athletic revealed some of those emails, which are pretty funny. Hudson does not work for the university, but she's operating as some sort of professional liaison for her septuagenarian boyfriend and his big-headed son.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Point/Counterpoint: JD Vance Drops The National Championship Trophy]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186969</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/point-counterpoint-jd-vance-drops-the-national-championship-trophy"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T17:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During Monday's White House visit by the FCS national champion Ohio State Buckeyes, former Ohio Senator and current Vice President JD Vance attempted to pick up the National Championship trophy and did not succeed. Vance fumbled both the top and the bottom of the trophy, the base of which tumbled to the ground. Here, Defector presents two perspectives on the incident.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YwOa4m0WRps]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mutilating Your Face For Big Daddy Dictator]]></title>
        <id>67fe72d8040a00000123f9a7</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/mutilating-your-face-for-big-daddy-dictator/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T15:36:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Know that these nightmare alterations were done for one man.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please Enjoy These Photos Of Drunk People At An English Horse Race]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186915</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/please-enjoy-these-photos-of-drunk-people-at-an-english-horse-race-2"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T13:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My computer recently prompted me to "look back at your memories!" along with a photo of a woman, who was not me, sitting down on a nondescript swath of pavement, surrounded by garbage. Now, while I did not personally attend the Grand National at Aintree, just outside of Liverpool, last year, it is true that I have fond memories of my time spent going through photos of that event. The Grand National is ostensibly a horse race, but after conducting my second detailed survey of Getty Images, I can conclusively say that it is actually an excuse for English people to get extremely drunk and sit on nondescript swaths of pavement whilst surrounded by garbage. And sometimes in shrubs. Here is the evidence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Meeting Richard Kind Changed The Course Of My Life]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186951</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-meeting-richard-kind-changed-the-course-of-my-life"/>
        <updated>2025-04-15T13:06:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am going to start with a confession: I used to do theater. I say “do theater,” because I did it all: I acted, I directed, I wrote. I designed costumes, I studied the Meisner technique, I rolled around on the floor in a leotard—I even made puppets. None of this was professional, it mainly took place in black boxes for hire, school auditoriums, and the workshops of eager hobbyists. But theater was my first love, and like it is with many first loves, my former feelings now often embarrass me—not just because I no longer feel them, but because falling out of love was so decisive, so shattering, so apocalyptic that the person I was when I did theater is a person who will never exist again.    
If this sounds dramatic, well, I did just confess to being a theater kid, and what prevented me from becoming a theater adult was character actor Richard Kind. You might be a little confused, wondering how someone who is fairly successful and otherwise innocuous could be an instigator for such discouragement. I can assure you that he did nothing bad; in fact, what he did was beautiful. I heard what he said to me very loudly and clearly at first, then more subtly over the course of my life, as I’ve returned to it and understood it differently at new ages, while he probably gave it less than two seconds of thought at the time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jen Vafidis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern problems / Ancient moods]]></title>
        <id>67fd77905aa1bd00010c6888</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-298/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T22:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Hioe on global authoritarians; a history lesson with Trevor Alixopulos]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hysterical Classicism]]></title>
        <id>67fd620a5aa1bd00010c6769</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hysterical-classicism/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T22:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a collective of 60 writers, on fire and hard to kill]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trevor Alixopulos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Are the World]]></title>
        <id>67fd40ba5aa1bd00010c6707</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/we-are-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T22:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The turbulent character of our times seems to have gone global; each day the news is like seeing the same film adapted in different languages. Draconian budget cuts? Youth-led protests? Resurgent authoritarianism? These could be taking place almost anywhere in the world.
Well, okay… only one country in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Hioe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nico Iamaleava Leaves Tennessee To Seek More Money In The Transfer Portal]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186878</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nico-iamaleava-leaves-tennessee-to-seek-more-money-in-the-transfer-portal"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T19:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the weekend, the Tennessee Volunteers and quarterback Nico Iamaleava went their separate ways, following a contract dispute and brief holdout in which Iamaleava didn't show up to the team's practice on Friday. His camp—mainly his father and agent—had been negotiating for around $4 million for the upcoming season, a significant raise over his expected $2.2 million. Iamaleava first garnered attention in 2022 for originally receiving an $8 million NIL deal over the length of his college career, when he was still a high school recruit. After one year as Tennessee's starting QB, he'll be looking for a new team.
After quarterbacks Carson Beck and Darian Mensah used the transfer portal to find better NIL deals at Miami and Duke, respectively, it seems Iamaleava's camp was seeking something similar. According to ESPN, this contract dispute had been "a growing source of frustration among administrators at Tennessee and within the locker room," with Iamaleava increasing demands as the spring transfer portal is set to open from April 16-25. When Iamaleava missed practice on Friday and didn't communicate with team staff, head coach Josh Heupel made the decision to move on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bad Faith And The Backlash Against 'Wokeism']]></title>
        <id>67fd4ca6f023ed0001ef23f2</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/bad-faith-and-the-backlash-against-wokeism/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T18:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything we're seeing today can be traced back to 2020]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oscar Piastri Takes It To Lando Norris]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186853</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/oscar-piastri-takes-it-to-lando-norris"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T17:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would it be so unreasonable to say that Oscar Piastri will one day win a World Drivers' Championship? Describing a driver as World Championship material is an entirely different matter from declaring that a driver will one day win. The statistics aren't in anyone's favor; the factors necessary (i.e. fast car, good strategy) are outside of any driver's control. Just ask Charles Leclerc. But with Red Bull's sharp decline in performance (or, perhaps, lack of necessary improvement), this year's McLaren is the undisputed fastest car on the grid. Perhaps the most unreasonable part of that declaration is the "one day" framing, which implies some far-off future, beyond rules overhauls and roster shake-ups. If Piastri is to someday win a championship, his best shot might be this year, when all he needs to do is beat Lando Norris. The Bahrain Grand Prix served as proof that he can.
Norris looked beatable all weekend, and was open about it, too. He struggled to find pace, culminating in a P6 finish in qualifying. "I feel like I've just never driven a Formula 1 car before," Norris said after the session. He managed to make up three places on the first lap of the race with an excellent start, but was penalized for being over his grid box. (Max Verstappen, lined up beside Norris on the grid in a struggling Red Bull, wasted no time in immediately calling him out over the radio.) After the first pit stops, Norris was overtaken by Leclerc's Ferrari, thanks to a rare Ferrari strategy win, and thus after the second pit stops had to try to pass both Leclerc and George Russell—perpetually seen in a podium position without quite being sure how he got there—in order to claim P2. He managed Leclerc to secure the podium; after an ill-judged attempt on Russell in the closing lap of the race, that was all he got.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rory McIlroy Feels It All On Sunday]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186858</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rory-mcilroy-feels-it-all-on-sunday"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T16:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What I like about that image up there is that it gives very little away. The shortened depth of field, which swirls the faces of spectators in lovely bokeh, leaves you with the raw emotions of the photo's subject. That subject is Rory McIlroy, the face of men's golf; the photo was taken Sunday on the 18th green of Augusta National, upon the completion of the final hole of the Masters Tournament. What is McIlroy feeling, there? Whatever it is, he is feeling a lot of it. I, the all-powerful blogger, know the answer. You, poor reader, are my prisoner: I could tell you anything! That is maybe an image of a man losing a golf tournament, and succumbing to crippling disappointment. Or, hell, maybe his caddy just told him that his grandmother died. Maybe the glow that lights this scene from behind the photographer is that of a huge mushroom cloud, and McIlroy is going Sarah Connor mode in his final moments. You don't know!
There are other, similar photos from this moment, only slightly less ambiguous. Is this anguish? Rage? Could it be joy? Surely it cannot be pure joy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cincinnati Reds Are Going Nowhere In Particular More Quickly Than Any Team Ever Has]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186844</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-cincinnati-reds-are-going-nowhere-in-particular-more-quickly-than-any-team-ever-has"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T16:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It may be quite easy to please baseball commissioner Rob Manfred, but you’d never know it. Credit to him, the man always looks like a traffic cop on a rainy day. Manfred long ago was accused of not enjoying baseball; based on his usual expression, he has clearly copped a plea on that particular change in lieu of mounting any kind of defense.
But there is one team that Manfred can love unreservedly. They do baseball like all the other teams, absolutely, but most important to Stopwatch Rob, they do it quickly. Absurdly so, in fact. They are the Cincinnati Reds, and if Manfred understands what his audience wants correctly, which is less of what they have paid for per serving, those Reds are the team that will save the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Has One Last Chance To Avert Disaster]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186835</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tottenham-has-one-last-chance-to-avert-disaster"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T15:52:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's another Premier League loss to a team in 15th place? For Tottenham Hotspur, the answer is both "not much" and "a sign of incoming apocalypse." Despite having more money and talent than plenty of teams above them on the table, Spurs continued their lost season on Sunday, traveling to Wolverhampton and coming away with a 4-2 defeat to Wolves, one of the few teams below the North London side in the standings. There's not much difference between 15th and, say, 13th, where Tottenham would have been with a victory, but on the eve of the most important match of its season, this side looks ready to limp to an underwhelming finish.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XySTGD-GPV0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For A Good Time And Great Laughs, Try ‘The Pitt’!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186832</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/for-a-good-time-and-great-laughs-try-the-pitt"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T15:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I always intend to take my parents' recommendations, but I never seem to get around to them. They’ll tell me to watch a movie or some TV series, and I really do want to. They have good taste, and I like talking to them about this sort of thing. Even the bonnet dramas my mom watches tend to be pretty entertaining. They recommended Jury Duty, and that became one of our favorite shows in a long while.
But my wife and I have a 16-month-old child. After he goes to bed, we are usually so exhausted that we just put on some reality schlock, and discuss whether 8 p.m. is too early for two adults to go to bed. So I had not seen The Pitt, the buzzy medical drama set in a Pittsburgh emergency room. My parents recommended it to me before the buzz got loud. As I started to hear from others about the show, I even told my parents that we planned to watch it. And we really did: As a man in my 40s, I try not to lie to my parents too often. But then exhaustion set in, and we watched the Golden Girls episode from Season 6 where Sonny Bono and Lyle Waggoner, playing themselves, woo Bea Arthur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, April 14: Statlines]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186854</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-april-14-statlines"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Step up and solve our Monday crossword. This week's puzzle was constructed by Brandon Koppy and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Brandon lives in Dripping Springs, Texas, just outside Austin, with his wife and two little girls. You can also find his puzzles in The New York Times or on his blog, see17across.com.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE. Note that we're pausing open submissions until April 18.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Messier, Namesake And Sole Voter Of Mark Messier Leadership Award Presented By Mark Messier, Knows How To Fix The Rangers: Mark Messier]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186838</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mark-messier-namesake-and-sole-voter-of-mark-messier-leadership-award-presented-by-mark-messier-knows-how-to-fix-the-rangers-mark-messier"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T14:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been a nightmare season for the New York Rangers, who were eliminated Saturday to become just the fourth team in NHL history to miss the playoffs one year after putting up the league's best record. In appropriate fashion, this season is ending with disgruntlement and dysfunction. Trade deadline acquisition Calvin de Haan said the way he's been treated by the team has been "fucked," and told a reporter he wanted to talk about it. Team PR stepped in and suddenly de Haan was no longer talking.
Nearly everything that could go wrong has in New York. The team's veteran core all seemed to age five years overnight. Offseason dramas with Jacob Trouba and Barclay Goodrow spiraled and appeared to infect the rest of the locker room. Talented youths failed to take the next step. Trouba, the captain, along with Kaapo Kakko, Filip Chytil, Ryan Lindgren, Reilly Smith, and Jimmy Vesey were all important parts of the lineup last year who were shipped out during this campaign. The team alienated its longest-tenured player, Chris Kreider, by leaking its willingness to move him. Instead he finished up what is expected to be the end of his stay on Broadway just as the rest of the team did: with an ineffective whimper. Elite goaltending and special teams carried the Rangers to the conference final last year, but when they regressed, what was left was a team that just wasn't very good. "So many things went together to bring us here," Artemi Panarin said after elimination.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Never Too Early To Get Ready For Gavin McKenna]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186797</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-never-too-early-to-get-ready-for-gavin-mckenna"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T13:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are prospects and then there are prospects. Gavin McKenna is talented enough and young enough, tearing up the WHL as a teen, and hockey-knowers have a good enough track record of identifying franchise-changing youths early, that the 2026 NHL Draft is settled at the top more than 14 months out. If you listen to the hype—and he's done nothing but live up to it so far—McKenna is the rare 17-year-old who already belongs in the consciousness of the casual fan, not just that of the scouts and the weirdos who are really into juniors. So, here's what a number of shitty NHL teams are going to be tanking for next year:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ITC8zeYHZTA]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NBA Playoffs Will Be A Clash Of Generations And Styles]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186794</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-nba-playoffs-will-be-a-clash-of-generations-and-styles"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A permanent axiom of the NBA: the style of play changes between the regular season and the playoffs. This is because the postseason's structure flattens out several key asynchronicities, like rest, travel, and other scheduling quirks, and because each possession becomes significantly more precious, and therefore subject to greater scrutiny. Rotations tighten as stars play more, the game slows down as laggardly transition defenders dedicate themselves to sprinting back after misses, and systemic and personnel deficiencies are exploited to ruthless extremes. Winning often hinges on which team's star can more effectively score one-on-one; defenses do not gamble.
But this year, winning in the regular season looks more different than winning in the playoffs ever has. Several of the best and most interesting teams in the league have found their success by leaning further away from the style that has tended to work in the playoffs. Teams like the Rockets, Thunder, and Grizzlies are winning with large groups of younger players, all of whom are running all over the place all the time. These teams are all different from each other, some in very significant ways, but they all play deep rotations and they all exert concerted pressure on opponents with their collective speed. They apply the principles of early small ball with a bunch of huge guys. They all play an adversarial defense that refuses to allow opponents with the ball to dictate terms of engagement. In other words, they play in such a way that is not going to work in the playoffs if opponents can successfully enforce the historic playoff style.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phallon Tullis-Joyce Makes Her Case As The USWNT Holds First Keeper Tryout In 30 Years]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186778</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/phallon-tullis-joyce-makes-her-case-as-the-uswnt-holds-first-keeper-tryout-in-30-years"/>
        <updated>2025-04-13T20:49:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For three decades, the U.S. women's national team has enjoyed the incredible luxury of stability between the posts. Keepers sustain notably longer and more stable primes than other players, and therefore turn over at the international and club levels far less often. But even then, the USWNT getting 30 years of world-class goalkeeping from Briana Scurry, Hope Solo, and Alyssa Naeher is extremely special. Their excellent, slightly overlapping careers cover every major tournament the USWNT has played since the 1991 World Cup. It is hard to imagine the team winning four World Cups and five Olympic gold medals without those six hands.
But Naeher retired from the USWNT last December, leaving the team without a no-shit first option for the first time in 30 years. Turnover was never a problem in past eras, as Solo was pushing Scurry for the No.1 shirt for years before she took over, just as Naeher pushed Solo. Nobody in the American player pool quite ever pushed Naeher, as the next-most-capped keeper, Casey Murphy, has faded from the picture. The three keepers called up for a pair of April friendlies against Brazil came to camp with 12 total caps. Emma Hayes has a minor succession crisis on her hands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin De Bruyne Has One More Job]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186765</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/kevin-de-bruyne-has-one-more-job"/>
        <updated>2025-04-13T20:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eight minutes into the match, after Eberechi Eze had calmly side-footed the ball over an undefended goal line to give Crystal Palace an early lead, I had for the first time this season the feeling that Manchester City really might not get off the mat.
Throughout City's season from hell, it has always felt like the squad was too strong, the manager too great, and the team too experienced to end the year in truly disastrous fashion by finishing outside of the Champions League places. Surely the midseason slump would eventually come to an end. Surely the superstars we've watched dominate the best league in the world in unprecedented fashion would finally find some form. Surely, even after it had become clear that there would be no magical click that would transform this team into the swaggering City of old, the Citizens would eventually stop bleeding points, play some simply decent soccer, and nab one of the Premier League's five Champions League spots. But then Eze put Palace ahead in what was for City a must-win home game, and I looked at the standings of this preposterously tight EPL top-five race, and I had to confront the idea that maybe City wouldn't ever wake up from this nightmare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pauline Ferrand-Prévot’s Quick Return Makes A Great Cycling Season Better]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186731</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/pauline-ferrand-prevots-quick-return-makes-a-great-cycling-season-better"/>
        <updated>2025-04-13T18:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pauline Ferrand-Prévot was not supposed to take the start line at Paris-Roubaix on Saturday, though the framework of expectation and surprise is insufficient when applied to a rider like Ferrand-Prévot; everything about her 2025 season has been and necessarily will be a surprise. Ferrand-Prévot is back on the road this year after a six-year hiatus spent dominating the mountain biking scene. She decided to swap out her thick tires for skinny ones after winning gold in Paris at last summer's Olympics, completing the career sweep in the process, and she's returned to a very different peloton than the one she left in 2018. Ferrand-Prévot is a former road-race world champion, so it's not like she doesn't know what she's doing. But she'd never raced against latter-day crushers like Demi Vollering and Lorena Wiebes. Could PFP beat the new generation?
As it turns out: yes, with flair. Ferrand-Prévot has been one of the best riders through the early-season cobbled classic swing, taking third at Strade Bianche, second at last weekend's Tour of Flanders, and continuing her linear ascent of podia by winning Paris-Roubaix on Saturday. Each performance has been more impressive than the last: she won a small-group sprint in Italy, made the elite four-rider selection and finished second in the sprint for the win in Belgium, then escaped all alone to win at home in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Place Sam Long On 15-Day IL, Call Up Evan Sisk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=848271</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/royals-place-sam-long-on-15-day-il-call-up-evan-sisk.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-13T14:39:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that left-hander Sam Long has been placed on the 15-day injured list due to inflammation in his throwing elbow.  Fellow southpaw Evan Sisk was called up from Triple-A in the corresponding move, and Sisk will be making his MLB debut whenever he appears in his first game. Something has clearly seemed amiss…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Notes: India, Outfield, Wright]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=848243</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/royals-notes-india-outfield-wright.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-13T02:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals seem to have avoided what could’ve been a brutal blow this evening when infielder Jonathan India exited the club’s game against the Guardians due to what the club later announced was a bout of right quad tightness. After the game, manager Matt Quatraro told reporters (including MLB.com’s Anne Rogers) that the tightness India…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>