<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-07-04T16:22:12.334Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Fourth Of July Open Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194426</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/your-fourth-of-july-open-thread"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T13:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're off today. Consider this your place to blab about sports, food, antiquing, or anything else that floats your boat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Guide To The 2025 Tour de France]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194239</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/your-guide-to-the-2025-tour-de-france"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T13:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bonjour et bienvenue! The 2025 Tour de France begins Saturday in Lille. If you want to about read the rhythms of the sport, you're in luck, because we have a two-part series on that for you. If you want a preview of the three weeks of racing, you have come to the right place.
A lovely rhythm to the Tour de France is that while the precise route is different every year, the rough shape holds. The Tour always gets more difficult as it goes, with the race beginning on flatter terrain before hitting the Alps and Pyrenees in some order in the second and third weeks to assort the winner. Over the past 15 years the Tour's organizers, the Amaury Sport Organisation (ASO), have set aside their haughty sense of superiority and made their race significantly better by borrowing from what works in other races. Gone are the interminable, 200-kilometer-plus days of pancake-flat racing and predictable mountain slogs, replaced with mixed, Ardennes-style hilly stages and shorter, punchier mountain days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Talking with the punk man about comic books]]></title>
        <id>6866fed55fc5d2000117465a</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-354/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T00:53:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zach Rabiroff in conversation with Billy Bragg about protest, comics, and cave walls]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Billy Bragg Met Alfred E. Neuman]]></title>
        <id>6865a6acf4a63e00017f70cb</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/when-billy-bragg-met-alfred-e-neuman/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T00:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Rabiroff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HYDRANYM No. 6: Vote!]]></title>
        <id>684ae0fee36b2c0001a46bc3</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hydranym-no-6-vote/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T00:19:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Make your choice from among these 21 convivial entries on the theme: 
REUNION 
to choose the victor of Hydranym No. 6. 
HYDRANYM is the Creative Writing word game especially for Flaming Hydra subscribers. Please join in! It’s fun, and you will also receive our glorious email newsletter each]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Michael Fulmer To Minor League Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=857854</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/royals-sign-michael-fulmer-to-minor-league-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T21:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced Thursday that they’ve signed righty Michael Fulmer to a minor league contract. He’s been assigned to Triple-A Omaha. Fulmer, a client of BBI Sports Group, recently passed through waivers and elected free agency after being designated for assignment by the Cubs. Fulmer, 32, is a former American League Rookie of the Year…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fireworks In The Age Of Fascism]]></title>
        <id>6866c80454e524000111a85e</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/fireworks-in-the-age-of-fascism/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T19:46:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Folks who aren't down with fascism are going to have no choice but to leverage patriotism to beat back creeping authoritarianism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poll: Will The Royals Trade Seth Lugo?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=857780</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/poll-will-the-royals-trade-seth-lugo.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T19:04:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals’ 2025 season has not gone as they surely hoped it would after they surprised the baseball world with a playoff berth in 2024 and invested heavily into the team over the offseason. While they entered June over .500, a brutal 8-18 swoon last month left the team very abruptly buried in the AL…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Interested In Bryan Reynolds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=857789</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/royals-interested-in-bryan-reynolds.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T16:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have been looking for outfield upgrades for years and Ken Rosenthal of The Athletic reports that they have interest in Bryan Reynolds of the Pirates, though Rosenthal adds that talks haven’t yet gained momentum and Kansas City is also interested in other hitters. Reynolds, 30, has been one of the faces of the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Team Tactics Shape The Tour de France, And Vice Versa]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194338</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-team-tactics-shape-the-tour-de-france-and-vice-versa"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T15:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In yesterday's story, How To Watch Cycling, I wrote offhand that the Tour de France was "poker on two wheels." That poker game is an important element of tactics, but it's not the only one. With the Tour so close and so much more coverage to come, it seemed worth addressing the principles of team tactics a little more thoroughly. How do the teams fight each other? What are they fighting for? And why is that interesting?
A team's primary weapon is riding hard enough to exact a toll on riders who want to stay in the peloton. Imagine a stage where the day's breakaway is not getting away from the peloton. Imagine that over the remainder of the stage there are, say, four medium to medium-hard climbs spread out over 100 kilometers. The team that has been managing the pace on a hilly day suddenly champs down on the bit and starts attacking. Their riders are taking turns setting a grueling pace, sustained by a willingness to accept burning some serious fuel. Whether that means a single rider pushing their limit or several riders taking turns expending serious efforts and then relieving each other, someone is going to expend more effort than the average rider could fully recover from by the next day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Mall I Loved Is Going Pitch Black]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192961</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-mall-i-loved-is-going-pitch-black"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T15:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The vote looked like a funeral. Residents showed up to the council meeting dressed in black, carrying prop tombstones. One carried drooping flowers. "I feel that what the council has just done has sentenced us to a long, agonizing death," she said. "We're disgusted," said another protester. Dire predictions had been made at earlier hearings. "I'm embarrassed to say I live in Bensalem," one woman told the council. "Do you know why? Because of what we've let it become."
It was 1997. The issue at hand in Bensalem Township, Penn., was the construction of an $11 million, 24-screen movie theater at the Neshaminy Mall. The township's planning commission had rejected the proposal. Residents of the nearby Belmont Hills neighborhood were concerned about increased crime and traffic. The arguments got a little esoteric. "When Arnold Schwarzenegger finishes saving the world, some rowdy people will come out of the theater spinning their wheels, and crime will inevitably occur," said the town watch co-chair. A planning commission board member wondered why anyone would even go to a theater: "Why should you get in your car and face all that traffic and all that aggravation just to see a movie?"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hanif Kureishi Writes Himself Anew In ‘Shattered’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194071</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/hanif-kureishi-writes-himself-anew-in-shattered"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T14:54:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That Joan Didion line, "We tell ourselves stories in order to live," is ubiquitous because like so much of her work, it gets at an essential truth. But the thing about that quote—the idea that we form narratives out of the things that happen to us—is that it suggests we do it in order to move forward in some way. "In order to live" implies that those stories make life easier, more understandable, maybe even conquerable. Didion is a master at also showing how those stories fail us, and yet there is still a kind of optimism embedded in her words. Didion may have been fragile, her life may have been difficult towards the end, but on the page, maybe in part because of her facility with landing on the mot juste, she always seemed like she could handle it—like she was fundamentally indestructible. 
So what happens when you tell yourself stories for a less inspiring reason? When the narrative you form out of the things that happen to you is in fact designed to keep you stuck? Or, my therapist's preferred term: tangled up. "We tell ourselves stories in order to die" doesn't have quite the same lift. It's also not exactly accurate. But there are plenty of us who tell ourselves stories, incessantly, relentlessly, which make it harder to live. We take the things that happen to us, and only see the dark side, even when the people around us keep on trying to extend some light our way. "You do it to yourself," my therapist told me recently, to which I did not respond (but wanted to): "And that's what really hurts."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Like A Bat In The Supermarket]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194063</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/like-a-bat-in-the-supermarket"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T14:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is probably enough to note that this week's episode of The Distraction, which was recorded last week, is A Vacation Episode. Regular listeners have encountered these before, and even those readers that have never listened to the podcast but have some understanding of words can probably guess at what this means. If you want to parse it even more finely, this is a Double Vacation Episode, given that Drew was on vacation when we recorded it—was, quite literally, slathered in sunblock and headed to the beach when I reminded him that we were scheduled to talk—and that I am on vacation now as the episode finds you wherever you get your podcasts. If you want to go in fully prepared, you should bear that in mind. Think about what a Double Vacation Episode might be like. OK, here you go:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘F1: The Movie’ Is Great If Your Favorite Part Of Racing Is All The Corporate Logos]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193930</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/f1-the-movie-is-great-if-your-favorite-part-of-racing-is-all-the-corporate-logos"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T13:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[F1: The Movie is not a good sports movie, but it also doesn't try very hard to be. Instead, it is a superhero flick dressed in a sports movie livery. Like a superhero movie, F1: The Movie primarily rewards nerds—in this case, fans who know too much about Formula 1—with opportunities to tap into the dopamine vault of recognition. There is no shortage of figures to recognize: the voices, and later profiles, of commentators David Croft and Martin Brundle; a fatuous aside about how that Max Verstappen guy's really good, huh; a shot of Lewis Hamilton's bulldog Roscoe happily trundling down the paddock; the phrase "shitbox"; Guenther Steiner, enough said.
Equally recognizable is the visual language, which successfully mimics an F1 television broadcast. Each race is introduced with the name printed in F1's proprietary font and a stylized diagram of the circuit stamped over an overhead helicopter shot. Much of the race footage is adapted from shots of the 2023 and 2024 F1 Championship, which means few new angles to work with, but plenty for fans to recall. There is the onboard shot, peeking above the bars of the halo. There is a shot of the drivers' helmets, seated on the grid before the start. Do the cars look like they're the fastest in the world? Not really, which proves a commitment to the aesthetics of the source material.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet The Crew Whose Job Is To Keep Rally Fans From Getting Themselves Killed]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193985</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/meet-the-crew-whose-job-is-to-keep-rally-fans-from-getting-themselves-killed"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T12:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Eight hours per day, we’re not allowed to do more,” FIA World Rally Championship safety delegate Nicolas Klinger jokes. “Eight hours in the morning, eight hours in the afternoon.” 
I’m sitting with Klinger in the WRC’s race control room at the Rally de Portugal, which took place in May. Klinger has been here since 6:00 a.m. and won’t leave until 9:00 p.m. or later. He’s doing important work, scanning video feeds of the 337-kilometer course for what he calls “mushrooms.” Before every stage, the WRC sends out a car to move spectators standing in unsafe locations. But some spectators wander back after the safety car is gone, or hide as it goes by, popping up like a mushroom after it passes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raphael Orlove</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big slugger / Warped colors]]></title>
        <id>68659638f4a63e00017f7073</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-353/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T01:40:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remembering Dave Parker with John Saward; Felipe De La Hoz in a purple haze]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Parker Trots Home]]></title>
        <id>68647519cd718d000107c5a2</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/dave-parker-trots-home/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T01:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six-foot-five, 245 pounds, a slugger from the age of behemoths and big-swingers, the real-deal furniture movers and bouncer-shaped designated hitters, the plodding old oafs running out of breath on stand-up doubles. But Dave Parker could move, was the thing; he could hit it all over, he could be pesky and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Saward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glow in the Dark]]></title>
        <id>6862e8e6e9904f0001974c32</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/glow-in-the-dark/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T01:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m using my precious Hydra space this month to write about something that’s often been on my mind: LomoChrome Purple, an ISO 100-400 color-shift film emulsion produced by the cheeky analog photography company Lomography, which renders most scenes in sumptuous hues of blue and purple.
Now,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felipe De La Hoz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Knicks Backed Their Way Into A Good Coach]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194304</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-knicks-backed-their-way-into-a-good-coach"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T19:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So after all that windmill-tilting, the New York Knicks are about to spear Mike Brown as their new head coach, and there will be some laughter because of all the time they wasted to get a guy they could have gotten 15 minutes after firing Tom Thibodeau.
Which matters exactly not at all in the long run. It's just us enjoying the shambolic Knicks for not receiving permission to bother all the coaches with all the reputations, just because they're the Knicks and should never not enjoy all the illusory benefits of habitual label shopping—especially if the shopping is done with an eye toward taking something someone else has.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Steps Forward, Three Steps Back: Michael Koresky On Hollywood’s Queer History]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193905</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/two-steps-forward-three-steps-back-michael-koresky-on-hollywoods-queer-history"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T17:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The history of mainstream filmmaking is prone to whiggish readings. The story is that Hollywood, an industry of entertainment and representation, has moved forward in a pleasing, gradually liberal-minded direction with every decade, enfranchising more audiences, capturing more imaginations, all for positive and idealistic reasons. 
Michael Koresky’s excellent new book Sick and Dirty: Hollywood’s Gay Golden Age and the Making of Modern Queerness troubles this idea. Training his eye on a period not generally known for its celebration of non-normative sexuality or gender expression, Koresky demonstrates how queerness occupied a complex, often contradictory position in the industry. He writes, “Future generations have come to accept on-screen images of the past as simply the way things were, but to believe people were naive rather than part of a heavily policed system is to misunderstand where popular art comes from.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Take Defector’s 2025 Reader Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194232</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/take-defectors-2025-reader-survey"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defector’s growth committee is hard at work preparing for all-company meetings in August, where we’ll set strategy for Year 6 and beyond. Our biennial reader survey is probably the most important single input to that process. You should take the survey! It’ll take you about five minutes, and you’ll gain entry into a drawing for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Watch Cycling]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193566</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-to-watch-cycling"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T16:34:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 112th edition of the Tour de France starts this weekend. La Grand Boucle is the biggest deal in cycling by a considerable margin, which means that a mass audience of non-enthusiasts will tune in for their first and only taste of road racing of the year, watch the beautiful scenery fly for five-plus hours, and shrug their shoulders, not quite having understood the appeal. 
It seems simple. One rider crosses the line before the others. I'm somewhat sympathetic to the skeptic's position here, not because it is correct, but rather because the visual and technical language of cycling is remarkably distinct from every other major sport. Cycling is a nested suite of sophisticated maneuvers masquerading as a straightforward fitness contest. The Tour de France, more than any other race, typifies this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malik Beasley Had His Wages Garnished By His Former Dentist]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194197</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/malik-beasley-had-his-wages-garnished-by-his-former-dentist"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T16:08:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NBA free agent Malik Beasley is currently the subject of a federal investigation into gambling, prop bets, and wire fraud. As a result, the Detroit Pistons have reportedly withdrawn a three-year, $42 million contract to their top three-point shooter. Beasley could have really used the money, judging by the grim financial picture painted by The Detroit News in a report published Tuesday.
Court records accessed by the News show that Beasley has been sued by a variety of parties. In order of severity:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A People’s History Of Climbing On Cars]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192757</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-peoples-history-of-climbing-on-cars"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T14:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The purpose of a car's design is to take something that will essentially exist to consumers as an appliance and elevate it into something that they can project an identity onto, and therefore justify blowing 10-to-100 grand to acquire. The grand project of drawing the most fuckable windowed toaster has brought many evolutions, and just as evolution keeps making crabs, car designers keep going, "Yo, what if they could climb on it?" What follows is a history of their attempts to help us goofy car owners clamber up our vehicles, and the reasons we have had to.
Why Climb? Poop Is Gross!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Bloom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLBTR Podcast: Depleted Mets’ Pitching, The Pirates Are Open For Business, And More!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=857629</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/mlbtr-podcast-depleted-mets-pitching-the-pirates-are-open-for-business-and-more.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T14:51:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest episode of the MLB Trade Rumors Podcast is now live on Spotify, Apple Podcasts, and wherever you get your podcasts! Make sure you subscribe as well! You can also use the player at this link to listen, if you don’t use Spotify or Apple for podcasts. This week, host Darragh McDonald is joined by Tim Dierkes of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Well Soon, Red Panda]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194185</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/get-well-soon-red-panda"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T14:20:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last few weeks have been a string of hard times for Indiana-based basketball, even with victories strewn across the landscape. The Indiana Pacers reached the NBA Finals—good—but lost Tyrese Haliburton to a torn Achilles tendon in Game 7—very bad. The Indiana Fever are now the WNBA's leading draw because of Caitlin Clark—good—but Clark has been injured twice, first her quad muscle and more recently her groin—bad—in addition to finishing ninth at her position in player voting for the All-Star Game—confusing—and being the subject of Christine Brennan's upcoming unauthorized hagiography—ominous.
But those were circumstantial. Now we know something is karmically amiss, because a vengeful universe has just taken out Red Panda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Kings Did Their Free Agency Shopping At A Bin Store]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194146</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-kings-did-their-free-agency-shopping-at-a-bin-store"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T13:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Los Angeles Kings entered free agency with one mission: to build a team better than the Oilers, who've eliminated them in the first round in each of the last four postseasons. Enter new GM Ken Holland, who in his post–Red Wings career has a pathological fetish for signing veterans and depth guys and then expecting too much from them in a cursed chimera of a lineup. Seriously, this guy hasn't met a roster he couldn't make older. He's testing the limits of how much he can pay a third defensive pairing and still find employment. He hasn't changed his opinion of what makes a useful NHL player since the Bush administration. He acts as if the salary cap is just a phase, and the league will toss it out any day now. He recoils from the word "rebuild" like a rabies patient from water.
So it was with both glee and trepidation that the world watched the Kings head into free agency with a whopping $23.5 million in cap space, and mostly bare shelves to spend it on, after nearly all the top available guys found homes before the store opened. True to form, their Day 1 spending spree proved to be extremely funny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is JD Vance Irish? Be Careful Who You Ask]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193697</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/is-jd-vance-irish-be-careful-who-you-ask"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T13:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only a few years ago, JD Vance was boasting about his immigrant roots. “To understand me, you must understand that I am a Scots-Irish hillbilly at heart,” Vance wrote in Hillbilly Elegy, the 2016 book that launched him into the public consciousness.
Given that he leveraged the success of that bestseller and the movie it spawned into a job just a heartbeat away from the top spot in the most anti-immigrant administration in American history, it's kind of delicious watching the foreigners he'd claimed as kin fail to admit he’s really one of them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vibes Are All That Matter Now]]></title>
        <id>6863efde22d8620001268bb7</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/vibes-are-all-that-matter-now/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T12:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The left has to accept that we have entered a post-materialist age, whether we like it or not]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global citizens]]></title>
        <id>686459cbcd718d000107c48e</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-352/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T01:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yemisi Aribisala on a questionable insurance policy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Born in the USA]]></title>
        <id>68645012cd718d000107c3dc</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/born-in-the-usa/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T01:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I visited a friend who was babysitting some relatives’ children, one Saturday afternoon 23 years ago. During the course of the visit, the children began to fight. One little boy had been called Nigerian, and as a consequence had become very offended. It emerged that they’d been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yemisi Aribisala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HYDRANYM No. 6]]></title>
        <id>68645ac4cd718d000107c49d</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hydranym-no-6/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T01:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Subscribe to Flaming Hydra to play HYDRANYM! It's bizarrely fun, plus you get to read the newsletters each weekday AND participate in the Comments Section.  YES.
THIS GAME ENDS MIDNIGHT PST WEDNESDAY, JULY 3

THE RULES
Create an ENTERTAINING and APT acronym from the letters provided. Use only]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bucks And Damian Lillard End Their Brief, Forgettable Relationship]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194082</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-bucks-and-damian-lillard-end-their-brief-forgettable-relationship"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T20:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Damian Lillard's tenure as a star almost certainly fell apart when his left Achilles tendon did in late April. Now his tenure as a Milwaukee Buck is over, too. The team announced Tuesday that it will waive Lillard and stretch the remaining $113 million on his contract over the next five years, thus concluding the oddly unsatisfying Giannis-Dame era.
On paper, it was a perfect fit; on the court, it never cohered. Lillard will receive all that money he's due without having to play another basketball game. Surely he wants to play more, however. He also turns 35 in two weeks, and will be 36 by the time he's ready to log serious minutes again, on a repaired tendon, as a 6-foot-2 guard already toeing the line of athletic viability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All I Want Is To Live In A World Where People Talk Normal]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193977</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/all-i-want-is-to-live-in-a-world-where-people-talk-normal"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T17:36:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about farmers markets, vibrators, dogs in mild peril, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wilyer Abreu Hit It To The Most Fun Spot In Fenway]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194030</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/wilyer-abreu-hit-it-to-the-most-fun-spot-in-fenway"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T16:38:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You might think that the coolest place to hit a baseball is over the fence. But Red Sox outfielder Wilyer Abreu is here to prove you wrong. In a Boston win where he also smashed a grand slam the traditional way, Abreu earned an inside-the-park dong with a trick shot off Fenway Park's centerfield wall.
The Sox attacked Reds rookie Chase Burns early, scoring seven in the first inning. By the time the bottom of the fifth came around, Cincinnati had plated four of their own to make the game a little more interesting. Abreu was the lead-off hitter, and he had a chance to tie his ex-teammate Rafael Devers for most dingers by a Red Sock this season. On 0-2, he got a juicy fastball up in the zone and turned on it, knocking the ball to that little angled nook in the deepest part of his 113-year-old ballfield. The Sock's sock was a few feet from a slow trot around the bases. Instead, he had to race the whole way, benefiting from a dramatic ricochet that sent the ball rolling along the warning track. Its path was so mischievous that the Reds couldn't even throw the ball back to the infield before Abreu slid head-first across the plate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ohio Caves To The Haslams, Tells Cleveland To Eat Dirt]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194034</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ohio-caves-to-the-haslams-tells-cleveland-to-eat-dirt"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T16:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kneejerk response to the Ohio legislature helping Cleveland Browns owner Jimmy Haslam to stop being the Cleveland part of that descriptor was a marvelous bit of cynicism-driven political powerlifting that, in its own way, is exactly what Ohio, the Browns, and particularly the Haslams deserve.
With three deft moves, the lawmakers cleared the track for the Haslams, Jimmy and Dee, to move the team out of Cleveland to the suburb of Brook Park, in contravention of the Modell Law, named after the bankrupted cur who moved the original Browns to Baltimore, by changing the wording of the law to undermine it entirely; they also claimed to find their $600 million share of the new stadium nut by seizing some treasure trove of unclaimed money; they then allowed the Haslams to continue to collect on their share of county's taxes against beer, hard liquor and cigarettes because, well, Deshaun Watsons don't come cheap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Lot Can Go Wrong While Attempting A Speed Record On Mount Everest]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193865</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-lot-can-go-wrong-while-attempting-a-speed-record-on-mount-everest"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T15:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2019, while in Peru as a camp counselor, Tyler Andrews set his first Fastest Known Time (FKT) on the 37.9-mile Salkantay Inca Trail, which leads to the summit of Machu Picchu. Andrews’s time beat the previous mark by more than two hours. He identified primarily as a distance runner back then—he’d earned a spot at the U.S. Olympic trials for the marathon in 2016, would do so again in 2020, and had a personal best of 2:15:52—but his performance on the Salkantay Inca Trail kickstarted a new athletic career as a full-fledged mountaineer ascending the tallest mountains in the world in pursuit of various speed records. In May, he aimed to set one on the loftiest setting of all: Mount Everest. 
Andrews exploded into elite-level running from inauspicious beginnings. He was a music and theater head in his younger years and didn’t crack 18 minutes in the 5K in high school. But he was fiercely hardworking, discovered he had an enormous VO2 max, and improved steadily all the way into the professional ranks. Like with his running career, once Andrews started making inroads into the mountaineering world and claiming FKTs, he didn’t stop. Since the Salkantay speed record, Andrews posted several new FKTs each year, setting new standards on Mount Fuji, Kilimanjaro, and the towering, 26,781-foot monster Manaslu, among many others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Owen Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Feels So Good To Be A Robber]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193969</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/it-feels-so-good-to-be-a-robber"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T14:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little less than 320 feet away, the ball leaves Matt Waldon's right hand. All night, it has been ornery. It has misbehaved. The ball is Waldron's enemy. It's supposed to knuckle, and instead it rebels, skittering out of his hand like it's possessed by some force other than the pitcher's arm. The strike zone? The ball doesn't care for that. Tonight, it wants the backstop. It needs it. It will do any thing to get to it.
Matt Waldron is the only pitcher in Major League Baseball who even bothers trying to throw the bewitched knuckleball, and still it betrays him. By the time the bottom of the third inning arrives, the ball has run away again and again. It's scurrying past the catcher, walking a man, letting him take second base while it visited (who else?) the backstop again. And then just to prove its dominance, it walks a second man to prove the wild pitch never mattered anyway.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just Give Me Some Normal Damn Dinosaurs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193967</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/just-give-me-some-normal-damn-dinosaurs"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T14:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It should be impossible—water-from-a-stone impossible, faster-than-light-travel impossible—to make a bad movie about scary dinosaurs. And yet, according to reviews for Jurassic World Rebirth, out this week, they have done just that for the fourth time in a row.
Something is amiss here. These are dinosaurs: the biggest, meanest fuckers to ever walk the Earth—the demons and dragons of nightmare and legend, surely the source of some deep mammalian atavistic fear in the basest parts of our brainstem. If filmmakers can't squeeze two hours of excitement out of being chased by these horrors of tooth and nail, filmmakers need to look at themselves in the mirror and ask, How am I failing the dinos? The answer is that they are not respecting them properly, and trying to invent, new, bigger, smarter, scarier versions of dinosaurs. This is pathetic. Stick to saurians!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Panthers Are Bringing Back All Their Guys]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193957</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-panthers-are-bringing-back-all-their-guys"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T13:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The morning after the Panthers raised the Stanley Cup, some idiot wrote that it would be "nearly impossible" for Florida to re-sign its two top pending free agents, forward Sam Bennett and defenseman Aaron Ekblad. That idiot didn't even include mention of Brad Marchand in the same sentence, because only a giant mega mondo idiot would even consider the possibility that they could bring back all three. Well. About that. You see. The thing is. 
The thing is that the Panthers and GM Bill Zito have done basically everything right over the last three years, and been rewarded with back-to-back Cups, and a roster that adores each other and winning and Florida's lack of income tax, and a bunch of stars willing to take less than their open-market value to keep all that going. So, in a huge blow to the rest of the league's chances next year, and to the potential for drama as true free agency opens up today, the Panthers locked down all three guys to long-term extensions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Old gold / Kitten kitchen]]></title>
        <id>686280b5e9904f0001974b1d</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-351/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T22:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anna Merlan's golden hours, and Brian Hioe’s adventures as a feline baker]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pizza Cat]]></title>
        <id>686059c2e9904f0001974870</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/pizza-cat/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T22:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Hioe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mellow Yellow]]></title>
        <id>6862e97ce9904f0001974c40</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/mellow-yellow/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T22:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Merlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The WNBA And Its Expansion Fees Are Getting Bigger]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193886</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-wnba-and-its-expansion-fees-are-getting-bigger"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T20:22:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The WNBA announced on Monday that it will expand to 18 teams by 2030, adding franchises in Cleveland, Detroit and Philadelphia. By the end of this transformative round of expansion, the league will have added six teams in six years. The Golden State Valkyries joined the WNBA as its 13th team this season; teams in Toronto and Portland will begin play next summer. 
Before the 2024 draft, WNBA commissioner Cathy Engelbert said the league’s goal was to expand to 16 teams by 2028. Sports Business Journal’s Tom Friend reported this past February that Cleveland would be awarded the 16th team. But he also reported that the WNBA had reevaluated its initial 16-team target and was now eyeing 18. “How do you walk away from three quarters of a billion dollars?” a source told Friend. These three new teams all have NBA ownership groups, and each indeed reportedly paid an expansion fee of $250 million, a ginormous increase from the $50 million fee Valkyries owner Joe Lacob paid to join the WNBA in late 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CM Punk Loves Saudi Arabia]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193871</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cm-punk-loves-saudi-arabia"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T18:40:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CM Punk ruled as the coolest guy in North American professional wrestling in a few different eras. An indie firebrand in the first half of the 2000s, the straight-edge icon signed with WWE in 2005 and built himself into an avatar for fans frustrated by the company's de facto monopoly on big-time wrestling. He cemented this position during a feud with quintessential company man John Cena in 2011. Punk (the on-screen character) spoke out against WWE's corporate incompetence; then, in front of a rabid Chicagoland crowd, he beat Cena for his championship to climax probably the best match in company history (even if it's sullied by the presence of Vince McMahon and John Laurinaitis).
A few years later, Punk became a man who spoke out against WWE without getting paid by them to do it, leaving the company acrimoniously in 2014 because of the toll his work for them took on his body. He went over seven years without a match, in any promotion, and in that time his name became a thing that WWE audiences chanted when they didn't like what they were seeing. Capitalizing on that increasing discontent with the main provider of wrestling in the U.S., All Elite Wrestling launched in 2019, and after it emerged from the limited crowds of the social-distancing era, they signed Punk. He debuted to an unforgettable ovation in the Bulls' arena, furthering the company's upstart momentum, then proceeded to have basically one good year and one year marred by injury and workplace drama. Punk was fired after a backstage altercation at Wembley Stadium in 2023, and he returned to a WWE that was no longer run by his old nemesis McMahon. He's been a wrestler there without off-screen incident ever since.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Posts From The Glorious Future: The Breaking Of The Man With The Iron Heart]]></title>
        <id>6862ca99d663ab0001f84064</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/blog-posts-from-the-glorious-future-the-breaking-of-the-man-with-the-iron-heart/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T17:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most radical reforms of the Great Redo were reserved for America's immigration policy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Bull Stares Into The Abyss]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193862</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/red-bull-stares-into-the-abyss"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T16:46:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Without Max Verstappen, Red Bull Racing would be last in the 2025 Constructors' Championship. Assume that whoever takes Verstappen's seat would perform on par with Red Bull's second drivers so far, and Red Bull can upgrade that to a tidy second-to-last place. So long as the car is not a rocket and the team no longer has Adrian Newey, Red Bull needs Max Verstappen; unfortunately for Red Bull, it also becomes harder and harder for them to keep Max Verstappen.
The prospect of Verstappen, currently third in the Drivers' Championship behind the two McLarens, leaving Red Bull was inconceivable even last year, during the height of Christian Horner's misconduct allegations. Though there's no such thing as loyalty in Formula 1, the idea is as aesthetically unimaginable as, say, Lewis Hamilton in a Ferrari. But at some point the noise becomes too much to deny. Two months ago, George Russell, who does not have a contract extension for next year, stated that it would be "totally understandable" for Mercedes to pursue Verstappen; just prior to the weekend's Austrian Grand Prix, Mercedes team boss Toto Wolff confirmed that he was having conversations with Verstappen behind closed doors; and on Saturday, Verstappen's was out-qualified by Liam Lawson in a VCARB, Red Bull's sister team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They Let The Fish Get Hot!!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193892</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/they-let-the-fish-get-hot"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T15:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the reasons there are so many games in any league's season is, well, greed. In fact, that's all the reasons because how else can we turn Caitlin Clark into sorghum futures on the hoof? 
But one of the hidden benefits of this conglomoglut of games is that every team can go on a heater every year, if only to momentarily lie to their fans about the rosy future they neither deserve nor will achieve. The Colorado Cleveland Spiders Of The New Millennium have won four in a row this season, for the love of the galactic pixies, so like we said, anyone can do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, June 30: My Girls (Themeless)]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193863</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-june-30-my-girls-themeless"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time to to wrap up the month with a challenging themeless. Keep an eye out for tricky clues and fun wordplay. This week’s puzzle was constructed by Brandon Koppy and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Brandon lives in Dripping Springs, Texas, just outside Austin, with his wife and two little girls. You can also find his puzzles in The New York Times or on his blog, see17across.com.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE. Note that our submissions are closed through July 31.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Severino And The A’s Can’t Wait For Luis Severino To Leave]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193882</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/luis-severino-and-the-as-cant-wait-for-luis-severino-to-leave"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T14:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Severino signed a three-year, $67 million deal this past winter to serve at the whims of the West Sacramento Athletics Of Yolo County. He knew he was signing with the A's because that's what they told him he was doing, but he had not sufficiently considered the West Sacramento Of Yolo County part, and is now miserable because of it.
In a chat with The Athletic's Yankees beat writer Brendan Kuty, Severino, who left New York last year to sign the largest contract in A's history, emptied out his grievances when asked why his road splits (2-2, 3.23, etc.) are so much better than his home splits (0-7, 6.79, etc.), and his analysis boils down to this: West Sac sucks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Wood If They’d Let Him]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193855</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/james-wood-if-theyd-let-him"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T14:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We haven't had a good philosophical whinge about the intentional walk in a while, mostly because we all have lives to attend to, but in the aftermath of Sunday's Nationals-Angels game (and speaking of philosophical whinges, can any Nats-Halos game truly ever matter enough to have an aftermath?) we can re-engage this mostly frivolous time-suck over extra cold-and-frothies. What else is a summer heat wave for if not that?
James Wood is today's protagonist, the young and sprightly centerpiece of the Washington Baseball Consortium in this, another mostly abandoned zinc mine of a season. A Judge-level mass of coiled talent nearly a year to the day since his promotion from the minor leagues, he was known mostly as a key component in the trade that sent Juan Soto to San Diego but has now reached full fright stage, as proven by his Sunday afternoon's work—a single, a grounder to second, and four intentional walks, the first time a hitter has been so overtly feared since Barry Bonds ate the planet in 2004.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warren Schaeffer Hit A Crazy Stance]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193848</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/warren-schaeffer-hit-a-crazy-stance"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T13:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rockies interim manager Warren Schaeffer works out. This is something you can tell just by looking at him. The 40-year-old former minor leaguer carries himself in a way that is meant to broadcast that he still gets after it in the gym. You just know the squat rack absolutely hates to see this guy coming.
Looking like Gabe Kapler hasn't previously had much of a positive effect on any MLB manager's performance, not even Gabe Kapler's. But during Sunday's game against the Brewers, Schaeffer found a way to put all the strength and dexterity contained in his haunches to good use. After home plate umpire Ramon De Jesus hit Tyler Freeman with a quick-trigger ejection for arguing a third-strike call in the top of the third inning, Schaeffer came charging out of the dugout to stick up for his player.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Players-Only Meeting, Return Of Dicky Lovelady Not Enough To Turn Mets’ Fortunes Around]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193832</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/players-only-meeting-return-of-dicky-lovelady-not-enough-to-turn-mets-fortunes-around"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T13:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Mets are no strangers to the players-only meeting. Astute readers will remember the fellas coming together for one such meeting in May 2024, when the team was 11 games under .500 and the season seemed to be slipping away. Those Mets ended up winning 89 games and making the playoffs, so clearly a lot of important issues were ironed out during that meeting. Perhaps it was the memory of that meeting's effectiveness that brought the players together for another confab before Sunday's series finale against the Pirates.
"At least they have the Pirates coming up," typed one unnamed Defector staffer into our workplace communication platform on June 23. The next day, the Mets lost to the Braves, despite the best efforts of Dicky Lovelady, to continue a slump had seen them lose 10 of 11 games. Two consecutive wins against the Braves followed, which set up the Mets to cruise into a potentially healing three-game series against the crap-filled Pirates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The All-Ireland Football Quarterfinals Were A Real Hoot]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193834</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-all-ireland-football-quarterfinals-were-a-real-hoot"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T21:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a weekend of quarterfinal crackers at Croke Park and a Sunday evening draw at GAA headquarters in Dublin, the Final Four of the 2025 All-Ireland football championships is set. Meath will face Donegal, and Kerry will take on Tyrone. 
More than 132,000 folks flocked to the mythically fab Croker for the four games over two days to see who would stay alive in the run for the Sam Maguire Cup, and who would be sent home Sam-less. In a topsy-turvy quarterfinal played at Croke Saturday afternoon, Donegal was down seven points to Monaghan at the half. But graybeard forward Michael Murphy, who was retired and working as a sports pundit for Irish TV for the last two years before un-retiring, and the rest of the surging Forgotten County squad blitzed their Ulster province rivals coming out of the break on the way to six-point win, 1-26 to 1-20.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malik Beasley’s Gambling Scandal Arrives At Worst Possible Time For Malik Beasley]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193822</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/malik-beasleys-gambling-scandal-arrives-at-worst-possible-time-for-malik-beasley"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T17:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malik Beasley had a career year with the Detroit Pistons this past season, during which he became one of the best high-volume three-point shooters in the league. That fabulous campaign, in which he made 319 threes and scored 16 points per game, came at a great time for Beasley's finances, as he is set to enter free agency tomorrow. Unfortunately, his career might now be over.
That grim possibility is brought to us by ESPN's Shams Charania, who reports that Beasley is currently the subject of a federal investigation into allegations of gambling on NBA games and prop bets. According to Charania, the investigation is focused on bets that were made during the 2023–24 NBA season, when Beasley was a member of the Milwaukee Bucks. According to ESPN's David Purdum, at least one U.S. sports book detected unusual betting interest on Beasley's statistics in January 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody’s Better At Selling Shitty Fights Than Jake Paul]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193816</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nobodys-better-at-selling-shitty-fights-than-jake-paul"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T16:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In what will someday rightly be known as boxing’s Jake Paul Era, it’s not how you fight that matters, it’s who you fight. 
Paul, a Disney kid turned punchfluencer, was at it again last night, beating another opponent whose name recognition outweighed his current level of abilities. The latest tomato can of the month was Julio Cesar Chavez Jr., a guy who despite holding the world middleweight title back in 2012 has always only gotten noticed for what comes before “Jr.”; his father, Julio Sr., who had a career 107-6-2 ring record and held belts in three weight classes, is perhaps the most popular Mexican athlete of all time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Harbaugh Sued In Expanded Hacking Case]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193805</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jim-harbaugh-sued-in-expanded-hacking-case"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T15:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Current Chargers and former Michigan head coach Jim Harbaugh was added as a defendant on Friday in a class-action lawsuit against former Wolverines assistant coach Matt Weiss. The suit, filed by 11 anonymous women, is just one of more than a dozen civil cases that have been brought against Weiss and the University of Michigan since Weiss was indicted in March on 14 counts of unauthorized access to computers and 10 counts of aggravated identity theft.
According to the federal case against Weiss, he gained access to student-athlete databases at more than 100 universities that were maintained by a third-party vendor. From about 2015 to 2023, Weiss allegedly used that access to download athletes' personal identifying information, which he then used to hack into email, social media, and cloud storage accounts belonging to more than 2,000 athletes. After accessing these accounts, Weiss is alleged to have downloaded personal and intimate videos and photos belonging to his victims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Notes: Marsh, Wright, Harvey]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=857269</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/06/royals-notes-marsh-wright-harvey.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T02:26:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Royals fans received some tough news today regarding their rotation depth. As noted by Anne Rogers of MLB.com, right-hander Alec Marsh has been shut down from throwing after the shoulder injury he’s been nursing all season did not respond well to his throwing progression. Meanwhile, Kyle Wright was scratched from his start for Triple-A Omaha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Super market]]></title>
        <id>685ee54ee9904f00019732c0</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-350/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T22:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amy Chu on shopping at Daily Table]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Table: the Nonprofit Grocery Story]]></title>
        <id>685ef6e3e9904f00019732fd</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/daily-table-the-nonprofit-grocery-story/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T22:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I finished undergrad in 2021, I quickly discovered that “rent eats first,” as housing costs gobbled up half of my $4,500 income from a summer internship at the Museum of Fine Arts. Later I found a full-time job working for the Massachusetts state government, where I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Chu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capri Sun The Long Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/capri-sun-the-long-way-6ca4</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/capri-sun-the-long-way-6ca4"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T20:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Long 1860s demand an equally long juice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirsten Gillibrand Has A Racist Meltdown Over Zohran Mamdani On Public Radio]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193737</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/kirsten-gillibrand-has-a-racist-meltdown-over-zohran-mamdani-on-public-radio"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T19:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zohran Mamdani's victory in the New York City mayoral primary has led to a lot of vile reactions from across the political spectrum. That'd be expected from any Republican, but plenty of liberals are willing to go against their own party and attack a Muslim who supports Palestinians. So it was surprising, but not that surprising, to hear a high-ranking Democrat like New York Senator Kirsten Gillibrand lose her mind over Mamdani on Thursday's edition of The Brian Lehrer Show.
WNYC host Brian Lehrer began the interview by asking Gillibrand if she would endorse Mamdani in November's general election. "Not today, but I did speak with him yesterday," the senator said. "I congratulated him on his victory, and I raised some issues that, if he does become the mayor, will be very important that we not only work on together, but I raised some concerns that I had."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Built Different or Skill Issue? A BaseRuns Game Show: Offense Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=466829</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/built-different-or-skill-issue-a-baseruns-game-show-offense-edition/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T16:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Which teams follow the BaseRuns rule and which ones are the exception?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiri Oler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call Her On Her Bullshit]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193730</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/call-her-on-her-bullshit"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T15:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I started the recently released Hulu two-part documentary, Call Her Alex, about the outlandishly successful host of the podcast Call Her Daddy, I knew only a handful of facts about Alex Cooper: She's very popular with young women, she’s beautiful in a way I strongly associate with posting Instagram stories from a yacht, and she talks about sex a lot. At the same time, I knew hundreds of facts about the world as it has existed for the past few decades. What this documentary hopes for is that I would be willing to set those aside.
"Part One" opens in 2023, as Cooper is preparing to embark on her first live tour. She’s excited but nervous about delivering a great show for her legions of devoted fans. It’s immediately clear that her success is the result not just of personal charisma, which she undoubtedly has, but a shrewd sense of what her audience wants, and the drive to make it happen. While she’s surrounded by a team, including husband and business partner Matt Kaplan, Cooper is very much in charge of the empire she’s created over the last six years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Jensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Leaks Became The Last Vestige Of Communal Music Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193516</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-leaks-became-the-last-vestige-of-communal-music-discovery"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T15:18:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Listening Habits, a column where I share the music I’ve been fixated on recently.
It's hard for music to feel as exciting and urgent today as it used to, back when it was central to pop culture. Today, music feels like that thing you hear playing at your favorite coffee shop or you listen to while at the gym when you can't find a podcast that blathers on for two hours. It's background noise for another activity rather than the activity itself. Unless you're a nerd about it, people don't seem to engage with it with much depth anymore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End Of EBUGs Means The End Of Dreams Coming True]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193699</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-end-of-ebugs-means-the-end-of-dreams-coming-true"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T14:41:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NHL and the Players' Association are reportedly close to announcing agreement on a new collective bargaining agreement, ensuring extended labor peace in a league that hasn't had much of that in the last couple decades. Some smallish things are set to change: the season expanding to 84 games; contracts being limited to seven years; the closing of the long-term IR loophole that allows teams to exceed the salary cap in the playoffs. One change, however, is the smallest of them all, yet also the ending of an era. If negotiations go as expected, we have already seen the last true emergency backup goaltender.
NHL teams can carry only two active goaltenders, but there has to be a contingency plan in place if both get hurt, to prevent games from turning into farces. The new CBA will allow teams to carry a permanent EBUG, who will practice and travel with the team, but not count against their roster. Previously, teams just sort of figured it out when needed—they'd designate as their EBUG for a given game a staffer who had played goal in college, or an adult league netminder in whatever city they were playing in, that sort of thing. It was thrillingly close to picking up a guy off the street and shoving him into an actual NHL game; a novelty and a dream come true for some hockey lifer who had never made the big show. If it was a stopgap solution, it was a fun one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My New Glasses Have Ruined My Ability To Read! Help Me!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193607</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/my-new-glasses-have-ruined-my-ability-to-read-help-me"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Ask The Book Doctor, a recurring series about books and reading them.
I like to put on my gym clothes nine hours before I actually go. I wake up, dress for the gym, and then sit at my desk blogging all day, because I know that if I do this, the likelihood of me actually going to the gym increases by 500 percent. If I put on another outfit, there is no way I will go to the gym, because this would require me to change into my gym clothes, and my brain hates me. My evil brain will accept any excuse to keep me from doing things that are good for me. So in an attempt to usurp my own brain, I outplay it. I lower the barriers to entry and make it as easy for me to go to the gym as possible. This is how I win.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine, To Hell With It: A T.J. McConnell Appreciation Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193280</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/fine-to-hell-with-it-a-t-j-mcconnell-appreciation-blog"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T13:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indiana Pacers backup guard T.J. McConnell exemplifies a type of basketball player I generally regard with disgust: the Skittering Little Rat Guy. This is the frenzied little gremlin always very visibly going 40 percent harder than anybody else at every single moment, constantly poking for steals, throwing himself theatrically to the floor (on his back to draw charges against better players, on his front after every halfway-loose ball he can turn into a monument to his own commitment), fouling a degree too hard, sprinting and yelling and gesticulating. Slapping the floor, even. Skittering Little Rat Guys are far more common in college basketball than in the NBA—some mid-major colleges start entire lineups of fifth-year Skittering Little Rat Guys—but they are found at all levels of the sport.
I regard the Skittering Little Rat Guy as basketball's most objectionable player type, both ethically and in simple visceral terms. For one thing, the Skittering Little Rat Guy's whole deal, his very presence on the court, is antithetical to the best, most breathtaking basketball stuff—and to the very idea of basketball as a stylish, expressive, creative game. He gunks up the works. He is an intruder into the cool sport from Mike Krzyzewski's vision of what it should be; not coincidentally, some of the most hateful Skittering Little Rat Guys in living memory—Bobby Hurley, Steve Wojciechowski, Grayson Allen—made themselves famous at Coach K's Duke program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Last Of Us Part II’ Insists There’s Artistry In All Of Its Violence]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193236</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-last-of-us-part-ii-insists-theres-artistry-in-all-of-its-violence"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T13:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to The Backlog, a series in which we will take a look back at 12 games from 2020 that, in one way or another, had a lasting impact on the video game industry. 
One of the more exhausting arguments you can have about video games grapples with the idea of value. Specifically, can video games be valuable as an art form? Truly, this doesn't matter at all. Enjoy what you enjoy and if you get value from it, then hell yeah, that rocks. And if someone tells you that video games are stupid or worthless or whatever else, then don't let that take away from your enjoyment and connection to a specific game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All-seeing eye]]></title>
        <id>685dddaee9904f0001971ce2</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-349/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T02:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A New York Times film reviewed by Maria Bustillos; vote for the Hydranym]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOVIE REVIEW: Peter Thiel and the Antichrist]]></title>
        <id>685dd7c7e9904f0001971cb8</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/movie-review-peter-thiel-and-the-antichrist/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T01:50:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Bustillos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HYDRANYM No. 5: Vote!]]></title>
        <id>685df148e9904f0001971dc6</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hydranym-no-5-vote/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T01:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friends, it is your solemn task to vote for Hydranym No. 5.
HYDRANYM is a word game for Flaming Hydra subscribers. Please join in by subscribing! It’s fun, and you will also receive our glorious email newsletter each weekday AND support press freedom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals’ Picollo On Trade Deadline Approach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=856973</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/06/royals-rumors-trade-deadline-controllable-bat-hitter.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T23:38:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals dropped their fifth straight game last night, falling 4-0 to the Rays. They’re now 38-43, dropping into fourth place in the AL Central behind a Twins club that has also struggled mightily over the past couple weeks. After playing winning baseball in both April and May, the Royals are 7-15 in June, due…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Agony Of Victory, With Ray Ratto]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193588</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-agony-of-victory-with-ray-ratto"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T19:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a general rule, if we are talking about politics on the podcast it is not going to be about good news. That just isn't the way that people talk about politics, but more to the point our politics just have not generated a lot of good news of late. This hasn't kept us from talking about it, for better and worse, but it has generally kept episodes with even trace amounts of political content in a specific emotional lane. That lane, which is basically Heated Dissatisfaction, would seem to be a good fit for a Ray Ratto guest spot, but while this week's episode does feature our beloved Grumpsville Bureau Chief, it also begins with nearly a half hour of shockingly sunny politics talk. Listening back over it, I found it more reassuring than anything else—a reminder that, if circumstances provide, I can actually talk about this stuff without sounding like someone shouting from atop a milk crate outside a public park.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Am Sick And Tired Of These Normie Gamer Athletes]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193615</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-am-sick-and-tired-of-these-normie-gamer-athletes"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T17:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, ESPN's Jeff Passan published a blog about Jacob Wilson, the West Sacramento A's rookie shortstop currently having a very impressive offensive season of the Luis Arráez variety. He is rocking the second-lowest strikeout rate in the league (behind Arráez) and the second-highest squared-up contact rate in the league (behind Arráez), and, perhaps expected of a man born in the Year of our Lord 2002, Wilson attributes his success to Fortnite.
"Kids are going to love this one. Parents are going to hate me," Wilson said. "I am a big believer in video games. It's fast decision-making strategy. I think that gets me ready for the game, because when you're in the box, you have to process a lot."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After All That, Ace Bailey Ends Up In Utah]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193617</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/after-all-that-ace-bailey-ends-up-in-utah"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T17:15:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The run-up to every NBA Draft has a pleasant, familiar rhythm. Some prospects distinguish themselves in workouts, while some leap up or crash down draft boards after their wingspans and standing reaches are measured. People deploy some of the most fluorescent comparative language you will ever see. Every year, one or two mysterious prospects—Shaedon Sharpe a few years ago, Cedric Coward this year—will vault from the fringes into the lottery despite precious little tape. Mock drafts are never correct in their particulars, though the rough mosaic they form serves well enough as a guide and a baseline to measure all the surprises against. If you listen to what scouts and insiders say, there is always a pivot point early in the draft, a team with obscure intentions or a notably polarizing prospect who terrifies both the teams that pass on him and the team that ends up taking him in equal measure. This year, the hinge of the draft was the fifth pick, which the Utah Jazz used to select Ace Bailey out of Rutgers.
Bailey came into his lone season of college basketball with sky-high expectations. He was the second-ranked recruit in his class behind only Cooper Flagg, and it was pretty obvious why: He's a spindly, athletic 6-foot-8, possessed of rare shooting and shot-creation abilities for someone that big and athletic. No player in college could stop him from getting to his spots and pulling up. Bailey made his defenders look like so many flailing nephews as he confidently dribbled through traffic, bumped his way into an inch of space, and pulled up with one of the sweetest gathers you'll ever see in an 18-year-old player. He was also a pretty nasty rebounder, which tends to be one of the more translatable NBA skills, and he also showed some real flashes as a defensive playmaker. If you squinted, you could see the outline of a multi-time all-star.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mighty Brewers Lad Out-Duels Paul Skenes]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193595</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mighty-brewers-lad-out-duels-paul-skenes"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T16:43:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want Jacob Misiorowski's internet. This fresh-faced child gets wholesome baseball. "I feel like everything I swiped was me and Skenes, me and Skenes, me and Skenes," said Milwaukee's fire-breather of a rookie pitcher, of the days before his start Wednesday, the third of his career. "I had to mute it, turn it off." You dear sweet lad, whatever algorithm you're plugged into beats the hell out of mine: Everything I swiped was, well, the entire rest of reality, which sucks turbo ass. Imagine muting the only remotely bitchin' thing left in the universe: A mid-week duel of 23-year-old phenoms, featuring baseball's scariest pitcher versus some damn kid from out of nowhere who is somehow even scarier. Before last week I think I had never even heard of Jacob Misiorowski. Whitney Tilson? Israel Katz? Thomas Fugate? If I cannot plug into Misiorowski's web, the very next best thing would be someone splitting my head right down the middle with a wood ax.
For a dog-days rubber match in the dreaded NL Central, this Pirates-Brewers tilt was a pretty big deal. For one thing, all Paul Skenes starts are events, even if the sad-sack Pirates have gotten next to nothing this season from his brilliance. Skenes entered Wednesday's start one of just four qualified pitchers in baseball with an earned-run average below 2.00; he was also in the top five in innings pitched, WHIP, and fielding-independent pitching, and was best in baseball in pitching wins above replacement, per Baseball Reference. The other two starting pitchers in the majors who began Wednesday allowing fewer than two earned runs per nine innings have a combined record of 18–5. Skenes, meanwhile, was 4–7, and the Pirates had played to a morally unacceptable 8–8 record in his starts. It's an embarrassment, is what it is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NBA Draft Provides Blessed Phrases Like “Chinese Jokic”]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193605</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-nba-draft-provides-blessed-phrases-like-chinese-jokic"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T16:17:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first round of the NBA draft on Thursday was pretty boring, with a few exceptions. Ace Bailey's strange, oafish attempts to get himself on an East Coast team of his choosing ended with him going to the Utah Jazz at No. 5. The New Orleans Pelicans made what appears to be a very dumb trade in order to take Derik Queen at No. 13. The Brooklyn Nets drafted one million guards. But nothing was as exciting as the arrival of Yang Hansen.
Yang, projected to be taken in the late first or second round, ended up going to the Portland Trail Blazers at No. 16. The 20-year-old, 7-foot-2 center has spent the last few seasons playing pro ball in the Chinese league. He's the kind of player who generally profiles as a long-developing project, which makes the Blazers' decision to take him in the middle of the first round something of a historic reach. So what gives? How did Yang jump so many spots?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chloe Dzubilo And The Perilous Path Forward For Trans Life]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193327</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/chloe-dzubilo-and-the-perilous-path-forward-for-trans-life"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T15:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“In 20 yrs, this will all be commonplace.”
These words were first penned in 2008 by Chloe Dzubilo. A trans femme, recovered heroin addict, and long-term HIV survivor who had stayed alive more than three decades after she was first diagnosed with a virus that killed her partner in the late ‘80s, Chloe knew what it meant to play the long game, to endure trials that nobody should have to face. By 2008, she’d lived many lives: champion show-horse jumper, drug addict, lead singer of a band called the Transsisters, and advocate for younger trans women and sex workers. Looking two decades into the future—still three incomprehensible years from where we stand today—she envisioned a world where trans life was obvious and indisputable. Still, she knew that the future required a fight. In a life marked by long-term disability and routine dehumanization by medical professionals, Chloe held her head high, the act of daily survival elevated to an artful refusal to accept the world’s hostile terms. The challenges she wove into her life and left behind in her art are ones we still face today, making her a critical teacher for troubled times.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Annie Howard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This U.S. Senate Candidate Wants To Fix The Rogue Supreme Court]]></title>
        <id>685d45eed663ab0001f832e2</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/this-u-s-senate-candidate-wants-to-fix-the-rogue-supreme-court/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T14:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Democrats who promise policy initiatives but don’t discuss court reform are living in a land of make believe."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Politics Of Fear Don’t Work Against A Candidate Who Isn’t Scared]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193508</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-politics-of-fear-dont-work-against-a-candidate-who-isnt-scared"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T13:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there is one takeaway from Zohran Mamdani's victory in the New York City Democratic mayoral primary on Tuesday, it's that there is no one takeaway. The democratic socialist and his wide-ranging canvassing team built a coalition that brought in voters of all backgrounds, leading to a defeat of Andrew Cuomo by a significant margin. There wasn't one sole factor that handed Mamdani the win, and everyone will have their own opinions on which campaign promise or tactic mattered the most. That said, it feels safe to say that one familiar opposition strategy resoundingly did not work.
Mamdani's primary agenda on his platform is to make New York City more affordable for its residents, through specific initiatives: freezing rent, free buses, no-cost childcare. While many of his opponents took time to pick at these progressive policies, they also relentlessly attacked his Muslim faith and support for Palestinians. In a race for mayor of New York City, they tried to make fealty to the state of Israel a strict qualification.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fugitive food]]></title>
        <id>685c4f4ce9904f00019707c5</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-348/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T23:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laurie Woolever talks with Michael Shaikh, author of 'The Last Sweet Bite']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cooking to Survive]]></title>
        <id>685c08e4e9904f0001970679</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/cooking-to-survive/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T23:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A conversation with Michael Shaikh]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurie Woolever</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dodgers Are Disappointing The People Who Want To Love Them The Most]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193208</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-dodgers-are-disappointing-the-people-who-want-to-love-them-the-most"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T20:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES — Few have been spared in the raids. They’ve taken people who came to Southern California from Mexico, El Salvador, Guatemala, Cambodia, Laos, and Vietnam. They’ve taken people from garment shops, street carts, farms, packinghouses, taquerias, big-box stores, home-improvement stores, and car washes. They've taken a union president (since released) and multiple U.S. citizens. They’ve taken people from what feels like every zip code, from the far-flung Coachella Valley to the manicured lawns of Pasadena, which shut down multiple city programs on Saturday after people got taken from a local park, to the grimy streets of Hollywood, where masked agents targeted a Home Depot in the heart of the city—just off a freeway, two blocks from local TV news station KTLA, and pretty widely known as one of the easiest spots in town to find a day laborer.
The fear of more raids has bled into everyday life, and led countless people to stay home. Even if you aren't afraid, you have friends or family or coworkers who are and it's impossible to avoid the constant warnings about the latest ICE raids springing up across social media. There is the sense of communities trying to stand up an immune system under duress, the better to warn vulnerable people in time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Love My Daily Sports Shows: Baseball And ‘Love Island’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193528</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-love-my-daily-sports-shows-baseball-and-love-island"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T19:27:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the winter, my television mostly stays off. The winter is when my brain is at its best. I am reading. I am writing. I am maybe watching a couple episodes of a show a week. But this feels crazy to type right now, at this moment in the summer, because I currently have a minimum of four hours of television I must watch every single day. I do not have time to read or have hobbies or do anything else, because I am too busy being locked the hell in. 
Television has been my best friend for several weeks because of two shows that come on every day. The first show is baseball. I am a Phillies fan, and baseball teams play 162 games over the course of six months every year. I watch most of them. But then I am also committed to another kind of sport, called Love Island.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Halc DJ’s Brazilian Funk Album Fights A Righteous War Against The Algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193393</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/halc-djs-brazilian-funk-album-fights-a-righteous-war-against-the-algorithms"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T17:22:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many great Brazilian funk albums, pressing play on Halc DJ's Bruxaria Não É Phonk is a little like fitting a jackhammer bit into your ear canal and waiting for the impending sonic onslaught to render you utterly, blissfully destroyed. Surprisingly, Halc makes you wait a bit for it. The album begins with "Phonk É o Caralho," a tour de force of funkery that, with no less than eight beat switch-ups across just three minutes, takes you on a breakneck journey through the breadth of the DJ/producer's talents and of the genre's possibilities. But you have to get a little more than 30 seconds into the opener, when its second beat-switch fades, an appropriately ominous voice belches the word "bruxaria," and a shrill whistle—these kinds of tinnital chirps are known as "tuim/tuin," the prevalence of tuim being one of the hallmarks of the bruxaria subgenre—rings steadily and then begins to strobe overtop a ratty, red-lining bass pulse. It's only then that Halc really drags you into the depths of the underworld where this type of joyously brain-scrambling funk lives and thrives.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jQSwEBAryu8]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Even Dicky Lovelady Could Rescue The Mets]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193480</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/not-even-dicky-lovelady-could-rescue-the-mets"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T15:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the hottest week of the year in New York City, but the Mets have been ice cold. Leaders of the NL East by five-and-a-half games less than two weeks ago, the boys from Queens now trail the Phillies by 1.5 because of a putrid ongoing stretch where they've lost 10 of 11. That slide includes Tuesday night's fall-from-ahead defeat at home, where even the much-anticipated team debut of 29-year-old reliever Richard "Dicky" Lovelady didn't provide the fans any pleasure.
Part of the sting of the Mets' slump has come from the fact that they're losing to three of the most frustrating and annoying franchises on the schedule. They got swept by the Rays in three by a combined score of 24-9. They managed one win in Philly to break up 10-2 and 7-1 drubbings. And if you didn't know already, I bet you can guess the remaining tormentor: the Atlanta Braves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simply Don’t Be A Shithead]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193479</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/simply-dont-be-a-shithead"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T15:14:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ketel Marte was 23 years old when his mother died in July 2017. He'd recently been summoned to the Arizona Diamondbacks from Triple-A Reno, where he'd been clobbering to smithereens the best pitching of the minor leagues. Marte had already played an accumulated season-plus of major-league games as a member of the Seattle Mariners, but following a trade to Arizona he was initially blocked at his positions of choice by veterans, and so the Diamondbacks made the unusual decision to ship a productive top prospect back to the minors for half a season. Marte's call-up came at the end of June; on July 29, in his 24th game with the big club, Marte took a mighty rip at a 2–0 pitch from Cardinals reliever Kevin Siegrist and crushed a laser of a dong over the wall in left, his fourth homer as a Diamondback. The moment carried some personal significance, as it was Marte's 10th home run at two combined levels that season, a benchmark he'd circled with a little inspiration from mom.
"When I was playing softball in the Dominican with my friend, she saw me hit a long homer," Marte told the Arizona Republic, back in 2017. "One day, before I came to spring training, she said, 'I want 10 homers this year.' Now, I’ve got 10 homers. When I hit my last homer, I called her. She had watched the game. I said, 'Now you’ve got 10 homers, how about that?' She was crying." Marte spoke again to his mother the following day, Sunday, after the rubber match in St. Louis and before boarding a plane for a short team flight to Chicago. While Marte and the Diamondbacks were in the air, a vehicle struck Marte's mother, Elpidia Valdez, as she drove a moped in the Dominican Republic. Marte learned of the accident when the team flight landed, but was given the impression that it was minor and that Elpidia would recover. That evening, at a team dinner, he received a phone call and was told that she'd died.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLBTR Podcast: The Braves Say They Won’t Sell, Jeimer Candelario DFA’d, And Injured D-Backs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=856904</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/06/mlbtr-podcast-the-braves-say-they-wont-sell-jeimer-candelario-dfad-and-injured-d-backs.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T14:48:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest episode of the MLB Trade Rumors Podcast is now live on Spotify, Apple Podcasts, and wherever you get your podcasts! Make sure you subscribe as well! You can also use the player at this link to listen, if you don’t use Spotify or Apple for podcasts. This week, host Darragh McDonald is joined by Anthony Franco of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What The Guru Left Behind]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191659</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-the-guru-left-behind"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T13:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A yoga empire struggles to reckon with its past after its guru is named as an abuser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Needelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>