<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-11-10T08:17:43.328Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AL Central Notes: Royals Pitching, Rodriguez, Manning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=830315</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/al-central-notes-royals-pitching-rodriguez-manning.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T23:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Michael Wacha retained on a three-year deal worth at least $51MM, “we don’t expect to be in the market for a starter moving forward.  We’re going to focus on some other things,” Royals general manager J.J. Picollo told MLB.com’s Maria Guardado and other reporters during the GM Meetings.  Picollo cited the projected top five…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tennessee Smokies return home, rebrand as Knoxville Smokies]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83265</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/09/tennessee-smokies-return-home-rebrand-as-knoxville-smokies/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T17:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A quarter century after leaving Knoxville, Tennessee, the Double-A affiliate of the Chicago Cubs is returning home and reprising their former name, the Knoxville Smokies. The Smokies, who play in the Southern League, announced this week that with their return to their once and future hometown, the team will change]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Caputo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here are Kansas City's best restaurants for Southern comfort cooking and soul food]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2024-11-09/kansas-city-southern-food-restaurants-soul-cooking</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2024-11-09/kansas-city-southern-food-restaurants-soul-cooking"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smack in the middle of the country, Kansas City is a melting pot of different cultures and cuisines — especially soul food. At this restaurants, there's plenty to enjoy with the big flavor, and portions, of Southern comfort cooking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shannon Carpenter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carolina Panthers To Wear New Uniform Combination During Sunday’s Game In Germany]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83297</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/09/carolina-panthers-to-wear-new-uniform-combination-during-sundays-game-in-germany/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T06:10:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Carolina Panthers will debut a new uniform combination during Sunday’s game against the New York York Giants at Allianz Stadium in Munich, Germany.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Houston Rockets Unveil Championship Banner-Inspired City Edition Uniforms]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83291</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/09/houston-rockets-unveil-championship-banner-inspired-city-edition-uniforms/basketball/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T05:23:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Houston Rockets will celebrate the 30th anniversary of their back-to-back NBA titles in 1993-94 and 1994-95 with their new City Edition uniforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wait, Is The Fifth Circuit The Reasonable One Here? — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077190</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/wait-is-the-5th-circuit-the-reasonable-one-here-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T00:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Makes The Fifth Circuit Look Normal: Meaningful standing doctrine still exists, kinda.
Don't Mess With Ginsburg: Man gets two years for illegally accessing late justice's medical records.
Talk To My Admin, Buddy: You don't need to outsource talking with your friends.
The Final Fours!: Cast your vote on the scariest words for a lawyer to hear!
It Isn't Getting Any Better For Giuliani: Some things will never change.
The post Wait, Is The Fifth Circuit The Reasonable One Here? — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David St. Hubbins blesses 2024 Thundergong! benefit for Steps of Faith foundation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=860445</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/david-st-hubbins-blesses-2024-thundergong-benefit-for-steps-of-faith-foundation/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T00:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thundergong! presser with Jason and Billy. // Photo by Brock Wilbur For the 8th year in a row, the THUNGDERGONG! evening of celebrity-heavy comedy and music will spotlight KC tomorrow night at the Uptown Theatre. The Steps of Faith Foundation, whose mission is to raise money to supply limbs to amputees, probably shouldn’t need to exist. In a better America,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Litigation Reach Of These Biglaw Firms Is Remarkable]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077181</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-litigation-reach-of-these-biglaw-firms-is-remarkable/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T00:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They're litigating all around the nation.
The post The Litigation Reach Of These Biglaw Firms Is Remarkable appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Media Can’t Figure Out Why Some Racist Israeli Soccer Hooligans Were Beaten Up]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172778</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-media-cant-figure-out-why-some-racist-israeli-soccer-hooligans-were-beaten-up"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T23:35:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stripped of context, visiting soccer fans getting drunk and causing havoc ahead of a big continental match in Europe would be so routine as to be almost unworthy of mention. But the hooligans in this instance were supporters of the Israeli soccer club Maccabi Tel Aviv, and the residents of Amsterdam weren't keen to their disruptive behavior, which meant that outlets like the New York Times and politicians like Joe Biden trained their focus on what happened and characterized it with their warped clarity.
After a few hours and several substantial edits, the Times' article about Thursday's events has something approaching a comprehensive picture of what went down—though to get it, you still have to patch together a timeline from the facts scattered throughout the article. It all started on Wednesday, the day before the match, when a sizable number of Maccabi fans arrived into Amsterdam to watch their team take on Ajax in the Europa League. Coinciding with the Maccabi fans' arrival, pro-Palestinian activists assembled in Dam Square in protest of Israel's ethnic cleansing of Palestinians in Gaza.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local Man Allegedly Co-Conspires With Unwitting IRS In Hedge Fund Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077158</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/11/local-man-allegedly-co-conspires-with-unwitting-irs-in-hedge-fund-scam"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T23:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fake tax bills along with the fake account statements? Bravo, Justin Murphy.
The post Local Man Allegedly Co-Conspires With Unwitting IRS In Hedge Fund Scam appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Cost Center To Command Center: How Legal Ops Leads With Resilience]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077177</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/from-cost-center-to-command-center-how-legal-ops-leads-with-resilience/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T23:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legal Ops professionals are ensuring that resilience is an embedded part of daily operations.
The post From Cost Center To Command Center: How Legal Ops Leads With Resilience appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>STEPHANIE COREY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why The Royals Should Be Primed For Another Big Offseason]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=830220</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/why-the-royals-should-be-primed-for-another-big-offseason.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T22:35:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals were the surprise spender of the 2023-24 offseason, putting down a combined $110.5MM on eight free agents: Seth Lugo, Michael Wacha, Hunter Renfroe, Chris Stratton, Will Smith, Adam Frazier, Garrett Hampson and Austin Nola. Several of the moves didn't pan out, but the ones that did paid of in spades. Lugo and Wacha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stat(s) Of The Week: Is Moving Out The Only Way To Move Up?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077187</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/stats-of-the-week-corporate-counsel-retention/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T22:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legal departments face retention challenges as in-house counsel eye the door.
The post Stat(s) Of The Week: Is Moving Out The Only Way To Move Up? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vera Djordjevich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conquering Conferences: Avoiding The Faux Pas Of Networking]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077077</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/conquering-conferences-avoiding-the-faux-pas-of-networking/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T21:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's explore these with a sense of humor and learn how to steer clear of them. 
The post Conquering Conferences: Avoiding The Faux Pas Of Networking appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEJAL PATEL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fifth Circuit May Become Even More Conservative During Trump’s Second Term]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077160</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-fifth-circuit-may-become-even-more-conservative-during-trumps-second-term/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T21:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This may mean that the Fifth Circuit's jurisprudence will be overturned even more by the Supreme Court in the future.
The post The Fifth Circuit May Become Even More Conservative During Trump’s Second Term appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reimagined museum restaurant, Oil on Linen, paints a new experience with bold flavor and color]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=860456</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/reimagined-museum-restaurant-oil-on-linen-blends-visual-and-edible-art/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T20:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oil on Linen // Photo by Anna Petrow Mulvihill Café Sebastienne at Kemper Museum of Contemporary Art has closed. After a time of reworking the menu and decor–both are equal elements of the experience–the dining space has reopened as Oil on Linen.  Named as a reference cleverly blending an art medium with imagery of a well-set dining table, Oil on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rudy Giuliani Waves Red Flag In Front Of Federal Judge In Freeman/Moss Case]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077182</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/rudy-giuliani-waves-red-flag-in-front-of-federal-judge-in-freeman-moss-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T20:15:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mayor Nine Lives is pushing it hard.
The post Rudy Giuliani Waves Red Flag In Front Of Federal Judge In Freeman/Moss Case appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Lawyers Can Master Content Creation: 4 Proven Steps To Boost Your Legal Practice]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077138</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/how-lawyers-can-master-content-creation-4-proven-steps-to-boost-your-legal-practice/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T19:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you aren't playing the game, you're sitting on the sidelines watching.
The post How Lawyers Can Master Content Creation: 4 Proven Steps To Boost Your Legal Practice appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Fretzin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Shower Beef Between Elephant Mary And Elephant Anchali, Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172621</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-shower-beef-between-elephant-mary-and-elephant-anchali-explained"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T18:52:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a beautiful Friday in autumn and I am here to share some drama with all of you: the story of two big, beautiful female elephants whose long-simmering resentments boiled over into an all-out brawl over one of the most coveted gadgets (by pachyderm standards). Our story takes place at the Berlin Zoo, and names have not been anonymized to bring you the cold, hard truth of what can happen when two divas have a trunk-off.
Without any further ado, let me introduce you to the Asian elephants at the heart of this story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 4 Scariest Words For Lawyers: The Finalists]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077161</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-4-scariest-words-for-lawyers-the-finalists/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T18:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Which four words do you think will scare a lawyer the most?
The post The 4 Scariest Words For Lawyers: The Finalists appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“You’ve Got Mail” Reminds Me Of A Specific Time And Place]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172717</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/youve-got-mail-reminds-me-of-a-specific-time-and-place"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T18:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Going online used to be an event. My early online experience was probably similar to many of our old millennial readers like me: I went into the house’s Computer Room, booted up the PC, waited the agonizingly long time it took for it to load, then opened up a program that allowed me to connect, via a phone line, to The Internet. It was a process; there was a distinctive grating sound involved. It was much different than carrying around the whirr of the world in my pocket at all times. It is not a particularly memorable experience when I unlock my phone or open up my laptop. Going online as a kid was something I had to plan for; I even had limited hours of access! I think it was 10 a month when I started. I can’t even imagine spending such little time online.
I don’t know if that’s good or bad. (It’s bad. It’s obviously bad.) I got online pretty early—I think it would’ve been 1994. We had AOL, which was basically online for babies. But I was 11, and so more or less a baby in computer years. I was so early on AOL that I was part of what became known as Eternal September: I was one of the early AOL users to begin looking at and posting in USENET newsgroups, messing up all the carefully cultivated norms that had been established over the years. I am pretty sure I had email alerts when I got a reply. All of which is to say that I have heard a voice from the computer tell me “you’ve got mail” more than I have heard basically any other sound in my life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friends Shouldn’t Use Admins To Schedule Catch-Ups With Friends]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076956</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/friends-shouldnt-use-admins-to-schedule-catch-ups-with-friends/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T18:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['Your friendship is highly valued. If this is about a life-threatening illness, push 1. A death in the family, push 2. Otherwise, push 3 to connect to my admin, who will see when I can fit you in.'
The post Friends Shouldn’t Use Admins To Schedule Catch-Ups With Friends appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Rothman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Going For Two Is Always The Correct Call]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172716</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/going-for-two-is-always-the-correct-call"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T17:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At some point early in the third quarter of Thursday night's great game between the Cincinnati Bengals and Baltimore Ravens, I began to believe that it just wasn't the Ravens' night. The game resembled many other Baltimore losses from the last couple years: bad defensive play, a lethargic offense, a bunch of unforced penalties. On top of that, star safety Kyle Hamilton went out with an ankle sprain and Lamar Jackson was stretching his apparently ailing throwing hand on the sidelines. It was 21-7 in the Bengals' favor at the time, and it seemed like things were only going to get worse.
But good teams make their own luck, and a fumble by the Bengals in Ravens territory set up a touchdown drive with yet another "Lamar Jackson does something amazing against Cincinnati" play, and also kick-started an onslaught in which the Ravens scored on every drive for the rest of the game. If not for some busted coverages from their highly bustable defense, the Ravens might have pulled away with the game the same way the Bengals threatened to at the beginning. But this is the AFC North, where things get wonky and close no matter what.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Some Young NBA Players Who Are Butt]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172727</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/here-are-some-young-nba-players-who-are-butt-2"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T17:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The early stages of each new NBA season are a time for widespread optimism and excitement. Many young players around the league will further establish themselves among the sport's elite: Paolo Banchero, Anthony Edwards, Victor Wembanyama, etc. Several more—your Chet Holmgrens, your Brandon Millers, your Evan Mobleys—will make the leap into stardom, or even superstardom, delighting their fans and promising years or even decades of excellence to come. Unfortunately, many other young NBA players are poop from the anus of fate. 
Here is that group:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmarks And Outcomes — Moneyball For GenAI (Part II)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077022</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/benchmarks-and-outcomes-moneyball-for-genai-part-ii/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T17:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a legal innovator, it is important to understand what success look likes for the larger organization.
The post Benchmarks And Outcomes — Moneyball For GenAI (Part II) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Crutchfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OHL’s Kitchener Rangers Mark 80th Anniversary of D-Day On Latest Remembrance Day Jerseys]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83283</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/08/ohls-kitchener-rangers-mark-80th-anniversary-of-d-day-on-latest-remembrance-day-jerseys/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T17:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Latest edition marks 19th season in a row that Kitchener Rangers have produced a Remembrance Day jersey; will be worn Friday, November 8, against the Soo Greyhounds]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from the Editor: And I do my little turn on the catwalk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858572</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/letter-from-the-editor-and-i-do-my-little-turn-on-the-catwalk/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T17:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome, dearest readers, to the annual BEST OF issue of The Pitch. We are so thrilled to have you joining us again this year—our 44th!—celebrating the highlights and heroes that define who we are as a city. This special mega-issue is a huge undertaking, starting with groundwork for the process which we begin formulating in February. For an entire vertical...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General Managers Address the Highs and Lows of Starter Innings]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=450466</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/general-managers-address-the-highs-and-lows-of-starter-innings/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T16:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five executives weigh in on the innings their teams got from starting pitchers in 2024, and what it might mean going forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Laurila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Appealing Weekly Roundup]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077176</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/how-appealing-weekly-roundup-94/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T16:34:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The week in appellate news.
The post How Appealing Weekly Roundup appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America Needs More Ravens/Bengals Football]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172719</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/america-needs-more-ravens-bengals-football"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T16:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have a pretty good idea that neither the Baltimore Ravens nor Cincinnati Bengals are going to the Super Bowl, if only because they're both far too fun to survive the difficult December/January gauntlet of bad-weather games and injuries that help make football the cruel and brutal slog it is. We definitely know they won't be playing each other in the Super Bowl because someone foolishly shoved them into the same conference 54 years ago. That’s a particularly egregious example of long-term vision impairment, but it also is what it is.
But also this is where Roger Goodell, the ginger banker who minds the money for the 31 descendants of Scrooge McDuck who run the NFL, could deliver a bold new idea that, if he sells it right, will land well with everyone in our fractured and shattered land. Namely, he could see to it that the Ravens and Bengals somehow are planted in the Super Bowl anyway, either by public fiat or quiet connivance. Given that we as a nation will clearly buy anything we're told and nod in stupefaction, even a middling Svengali like Goodell could carry this off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AHL’s Manitoba Moose Turn Back the Clock for 25th Season Celebration Jerseys]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83271</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/08/ahls-manitoba-moose-turn-back-the-clock-for-25th-season-celebration-jerseys/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T16:07:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front of jersey featured recolored version of team's "happy moose" logo, which they wore from 1996 to 2005; Moose will debut jerseys on ice on Saturday, November 23, against the Chicago Wolves]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Fast rains and mild days (FRI-11/8)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3723046</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-fast-rains-and-mild-days-fri-11-8/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T15:43:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well clouds are going to be the thing for today, and while the chances of any meaningful rains will wait till early Saturday it appears, the skies won't be nearly as blue in the afternoon as they have been recently. The system coming our way is a big snowmaker across the Plains of CO into [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man Who Illegally Accessed Ruth Bader Ginsburg’s Medical Records Before Her Death Gets Prison Time]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077172</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/man-who-illegally-accessed-ruth-bader-ginsburgs-medical-records-before-her-death-gets-prison-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T15:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He blamed his cat for the offense, and received a hefty sentence.
The post Man Who Illegally Accessed Ruth Bader Ginsburg’s Medical Records Before Her Death Gets Prison Time appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fifth Circuit: Lol, No, RFK Jr. You Don’t Have Standing To Sue Joe Biden Because Facebook Blocked Your Anti-vax Nonsense]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077174</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/fifth-circuit-lol-no-rfk-jr-you-dont-have-standing-to-sue-joe-biden-because-facebook-blocked-your-anti-vax-nonsense/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T15:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the try-try-again dept
The post Fifth Circuit: Lol, No, RFK Jr. You Don’t Have Standing To Sue Joe Biden Because Facebook Blocked Your Anti-vax Nonsense appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Techdirt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cowards Are Already Making Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172631</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-cowards-are-already-making-plans"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T14:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An electoral defeat like the one just suffered by Kamala Harris and the Democratic Party is guaranteed to keep the Recrimination Engine redlined throughout the weeks and months to come. Right now, it's impossible to turn on the news, read a mainstream liberal publication, or scroll through social media without immediately being confronted with someone's diagnosis of where it all went wrong for the Democrats, followed by a strident declaration about what needs to happen next.
The worst versions of this ritual are undertaken for the sake of self-preservation. Pundits and politicians are scrambling to define the terms of the defeat in whatever fashion will most easily allow them to hang onto their influence. This is why Bernie Sanders, who just spent the last four years enthusiastically stumping for Joe Biden and his administration, is suddenly reaming out the Democratic Party for having abandoned the working class. It's why a pundit like Matt Yglesias, a liberal in name only who just watched the Harris campaign completely eat shit while running on the kind of centrist policies he has long championed, has to quickly invent a new reality in which Harris lost because she somehow wasn't centrist enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End MLB Pride Nights]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172599</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/end-mlb-pride-nights"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T14:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than Freddie Freeman or Francisco Lindor or those Yankee jamokes who tried to rip off Mookie Betts's hand, I will remember the 2024 MLB postseason for the commercials. Specifically, it was impossible to sit through any game across the entire month of October without being forced to watch multiple Donald Trump campaign ads that fear- and hate-mongered about trans people. Here's an example, if you somehow missed them:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3xzybGKwIGk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Season three of Somebody, Somewhere embraces laughter, tears, and all things Manhattan, Kansas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858553</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/season-three-of-somebody-somewhere-embraces-laughter-tears-and-all-things-manhattan-kansas/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T14:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Sandy Morris/HBO For a low-key comedy actress, Bridget Everett sure does a lot of crying in the third season of HBO’s award-winning series Somebody, Somewhere. The show—set in Manhattan, Kansas—has seen Everett’s alter-ish ego character, Sam, tackle plenty of personal highs and lows over the past two seasons. Now, in its final season, Sam’s emotional arcs quietly peak… crater… and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 11.08.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077171</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/morning-docket-11-08-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T13:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Diddy's team unhappy that grand jury witnesses are talking, worrying that the publicity hurts his chances to Finna Get Loose. [NewsNation]
* Trump judge blocks immigration rule because the law allowing the government to choose to allow immigrants with citizen spouses to "into the United States" legally on parole while their status is processed couldn't support letting those people serve parole while their status is processed if they were already in the United States when the decision was made. It's like Textualism, but a game of Balderdash. [Law360]
* OpenAI wins copyright suit over using material to train the model on the English language. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Judge says his jurisdiction is just more sweary. [Roll on Friday]
* Trump was never going to get jail time -- if the judge didn't put him in a cell for contempt for his behavior during the trial, he was never going to -- but now it's pretty much certain that this will be an all cash sentencing. [New York Law Journal]
* It's a good time to be a partner who does deals that would otherwise violate the Sherman Act! [American Lawyer]
* Firm leaders still convinced that generative AI will have a big impact on the profession. [Thomson Reuters]
The post Morning Docket: 11.08.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC renters in tenant union enter a second month of strike against landlords]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=860317</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-renters-in-tenant-union-enter-a-second-month-of-strike-against-landlords/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T04:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Paige Eichkorn “NOT ONE CENT FOR THE SLUM LORDS!” “DON’T PAY RENT!” Tenants at Independence and Quality Hill Towers led chants and marched outside their buildings on Friday in protest of the Federal Housing Finance Agency’s redaction of their offer for a bargaining meeting with Director Sandra Thompson in Washington, DC. This came after leaders of the Tenant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paige Eichkorn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Invicta FC 58: Ducote vs. Ostroverkhova from Memorial Hall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859941</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-invicta-fc-58-ducote-vs-ostroverkhova-from-memorial-hall/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T01:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Tarik Sykes On Wednesday, Nov. 6, Invicta Fighting Championships hosted Invicta FC 58: Ducote vs. Ostroverkhova from Memorial Hall. In the night’s main event, former strawweight champion Emily Ducote re-established herself as a contender with a submission win over Russia’s Yulia Ostroverkhova. Our photographer Tarik Sykes was there to capture the entire event: Categories: Sports Tags: Emily Ducote,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarik Sykes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Partner In Neighborly Dispute Drops Slur Using His Work Email — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077157</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/biglaw-partner-in-neighborly-dispute-drops-slur-using-his-work-email-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T00:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty Harsh Language There, Partner: Not a good look for Goodwin Procter.
Now That's A Smart Investment!: Billionaires dropped millions to get their chosen judges elected in Texas.
You Know We Can Hear You, Right?: Giuliani doesn't seem too torn up about his defaming.
There's A Lot Of Phish Out There: Watch out for this phishing scam!
Here's How To Manage The Career Bumps: Being an in-house lawyer isn't always easy, but at least there's help.
The post Biglaw Partner In Neighborly Dispute Drops Slur Using His Work Email — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Big Thanks To Our Advertisers]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077125</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/a-big-thanks-to-our-advertisers-21/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T00:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We love working with you.
The post A Big Thanks To Our Advertisers appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[<em>Survivor</em> Alum Makes Legal History]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077146</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/survivor-alum-makes-legal-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T23:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He's been pretty busy since his reality TV debut 23 years ago.
The post <em>Survivor</em> Alum Makes Legal History appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rudy Giuliani Is Exactly That Fool Of A Client]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077144</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/rudy-giuliani-is-exactly-that-fool-of-a-client/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T22:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Putting a microphone in front of 2024 Rudy? What could possibly go wrong?
The post Rudy Giuliani Is Exactly That Fool Of A Client appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Will Be Looking For ‘More Bold, More Fearless’ Judges In His Second Term]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077128</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/trump-will-be-looking-for-more-bold-more-fearless-judges-in-his-second-term/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T21:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moderate Republican judges are being urged to step aside to allow a wave of even more conservative, younger judges to be appointed to the federal courts.
The post Trump Will Be Looking For ‘More Bold, More Fearless’ Judges In His Second Term appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ECHL’s Adirondack Thunder Launch Special Jerseys for Military Appreciation Night]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83255</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/07/echls-adirondack-thunder-launch-special-jerseys-for-military-appreciation-night/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ECHL team based in Glens Falls, New York, goes with grey digital camouflage pattern for base of jersey; Viking in primary logo swaps out blade of hockey stick for American flag]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Beck and Bryan Woods’ holy terror Heretic casts Hugh Grant as a nightmare nihilist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=860356</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/scott-beck-and-bryan-woods-holy-terror-heretic-cast-hugh-grant-as-nightmare-nihilist/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T21:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When cataclysmic events happen — the kind that take time to recover from, if you recover at all — the first thing we reach for is explanation. What could we have done differently? Were we destined to end up where we did? If you’re a person of faith, you may wonder where God is in all this. What do your...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creature Drops: A Big Baby From Patagonia]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172666</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/creature-drops-a-big-baby-from-patagonia"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Newsletterer's Note: Each weekday, I send out a newsletter called The Cipher to Defector Pal-level subscribers, which has a recap of the blog day, links to other sites, and extra takes and bits from staffers. (You can change your newsletter preferences or upgrade your subscription at the My Account page.) Today, we are inexplicably locked out of Sendgrid, so everyone gets a bonus bit from Sabs.
Also, an announcement: Defector Trivia is happening on Twitch today at 5 p.m. ET. I would have put that in the newsletter, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Money Changed The Texas Judiciary]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077148</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/billionaire-money-changed-the-texas-judiciary/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T21:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who needs justice for all when you could have corporate interests?
The post Billionaire Money Changed The Texas Judiciary appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Partner Drops Slur In Dustup With Neighbors]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077132</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/biglaw-partner-drops-slur-in-dustup-with-neighbors/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T20:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not a good look for the partner.
The post Biglaw Partner Drops Slur In Dustup With Neighbors appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Taste Of That Football-Shaped Bread, With Ray Ratto]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172582</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-taste-of-that-football-shaped-bread-with-ray-ratto"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T20:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are times when the lag between when we record The Distraction (on Tuesday mornings) and when it goes up (the first minutes of Thursday) is not to our advantage. But there are also instances, like this week, where it is absolutely essential. 
As frustrating as this can be, I think the very fact that this week's episode is a pretty straightforward football-and-Funbag installment of the pod, and not a morose reckoning with the horror and unknowability of this country and this moment, is a good thing. You'll get one of those soon enough, but for the time being perhaps I could interest you in something more along the lines of "Three guys trying to figure out what's wrong with various lousy NFL teams, as if they had no other care in the world." Also I got kind of upset about my co-hosts' bagel orders of choice, which is maybe small or ungenerous of me, but which I also stand by.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Case Management Platform Clarra Unveils Suite Of New Features, Including Gen AI, Analytics, And Tracking Of Client Communications]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077103</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/11/case-management-platform-clarra-unveils-suite-of-new-features-including-gen-ai-analytics-and-tracking-of-client-communications.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T19:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tech-forward approach makes Clarra particularly attractive for law firms looking to migrate away from older systems or avoid the pitfalls of merging incompatible tech stacks.
The post Case Management Platform Clarra Unveils Suite Of New Features, Including Gen AI, Analytics, And Tracking Of Client Communications appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week In Skeletons]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172577</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-week-in-skeletons"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T19:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are looking for some wonder and whimsy from the animal kingdom to lift your spirits this week—some uplifting tale of a shrew that is so small that it sails on gusts of wind, or a fossil of an ancient crab that had an exquisitely defined buttcrack—you have not come to the right place. Instead, I have two tales about dead people and the bones they left behind. Is it the news we want? No. It is the news we have.
Skeleton No. 1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: A new emo bar, Sido’s third location opens, and kudos to Kata Nori]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859838</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-a-new-emo-bar-sidos-third-location-opens-and-kudos-to-kata-nori/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T19:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Life in KC is pretty delicious. In fact, there is often so much going on that it can be hard to decide where to go and what to try. That’s where I come in.  I’ve curated this weekly list of events, openings, deals, and celebrations to keep you in-the-know. Cheers! Today’s Tip Have you ever wondered...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back To Law (Practice) School: The Essential Skills You Didn’t Learn In Law School [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077015</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/back-to-law-practice-school-the-essential-skills-you-didnt-learn-in-law-school/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T18:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve got new answers to the ongoing test of law firm management strategy!
The post Back To Law (Practice) School: The Essential Skills You Didn’t Learn In Law School appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JARED CORREIA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Big Boy Sam Darnold Is Big Fun]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172590</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/my-big-boy-sam-darnold-is-big-fun"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T18:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out,”through here.
Here are some Dad Facts for you. Sam Darnold is 27 years old, three years older than Falcons rookie Michael Penix. He became the youngest starting quarterback in post-merger NFL history after the Jets drafted him. He played for three different franchises in his first six seasons. His first head coach was Todd Bowles, who was fired at the end of his rookie season. His second head coach was Adam Gase, who is Adam Gase. His third head coach was Matt Rhule, who was fired early into Darnold’s second season in Carolina. And his fourth head coach (if you don’t count Steve Wilks, who took over the Panthers as interim coach after Rhule oozed back down to the college ranks) was Kyle Shanahan, who used him exclusively as a backup. His career was Ryan Fitzpatrick’s in miniature, with the proportionately diminished reputation to accompany it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embrace The Future: How In-House Legal Professionals Can Thrive By Partnering With AI]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1072595</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/embrace-the-future-how-in-house-legal-professionals-can-thrive-by-partnering-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T18:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For in-house legal professionals, AI isn’t just a buzzword.
The post Embrace The Future: How In-House Legal Professionals Can Thrive By Partnering With AI appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga V. Mack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Champions League Format Actually Rocks]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172595</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-new-champions-league-format-actually-rocks"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T17:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As loyal readers of Defector know, I am never wrong. I've certainly never written an article that was eventually proven to be overly optimistic, overly pessimistic, or overly incorrect. Given my general infallibility, I come today to apologize for my first incorrect thought in at least three years: The new Champions League format kind of whips ass.
I didn't think it would, and I wasn't alone in that thought. When it was announced, my first reaction was that this would just make the group stage—now called the league stage—even more tilted in favor of the big clubs on the continent. Whereas before, these clubs could be thrown in together in a group of death—like last season's Dortmund-PSG-Milan-Newcastle meat grinder—now, my theory went, they would just be able to mop up on a diet of weak clubs to secure a spot in the knockout rounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baltimore Ravens To Debut “Purple Rising” Alternate Helmets On Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83247</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/07/baltimore-ravens-to-debut-purple-rising-alternate-helmets-on-thursday/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T17:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Baltimore Ravens will debut their new "Purple Rising" alternate helmets during Thursday night's game against the Cincinnati Bengals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Has Come To This: A Derrick White Appreciation Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172593</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/it-has-come-to-this-a-derrick-white-appreciation-blog"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T17:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Derrick White, unglamorous secondary ball-handler for the defending champion Boston Celtics, does many things well. He's a knock-down shooter who in his eighth professional season is attempting a career-high 9.6 threes per game, or about 68 percent of his total shot output. He's a Tony Allen-level perimeter defender, a Danny Green-level transition defender, and among the greatest shot-blocking guards in NBA history. You might lazily describe him as a 3-and-D specialist, except that he is also a competent and quick-thinking passer, a slick and reliable pick-and-roll operator, and an artist from floater range. Through nine games this season he is giving the Celtics 20 points a night on 64 percent true shooting, and is averaging better than three assists per turnover, and is using just a shad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Of Times, The Worst Of Times: Navigating The Emotional Roller Coaster As An In-House Lawyer]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076908</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-best-of-times-the-worst-of-times-navigating-the-emotional-roller-coaster-as-an-in-house-lawyer/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T17:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’re not just the company lawyer; you’re also a trusted confidant.
The post The Best Of Times, The Worst Of Times: Navigating The Emotional Roller Coaster As An In-House Lawyer appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lisa Lang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Warriors Are Still Doing It The Warriors Way]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172609</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-warriors-are-still-doing-it-the-warriors-way"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T16:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Golden State Warriors are evidently the dynasty that won't die. It is a dynasty that will age and eventually expire, of course, because they all do, and maybe this will all collapse in a heap of spent tendons and uncontrolled rage. But dynasties can sometimes linger beyond their rational shelf life; San Antonio's fifth championship came seven years after its fourth. And every time the Warriors seem to flatline—the 2024 season, for one example—they rise up and remember themselves. What they remember, specifically, is not really that complicated. When the Warriors defend, they are truly dynastic. It’s not as easy as they make it look, but it is almost as simple as that.
Their 118-112 win over Boston last night was a fresh reinforcement of that essential truth. Yes, many folks will be distracted by Steve Kerr having the carte blanche to yell at Stephen Curry after Curry passed the mythical 3,000 career turnover mark, but all that has been true forever; Curry turnovers, Kerr getting cranky about it, Curry not making a thing out of getting yelled at, and so endlessly on. Same as it ever was, same as it ever was.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is AI The Key To Efficient Contract Reviews? [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077088</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/is-ai-the-key-to-efficient-contract-reviews/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T16:32:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our friends at LegalOn Technologies share real world use cases on how legal professionals are transforming their contract review process. 
The post Is AI The Key To Efficient Contract Reviews? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LegalOn Technologies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri AG Andrew Bailey’s electoral victory foreshadows a civil liberties nightmare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859836</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missouri-ag-andrew-baileys-electoral-victory-foreshadows-a-civil-liberties-nightmare/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T16:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri Attorney General Andrew Bailey delivers a victory speech to supporters in Columbia after winning the primary election against Republican attorney general hopeful Will Scharf on Tuesday (Anna Spoerre/Missouri Independent) Andrew Bailey, the incumbent Republican Attorney General of Missouri, won his first election in a landslide over Democratic rival Elad Gross. This was expected, given the remarkable success of now-President-elect...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael McGrady Jr.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quincy Jones Was Greater Than Any One Era]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172447</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/quincy-jones-was-greater-than-any-one-era"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T15:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Quincy, the 2018 documentary meant to capture the totality of Quincy Jones's contributions to the last 70-plus years of music, film, and television, he spoke about his time living in Paris in the late 1950s and working under acclaimed composer Nadia Boulanger. "There are only 12 notes, and you should investigate what everyone did with those 12 notes," she said to him, as he explains in the doc. It was the lesson of not just the outward simplicity of music, but the lineage and vast worlds contained within its grand history. It was a call to be a student of the art, just as much as a player.
Jones, who died on Sunday at the age of 91, leaves behind an enormous absence in entertainment. He was the ultimate connective tissue in making the greatest media of the last few eras of entertainment. He orchestrated Count Basie's band when they played for Frank Sinatra. He composed the theme for Sanford and Son, and scored films like In The Heat of the Night, The Italian Job, and The Color Purple. He produced The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air, co-founded Vibe magazine, brought jazz and hip-hop together for his Back On The Block album. Off The Wall, Thriller, Bad—there is not one medium, genre, or business within entertainment that did not have Jones's hand in it. He was just as eager to teach the intricacies of making good music and art as he was to tell those ribald stories about Sinatra, Michael Jackson, or Prince. His death is not a surprise, but it is upsetting all the same, less because of what he's done and more because of how little the modern entertainment industry resembles the kind of place that fosters that kind of artistic talent and allowed him to thrive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert For Lawyers: Don’t Fall For This Federal Courts Phishing Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077129</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/alert-for-lawyers-dont-fall-for-this-federal-courts-phishing-scam/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T15:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Be very careful, lawyers, because your personal or client data could be at risk.
The post Alert For Lawyers: Don’t Fall For This Federal Courts Phishing Scam appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PWHL Unveils Jerseys for All 6 Teams Ahead of 2024-25 Season Start]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83205</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/07/pwhl-unveils-jerseys-for-all-6-teams-ahead-of-2024-25-season-start/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T15:42:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After team names and logos were revealed in September, jerseys hit shelves with just over three weeks until the puck drops on the 2024-25 PWHL regular season]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Admin Will Bring ‘Uncertainty,’ Opportunities For Defense Industry: Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077102</id>
        <link href="https://breakingdefense.com/2024/11/trump-admin-will-bring-uncertainty-opportunities-for-defense-industry-analysts/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T15:03:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘The makeup of Congress, and specifically the makeup of the House, I think will actually matter much more to the future of the defense budget than whoever the president is,’ said Todd Harrison of AEI.
The post Trump Admin Will Bring ‘Uncertainty,’ Opportunities For Defense Industry: Analysts appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VALERIE INSINNA - BREAKING DEFENSE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trying To Catch Up With Lael Wilcox As She Biked Around The World In 108 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172248</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/trying-to-catch-up-with-lael-wilcox-as-she-biked-around-the-world-in-108-days"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WHITEHORSE, Canada — I stood on an empty stretch of the Alaska Highway and squinted north as the sky darkened. I had parked a couple of miles away, at a relatively busy intersection on the edge of the Yukon’s small capital city, and pedaled north up a long hill onto this quieter stretch of road. It was just after 9:30 on a Saturday night. I waited on the southbound shoulder, helmeted and hi-vis-vested, watching for a cyclist.
When a black dot crested the next hill, my heart started beating a little faster. I turned, threw a leg over my own bicycle, and stood on my toes, checking over my shoulder as the dot coalesced into a woman pedaling steadily toward me. As she came closer, I pushed off and started riding, trying to get up to speed so she wouldn’t just blow right by.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eva Holland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 11.07.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077131</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/morning-docket-11-07-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T13:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Biglaw thinks Trump's next administration will be good for business. I guess they missed the part where his economic czar Elon pledged to crash the economy as part of the plan. [National Law Journal]
* We're already talking about Supreme Court shortlists as though it's not just the loudest mouths from the Fifth Circuit. [Law360]
* Remember polio? That was fun, right? [Bloomberg Law News]
* Jack Smith preparing to drop criminal cases against Trump before the new president has to pardon himself and potentially put a controversial constitutional question to the test. [ABA Journal]
* American lawyers in London report working 13-hour days. Which... is that not how all of Biglaw works anymore? [Fortune]
* Good news for the heroin trade, as Trump seems likely to turn the SEC over to the crypto industry. [Cointelegraph]
* What happens with Trump's state law issues now? [Courthouse News Service]
The post Morning Docket: 11.07.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Tree Theatre’s musical adaptation of Bubble Boy makes for oddly prescient cultural commentary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859286</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/spinning-tree-theatres-musical-adaptation-of-bubble-boy-makes-for-oddly-prescient-cultural-commentary/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T13:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joshua Johnson as Jimmy Livingston (the Bubble Boy) and Jordan Rosenwald as Chloe Molinski. // Photo by Micah Thompson/Spinning Tree Theatre If you caught the 2001 Jake Gyllenhaal film Bubble Boy, there’s a better than non-zero chance you haven’t thought about it since. The cartoonishly over-the-top story about a boy allergic to the air is probably more closely associated with the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partner? More Like Buddy Of The Firm — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077100</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/partner-more-like-buddy-of-the-firm-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T00:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Is A Title Worth?: Nonequity partners cover liability without sharing profits.
UK Firm Is Closing Foreign Doors: Eversheds Sutherland is shutting its Beijing office.
No Thanks to DeSantis!: Monique Worrell is back in the big seat.
Utah Is Considering Its Options: A bar exam alternative may be underway!
Last Call!: Send in your final submissions for Above the Law's 15th annual Legally Themed Halloween Costume Contest!
The post Partner? More Like Buddy Of The Firm — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Impact Of Trump’s Second Term On The Federal Judiciary]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077087</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-impact-of-trumps-second-term-on-the-federal-judiciary/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T23:18:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Senate has confirmed 213 of Joe Biden's nominees.
The post The Impact Of Trump’s Second Term On The Federal Judiciary appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw’s Betting On Trump’s Presidency Being Good For Business]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077039</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/biglaws-betting-on-trumps-presidency-being-good-for-business/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T22:27:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’ll certainly be good for specific Biglaw practice groups, that is.
The post Biglaw’s Betting On Trump’s Presidency Being Good For Business appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Utah May Add A New Path To Practicing Law]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077086</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/utah-may-add-a-new-path-to-practicing-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who doesn't love options?
The post Utah May Add A New Path To Practicing Law appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sir Sam Alito Decides No Pesky ‘Constitution’ Governs Him]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077079</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/sir-sam-alito-decides-no-pesky-constitution-governs-him/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T21:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That Governing Document Can't Stop Me Because I Can't Read!
The post Sir Sam Alito Decides No Pesky ‘Constitution’ Governs Him appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Football League’s Adelaide Crows Flying High With Launch of New Logo]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83199</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/06/australian-football-leagues-adelaide-crows-flying-high-with-launch-of-new-logo/other/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T20:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New logo depicts full body of swooping crow — in stark contrast to previous version, which only depicted crow's head — with red and gold streaks in wings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VP Harris concedes presidential race in phone call to Donald Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859828</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/vp-harris-concedes-presidential-race-in-phone-call-to-donald-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T20:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vice President Kamala Harris delivers remarks Nov. 6, 2024, at Howard University in Washington, D.C., after conceding the presidential race to Donald Trump. (Grace Hills/Kansas Reflector) WASHINGTON — Vice President Kamala Harris Wednesday afternoon called Donald Trump to concede the 2024 presidential race, according to a senior Harris aide. During the call, the Democratic presidential nominee “discussed the importance of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ariana Figueroa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whether Your Candidate Won Or Lost, Don’t Blame The Election Results For Whatever The Stock Market Is Doing]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077019</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/whether-your-candidate-won-or-lost-dont-blame-the-election-results-for-whatever-the-stock-market-is-doing/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T20:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most stock prices do not react instantaneously to election results.
The post Whether Your Candidate Won Or Lost, Don’t Blame The Election Results For Whatever The Stock Market Is Doing appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Wolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Last Time Was Lucky]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172572</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/last-time-was-lucky"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter, examining the apocalyptic politics and coverage of Campaign 2024.
On the last day of vamping about opinions before the election became a fact, in a roundtable discussion among New York Times pundits, the respectable conservative David Brooks tried to turn to history to understand what might be coming. "Mostly I just worry about Trump's general incompetence," Brooks wrote. "We got lucky during his term, because there were no existential or complicated threats, until the pandemic."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Non-Equity Partners Are ‘Partners’ For Covering Firm Costs But Not Partners For Pay]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077082</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/non-equity-partners-are-partners-for-covering-firm-costs-but-not-partners-for-pay/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['Partner' isn't the deal it used to be.
The post Non-Equity Partners Are ‘Partners’ For Covering Firm Costs But Not Partners For Pay appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ultimate Fakebook and friends celebrated 25 years of This Will Be Laughing Week Saturday night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859497</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/ultimate-fakebook-and-friends-celebrated-25-years-of-this-will-be-laughing-week-saturday-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ultimate Fakebook. // photo by Whitney Young Ultimate Fakebook with Schatzi, Jon Snodgrass, and the Touchdowns The Bottleneck Saturday, November 1 Going to a show the night after Halloween when you and your wife went bar-hopping means you’re gonna be tired. But it’s Ultimate Fakebook, doing their penultimate show after playing their 1999 album, This Will Be Laughing Week, in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Surprising Insights That Will Change Your Mind About BI [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076989</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/5-surprising-insights-that-will-change-your-mind-about-bi/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:43:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on November 20th for this CLE-eligible webinar and learn how BI can revolutionize your law firm's approach to data, driving efficiency and informed decision-making. 
The post 5 Surprising Insights That Will Change Your Mind About BI appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Litera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Might As Well Believe In The Winnipeg Jets]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172565</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/might-as-well-believe-in-the-winnipeg-jets"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We open today's reading with Susie Dent's Word Of The Day. That word is “recrudescence,” and it means “the return of something terrible after a time of reprieve.” It originates in the 17th century, and lives in the 21st.
With that as our guiding rubric—always trust a brilliant lexicographer from another land to contextualize America's decision to put itself on Santa's Seriously Pissed Off List—let us now turn our attention instead to the best team in the National Hockey League, the profoundly Who The Hell Are They And Why Are They Doing This Winnipeg Jets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final Call For Submissions: ATL’s 15th Annual Legally Themed Halloween Costume Contest]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077081</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/atls-15th-annual-legally-themed-halloween-costume-contest/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you got what it takes to top the winners of years past?
The post Final Call For Submissions: ATL’s 15th Annual Legally Themed Halloween Costume Contest appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progressive State Attorney Thumbs Her Nose At Ron DeSantis]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077072</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/progressive-state-attorney-thumbs-her-nose-at-ron-desantis/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T17:12:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voters disagreed with DeSantis on this one.
The post Progressive State Attorney Thumbs Her Nose At Ron DeSantis appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to providing care, time is obsolete for The Pitch’s 2024 Best Budtender Damone Garrison]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859745</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/when-it-comes-to-providing-care-time-is-obsolete-for-the-pitchs-2024-best-budtender-damone-garrison/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T17:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Joe Ellett The votes are in, and the stage is set as The Pitch’s Best Of Kansas City picks have been announced. Across the community, there are countless individuals and institutions who have been crowned ‘Best Of’ in their respective areas. “Best Bartender” has been a popular category in the city for years on end. This year, its...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Ellett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is How My Brownies Turned Out]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172534</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/here-is-how-my-brownies-turned-out"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T16:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A frugal baker can also be an adventurous baker, in the sense that leftover ingredients from one recipe can be used as an excuse to try something new. I still had a bunch of marshmallows from the fudgy frosting I made for these decadent peanut butter brownies that use approximately one tanker truck full of sugar (they tasted spectacular; I will go to the hospital if I eat one more before at least 18 months have passed). I can use marshmallows in hot chocolate, but it is 75 degrees right now, so instead I thought of the one other use I know for marshmallows. I did a search for "smores brownies" and hit this extremely basic and simple recipe, which I thought would occupy my mind without providing any extra stress on Tuesday night.
Basically, all you're doing in this recipe is baking brownies from a mix and putting a bunch of s'mores toppings on it midway through. I'd actually never in my life used a pre-packaged mix before, but I appreciated the shortcut on this occasion. I baked it for 15 minutes, took it out of the oven, and added a very appealing collage of chocolate, marshmallow, and graham cracker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tackling Deposition Anxiety: How AI Is Changing The Way Lawyers Do Depositions [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076656</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/tackling-deposition-anxiety-how-ai-is-changing-the-way-lawyers-do-depositions/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T16:33:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Depo CoPilot is a cutting-edge technology laser-focused on helping you perform your very best at every deposition.
The post Tackling Deposition Anxiety: How AI Is Changing The Way Lawyers Do Depositions appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FILEVINE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bromance Languages 101]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172545</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bromance-languages-101"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T16:28:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some college students plunge into parties, hookups and dates without hesitation, while some of us linger on the diving board, paralyzed by such questions as Sex: how? What is attraction anyway? And the classic Am I worthy of love?
But how are matters of the heart mediated through the sometimes delicate, sometimes volatile state of brohood? Could you leap without looking into a new romance if subtly pushed, or, perhaps, hit by a flying tackle from your most supportive bro? Can two college-aged bros survive a bond of mutual support without serious injury?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172537</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/after-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T16:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I went for a run on Election Day. The streets near my neighborhood, normally clogged with cars dropping off children at an elementary school down the road, were mostly empty. Public schools were closed, and the same yard signs I’d been walking and driving past for the last several months—Trump/Vance, Harris/Walz—seemed, ironically, beside the point. In a country where the lead-up to a presidential election is excruciatingly drawn out, where, in this specific case, an incumbent head of state more closely resembling a corpse threatened to run for office again before bowing out at the last second, throwing the entire race into disarray, the eventual arrival of the day itself was lackluster. I drove to work, where I overheard murmurs from customers about how they voted, the increased police pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The First U.K.-Based Biglaw Firm To Shutter An Office In Mainland China]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077049</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-first-u-k-based-biglaw-firm-to-shutter-an-office-in-mainland-china/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another Biglaw firm closes the door on a Chinese office.
The post The First U.K.-Based Biglaw Firm To Shutter An Office In Mainland China appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Where's the cold air (WED-11/6)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3720601</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-wheres-the-cold-air-wed-11-6/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:29:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's feeling like fall for sure, but in the big picture of things, there really isn't much in the way of unusual cold coming towards the region anytime soon. Some transient cool air masses that will slip in and through rather quickly to be replaced with above average temperatures on the bigger picture of things. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off Contemplates The Melting Method For Autumn Week]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172444</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-not-so-great-defector-bake-off-contemplates-the-melting-method-for-autumn-week"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off, where Kelsey and Chris attempt to complete the technical challenges from the newest season of The Great British Bake Off in their own home kitchens, with the same time parameters as the professional-grade bakers competing on the show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSC Napoli Brings A Little Bit of Japan to Italy With New Third Kit]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83192</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/06/ssc-napoli-brings-a-little-bit-of-japan-to-italy-with-new-third-kit/soccer/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:25:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shirt celebrates Naples' sister city of Kagoshima with blend of Italian and Japanese art styles and characters representing seven Bushido virtues down the right side]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why AI Governance Is The Number 1 Issue On This Health System Exec’s Mind]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077067</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/11/ai-healthcare-technology/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Hill, Ochsner Health’s innovation officer, said he goes to sleep most nights and wakes up most mornings worried about one thing: the state of generative AI governance in healthcare. To him, providers and other healthcare organizations are in dire need of frameworks to ensure their AI tools are safe and perform well over time.
The post Why AI Governance Is The Number 1 Issue On This Health System Exec’s Mind appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KATIE ADAMS - MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Saying goodbye to a legend, plus a visit to Thou Mayest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859691</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-saying-goodbye-to-a-legend-plus-a-visit-to-thou-mayest/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T14:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Of Anita’s Famous Rolls On my recent visit to Anita’s Famous Rolls, I was met with the cozy, nostalgic scent of cinnamon and freshly baked rolls wafting through the air—instantly transporting me back to childhood Christmas mornings. More than just a bakery, Anita’s is a heartwarming spot where tradition and a genuine love for baking take center stage. It’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Place Is All Fucked Up]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172500</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-place-is-all-fucked-up"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T13:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It doesn't appear to have been close. Georgia flipped for Trump. Pennsylvania and Wisconsin, too. The Blue Wall crumbled like Jericho's. Just about everywhere voted redder than in 2020. Young people went right. New York City went right. The polls said what they said, but then Americans went to the voting booth and said what they said, which is that they want four more years of Donald Trump. This feels worse than 2016. That was a squeaker, and you could convince yourself it was a fluke. The Comey letter. No Midwest Dem ground game. A uniquely unpopular candidate. Belief that maybe Trump wasn't being totally serious about the things he said, or might surround himself with smarter, better people. Maybe it was possible people were voting for Trump just to seize on an intrusive thought, a call of the void. You can't tell yourself these stories this time. Trump is a known quantity. We know what he would do as President, and we know all the things he'd promised to do as President a second time, and millions of Americans took all that into consideration and said, Yes, I want that.
What do you do in a place like this, with an electorate like that? You survive it, mostly, unless you don't. You will try to figure out how it got there, got so angry and stupid and cruel, so that you can nudge it somewhere else next time. You do this by seeing what went wrong this time. This seems like an impossible task this morning, because everything went wrong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 11.06.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077066</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/morning-docket-11-06-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T13:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* To all you public defenders trying to get criminal clients off... have you considered just winning the electoral college? [Guardian]
* If you're the worst student at your law school, but belong to FedSoc and want a federal judgeship, STAY IN LINE. [Yale Daily News]
* Law firms ask judge to dismiss "incoherent" lawsuit. [ABA Journal]
* Tug of war continues as voters reinstall prosecutor that DeSantis removed. [Bloomberg Law News]
* The firms poised to benefit from hitching their brand to the convicted felon rapist guy. [Law360]
* A fake money business isn't the height of professionalism? Shocking. [The Recorder]
* Cute! States seek to enshrine reproductive rights in their constitutions like that will matter. [NPR]
The post Morning Docket: 11.06.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missourians vote to increase minimum wage, require paid sick leave]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859794</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missourians-vote-to-increase-minimum-wage-require-paid-sick-leave/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T05:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Tucker, a leader with the Missouri Workers Center, teaches chants customized to an initiative petition to raise the minimum wage and mandate paid sick leave outside of the Secretary of State’s office building in Jefferson City in May (Annelise Hanshaw/Missouri Independent) An effort to hike the state’s minimum wage to $15 an hour and guarantee paid sick leave won...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clara Bates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Could Listen On Kris Bubic, Alec Marsh In Search For Offense]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=829962</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/royals-could-listen-on-kris-bubic-alec-marsh-in-search-for-offense.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T05:17:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals already knocked out one key bit of offseason business, re-signing Michael Wacha to a $51MM deal just before the veteran starter could discuss contracts with other teams. It seems they’ll now turn their attention to deepening a top-heavy lineup. Will Sammon and Katie Woo of the Athletic write that the Royals are looking for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri voters approve Amendment 3, overturn state’s abortion ban]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859766</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missouri-voters-overturn-states-near-total-abortion-ban/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T04:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maggie Olivia, a senior policy manager with Abortion Action Missouri, embraces abortion-rights supporters after the race is called in favor of Amendment 3 on Tuesday in St. Louis (Anna Spoerre/Missouri Independent). Abortion rights will be enshrined in the Missouri Constitution after voters on Tuesday overturned the state’s near-total ban. The Associated Press called the race at 10:30 p.m. with Amendment...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Spoerre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josh Hawley defeats Lucas Kunce in Missouri U.S. Senate race]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859747</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/josh-hawley-defeats-lucas-kunce-in-missouri-u-s-senate-race/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T03:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senator Josh Hawley speaks to reporters at the governor’s ham breakfast at the Missouri State Fair in Sedalia on Aug. 15 (Annelise Hanshaw/Missouri Independent) OZARK — U.S. Sen. Josh Hawley won a second term on Tuesday, overcoming a well-financed rival in a state that hasn’t elected a Democrat to statewide office since 2018. Hawley led Marine veteran Lucas Kunce 51%...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Hancock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republican Mike Kehoe wins Missouri governor’s race over Democrat Crystal Quade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859734</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/republican-mike-kehoe-wins-missouri-governors-race-over-democrat-crystal-quade/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T03:25:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Kehoe, the Republican candidate for Missouri governor, thanks supporters as he steps onstage for his victory speech the night of the primary election in August (Annelise Hanshaw/Missouri Independent). Missouri’s next governor will be Mike Kehoe, a Republican who cruised to victory Tuesday night over Democrat Crystal Quade. The Associated Press called the race at 8:30 p.m. with 22% of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Rivas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They Let You Say Anything When You’re A Law Professor! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077046</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/they-let-you-say-anything-when-youre-a-law-professor-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T00:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Professor Echoes Donald Trump's Message Of Peace: It rings almost as hollow as his skull.
Do It On Your Own Time: Fewer firms are giving paid time off to vote this time around.
That's Thinking Like A Lawyer!: See if you recognize any of the names on Kamala's transition team.
Not Worth Losing Your License Over: Learn from the ones who lost their licenses over MAGA.
Was The Fight Worth It?: Lawyer hit with ethics complaint after escalating their $550 typo.
The post They Let You Say Anything When You’re A Law Professor! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gold Star Standard For Election Day]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077023</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-gold-star-standard-for-election-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T00:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don't be like Oklahoma.
The post The Gold Star Standard For Election Day appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supreme Courts Of Delaware And Georgia Act To Regulate Use Of Generative AI In The Courts]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076986</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/11/supreme-courts-of-delaware-and-georgia-act-to-regulate-use-of-generative-ai-in-the-courts.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T23:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courts continue to make rules about the use of artificial intelligence within the practice of law.
The post Supreme Courts Of Delaware And Georgia Act To Regulate Use Of Generative AI In The Courts appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers, Take Note: Microsoft Offers Current Advice On Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076988</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/lawyers-take-note-microsoft-offers-current-advice-on-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T23:18:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These simple steps can be quickly implemented by lawyers at no or little additional cost.
The post Lawyers, Take Note: Microsoft Offers Current Advice On Cybersecurity appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharon D. Nelson, John W. Simek, and Michael C. Maschke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RNC Face Plants In Suit To Toss Out Georgia Ballots]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077030</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/rnc-face-plants-in-suit-to-toss-out-georgia-ballots/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T22:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it good when the judge says you failed in your duty of candor? 
The post RNC Face Plants In Suit To Toss Out Georgia Ballots appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Books You Can Read Tonight To Distract Yourself From Whatever Is To Come]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172483</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/books-you-can-read-tonight-to-distract-yourself-from-whatever-is-to-come"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T22:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one knows anything. Everyone claiming to know something is lying. The odds are 50-50, always, even if they say the odds are different. And though it can be a delicious hell to watch cable news and scroll on your phone all night, it does not make actually the election get decided any faster. In all likelihood, there will be nothing to know until well past midnight, if not several days from now. It is perhaps unreasonable to expect anyone who cares about this country to truly log off in any real way, but perhaps you can make your evening less miserable as the polls close. What if you could go to the bookstore and pick up something that would be gripping enough to stop you from watching Steve Kornacki zoom in on some random county that is behaving slightly differently than it did four or eight years ago? What if you could escape this mortal level of hell by entering your imagination guided by a sure hand? 
Well, you could try! The key to choosing a good book for election night is that it must be engaging, plot-heavy, and more desirable than your phone. You must be so mesmerized by what is happening that you are more invested in the next page than you are in the results out of Fulton County, which, remember, you cannot affect with your television-watching. This is both a high bar and a low bar for fiction to clear. Also: The book should not explicitly contain material that reminds you of the election, and it should not be so highbrow that if you check your phone every 10 minutes (you are allowed to cheat, and will) you will lose the plot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hundreds Of Biglaw Attorneys Staffing Election Protection Hotline To Help Voters]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077002</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/hundreds-of-biglaw-attorneys-staffing-election-protection-hotline-to-help-voters/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T21:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These lawyers understand how important it is to protect voter access on Election Day. Thank you!
The post Hundreds Of Biglaw Attorneys Staffing Election Protection Hotline To Help Voters appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attorney’s Response To A Zelle Typo Could Be A Stain On Her Career]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077027</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/attorneys-response-to-a-zelle-typo-could-be-a-stain-on-her-career/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T21:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would have never happened on Cash App.
The post Attorney’s Response To A Zelle Typo Could Be A Stain On Her Career appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>