<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-10-06T14:13:00.474Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Nearly Losing His Job, Alex Verdugo Comes Through on Both Sides of the Ball in ALDS Opener]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=448150</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/after-nearly-losing-his-job-alex-verdugo-comes-through-on-both-sides-of-the-ball-in-alds-opener/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-06T06:05:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The much-maligned left fielder helped the Yankees overcome a shaky start from Gerrit Cole to take Game 1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Jaffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL Week 5 Uniform Schedule: Broncos, Jaguars, 49ers Wearing Throwback Uniforms, Texans Debuting H-Town Blue Color Rush Set]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82484</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/06/nfl-week-5-uniform-schedule-broncos-jaguars-49ers-wearing-throwback-uniforms-texans-debuting-h-town-blue-color-rush-set/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-06T05:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our new weekly series that looks at every uniform matchup across the NFL is headlined by throwback threads for the Denver Broncos, Jacksonville Jaguars and San Francisco 49ers, as well as the debut of the Houston Texans' H-Town blue-accented Color Rush uniforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cravath Who?! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075856</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/cravath-who-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T23:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Boutique Firm Is Above Market!: You get paid how much!?
Show US The Money!: when do you think your firm will hand out bonuses?
Development In Shooting Of Judge Mullins: The motive remains unknown.
Turley Better Watch Out!: A new jester is on the loose with knee-slapping legal opinions.
So Much For The 60-Day Rule!: Which doesn't exist, by the way. But Jack Smith’s brief is very real!
The post Cravath Who?! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Danforth blames Josh Hawley for Missourians losing out on radiation compensation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=854278</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/jack-danforth-blames-josh-hawley-for-missourians-losing-out-on-radiation-compensation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T23:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senator Josh Hawley speaks to reporters after joining challenger Lucas Kunce in the middle of the floor of the governor’s ham breakfast at the Missouri State Fair in Sedalia Thursday morning (Annelise Hanshaw/Missouri Independent). U.S. Sen. Josh Hawley’s failure as a legislator is most glaringly obvious in the demise of a bill providing coverage to Missourians exposed to radiation...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rudi Keller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri Amendment 6: Should court fees fund retirement for law enforcement personnel? Voters get to decide.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=854263</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missouri-amendment-6-should-court-fees-fund-retirement-for-law-enforcement-personnel-voters-get-to-decide/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T23:31:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri voters will decide Nov. 5 if retirement funds for sheriffs and prosecutors should be supported with fees collected on court cases. A fee used to fund sheriffs’ pensions was put in place by state law in 1983. The Missouri General Assembly placed Amendment 6 on the ballot to reverse a 2021 Missouri Supreme Court ruling that found the fees...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary Sanchez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Real Reason To Go In-House]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075850</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-real-reason-to-go-in-house/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T23:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most people agree.
The post The Real Reason To Go In-House appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Prosecutor Gets Caught With 1,000 Pounds Of Weed At His Law Office]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075842</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/former-prosecutor-gets-caught-with-1000-pounds-of-weed-at-his-law-office/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T22:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He should have kept his cannabis law practice separate. 
The post Former Prosecutor Gets Caught With 1,000 Pounds Of Weed At His Law Office appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stat(s) Of The Week: Is Bullying Endemic To The Profession?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075814</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/bullying-endemic-legal-profession/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T21:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New study finds that one in four lawyers have been bullied on the job.
The post Stat(s) Of The Week: Is Bullying Endemic To The Profession? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vera Djordjevich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[American League Division Series Preview: New York Yankees vs. Kansas City Royals]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=448042</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/american-league-division-series-preview-new-york-yankees-vs-kansas-city-royals/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T21:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York is the better team, but Kansas City is already talking about creating its own legacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Martell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JD Vance’s Yale Law Classmates Donate Money To Undo His Damage To The Springfield, Ohio, Haitian Community]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075833</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/jd-vances-yale-law-classmates-donate-money-to-undo-his-damage-to-the-springfield-ohio-haitian-community/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T21:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not all Yale Law graduates support the Republican vice-presidential candidate's debunked rumors concerning the stealing and eating of pets.
The post JD Vance’s Yale Law Classmates Donate Money To Undo His Damage To The Springfield, Ohio, Haitian Community appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smoke Show: Rounding-up Missouri’s fall cannabis launches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=852932</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/smoke-show-rounding-up-missouris-fall-cannabis-launches/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T21:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Zach Bauman The cannabis market—here, in Missouri, and around the country—is everchanging. New and old legislation are consistently ongoing, making it hard to keep up with the evolving technical moving parts within the state. While it is important for consumers to stay up to date with the current regulations, it can be complicated to dissect and overwhelming. But...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Ellett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Phillies/Mets NLDS Preview, In The Classic Shopping Mall Format]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169307</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-phillies-mets-nlds-preview-in-the-classic-shopping-mall-format"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T20:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have enjoyed multiple trips to malls together in the past, and recently hit the Wildwood boardwalk for a T-shirt report; we believe our work has built bridges between the Mets and Phillies fans communities, or at least demonstrated that members of both groups can get pizza and walk around together for a little while without trying to harm each other. And we believe, too, that we can fit a chat about this topic into that format, because baseball is like a mall, in that baseball stadiums also have escalators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Appealing Weekly Roundup]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075836</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/how-appealing-weekly-roundup-89/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T20:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The week in appellate news.
The post How Appealing Weekly Roundup appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calling All Biglaw Associates: 2024 Bonus Season Awaits]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075834</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/calling-all-biglaw-associates-2024-bonus-season-awaits/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T19:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Make your predictions and share your thoughts in our annual bonus season survey.
The post Calling All Biglaw Associates: 2024 Bonus Season Awaits appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, The Timing Of The Special Counsel Brief Is Political, And You Can Thank Chief Justice Roberts For That]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075844</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/yeah-the-timing-of-the-special-counsel-brief-is-political-and-you-can-thank-chief-justice-roberts-for-that/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T18:44:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kwitcherbitchin.
The post Yeah, The Timing Of The Special Counsel Brief Is Political, And You Can Thank Chief Justice Roberts For That appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terry Francona Just Couldn’t Resist One More Managing Gig]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169322</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/terry-francona-just-couldnt-resist-one-more-managing-gig"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T18:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday night, ESPN’s Jeff Passan broke some surprising news: The 65-year-old Francona will manage again, in Ohio but not with the Guardians.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elie Honig Makes Pitch To Become Donald Trump’s Favorite Legal Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075839</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/elie-honig-makes-pitch-to-become-donald-trumps-favorite-legal-analyst/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T18:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Move over, Turley! Take a seat, Dershowitz! Donald Trump may have a new favorite cable news law talkin' guy. 
The post Elie Honig Makes Pitch To Become Donald Trump’s Favorite Legal Analyst appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do You Know You Need A Case Management Upgrade? [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075803</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/how-do-you-know-you-need-a-case-management-upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T17:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two signs that it’s finally time for a change. 
The post How Do You Know You Need A Case Management Upgrade? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Noble Muscadine Can Replace Your Gummy Fix]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169318</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-noble-muscadine-can-replace-your-gummy-fix"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T17:23:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you find yourself involuntarily salivating for Twin Snakes or Starmix? Are you standing tippy-toe for a handful of Sour Patch Watermelons? Is there a nonstop conveyer belt of tart treats going down your gullet? There is another way. I want to open a muscadine clinic for all the Haribo loyalists in the world. Nature's gummy candy could fill the void as summer turns to fall.
The muscadine is a grape, but not the kind that populates fruit salads and Ziploc baggies. Those are mushy, easily yielding to the teeth, tossed into the mouth and eaten whole. Instead, the muscadine is an imposing orb that forces the eater to meditate upon its structure. Its skin might be a dull green with a purplish blush, or a wine-dark purple with a pinkish blush; it might have a dusty metallic sheen. It might be rough and speckled on the surface, a little leathery, and strangely taut. If that doesn't sound like a pleasant bite of fruit, that's fine—you won't actually be eating that part. Think of the muscadine as an individually packaged treat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seether, Skillet co-headline Midland for an evening of grunge nostalgia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853965</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/seether-skillet-co-headline-midland-for-an-evening-of-grunge-nostalgia/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T17:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rock band Seether’s lead vocalist Shaun Morgan performs on stage at the Midland Theatre on Oct. 2. // Photo by Lane Rozin Coheadliners Seether and Skillet rocked the house last night at The Midland for their third tour together. Seether performed several fan favorites, such as “Remedy,” “Fake It,” and “Broken,” along with new songs from their album The Surface Seems...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Details Emerge In Small Town Murder Of Judge]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075841</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/more-details-emerge-in-small-town-murder-of-judge/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T16:48:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're still learning what was behind the crime.
The post More Details Emerge In Small Town Murder Of Judge appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Cousins Had The Kirk Cousins Of Football Games On Thursday Night]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169344</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/kirk-cousins-had-the-kirk-cousins-of-football-games-on-thursday-night"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T16:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For all things that made Thursday such a gravy-balloon fight—Pete Alonso’s heroics, Terry Francona’s refusal to stay retired, the one person who didn't vote for Caitlin Clark as WNBA Rookie of the Year and their savvy choice to stay anonymous, Antonio Pierce’s suspension in exile by the NCAA—nothing beat this:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FjolnrWV7s4]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Films At The 2024 New York Film Festival]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169285</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-best-films-at-the-2024-new-york-film-festival"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T16:09:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is fall, and along with football, sweaters, and pumpkin spice latte memes, this time of year is reserved for marathon film screenings at the New York Film Festival. It's a pivotal period in which the best movies expected to arrive just before the year's Oscar cutoff get an early screening. This year's edition has amassed a roster of greatly hyped and neat surprise movies from all over the world. Some of these movies, like the sure-to-be-favorite of the extremely online Anora, the masterful Nickel Boys, Luca Guadagnino's ambitious William S. Burroughs adaptation Queer, and David Cronenberg's latest The Shrouds, deserve their own blogs as the wider public gets to see them. In the meantime, here are a collection of movies I enjoyed and wanted to say a little something about.
The Brutalist (Dir. Brady Corbet)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephonne, Lizard Brain Trust, Blackstarkids, and more of the best recent local music videos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853872</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/stephonne-lizard-brain-trust-blackstarkids-and-more-of-the-best-recent-local-music-videos/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T16:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illustration by Katelyn Betz As we move toward fall and enter Rocktober, the music videos seems to be coming fast and furious from local acts. It’s as though everyone took advantage of some free time this summer and broke out the cameras to present you with some fine visuals to match with equally-excellent sounds. Be it grinding hardcore, silky indie...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boutique Firm Beats Cravath Scale, Showering Associates With Eye-Popping Salaries Of Up To $475K]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075837</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/gjerset-lorenz-compensation-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T15:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These huge raises are an October surprise that everyone can get behind! 
The post Boutique Firm Beats Cravath Scale, Showering Associates With Eye-Popping Salaries Of Up To $475K appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ranking The Law Firms Lawyers Love [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075710</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/ranking-the-law-firms-lawyers-love/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T15:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re pleased to introduce our list of Most Desirable Firms, along with other insights from our survey of more than 700 attorneys. 
The post Ranking The Law Firms Lawyers Love appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ABOVE THE LAW AND LATERAL LINK</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LAPD Raids Medical Lab For (Nonexistent) Weed, Get Gun Stuck In An MRI Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075835</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/lapd-raids-medical-lab-for-nonexistent-weed-get-gun-stuck-in-an-mri-machine/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T14:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the keystone-kops-handling-the-Drug-War dept
The post LAPD Raids Medical Lab For (Nonexistent) Weed, Get Gun Stuck In An MRI Machine appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Techdirt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Do No Harm: Support Legislative Efforts To Combat The Adverse Drug Event Epidemic]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075817</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/10/first-do-no-harm-support-legislative-efforts-to-combat-the-adverse-drug-event-epidemic/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T14:06:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hippocratic oath can’t stop with direct patient care; the healthcare industry and its key stakeholders must address persistent public health problems systematically. We have the tools to reduce medication harm by half or more; it is long past time to make this a public health priority.
The post First Do No Harm: Support Legislative Efforts To Combat The Adverse Drug Event Epidemic appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KRISTINE ASHCRAFT via MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Folie À Poo: Boredom Is A Joker Sequel]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169294</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/folie-a-poo-boredom-is-a-joker-sequel"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T14:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Foster Wallace had a thing for boredom. He had such a thing for it that he turned it into a kind of last legacy. According to a lengthy (and pretty great) piece in The New Yorker by D.T. Max published a year after Wallace died by suicide in 2008, he left behind a third of his final novel, The Pale King, for which he had spent countless hours researching boredom. A typed note he also left behind laid out the book’s central intention: “Bliss—a-second-by-second joy and gratitude at the gift of being alive, conscious—lies on the other side of crushing, crushing boredom. Pay close attention to the most tedious thing you can find (Tax Returns, Televised Golf) and, in waves, a boredom like you’ve never known will wash over you and just about kill you. Ride these out, and it’s like stepping from black and white into color. Like water after days in the desert. Instant bliss in every atom.” 
This interest of Wallace’s has been closely connected to mindfulness, but the two things are a little different. Mindfulness is an awareness of things as they come, it is a kind of riding out, but that’s not exactly bliss you find through it so much as a kind of acceptance—which, to a person in constant distress, can no doubt, relatively speaking, feel like bliss. “Pay close attention to the most tedious thing you can find.” I didn’t realize this would be Joker: Folie à Deux.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.04.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075831</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-04-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T13:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Starbucks CEO broke labor law telling employees considering unionizing that they "can go work for another company." If you're one of those people who don't see that as an explicitly anti-union message, this is a company that refuses to use small, medium, and large so it's all about coded messages. [CNN]
* Student loan forgiveness plan back in action according to judge. [ABA Journal]
* Partner banned for 5 years after constantly pestering junior attorney. [Roll on Friday]
* Sexual assault lawsuit filed against Garth Brooks. [Reuters]
* Big fight brewing over bleeding edge tech tools employed by law enforcement... where junk science never ceases to find a buyer. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Crowell & Moring fail to get a COVID rent refund. [Law360]
* Sidley trying to corner the private equity market in London. [American Lawyer]
The post Morning Docket: 10.04.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Very Ugly Year In The Life Of A D.C. Little League]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169085</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-very-ugly-year-in-the-life-of-a-d-c-little-league"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T13:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On July 8, an all-star team from the Northwest Washington Little League (NWLL) faced off against Mamie Johnson Little League to open the D.C. city championship tournament, the first round in the global annual tournament for ballplayers 12 years old and under that ends with the Little League World Series. The game came to a halt in the middle of the sixth and final inning, when the NWLL first baseman picked up the game ball on his way to his position, prompting the home plate umpire to loudly declare that the first baseman now had to pitch. With NWLL up 6-0 and three outs away from advancing, manager Mike Klisch walked onto the field and spent several minutes conferring with the umpire. The first baseman had already pitched the first four innings before being relieved, so he was likely ineligible to return to the mound. It took a phone call from the ump to Little League headquarters to untangle the rules. 
“Is there a 24-hour line to answer questions about rules?” an NWLL mother in the crowd asked as the game resumed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drink This Now: Cocktails at Mitch e Amaro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853041</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/drink-this-now-cocktails-at-mitch-e-amaro/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T13:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[n/a margarita and white Manhattan at Mitch e Amaro // Photo by Sarah Sipple Armour Road in North KC is a destination in itself, partly due to unique places like Mitch e Amaro. The cocktail supply and amaro bar is a small but tidy shop where you can stock your home bar, sample new spirits or bitters, or grab a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lucas Erceg’s Changeup Will Take Him Far]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=447752</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/lucas-ercegs-changeup-will-take-him-far/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T13:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former minor league third baseman is pronating his way to the top of the Royals bullpen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Rosen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert DeLong shuffles us through his Playlist of Doom ahead of Madrid gig]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=837788</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/robert-delong-shuffles-us-through-his-playlist-of-doom-ahead-of-madrid-gig/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T01:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert DeLong. // Photo by Corinne Schiavone One of September’s best gifts to the dance-punk infused among us was the release of the latest album from electro-pop raconteur Robert DeLong. Playlist of Doom. His first full length since 2021, sees the wildly eccentric multi-instrumentalist feeling out the edges of what genre divisions he can stretch, while tap-dancing across new tones...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Those Threats Won’t Fly — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075816</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/those-threats-wont-fly-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T22:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since When Can You Do That?: Biglaw firm gets in trouble for their legal strategy.
Time To Pony Up: Colorado is saddled with the 303 Creative legal fees.
Keeping Things Relative: Check out the Relativity Recap!
Deleting Isn't As Permanent As You Think!: Learn from Eric Adam's & Co's blunder.
Spoiler Alert!: Anybody watching the Matlock reboot should pick up on this obvious issue.
The post Those Threats Won’t Fly — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Appreciate Our Advertisers]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075758</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/we-appreciate-our-advertisers-12/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T22:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We love working with you.
The post We Appreciate Our Advertisers appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Reitman’s Saturday Night is a self-mythologizing tome that insists upon itself. It’s still the best possible version of an unavoidable film.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853691</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/jason-reitmans-saturday-night-is-a-self-mythologizing-tome-that-insists-upon-itself-its-still-the-best-possible-version-of-an-unavoidable-film/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:54:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dedicating an entire movie to the concept of sketch comedy’s longest-running institution, Saturday Night Live, requires coming to some kind of grasp on the degree to which SNL actually exists as an institution—and who is responsible for its cultural placement. Jason Reitman’s new film Saturday Night attempts to tell the story of a historic television show and revolutionary, transgressive network experiment run...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biglaw Firm Making Major Strides In The Rankings]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075815</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-biglaw-firm-making-major-strides-in-the-rankings/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mergers can really help a firm's bottom line.
The post The Biglaw Firm Making Major Strides In The Rankings appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Players Elect Free Agency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=826317</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/11-players-elect-free-agency.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the offseason nears, a number of players elect minor league free agency each week. These players are separate from six-year MLB free agents, who’ll reach the open market five days after the conclusion of the World Series. Eligible minor leaguers can begin electing free agency as soon as the regular season wraps up. These…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is The YSL Trial Taking So Long?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075808</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/why-is-the-ysl-trial-taking-so-long/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's wrap this up!
The post Why Is The YSL Trial Taking So Long? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OHL’s Flint Firebirds Mark 10th Anniversary With Orange Third Jerseys]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82478</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/03/ohls-flint-firebirds-mark-10th-anniversary-with-orange-third-jerseys/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New third jersey takes orange — which served as an accent color until now — and puts it front and center; team's 10th anniversary logo appears on left chest]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Relaunched <em>Matlock</em> Should Be Disbarred]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075797</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/relaunched-matlock-should-be-disbarred/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T20:41:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The plot twist isn't good for real lawyers.
The post Relaunched <em>Matlock</em> Should Be Disbarred appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost In The Orc Section, With Jason Schreier]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169007</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lost-in-the-orc-section-with-jason-schreier"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T20:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the morning that our former GMG buddy and current bestselling author Jason Schreier joined us to record this week's Distraction, our producer Eric noted that his podcast feed featured three other shows on which Jason was a guest. While Jason's new book—it's called Play Nice: The Rise, Fall, And Future Of Blizzard Entertainment, and comes out next week—will in some sense sell itself due to Schreier's status as a titan in his field and Blizzard's massive following, in another and more literal sense the guy still has to go out there and sell it. All we could do was our part to help, which in this case was talk about the current New York Jets and our varied experiences of the Keith Van Horn Administration with the New Jersey Nets for 12 minutes before turning to Jason's (fascinating) book.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deleting Evidence? Think Again: Lessons From The Eric Adams Scandal]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075795</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/deleting-evidence-think-again-lessons-from-the-eric-adams-scandal/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T20:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More and more relevant data travels through phones, as this case shows.
The post Deleting Evidence? Think Again: Lessons From The Eric Adams Scandal appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hundreds of hours went into bringing spooky phantasm to life at Nightmare on Mass Street]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853702</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/hundreds-of-hours-went-into-bringing-spooky-phantasm-to-life-at-nightmare-on-mass-street/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T20:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nightmare on Mass Street. // Photo by Nick Spacek From Thursday, Oct. 3, through Sunday, Nov. 3, Lucia in downtown Lawrence is transformed into Nightmare on Mass Street—a Halloween-themed pop-up put together by their neighbors at 1313 Mockingbird Lane—the toy and collectible shop right across the street. If you’ve attended Lucia’s Christmas pop-up, Snowed Inn, in the past, you think...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recapping Relativity Fest]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075801</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/recapping-relativity-fest/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T19:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The press gathers to discuss discovery.
The post Recapping Relativity Fest appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Clutch and Rival Sons were a two-headed beast at the Uptown Wednesday night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853713</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-clutch-and-rival-sons-were-a-two-headed-beast-at-the-uptown-wednesday-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T19:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Barry Meitler Clutch and Rival Sons w/ Black Stone Cherry Uptown Theater Wednesday, Oct. 2 Hard rockers Clutch and Rival Sons brought The Two Headed Beast co-headlining tour to the Uptown Wednesday night, with blues rockers Black Stone Cherry in tow. Not only did Clutch play their 2004 album, Blast Tyrant, in full, percussion madman Mike Dillon hopped on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Meitler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: Two iconic Kansas City meal collabs, two new restaurants, and three tasty weekend festivals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853879</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-two-iconic-kansas-city-meal-collabs-two-new-restaurants-and-three-tasty-weekend-festivals/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T19:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Looking for delicious plans? Whether you want to impress a date, show your fam the best of KC, or just get out of the house, we’ve got you covered… all while supporting (mostly) local.  Here is your weekly roundup of the best food and drink offerings around Kansas City. Cheers! Something New Kaw Valley Winter Wine...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MyCase Announces New AI, Accounting, And Immigration Features, Plus Update on Smart Spend]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075760</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/10/mycase-announces-new-ai-accounting-and-immigration-features-plus-update-on-smart-spend.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T18:47:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this week, the law practice management platform MyCase rolled out three exciting product updates.
The post MyCase Announces New AI, Accounting, And Immigration Features, Plus Update on Smart Spend appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bet You’ll Always Lose]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169124</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-bet-youll-always-lose"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T18:22:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here. Drew is out this week and Ray Ratto is pinch-hitting, which is to say fouling the franchise.
The NFL and DraftKings/FanDuel have generally been pretty savvy and always been very cynical in their hostile takeover of our brains, but the Amit Patel story reminds that there is always more than one way to bleed a bettor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[False names used in testimony to Missouri House committee studying immigrant crime]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853991</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/false-names-used-in-testimony-to-missouri-house-committee-studying-immigrant-crime/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T18:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State Rep. Lane Roberts, a Republican from Joplin, is chairman of the House Special Interim Committee on Illegal Immigrant Crime. He is shown during a Jan. 18 public hearing on a bill he introduced (Tim Bommel/Missouri House Communications) A Columbia woman charged with using multiple aliases to accuse restaurant competitors of criminal activity also used fake names for testimony to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rudi Keller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colorado Loses Again, Has To Pay 303 Creative’s Legal Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075802</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/colorado-loses-again-has-to-pay-303-creatives-legal-fees/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T18:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shame they can't "Free Speech" their way out of this tab. 
The post Colorado Loses Again, Has To Pay 303 Creative’s Legal Fees appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Temwa Chawinga save Current from dropping a match against Gotham FC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853871</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-temwa-chawinga-save-current-from-dropping-a-match-against-gotham-fc/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T17:56:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KC Current versus Gotham FC on Saturday, Sept. 28. // Photo by Jordan Hirsekorn The Kansas City Current faced off against Gotham FC last Saturday, Sept. 28, resulting in a 1-1 draw between the two clubs. The Current dropped a goal early in minute 23 when Alana Cook scored an own goal—Don’t worry, it happens, even to the best. Just...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Hirsekorn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off Almost Immediately Regrets Returning For Cake Week]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169076</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/not-so-great-defector-bake-off-almost-immediately-regrets-returning-for-cake-week"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T17:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The challenge this week was to make Paul Hollywood's recipe for eight miniature Battenberg cakes, filled with freshly made jam and draped in a tight-fitting marzipan outer coat. We were tasked with completing this technical challenge with no instructions whatsoever, just a list of ingredients. What is a Battenberg, you ask? I have been trying to tell you this the entire time: We don't know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Penn State Unveils New Nittany Lion Mascot Logos, Signature Mark]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82473</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/03/penn-state-unveils-new-nittany-lion-mascot-logos-signature-mark/college/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T17:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an effort to modernize its iconic brand, the Penn State athletic department recently released new logos and signature mark for its beloved mascot, the Nittany Lion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Go Ahead And Bet On The 2024 Election]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075800</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/you-can-go-ahead-and-bet-on-the-2024-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T17:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Betting on democracy? What's more American than that?
The post You Can Go Ahead And Bet On The 2024 Election appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Well Well Well, Not So Bad To Have A First-Round Bye Now, Is It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169213</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/well-well-well-not-so-bad-to-have-a-first-round-bye-now-is-it"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T17:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How fast the mighty fall, and timely, too. The Houston Astros' seven-year streak of reaching the ALCS ended the same night that the Atlanta Braves' six-year streak of reaching the NLDS did the same, and each in an unceremonious sweep—at least, as much as a sweep can be a sweep in a three-game postseason series. At the very least, the Milwaukee Brewers spared us an extra day without any postseason baseball by forcing a Game 3 against the Mets.
No sensible person will cry about these developments. The Astros are the Astros, and the Braves were a dead team walking even entering the playoffs; better they just be put out of their misery. Other than the overarching sentiment towards both teams' failings, conflating them is a bit misleading. The postseason record that the Astros strung together might be distasteful, but has to garner some level of respect: No other team has managed it. Meanwhile, "reaching the NLDS" can sound impressive when phrased that way, but even in the expanded playoffs, half the teams that reach a Divisional Series do it through the regular season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They Let The Cats Get Hot!!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169222</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/they-let-the-cats-get-hot"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T16:44:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's the absolute best kind of hit? A grand slam, you might say. I suppose, yeah, objectively, that's right. But after Andy Ibáñez knocked a bases-loaded double into the left corner pocket in the eighth inning of a tied Tigers-Astros game on Wednesday, Tigers fans might disagree. With the bases-clearing two-bagger, they received beat after beat of great news: the suspenseful declaration that the ball was fair, and then the dramatic build of an incrementally larger lead. "One run scores! ... Two runs score! ... Evvvvvverybody scores!" It was as good as it gets, and so was the rest of the afternoon for the Detroiters, as Houston went 1-2-3, 1-2-3 to eject themselves from the postseason barely 24 hours after it began.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b8sc5XS5hgw]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoCounsel Drafting: An AI-Powered Game Changer For Legal Professionals [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075304</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/cocounsel-drafting-an-ai-powered-game-changer-for-legal-professionals/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T16:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leverage AI for drafting documents.
The post CoCounsel Drafting: An AI-Powered Game Changer For Legal Professionals appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Legal Tech Publishing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analog Adventures: The Get Up Kids, Sylvester, film scores, and more new vinyl releases for September 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853591</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/analog-adventures-the-get-up-kids-sylvester-film-scores-and-more-new-vinyl-releases-for-september-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T16:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Analog Adventures, where we run down the latest stacks of wax to hit our mailbox. Reissues, new releases, and more are all on the turntable as we spin these records. Diana Ross & The Supremes Love Child The Temptations Meet the Temptations Marvin Gaye In the Groove (Elemental Music) In this triptych of Motown reissues from Elemental Music,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent Law Firm Hit With Lawsuit Over Alleged Litigation Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075791</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/prominent-law-firm-hit-with-lawsuit-over-alleged-litigation-tactics/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T15:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm has vowed to fight the case.
The post Prominent Law Firm Hit With Lawsuit Over Alleged Litigation Tactics appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering Legal Operations: 3 Unexpected Lessons For Success In A Dynamic Field]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074560</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/mastering-legal-operations-3-unexpected-lessons-for-success-in-a-dynamic-field/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Becker's path is a testament to the evolution of the legal field and offers valuable lessons.
The post Mastering Legal Operations: 3 Unexpected Lessons For Success In A Dynamic Field appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga V. Mack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Fantasy Football Means To Incarcerated Managers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169051</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-fantasy-football-means-to-incarcerated-managers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:45:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was produced in partnership with Empowerment Avenue, a program that supports incarcerated writers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antoine Davis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forging A Noncompete Policy That Works for Healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075762</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/10/forging-a-noncompete-policy-that-works-for-healthcare/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A more measured approach to noncompete clauses can be fair to physicians and provider organizations, and also serve patients better. Here are four elements for a policy on noncompetes that will work for healthcare.
The post Forging A Noncompete Policy That Works for Healthcare appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasen Gundersen via Medcity News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surely, Erik Ten Hag Can’t Survive Yet Another Horrendous Start … Right?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169029</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/surely-erik-ten-hag-cant-survive-yet-another-horrendous-start-right"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T13:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here we are again. For most of Erik ten Hag's tenure at Manchester United, England's most storied club has been reeling. Though his first season, the 2022-23 edition, was a moderate success—third place in the Premier League and a League Cup trophy, after a 2021-22 season in which the club finished sixth with no trophies—it's been downhill since. Instead of building on that return to decency, last season United finished eighth in the league and last in its Champions League group, looking dire for most of the campaign.
The Dutch manager was almost immediately on the hot seat last season, losing four out of seven matches in the first six weeks, and it didn't get much better as the season went on. A 4-0 loss to Crystal Palace in early May seemed to signal the end of his time at Old Trafford, but a shock FA Cup final victory over Manchester City bought him enough of a reprieve to try again this season. A spendy summer followed that victory, and if not a return to title contention, the United faithful and brass probably expected a solid push for the top four. If the first six weeks of this season are to be believed, however, they're in for more of the same, which has to have put Ten Hag on the brink of the unemployment line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The WNBA’s Season Of Clash Is Big Business For The Permanently Aggrieved]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168409</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-wnbas-season-of-clash-is-big-business-for-the-permanently-aggrieved"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T13:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A woman in the stands at last week's playoff game between the Indiana Fever and Connecticut Sun wore a shirt that read “BAN NAILS.” She had evidently put some thought into this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.03.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075792</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-03-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T13:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Latest redacted filing in Trump case paints an overwhelming portrait of criminality that the Supreme Court will make up even more new rules to squelch. [New Republic]
* Judge who handcuffed innocent teen is back presiding over cases. [ABA Journal]
* Eight states will vote on banning non-citizens from voting... which is already illegal. [Reuters]
* UnitedHealth sues the government after its ratings dropped based on bad customer service. A health insurer paying lawyers to file a lawsuit rather than fix customer service is the most American health industry outcome. [Bloomberg Law News]
* SEC Enforcement director moving on. [Law360]
* Mansfield certifications released. [American Lawyer]
The post Morning Docket: 10.03.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Witt, Royals Dash to ALDS]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=447768</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/witt-royals-dash-to-alds/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T02:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For all his other attributes, it’s important to remember that Bobby Witt Jr. is freakishly fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Baumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome To The Fold, Partner! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075782</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/welcome-to-the-fold-partner-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T23:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Firm Welcomes Massive Partner Class: Wonder how much of that comes with equity?
Is That Who I Think It Is?: Steven Chung looks at the legal dimension to voice acting and AI.
Mind Your Digital Footprint!: Better yet, get Page Vault to do it for you.
YSL Is Still Giving WTF: Here's a compilation.
Get Your Outlines Ready: California is back on path to replace the bar.
The post Welcome To The Fold, Partner! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overseeing The Eric Adams Corruption Case]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075737</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/overseeing-the-eric-adams-corruption-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T23:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The case is sure to garner a lot of attention.
The post Overseeing The Eric Adams Corruption Case appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California Bar Takes Steps To Continue With Its Bar Replacement]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075775</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/california-bar-takes-steps-to-continue-with-its-bar-replacement/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T22:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's get this process rolling!
The post California Bar Takes Steps To Continue With Its Bar Replacement appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Already Robust Law Firm Merger Activity To Reach ‘Higher Level’ In 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075740</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/already-robust-law-firm-merger-activity-to-reach-higher-level-in-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T21:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does your law firm have the urge to merge? Join the club!
The post Already Robust Law Firm Merger Activity To Reach ‘Higher Level’ In 2025 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Judas Priest went hellbent for leather at Cable Dahmer Arena Tuesday night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853361</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-judas-priest-went-hellbent-for-leather-at-cable-dahmer-arena-tuesday-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T21:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Judas Priest // Photo by Mike Dotson Judas Priest w/ Sabaton Cable Dahmer Arena Tuesday, Oct. 1 Touring in support of their latest album, Invincible Shield, British metal legends Judas Priest brought the fire when they played Cable Dahmer Arena on Monday night and proved that they’re still a vital presence after more than five decades of making music. Swedish...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Dotson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Devin Nunes Defamation Juggernaut Runs Aground]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075757</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-devin-nunes-defamation-juggernaut-runs-aground/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T20:43:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you sue, so shall ye reap.
The post The Devin Nunes Defamation Juggernaut Runs Aground appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carlos Alcaraz Is Most Dangerous When He’s Cornered]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169053</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/carlos-alcaraz-is-most-dangerous-when-hes-cornered"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T20:23:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the China Open final, the best player in men's tennis faced the best player in men's tennis. It just depends on what you value.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YSL RICO Trial So Bad Judge Needs A Breather & More!]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075751</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/ysl-rico-trial-so-bad-judge-needs-a-breather-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T20:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each day we move closer and closer to a mistrial. 
The post YSL RICO Trial So Bad Judge Needs A Breather & More! appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Wild Rivers bring Never Better to The Truman]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853367</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-wild-rivers-bring-never-better-to-the-truman/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T20:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wild Rivers. // photo by Tommy Vean Wild Rivers w/ Lily Meola The Truman Saturday, Sept. 28 Saturday night, Sept. 28, Canadian indie folkers Wild Rivers played The Truman ahead of the release of their new album, Better Now, due out Oct. 18. That record serves as a companion to their latest, Never Better, released this past July, and songs from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tommy Vean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clients Are More Likely To Stiff Lawyers On Their Last Invoice]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075692</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/clients-are-more-likely-to-stiff-lawyers-on-their-last-invoice/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T19:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some clients have a blind spot about how attorneys want to be paid promptly for work performed.
The post Clients Are More Likely To Stiff Lawyers On Their Last Invoice appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Rothman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rainbow Kitten Surprise rolled through Starlight last Friday on their Love Hate Music Box Tour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853356</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/rainbow-kitten-surprise-rolled-through-starlight-last-friday-on-their-love-hate-music-box-tour/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T19:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rainbow Kitten Surprise // Photo by Zoe Strohm Rainbow Kitten Surprise w/ Ethan Regan Starlight Theatre Friday, Sept. 27 Rainbow Kitten Surprise sold out Starlight Theatre on last Friday’s stop of the Love Hate Music Box tour, bringing new songs and friends since their last Kansas City stop in 2022. The alt rock band hailing out of Boone, North Carolina,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zoe Strohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JD Vance Found A Debate He Couldn’t Win]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169079</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jd-vance-found-a-debate-he-couldnt-win"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter, examining the apocalyptic politics and coverage of Campaign 2024.
"Look," JD Vance said, during the final round of questioning in Tuesday night's vice-presidential debate. "What President Trump has said is that there were problems in 2020. And my own belief is that we should fight about those issues, debate those issues peacefully in the public square."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collecting All The Embarrassing Nonsense Your Adversaries (Or Employees) Put Online]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075722</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/collecting-all-the-embarrassing-nonsense-your-adversaries-or-employees-put-online/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T18:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a lot more online these days. Lawyers need to get at it.
The post Collecting All The Embarrassing Nonsense Your Adversaries (Or Employees) Put Online appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence Can Make Iconic Characters Immortal But It Can Create Legal Problems For Studios And Actors]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075285</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/artificial-intelligence-can-make-iconic-characters-immortal-but-it-can-create-legal-problems-for-studios-and-actors/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Earl Jones has entered the cornfield after completing the circle of life. But Darth Vader’s voice is still available in this galaxy thanks to AI.
The post Artificial Intelligence Can Make Iconic Characters Immortal But It Can Create Legal Problems For Studios And Actors appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Chung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Was A Time When Everyone Cared How Pete Rose Smelled]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168945</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/there-was-a-time-when-everyone-cared-how-pete-rose-smelled"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:36:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year is 1979. The Phillies are playing the Reds. Pete Rose tries to steal second, and the throw arrives late. The ump signals safe, and instead of arguing the call Cincinnati second baseman Joe Morgan just says: “It’s Pete Rose of the Philadelphia Phillies!” Never mind that Morgan and Rose were teammates for six years on the Reds. Never mind that Rose would’ve been announced earlier as part of the starting lineup, or that he would’ve made it to first base in some way before taking second. It's a commercial, so you have to cut it some slack.
Still, it stands to reason that Joe Morgan would not be particularly shocked to see Rose at second. But he also wasn’t paying all that close attention if he only noticed Rose when the two were right next to each other. The scenario raises a lot of questions, but not necessarily the one that Morgan asks: “And what kind of aftershave you using?”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantastic Fest 2024: Queens of Drama brings the tunes, the camp and the pathos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853334</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/fantastic-fest-2024-queens-of-drama-brings-the-tunes-the-camp-and-the-pathos/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Fantastic Fest This is part of our coverage from Fantastic Fest 2024 in Austin, TX where genre films are debuting before they get wider release. Check out all of our coverage here.  Imagine if Kaboom-era Gregg Araki made Velvet Goldmine, but set in the early aughts and focused on pop divas. If that sounds like your jam, the brazenly queer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Torres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diamond Sports Group Planning To Cut Ties With 11 MLB Clubs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=826253</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/diamond-sports-group-planning-to-cut-ties-with-11-mlb-clubs.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:24:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diamond Sports Group said in court today that it plans to broadcast just one MLB club next year, the Braves, per reporting from Evan Drellich of The Athletic. The company, which owns the Bally Sports Networks, also had deals with the Reds, Tigers, Royals, Angels, Marlins, Brewers, Cardinals and Rays but plans on walking away…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Adams Must Really Hope Supreme Court Is Serious About Blowing Up Bribery Laws]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075745</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/eric-adams-must-really-hope-supreme-court-is-serious-about-blowing-up-bribery-laws/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The majority of the Supreme Court keeps diluting bribery laws and Eric Adams had best hope they aren't done yet.
The post Eric Adams Must Really Hope Supreme Court Is Serious About Blowing Up Bribery Laws appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s Trending Up And Trending Down In The ‘Industry’ Season 3 Finale]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168947</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/whos-trending-up-and-trending-down-in-the-industry-season-3-finale"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T16:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And with that, episodes 7 and 8 bring Industry's roller-coaster third season to a close. These past 8 weeks may have flown by, but it also feels like we've just finished running a marathon and are in desperate need of an IV drip of fluids straight into the bloodstream. Season 3 of Industry was exhausting, operatic, and stuffed to the gills with action, plot, degradation, sex, and violence. And if the comments on these recaps are any indicator, it has also been a divisive season, with people torn on its pacing, its ratcheted-up storylines episode to episode, and its sensory overload, which undermined the impact of its most catastrophic and exhilarating moments. Season 3 was not interested in patience, letting things breathe, or drawing things out. That worked both to and against the show's …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Quiet Luxury Gets Loud]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168928</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/when-quiet-luxury-gets-loud"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T16:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do two former child stars build a billion dollar luxury fashion brand? By selling the very things money can’t buy.
If Mary-Kate and Ashley Olsen’s brand, The Row, has permeated the imaginations of ordinary people who can’t afford $1,000 sandals, it may be because it’s become synonymous with the abysmal internet brainrot trend “quiet luxury,” a backlash to the labelmania that defined much of 2010s fashion, and perhaps an encapsulation of increasing class consciousness in the years coming out of the pandemic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World’s Richest Biglaw Firm Announces Another HUGE Partnership Class]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075741</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/worlds-richest-biglaw-firm-announces-another-huge-partnership-class/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T16:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With 200 new partners, how many of them will enter the firm's equity ranks?
The post World’s Richest Biglaw Firm Announces Another HUGE Partnership Class appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Main Street Saints’ lone full-length album gets wax treatment for 25th anniversary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850647</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/just-like-heaven-main-street-saints-lone-full-length-album-gets-wax-treatment-for-25th-anniversary/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Main Street Saints In the ‘90s, few genres of music were as omnipresent in Kansas City as punk rock. Thanks to places like Fred P. Ott’s, The Pub (now The Brick), and Davey’s Uptown, along with all-ages venues like The FuseBox, The Daily Grind, El Torreon, and Gee Coffee, you could step out to hear loud, fast,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Borussia Dortmund’s Newest Star Is Born]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169005</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/borussia-dortmunds-newest-star-is-born"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Borussia Dortmund is famous for something, it is for being the most consistent, and so far the most successful, challenger to Bayern Munich's Bundesliga supremacy in the 21st century. If Borussia Dortmund is famous for something else, it is for being Europe's premier finishing school for young talents destined for bigger and better salaries and transfer fees upon graduation. Here's a short list of players who have passed through Dortmund in the last 15 years or so, in no particular order: Robert Lewandowski, Ousmane Dembélé, Jadon Sancho, Ilkay Gündogan, Mario Götze, Christian Pulisic, Jude Bellingham, Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang, Erling Haaland, Mats Hummels ... Ok, maybe the list isn't so short, and not all of those players starred upon leaving Dortmund. However, the impressive history of talent detection and refinement is there, and that list is about to get a little bit longer, now that Karim Adeyemi appears to be hitting a new level of excellence.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lv1mY5JAzyo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gen AI + Law Firm Data: Gaining A Key Competitive Edge [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075723</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/gen-ai-law-firm-data-gaining-a-key-competitive-edge/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join this webinar on October 30th to learn how your firm can deliver better client service, improve case outcomes, and empower its teams. 
The post Gen AI + Law Firm Data: Gaining A Key Competitive Edge appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Litera and Above The Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create A Fulfilling Law Practice]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075735</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/how-to-create-a-fulfilling-law-practice/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These lawyers align their skills with their passions.
The post How To Create A Fulfilling Law Practice appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: A taste of summer with no rain (WED-10/2)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3682930</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-a-taste-of-summer-with-no-rain-wed-10-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a crisp morning in the area with lows down into the lower 40s with mid 30s is some of the outlying areas, and if there was some frost out there somewhere, I wouldn't have been shocked. This cooler weather will moderate today thanks to south winds this afternoon and tomorrow looks to be [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personalize Patient Care With Confidence Through Efficient, HIPAA-Compliant Data Usage]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075738</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/09/personalize-patient-care-with-confidence-through-efficient-hipaa-compliant-data-usage/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:03:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Responsible procurement and handling of data and digital marketing insights by hospitals can generate useful information to improve patient wellness and operational efficiency without compromising compliance.
The post Personalize Patient Care With Confidence Through Efficient, HIPAA-Compliant Data Usage appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WENDY ERTERR via MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fat Bear Week Delayed By Bear Killing Bear]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168970</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/fat-bear-week-delayed-by-bear-killing-bear"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T13:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My first pets were a pair of hamsters, sisters from the same litter. I was surprised that such tiny little brains could hold such distinct personalities: Harley, golden and white, was more athletic, more aloof, notably smarter, happy to play by herself; Yankee, a chubby cream-colored meatball, craved human touch—she'd run to the door at the top of her cage and stare up, unable to see much with a hamster's terrible eyesight but secure in the knowledge that I'd soon come to scoop her up. All she wanted was to be held and petted. She was the biggest little sweetie on god's green Earth. The sisters got along grandly in their shared, three-tiered cage. And then one day out of nowhere, and for reasons I never understood and I suspect they didn't either, Yankee starting beating the shit out of Harley every time they'd cross paths—biting her, scratching her, screaming with fury at the mere sight of her previously beloved sister. We separated them, giving each their own cage, and they each lived out their long happy hamster lives in solitary. But it was a good lesson for young me. No matter how fuzzy or friend-shaped, creatures are not simply furry people and can't be viewed or treated as such. Animals are animals.
Grizzly bears, despite looking an awful lot like thousand-pound hamsters, are ur-predators. They are secretive, unknowable, capable of tremendous acts of strength and violence. Our ancestors knew this: The word "bear" was originally a euphemism, invented by our Germanic-speaking predecessors afraid to use the animal's true name, made taboo out of a superstitious fear that speaking it would cause them to meet one. Our Enlightenment-era men of science were no less intimidated—it was designated Ursus arctos horribilis for a reason. This week in Alaska, nature provided a morbid and useful reminder that bears are bears, with all that entails.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.02.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075742</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-02-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T13:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Former Jaguars financial administrator in jail for embezzling millions in team funds for his own gambling suing FanDuel accusing the app of exploiting his addiction. Somewhere Diddy is preparing a filing against baby oil manufacturers. [Law360]
* Fifth Circuit stops Amazon case to consider whether the NLRB has secretly been unconstitutional for the last 90 years and they're the first ones to notice. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Record labels suing the internet archive over old recordings, draping themselves in concern for the rights of the artists hoping no one ever notices that the labels routinely and aggressively rip off artists, especially artists of color. [Rolling Stone]
* California plan to break with the NCBE monopoly sent to the state supreme court. [ABA Journal]
* Lawyers often victims of workplace bullying. [Reuters]
* Profile of the law school dean who helped push Trump's election denial efforts. [The Intercept]
* New tax hypo just dropped: "it's not a vacant commercial property, it's a snail farm." [Lowering the Bar]
The post Morning Docket: 10.02.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Shambling, Half-Dead Braves Have Gone Far Enough]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168968</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-shambling-half-dead-braves-have-gone-far-enough"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T13:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Atlanta Braves will play their second elimination game in three days Wednesday afternoon, when Max Fried leads them against Joe Musgrove of the San Diego Padres in Game 2 of their National League Wild Card series. With all due respect to Atlanta's handful of healthy players, the Braves are not wanted here! Four of their, what, six best players are out; the team only nosed into the Wild Card at all because of a preposterous first-in-history gap-day doubleheader, where everyone knew going in that both teams could advance with a split. It's hard to imagine a less legitimate playoff berth than one earned in the second of these two games, after your opponent has already lost all motivation.
It's clear that God has seen enough of the Braves. Three road teams won on Tuesday, including the even more road weary New York Mets, who haven't played a game at home since Sept. 22 and who failed America by going hangover mode in Monday's late game and allowing Atlanta to shamble onwards. The Braves, meanwhile, advanced one single runner to third base in nine innings Tuesday night, struck out 15 times, and were ruthlessly blanked by playoff debutante Michael King and a pair of Padres relievers. For lack of anything even vaguely resembling a suitable alternative, Atlanta manager Brian Snitker handed the ball to A.J. Smith-Shawver, a 21-year-old prospect with fewer than 30 total innings of work in the majors, who threw 87 pitches for the big club this year, all of them back on May 23. Smith-Shawver watched his team squander a first-inning scoring opportunity, then took the mound in a Braves uniform for just the second time in 2024. Seven pitches later, this happened:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Black Feast Week and flavor-packed aguachiles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853320</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-black-feast-week-and-flavor-packed-aguachiles/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T13:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matties Food // Photo By Tiffany Watts Mattie’s Foods for Black Feast Week As Kansas City celebrates its first-ever inaugural KC Black Feast Week, hosted by The Kansas City Defender, there’s no better time to spotlight the city’s extraordinary Black culinary talent. From October 1st to October 14th, Black Feast Week highlights nearly every major Black-owned restaurant in Kansas City....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>