<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-05-16T10:18:53.270Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[READER POLL ONLINE: RELEASE the Hydra Blogs of Your Choosing]]></title>
        <id>682636ab37814f00018880a2</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-321/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-16T00:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[READER POLL: RELEASE the Hydra Blogs of Your Choosing]]></title>
        <id>682652c537814f00018880ea</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/choose-your-favorite-flaming-hydra-blogs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T23:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Hydra readers, we ask for your help in selecting five new blogs to release into the wild, in order that new readers may get a good sense of what Flaming Hydra is all about. This list is long, but not long enough, because we were forced by sheer exhaustion]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Mitchell’ Is Part Of Joe Don Baker’s Legacy, For Better Or Worse]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189824</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mitchell-is-part-of-joe-don-bakers-legacy-for-better-or-worse"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T19:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“When Mitchell finally reaches the tube,” Boston Globe movie critic Kevin Kelly wrote in his review of the 1975 film, “you can alleviate its unending boredom by looking forward to the commercials.” Kelly was right that the movie needed an upgrade, and that TV would provide it. But it turns out there was a better way to alleviate the unending boredom of Mitchell.
The movie, in which Baker plays the slobbish cop who gives the film its name, is shown in one of the funniest episodes of Mystery Science Theater 3000. In Joel Hodgson’s last episode, he and the bots absolutely ravage Mitchell star Joe Don Baker. They mock his weight. They howl in disgust at a sex scene. “He looks like a middle-aged Chucky.” Tom Servo says. The phrase “chubby blue line” is spoken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hands Like Small Turkeys, With Brandy Jensen]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189736</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/hands-like-small-turkeys-with-brandy-jensen"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T19:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lately we have been on a little run of decently substantive episodes of The Distraction. Not all of them are substantive in a classically Substantive way: Last week's episode was about online and offline media, but about a quarter of it was about a truly horrifying regional sandwich; the NBA playoffs and NFL draft episodes were about the NBA playoffs and the NFL draft, but were about those things in a more focused and informed way than some of our previous installments. This week, in welcoming Culture Editor Brandy Jensen to the podcast, we managed to keep the quality streak going while also bringing back the dumb stuff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swole Woman Casey Johnston Has Written A Swole Book]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189545</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/swole-woman-casey-johnston-has-written-a-swole-book"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T19:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is nothing I find more annoying than the fact that exercise makes your brain feel better. Every time I am grumpy and miserable and depressed but still drag my ass off the couch and to the gym, I am filled with annoyance after I'm done. Why does picking up a few heavy things and setting them back down make me feel so much better? Why can't I be rewarded for simply lying down on my couch and watching television? Why do brains work like this? What is the point in having a body?
These questions haunt me, so I was thrilled to read Casey Johnston's new book A Physical Education: How I Escaped Diet Culture and Gained the Power of Lifting. Johnston is a beloved writer for the swole community. She has written about lifting weights for almost a decade, founded a program for people trying to learn how to lift, and now has written the book on why it all matters. She encouraged me almost five years ago to begin lifting, and it quickly became the only form of exercise that did not make me so miserable I wanted to quit it immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Idiot Chatbot Goes Full Boer]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189791</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/elon-musks-idiot-chatbot-goes-full-boer"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T18:38:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that there's a white genocide happening in South Africa? Me neither. We can give ourselves a break, I think: This is less a matter of gross ignorance than it is a simple epistemological deal. Namely, we can't really know that there's a white genocide happening in South Africa, because there isn't one. A person certainly could, however, think or believe that there's a white genocide happening in South Africa. Elon Musk's chatbot spent much of Wednesday working to accomplish that, with all the uncanny ineptitude implied by the terms "Elon Musk" and "chatbot" and "Elon Musk's chatbot."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BFT Podcast: The Machines Won't Play Elon Musk's Bad-Faith Game]]></title>
        <id>68262c5c7bab250001b2eaa9</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/bft-podcast-the-machines-wont-play-elon-musks-bad-faith-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T18:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grok isn't playing ball with Musk's effort to convince people that white South Africans are a persecuted minority]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Shrouds’ Is David Cronenberg’s Typically Prescient Epitaph For Our Present And His Career]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189768</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-shrouds-is-david-cronenbergs-typically-prescient-epitaph-for-our-present-and-his-career"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T17:31:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aisles of locked plastic cabinets in drug stores. Audiologists in the UK whose videos of cleaning skin and wax out of patients’ ears amass millions of views. James Woods, who starred in Videodrome as a man who was sent hallucinations by a CIA cutout, claimed a photo of a crowd gathered to see Kamala Harris was AI generated because one man had a very long neck. While none of these things have appeared in David Cronenberg’s films, they’re all reminiscent of the darkly comic, clinical, technoskeptic essence of his work. Cronenberg never set out to predict the future, but here we are, 26 years after eXistenZ—a film that clocked the immersiveness of video games and the fanaticism of gamer culture—living through the inevitable perils of the technological extension of the human mind and body. His…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Violet Lucca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Picture Of Dorian Gray’ Is A Digital Monument To Vanity]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189782</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-picture-of-dorian-gray-is-a-digital-monument-to-vanity"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T17:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the first 20 or so minutes of The Picture Of Dorian Gray, the Broadway adaptation of the Oscar Wilde novel as a one-woman show starring Sarah Snook, the production asks a genuinely disturbing question: "What if you were watching TV, instead?" At the top of the hour, Snook enters the stage without fanfare, surrounded by crew members—really, they should be considered performers, too—who will spend the next two hours filming her with compact cameras. She takes a seat behind the gigantic vertical screen in the middle of the stage, looks into a lens, and speaks to the audience two-dimensionally.
What follows is a by-heart reading of the start of the book—I'm pretty sure, at least, because I've never read it. Snook does the narration and the dialogue, and then the scope expands, but only sort of. Soon, Snook is costumed as Dorian—one of many characters she plays—and moves around the stage giving, basically, just that performance, as the young man poses for and then desperately admires a painting of himself. Filling out the show is prerecorded work: other Snook performances superimposed on screen or piped in as audio. In a dinner party sequence, for example, she performs live as Lord Henry while portraying the guests—all with their own elaborate costumes and ways of speaking—on the Broadway Jumbotron. In an adaptation of a story about vanity, the actress is playing with nobody but larger-than-life versions of herself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Friendship’ Can’t Sustain The Relationship]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189275</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/friendship-cant-sustain-the-relationship"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T15:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would you be into watching a 100-minute I Think You Should Leave sketch? Because that’s basically what Friendship is—a Tim Robinson sketch stretched out way past its welcome. Robinson stars as Craig Waterman, that familiar everyman that Robinson is so good at portraying, a middle-of-the-road dude in literal beige who basically becomes undone by his own squareness. The guest star in this one is Paul Rudd, as hammy as ever as Austin Carmichael, the cheesy-unless-you-don't-know-what's-cheesy weatherman with the hidden hairpiece, the loud band, and the cowboy-kerchief attitude. The premise? Craig seems incapable of making friends while everyone around him—from the jerks at work who can't stop talking about the new Marvel movie he hasn't seen yet, to his wife (straight woman Kate Mara) and son …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toronto Once Again Wins The Stanley Cup Of Angst]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189779</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/toronto-once-again-wins-the-stanley-cup-of-angst"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T14:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am, as a general rule, resistant to blaming a losing team for some sort of moral failing: bowing under pressure or not caring enough or whatever. Largely this is because it ignores the performance of the winning team, and most of the time sports really are as simple as one team playing better than the other. So it is with the skeptic's eye (but still the hater's temptation) that I find myself loath to credit the Maple Leafs' ongoing collapse, from up 2-0 on the Panthers to down 3-2 after a 6-1 shellacking Wednesday night, to some sort of inherent Leafiness. Do I really believe that the tension is too much for successful pro athletes like Auston Matthews, still goalless in the series? Is the second round that much more stressful than the first, in which they seemed fine? Would the most competitive people on Earth really lay a Game 5 stinker because they just happened to not feel like giving full effort that day?
That is for Canadian sports media to discuss all summer, and they will, and it will get very stupid. But I do find my stony resolve cracking a bit when I see what the Leafs themselves had to say about a game in which they allowed six unanswered. "We all need to be better, me included," head coach Craig Berube said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, You’re Outta Here!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189766</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/no-youre-outta-here"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diamondbacks manager Torey Lovullo is real good at getting ejected from a baseball game. A fellow ought to get his dang money's worth; there are too many managers out there—sleepy, retiring types, or the constitutionally frail—who do not or cannot make a truly cinematic moment out of an argument. Fans and players alike appreciate a manager who kicks huge ass. At least one Washington National, for example, is reportedly chafing at the recent passivity of the team's cardiovascularly challenged head guy. Lovullo will not leave his men wanting: When he marches out there, odds are someone is going to take a reaming for the ages. 
And Lovullo, God bless him, doesn't need much of an invitation. Only seven active managers have been tossed more; Lovullo, in his ninth season as a manager, is already in the top-100 all-time, with 22 career ejections. By way of comparison, it took Hall-of-Famer Hughie Jennings 16 seasons to get to 24. Lovullo may not have Bobby Cox's prodigious, historic pace—a fantastic 162 career ejections in 30 seasons—but then this is a different era. As broken down in a 2019 New York Times story, the manager meltdown is considered somewhat déclassé in the modern game. "I tell [today's umpires], 'You guys are lucky you weren’t around 20, 30 years ago," says Reds manager Terry Francona, who has been run just 51 times in 23-plus major-league seasons. Giving a volcanic helping of The Business to those antagonists in the blue shirts was, in earlier times, considered an important part of the job, not just to address umpire performance but to inspire one's own team out of mid-summer ennui.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How The Japanese-American Basketball Leagues Built Natalie Nakase]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189585</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-the-japanese-american-basketball-leagues-built-natalie-nakase"/>
        <updated>2025-05-15T13:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Natalie Nakase is many things: a 5-foot-2 former walk-on who became the starting point guard for UCLA, a WNBA champion as an assistant coach with the Las Vegas Aces, and “a unifier,” as Golden State Valkyries general manager Ohemaa Nyanin put it in an introductory presser last October. When the Valkyries play their season opener in San Francisco this Friday, Nakase will add to that list, becoming the first head coach of the franchise, and the first Asian-American head coach in WNBA history. She is a third-generation Japanese American from Southern California, raised by a basketball-loving father who kept his daughters in the gym the way some parents bring their children to church.
Basketball has been an integral part of Japanese-American communities on the West Coast since the early 1900s. Shaped by forcible internment during World War II, Japanese-American basketball leagues (colloquially known as the “JA leagues”) flourished for decades as a way to cultivate second- and third-generation talent, and still operate to this day. The use of digital archives dating back to the 1940s, as well as interviews with relatives and members of the JA league community, can demonstrate how the story of Natalie Nakase is the story of Japanese-American basketball. Go through her family history, and you’ll find competition and resilience that transcends the sport itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maya Goldberg-Safir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Birds and bees / Political potency]]></title>
        <id>6823e2b885d28b00015c2431</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-320/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A stroll among the flowers with Emily Flake; a scandal explained by Jídé Salawu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pollinator Gardens Explained]]></title>
        <id>6824c55e37814f0001886b72</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/pollinator-gardens-explained/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Flake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sign of the Father]]></title>
        <id>6823e1eb85d28b00015c241d</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/sign-of-the-father/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T19:18:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, on March 5, Nigerian senator Natasha H. Akpoti-Uduaghan—one of only four women in the 109-member senate—submitted a petition alleging sexual misconduct against Senate President Godswill Akpabio, an act that resulted in her suspension for “misconduct” the following day, and, eventually,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jídé Salawu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nikola Jokic Is Outnumbered]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189689</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nikola-jokic-is-outnumbered"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T18:54:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After his Oklahoma City Thunder finished up a spectacular Game 5 win against the Denver Nuggets, Shai Gilgeous-Alexander fielded a question about the game's best player: Nikola Jokic. The reigning MVP put together a near-perfect game against the presumptive MVP's team, with 44 points on 25 shots, 15 rebounds, and five assists that could have been thrice as many if any single one of his teammates could have hit one single shot after halftime. "It's a team sport," Gilgeous-Alexander said. "No one guy can do it." In what was comfortably the best game of the whole second round, and close to the best game of the 2025 NBA playoffs, one guy very nearly did it. That he could not answers some pretty important questions.
Jokic had not had a good series before Game 5. Apart from his Game 1 masterclass, Oklahoma City has been defending the hell out him, keeping Isaiah Hartenstein glued to his right shoulder while sending their ballhawking wings down to swipe at the ball and deny him the easiest pressure-release passes. He had 21 made field goals and 16 turnovers in the middle three games of this series, often looking flustered by all the pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired Contract Specialist At The Office Of Personnel Management]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189113</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-contract-specialist-at-the-office-of-personnel-management"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T18:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most years, Patricia Gibson decorates her home for Memorial Day—putting up a sign or placing some flags in her flower pots. But this year, when she saw decorations in the store, she paused in the aisle. "Should I decorate some red, white, and blue for outside?" Gibson remembered asking herself. "And I'm just like, no. I'm really not feeling the miracle right now, and who's representing it." Because in February, after working for the federal government for 17 years, Gibson learned that she would lose her job as a contract specialist at the Office of Personnel Management, through no fault of her own.
OPM, essentially the federal government's human resources agency, has historically flown under the radar of the general public. But this winter, Elon Musk and DOGE functionally took over the agency to carry out their campaign of mass firings. As CNN reported in March, OPM employees who previously sent communications to federal agencies watched from the sidelines as Musk's OPM sent a barrage of termination notices to federal employees. One such notice was the "Fork in the Road" email, which offered workers a chance to be paid through September if they left their posts—an attempt to downsize the federal workforce and remove anyone resistant to Trump's agenda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Belichick Brought Along His Merry Band Of Losers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189666</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bill-belichick-unc-brought-along-his-merry-band-of-losers"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T17:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s check in on America’s First Couple, Bill Belichick and Jordon Hudson, aka Jordochick. There’s so much to tell you, I can hardly stand it! After the two filled their collective diaper in front of CBS cameras, Pablo Torre’s podcast reported that the University of North Carolina had banned Hudson from its football team’s facilities (which the school denied in a statement that I can poke more holes in that Belichick's formalwear). Then the Washington Post published a letter from Hudson resigning from her cheerleading gym, and the paper informed all of us that Hudson’s mother runs a “popular sex boutique” in Provincetown, Mass. Oh, and Hudson finished third in the Miss Maine USA pageant. A nation wept.
Now that’s a lot of information to take in. I’m so wrapped up in the story of Jordon Hudson—our heroine used to give henna tattoos to customers in Provincetown while wearing her regional beauty pageant sash—that I nearly forgot about the football part of this story. Lucky for you and me, Tar Heels GM Mike Lombardi has entered the chat room to remind us that actual work of assembling a winning football team in Chapel Hill isn't going so well, either:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Hill Starts Yet Another Climb, This Time With the Royals]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=463521</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/rich-hill-starts-yet-another-climb-this-time-with-the-royals/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T17:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Hill says he feels 100%. Rich Hill is 45 years old. The math may not add up, but how good are his chances to play for his 14th big league club?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davy Andrews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Javy Báez Comes Back For Seconds]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189635</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/javy-baez-comes-back-for-seconds"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T16:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is our second blog this week about Javy Báez, because the Detroit center fielder (yes, center fielder!) has simply demanded it. There are players in MLB who can boast a higher WAR or more home runs, but nobody in baseball has surprised like Báez through his first 34 games. Once one of the sport's most exciting young talents with the Cubs, then an absolute washout who OPSed below .600 in back-to-back years, a humbled Báez returned from season-ending surgery last August to a growing team that had unexpectedly fashioned itself into a contender. But rather than be an awkward appendix on a roster that seemingly proved it was better off without him, Báez has pieced himself back together. Now, he's a leading hitter on—I swear this is real—Baseball Reference's World Series favorite. And Tuesday night's performance against the Red Sox was his most endearing yet in a Tigers uniform.
With some wet weather in Detroit and a Tarik Skubal start scheduled for the next day, it wasn't a big crowd that witnessed Javy's heroics live. But Michigan is following the Tigers more closely than it has in any spring for the past decade, and I could feel the reverberations from a thrilling 11th inning all the way out in Brooklyn, where I listened to Dan Dickerson on the radio call during my walk home. It was Javy who was responsible for extras in the first place, scoring from third on a botched pickoff from the Boston catcher early on and then clobbering a breaking ball to left for a three-run shot in the sixth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baseball Frees Its Gambling Ghosts]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189670</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/baseball-frees-its-gambling-ghosts"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a sentence you probably haven't imagined ever reading: The 1919 Black Sox are BACK!
Oh sure, you fell for the splashier "Commissioner Lifts Lifetime Ban On Pete Rose Because He's Stopped Being Alive" headlines, in part because it looks Manfred gave in to the whims expressed during a regularly scheduled unhinged rant of the current President. But Manfred went further with his favor-currying than anyone could have imagined. The commissioner’s elite constituent service expanded by sucking up to the still-new Pope by forgiving the greatest scandal in the sport's history, which just happens to have been authored by the Chicago-born Pope’s team of choice. Say what you want about baseball's place in the culture, but no other commissioner is nuzzling up to this many levels of power quite like our Robbo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stewing In Anger]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189663</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/stewing-in-anger"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T15:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Normal Gossip inbox is chaotic at the best of times. We get all sorts of gossip, from all over the world, much of which isn’t remotely radio-safe. There are a few common themes: Lots of people seem to be sleeping with their coworkers. Lots of people seem to be fighting over an inheritance. And lots of people seem to be struggling with their roommates. 
Today we’ve got a special treat for you—the cream of the roommate-drama crop. Imagine a bad roommate with all the fixings: hogging the bathroom, leaving dirty dishes in the sink, not paying their fair share of a household expense. Now imagine that roommate has a passion for perpetual stew.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No One Ever Sees The Pacers Coming]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189639</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/no-one-ever-sees-the-pacers-coming"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T14:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Indiana Pacers have been living in the shadow of the snobbery of others for far longer than they deserve. They don't play in a cool town, or a cool state. They don't tell a cool story. They play a fun, fluid style of basketball, but the team itself isn’t cool. They're just the team that kicks your arse more often than you kick theirs, and if it’s mostly the arse-kicking part that might make you sad, it surely adds some insult to that injury that they're not telling a fashionable story while doing it. They're a four-seed in the Eastern Conference, from the 25th-largest media market in America, and so they're easy to ignore until they aren't. Like now, and maybe only for a moment.
And here they are, in this moment, back in the Eastern Conference Final for the second year in succession because, well, up yours. They don't have a better answer than that, and truthfully, they don't need one. They're here and you're not, so spin on that, you snotty, arrogant, elitist bastards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikael Granlund Takes Jets Downapeg]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189613</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mikael-granlund-takes-jets-downapeg"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the road, they're the Loseipeg Jets. After falling 3-1 to the Stars Tuesday to go down in the series by the same tally, the Manitobans are now an incredible 0-9 in their last nine road playoff games dating back three years. They've been outscored 45-14 over that stretch, and 25-8 in their 0-5 road showing this spring. It is, frankly, kind of baffling. Can Connor Hellebuyck only see pucks against a white-out of shirts? Is having wifi too much of a distraction? "If I had the answer to why," said Nik Ehlers, "we would have gotten one at some point."
The thing is, they played fine last night. They might've been the better team on the ice: they certainly won the shot and possession battles. It's just that Jake Oettinger was near-flawless, and the Dallas power play was flowing, and Mikael Granlund, of all people, beat Hellebuyck glove-side three separate times, on his only three shot attempts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding The Limit At Le Mans]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189372</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/finding-the-limit-at-le-mans"/>
        <updated>2025-05-14T13:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LE MANS, FRANCE — The MotoGP championship standings table, going into the Grand Prix de France at Le Mans, was headed by two brothers of disparate levels of previous success. Marc Márquez, one point behind in second place, suffers from the elder child's plight of being shorter than his younger brother. Álex Márquez, the championship leader, suffers from the younger child’s plight of having an older brother who is considered by many to be the greatest of all time in their sport. You know how it is.
They have been on the same team twice. The first time was in 2020. Before that, between 2013 and 2019, Marc Márquez cemented the end of the Valentino Rossi dynasty. He became the youngest major champion in motorcyclesport, and then won five more championships on the back of his remarkably aggressive style. In his obscene 2019 season, he had one retirement, and otherwise finished top-two in every single race of the year. He accomplished all this without much help from his machinery: The Honda was broadly considered far from the best bike on the grid at the time. Like a lot of greats, Marc Márquez is either loved or resented, though the latter is no knock on his public demeanor. He is noticeably smiley. The same wide, full-faced grin has stayed with him from then, into 2020, and onto now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody Can Do That]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189568</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nobody-can-do-that"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T20:29:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps it is time to coordinate an emergency delivery of some rudimentary lessons about human biology to the sportswriters of America. It was less than a month ago that The Athletic's Fred Katz mistook the basic act of "hearing things" for echolocation, and now we are confronted with ESPN's Ramona Shelburne forgetting how eyeballs work. 
Here is a snippet from Shelburne's most recent article, about how Russell Westbrook has fit in with the Denver Nuggets this season:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Rich Hill To Minor League Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=851867</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-sign-rich-hill-to-minor-league-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T19:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that they have signed left-hander Rich Hill to a minor league deal. He will report to the club’s spring training/Complex League facility in Surprise but will be heading to Triple-A Omaha soon. The veteran lefty has already defied the normal aging curves and seems determined to do so again. Now 45 years…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes From A Reborn NBA Fan]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189566</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/notes-from-a-reborn-nba-fan"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T19:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about wearing pajamas in public, hating REM, and more.
John:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use your words / Fear your data]]></title>
        <id>6822680f74fb8d000119f328</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-319/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T17:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seizing the megaphone with Osita Nwanevu; Nathan Munn reveals the monster in the machine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pivot to Video]]></title>
        <id>6822821674fb8d000119f4d4</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/pivot-to-video/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T17:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Osita Nwanevu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatic for the People]]></title>
        <id>6822689d74fb8d000119f335</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/automatic-for-the-people/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T17:31:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Munn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Clair Obscur: Expedition 33’ Makes Your Wandering Worth It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189408</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/clair-obscur-expedition-33-makes-your-wandering-worth-it"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T16:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I play a new video game, I am a dirty walkthrough follower. I never feel like having three monitors is more useful than when I can play the game on my main one and have a guide on a secondary screen. The reason I do this is simple: I like thoroughness in my gaming. I don't want to miss the secretly overpowered item in Act I because I didn't know where it was. I want to see it all, even if that means being guided by the hand.
Imagine my shock, then, over how I played Clair Obscur: Expedition 33, the ridiculously named role-playing game by French studio Sandfall Interactive that became one of the best reviewed games of all time shortly after its release on April 24. I had not heard of Clair Obscur before the reviews and hype started rolling in, and I immediately bought and downloaded it. A turn-based RPG that is both gorgeous and almost hilariously French? With timing-based parries and dodges, like some form of modernized, Francophile Super Mario RPG? Yes, please.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When The Unreality Is Too Unreal]]></title>
        <id>68235ba5761ee70001e49411</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/when-the-unreality-is-too-unreal/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T15:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Characterizing white South Africans as a persecuted minority in need of saving is a miscalculation by the bad-faith unreality creators among us]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Can All Go To Hell In A Hurry]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189541</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/it-can-all-go-to-hell-in-a-hurry"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T14:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With just over three minutes left in Game 4 of the second-round series between the Celtics and Knicks, it was feeling pretty over for Boston, who were trailing by seven and facing a 3-1 series deficit. And then a few seconds later, it was really over.
We are still awaiting official word on what kind of injury Jayson Tatum suffered when he made a move for a loose ball, crumpled to the floor, and then screamed in agony while grabbing the back of his right ankle. We have all seen this particular non-contact injury enough to understand that what happened to Tatum is not good, and that a torn Achilles would keep him off the floor for at least a year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nottingham Forest Is Missing A Trick]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189451</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nottingham-forest-is-missing-a-trick"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T14:19:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unless you're a fan of one of the big clubs that needed a late Nottingham Forest collapse to help mask your own team's piss-poor season (we're looking at you, Man City and Chelsea), you have to feel for the Trees. Forest maintained its over-performing underdog act for so long and so admirably this year, and it was just starting to look like the team might avoid the Icarian fate that usually befalls the (relatively) low-spending high fliers of any given Premier League season. Alas, with Sunday's 2-2 draw against Leicester City, it appears that the wax is running, the feathers are falling out, and Forest has entered what could be a tailspin.
No one could really say it's surprising that the Tricky Trees have fallen off the pace that had them soaring in the Champions League places. Over the course of 38 matches, it's hard for the talent of the big boys, the health of your overachievers, and the god of regression not to eventually catch up with even the most brave and resilient upstarts. In Forest's case, rivals like Man City, Newcastle United, and Chelsea have started to hit some better form entering the final stretch, key Reds like Callum Hudson-Odoi and Murillo have picked up untimely injuries, and Chris Wood, the big galoot who could not stop scoring goals (he has 20), has more or less stopped scoring goals (two in his last nine games). As such, the Trees have picked up just five points from their last six matches, which has seen them drop from a comfortable third place down to seventh.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Goddamn Mavericks Won The Goddamn Draft Lottery]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189511</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-goddamn-mavericks-won-the-goddamn-draft-lottery"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T13:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right now I would like to punch something, hard enough to make jelly of my fist. Not because I am a fan of the Washington Wizards! Nowadays being a fan of the Wizards means hoping they will lose—they trained me for this, by trying hard for six months to lose as much as possible—and I'll be damned if I can switch off that impulse in time for the draft lottery. Unto the Wizards I say: Ha ha! Screwed by fate, but not a cruel one: A just and righteous fate, a Rod Serling-ish fate rather than a Stephen King-ish one. Also screwed by the universe: the Utah Jazz and the Charlotte Hornets, fellow practitioners of the Vomit Arts. Owned to hell, all of you! Ha ha!
Still this morning I would like to ram my head into one of those industrial rock smashers, because of who won the lottery. The son-of-a-gun Dallas Mavericks—those selfsame bozos who just torched their future, proudly and defiantly, for a foundation of two unreliable and rapidly eroding veteran stars—jumped an incredible 10 spots and won the top overall pick in the 2025 draft. Their odds of winning were less than two freakin' percent. A third of the damn league had better odds of landing that pick; a solid seven of those teams might even have been able to say they deserved a friendly turn from the cosmos. Instead, fortune smiled down on the asshole Mavericks, to my mind the very most odious option of all. Screw.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physicality Is Where Basketball Lives And Careers Die]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188921</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/physicality-is-where-basketball-lives-and-careers-die"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T12:59:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO —The NBA playoffs have been going for nearly a month and everyone is suffering. Jayson Tatum awaits an MRI on a Monday night leg injury that may well have ended his playoffs and Boston's title repeat hopes; Damian Lillard's Bucks career ended with an Achilles tear; and Steph Curry is down with a strained hamstring. The headlining injuries hardly even tell the story. The eight teams still in contention look battered and out of gas: The Nuggets just scored eight points in a first quarter, the Celtics whimpered and died in two straight fourth quarters, and the ailing Cavaliers were just ground into a fine powder by the Pacers. Things are going to get worse, as we're not even halfway through the playoffs. It is hard to shake the feeling, especially after the Tatum injury, that the eventual champion will not necessarily be the best team but the least damaged. Which brings us to the word of the playoffs: physicality.
Throughout this NBA postseason, players and coaches cannot stop talking about physicality, and the necessity of meeting it. "I think the physicality was there," Magic coach Jamahl Moseley said after his team lost Game 2 against the Celtics. "I don't think they were dirty plays, but I think it passed a line of physicality," Cavs coach Kenny Atkinson said after his team lost Game 1 to the Pacers. "Our physicality was great tonight," Jaylen Brown said after taking a 3-1 lead against the Magic. "If you look around the playoffs right now, it’s super physical," Timberwolves coach Chris Finch said in the first round of his team's series against the Lakers. "To me, they’ve gone way too far on the physicality. [...] It feels like it’s physicality without purpose." After his team lost Game 3 against the Clippers, Nuggets coach David Adelman provided the diagnosis: "Defensively, we have to meet their physicality."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A’s Return Rule 5 Pick Noah Murdock To Royals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=851816</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/as-return-rule-5-pick-noah-murdock-to-royals.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T02:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The A’s returned Rule 5 draftee Noah Murdock to the Royals, as first reflected on the MLB.com transaction log. Kansas City assigned him to Triple-A Omaha. Murdock does not occupy a spot on their 40-man roster. This was the likeliest outcome after the A’s designated Murdock for assignment last Friday. Any team that traded for him…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edible itinerary / Canine companionship]]></title>
        <id>6822385574fb8d000119e098</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-318/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T20:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A luscious food (and book) tour with Laurie Woolever, and memories of Misha Angrist’s best friends]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Life in Dogs]]></title>
        <id>68220b1774fb8d000119df2f</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/my-life-in-dogs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T20:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Misha Angrist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Ate on Book Tour]]></title>
        <id>68222da674fb8d000119e000</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/what-i-ate-on-book-tour/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T20:18:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wrote a book about food (and drinking, and sex, and marriage, and celebrity, and death) that came out in March, and for which my publisher sent me on a book tour that kicked off in New York. Before that event, I had dinner with my editor and publicist at]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurie Woolever</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Took Two Years And Four Overtimes For The Victoire To Live Up To Their Name In The Playoffs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189487</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/victoire-4ot-charge-owhl-playoffs"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T19:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The whole season, win or lose, Montreal Victoire head coach Kori Cheverie and her players spouted their belief in the team. Listening to them week after week, the message started to feel tired. How sincerely can you focus on the good things after you lose? When goalie Ann-Renée Desbiens got hurt, then Kati Tabin got served a multi-game suspension, it was hard to picture this as a team that could sustain their early-season dominance. In March and April, the Victoire lost as much as they won. Come playoffs, would they show up and win games, or would they bow out suddenly and gracelessly like last year? But it really was true that every single player talked about the team’s confidence, every game. What comes first: the belief or the act of professing it? For the Victoire, maybe it doesn’t matter.
In Game 1, Montreal suffered from a serious case of playoff nerves. Silly mistakes saw pucks slip through Ottawa’s crease unanswered, and Montreal never led. Both the Victoire’s goals came off of power plays—a good showing for their special teams—but they couldn’t figure out how to score without l’avantage numérique. Despite outshooting Ottawa, they did what they’d always done in the playoffs: lose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abigail Segel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Javier Báez Can’t Do It All, But He Sure Will Try]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189240</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/javier-baez-cant-do-it-all-but-he-sure-will-try"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T19:34:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Soon after Javier Báez signed a six-year, $140 million contract with the Detroit Tigers, he began the least productive stretch of his MLB career, and I began my new life as the world’s No. 1 Javy Báez apologist. Javy hatred, I thought, was the sign of a dull mind. It linked everything I resented in my fellow Tigers fans: their sourness; their temper; their archaic obsession with “errors”; their belief in a baseball value system that didn’t resemble mine and could never account for the singularity of Javy. It bothered me when the complaints tipped into falsehoods, the insistence that Javy was “lazy,” that he’d gotten his bag in 2022 and then stopped trying.
Of course, I was watching the games and seeing what everyone else saw. Báez's power numbers fell to such lows that the rare home runs he did hit were kind of funny. His on-base percentages had always skewed low—the cost of a free-swinging approach—but three seasons into the contract, they were dire. In 2024, he slashed .181/.221/.294. The less he got on base, the sillier I felt defending him on the grounds of his “baserunning genius.” Like a Joe Biden aide, I had a job to do, and I would do it, but privately, I knew he was cooked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is My Senator Good For?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189229</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-is-my-senator-good-for"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T18:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My gargantuan senator is throwing a hissy fit. According to reporting by the Associated Press, Pennsylvania Sen. John Fetterman attended a meeting last week with representatives for a teachers union, at which Fetterman says that they "had a spirited conversation about our collective frustration with the Trump administration’s cuts to our education system." The other people in the meeting say that the Senator started repeating himself and shouting. They say he was yelling, "Why does everyone hate me, what did I ever do?" and "Why is everybody mad at me?" A member of Fetterman's staff ended the meeting, ushered the visitors into the hallway, and then broke down crying and had to be comforted by the teachers.
This is toddler behavior. Why does everyone hate me? What did I ever do? Why is everyone mad at me? Sir! You are 6-foot-8 and a Senator for a purple state. By the nature of your job, something like 50 percent of the people in your own state will hate you at all times, and that's not including the people in your own party who also don't like you. Being an elected public servant is not a long red-carpet strut where everyone treats you like a pop star and bows to you and asks who you're wearing. Power is a responsibility, and with it comes the reality that not everyone is going to like you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make It Nice: Bringing Order To Chaos]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189416</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/make-it-nice-bringing-order-to-chaos"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T17:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first official edition of Make It Nice. Each month, I’ll tackle your interior design questions and help you make your space feel beautiful. Today we have questions about storage, room dividers, and a kitchen conundrum. Let’s get into it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veronica de Souza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYT Reporter: It’s Not Corruption Unless The Envelope Says “Bribe” On It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189418</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nyt-reporter-its-not-corruption-unless-the-envelope-says-bribe-on-it"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T16:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump launched a memecoin a few days before the inauguration of his second presidential term. Its sole purpose, to Trump, is unambiguous and unmistakable: It is a vehicle for him to become richer. Likewise, its only conceivable value to literally any other person or entity on the face of the earth is also quite clear: It is a way to buy favor from the president of the United States. Its very existence is an announcement: Here is how you pay President Donald Trump for stuff.
To wit:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Colorado Rockies Can’t Even Lose Right]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189441</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-colorado-rockies-cant-even-lose-right"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T15:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has been a spirited race toward Major League Baseball's Dumpster of Distinction all season, with a number of candidates trying to join the increasingly popular 100-loss club. But there are ways to fail, and then there are stylish ways to fail. Miami and Baltimore are failing, but it's pretty boilerplate stuff—the Marlins don't pitch, the Orioles don't hit. Nothing especially novel there, give or take Baltimore's 192 wins over the previous two seasons.
In other words, in an era in which losing 100 is no big thang—there have been 22 teams that have managed it since 2018—the way you get to 100 matters. The Chicago White Sox figured that out last year by reaching 100 in the last week of August and ending up with 121 losses, the second most defeats in baseball history. They stunk, but they found a way to do it at a rate that no other team had figured out before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, May 12: Balls Out]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189365</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-may-12-balls-out"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a shot at our Monday crossword! This week's puzzle was constructed by Kate Chin Park and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Kate is a puzzle editor and constructor who hopes that if you enjoy crosswords, you'll consider signing up for Westwords, which will take place both virtually and in Berkeley, Calif., on Sunday, June 22! Visit the website to learn more.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Vibe Shift Is Not Happening By Accident]]></title>
        <id>681e4abe0643d000010d39ac</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/this-vibe-shift-is-not-happening-by-accident/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T14:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical alternate consciousness is manifesting in myriad ways. It's a hopeful development in a hopeless time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rulebook Aficionados: Let’s Ride]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189376</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/stars-jets-petrovic-hellebuyck"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T14:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These playoff have had everything, from unlikely comebacks to huge upsets to bloody feuds to preternatural feats of athleticism. You can keep all that. We true connoisseurs of professional sports controversies have been craving a rulebook kerfuffle, and in Sunday's Stars home win over the Jets, we finally got one. This is why they play the game; it's time for some lawyerpuck.
The third-period, tie-breaking goal in an eventual 5-2 Dallas win was credited to Alex Petrovic, but that doesn't come close to telling the story. Petrovic, skating past the side of the net, tried to gather a rebound and directed it with his left skate into the crease. It appeared that untouched it would have slid harmlessly through the crease, but Connor Hellebuyck, trying to clear the puck, angled it into his own net. Goal? After eight minutes of video review, and no doubt the frantic flipping of rulebook pages in the NHL's Situation Room: Goal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teachable Moment]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189375</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/teachable-moment"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T13:41:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter.
This was how Columbia University's acting president, Claire Shipman, described what happened at a protest in the school's Butler Library on May 7:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Of You Motherfuckers Are On Fraud Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189374</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/all-of-you-motherfuckers-are-on-fraud-watch"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T13:17:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone line up.
Cleveland Cavaliers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Savannah Bananas Make Baseball Boring]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189317</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-savannah-bananas-make-baseball-boring"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T16:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["What's the deal with the Savannah Bananas?"
Like five different times over the past few months, someone at this website has posed that question to the rest of the folks who work here. For the uninitiated, I will begin with the most dispassionate, factual answer in the paragraph below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Sox Now Chasing Rafael Devers Across The Country, Waving Lineup Card]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189329</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/red-sox-now-chasing-rafael-devers-across-the-country-waving-lineup-card"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T15:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rafael Devers did what his bosses wanted. The Red Sox went out and grabbed a big-time addition over the winter, but to maximize their investment they needed Devers to shift away from his preferred position—the one he's been playing his entire career, and the one the Red Sox extended him a nine-figure contract to continue playing off into the future. Devers wasn't happy about the request and resisted for a while. He eventually caved, and then he endured an embarrassing, historically awful start to the season while adjusting to this new deal. But he's recovered admirably and been a reliable and productive contributor for a fun and competitive Red Sox team.
Now the team is at it again. First baseman Triston Casas, off to a hateful, miserable start of his own, nuked his left knee while trying to beat out an infield single on May 2 and has been lost for the year. The Red Sox have since tried out Romy Gonzalez, Abraham Toro, and Nick Sogard over at first, with results that you would call broadly lousy—7-for-26 at the plate with zero extra-base hits—were it not for the fact that Casas was producing an OPS+ of [awful retching noises]. It's not that these are especially terrible baseball players—although scanning Toro's Baseball Reference page is causing an alarming intensification of the retching—but certainly none of those poor bozos is the sort of guy a team is eager to get into the lineup, least of all a team with semi-credible playoff aspirations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leon, No!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189334</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/leon-no"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T14:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It didn't matter that the Oilers jumped out to a 2–0 lead in Game 3. It didn't matter that Stuart Skinner, forced back into action after Calvin Pickard's injury, allowed fewer goals than he did in his two catastrophic starts against the Kings. And it didn't matter that, with the score 3–2 Vegas in the final few minutes, Connor McDavid unlocked the Golden Knights' defense with a little pass from the corner that went in off an enemy skate. All anyone's going to remember from Saturday night is the very last second, which is how Vegas managed to cut into Edmonton's 2–0 series lead.
Any reasonable person would have been ready for overtime as William Karlsson broke into the offensive zone and took the puck behind the net with under five seconds to play. But in retrospect, when the VGK original sent the puck flying backward into the slot for another one of his expansion-season brethren, Reilly Smith, neither man had yet given up on the third period, and there was still enough time to inflict the knockout blow. Smith, using nearly every tenth of a second allotted to him, zoomed past a diving Oilers defender and tried to round a sliding Skinner as he fired a shot in the direction of the crease. The puck bounced so quickly that in real time, the closest official didn't see a goal. But replay review revealed the buzzer-beater, and worse, the person most responsible for it crossing the line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtics Flatten Knicks By Sticking To The Formula]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189322</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/celtics-flatten-knicks-by-sticking-to-the-formula"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T13:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Boston Celtics and New York Knicks have played 149 minutes across three games of their second-round playoff series. The Celtics—the higher seeded team and the defending NBA champions—have led outright for about 128 minutes of that time, and the teams have spent about another 11 minutes tied, meaning the Knicks have led in this series for a little over 10 total minutes. The Celtics have gained leads of at least 20 points in each game, while the Knicks have never led by double digits; they have, in fact, never once had a three-possession lead. This isn't a real metric, I may have just made it up while I sat here, but: If you total together New York's maximum lead from each of the three games, and then multiply the sum by the total minutes they've spent in the lead, you get 90. If you do the same for the Celtics—20 points in Game 1, another 20 in Game 2, 31 points in Game 3, added together and then multiplied by total time in the lead—you get 9,088.
This is very dumb, meaningless math, but for some weird reason I have always been tickled by one number being way huger than another number. The Knicks have 90 units of advantage through three games, against Boston's 9,088: Wow! And also: Ha! By my dumb metric, it would be absolutely ludicrous to guess that the team holding the overall lead in the series today is the New York Knicks. But here we are! Boston needed a win Saturday to avoid falling into a 3–0 hole in a matchup that they have otherwise absolutely dominated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyle Wright Pulled Off Rehab Stint With Shoulder Fatigue, Continuing To Play Catch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=851551</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/kyle-wright-pulled-off-rehab-stint-with-shoulder-fatigue-continuing-to-play-catch.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-10T02:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyle Wright’s first appearance with the Royals will wait a little longer than hoped. The team announced this evening that they’ve pulled him back from his rehab assignment in Double-A after Wright reported shoulder fatigue. The club specified that they believe it to be a minor setback, saying the “tentative plan” is for him to skip…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maple leaf rage / Undead blues]]></title>
        <id>681e5f3174fb8d000119c8a2</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-317/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T21:47:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nathan Munn explains the Canadian election to Zach Rabiroff; the music of ‘Sinners’ enchants Rax King]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PODCAST Round Table! Episode 9: Canadasplainer!]]></title>
        <id>681e5e5874fb8d000119c895</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/podcast-round-table-episode-9-canadasplainer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T21:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nathan Munn, Canadian, and Zach Rabiroff, New Yorker, discuss the recent and somewhat surprising results of the big election in Canada. Joe MacLeod pressed the RECORD button.
Listen on Apple/Spotify/RSS/plus more options at pod.link

Episode 9: CANADASPLAINER
Nathan Munn, Canadian, and Zach Rabiroff, New]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Munn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pick Poor Robin Clean]]></title>
        <id>681e5a5774fb8d000119c879</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/pick-poor-robin-clean/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T21:25:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rax King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A’s Designate Noah Murdock For Assignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=851501</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/as-designate-noah-murdock-for-assignment.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T21:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The A’s designated Rule 5 pick Noah Murdock for assignment, relays Martín Gallegos of MLB.com. Righty Elvis Alvarado was recalled from Triple-A Las Vegas to take his spot in the bullpen. Alvarado is already on the 40-man roster, so the move drops their count to 39. Murdock, 26, was the fourth player selected in last winter’s Rule…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Staff Chat Begins Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189296</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-staff-chat-begins-right-now"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T18:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello. It's Friday. Let's chat. We'll be down below waiting to answer all of your burning questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lamine Yamal’s Wait Is Over]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189044</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lamine-yamals-wait-is-over"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T17:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the conclusion of Tuesday's Barcelona vs. Inter match, Lamine Yamal had taken up the traditional loser's pose: sitting on the ground, his arms encircling his knees in a loose hug, his back curved in a hunch of exhaustion and dejection, eyes vacantly staring into the distance.
Something about that image made stark the irresolvable paradox of this 17-year-old and his staggeringly advanced game. Part of it was the akimbo posture, accentuating the youthfulness of his sinewy limbs, which, unlike when the ball is at his feet, made him look every bit the callow teen he is. Part of it was the emotional tenor of the moment, the blessed, childlike state into which sports can transport anyone—child or adult, on-pitch participant or TV viewer from thousands of miles away—where the result of a silly little game can send hot tears of anguish streaming down millions of faces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Reads A Book: Defector Rides A Bike]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188904</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-reads-a-book-defector-rides-a-bike"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T17:22:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In college, I briefly and unsuccessfully raced bikes, a humbling experience that taught me that the dog in me was not of requisite size to hang with anyone who wasn't a middling amateur. Every part of racing was a drain, from being nervously sardine-packed alongside dozens of other gangly 20-year-olds to figuring out when to burn energy and when to chill in the pack so that I actually had energy to burn. I never won anything or even came close, though loving bike racing means loving the draining stuff. That's all you can count on.
This is the right way to think about professional cycling, and really any form of racing. Think about this sort of competitive framework seriously enough, and you rub up against the limits of describing or thinking about racing in cold, analytical language. Easy and forgivable as it is to roll one's eyes at a conception of bike racing rooted in romantic notions like bravery, or the virtues of suffering with dignity, those do form the competitive substrate of the sport. Like most racing sports, cycling is foremost a pain tolerance contest. Strategic thinking is centered on how to trick other people into suffering more than you. How could you not think about guts, in both usages?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Bea]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189238</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/for-bea"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T17:03:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was still reeling in the aftermath of our dog Chop's sudden and horrible heart-failure death, stunned and breathless with grief, feeling very much the way you do after taking a hard blow to the head, when all at once our Bea became a ghost of herself. She was old, and had been thinning in the way old dogs do in their final year, but still in all outward respects her loud, wiseass, insistent self, buzzing with impatience, shepherding my wife to bed at The Appointed Time, shoveling her snout under your hand and levering it onto her neck when she wanted pets: Bea.
Then, on a Saturday evening in early April, she all at once flipped out at our other dog, Grover, when he came up behind her: Snarling and snapping, fighting as though for her life. We had to pull them apart. In the immediate aftermath, she was the most alarmingly depleted dog I have ever seen. She could scarcely stand. It was as though a band had snapped in there. It was as though she had spent the absolute last of herself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Notes: Outfield, Caglianone, Harvey]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=851428</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-rumors-jac-caglianone-promotion-leody-taveras.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T16:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals enter the weekend with the American League’s fourth-best record (23-16) and in possession of the league’s second Wild Card spot. Their starting rotation, as highlighted by MLBTR’s Anthony Franco yesterday, looks exceptional. Their top four relievers, by workload, have ERAs of 2.65 or better. Pitching was never going to be the question with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restart Your Computer!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189232</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/restart-your-computer"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T15:25:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At our bi-weekly all-hands meeting, Jasper Wang, our Business Man, will usually share his screen with the appropriate slides. But this week, his computer was bogged down and wouldn’t load said slides. Jasper offhandedly remarked that he was paying the price for not having restarted his computer for a couple weeks, and I similarly offhandedly implored everyone to restart their computers once a day, if not more. Immediately a horde of my coworkers began clowning my adherence to good computer hygiene, and even more so when I mentioned that I have been known to restart my computer four or five times a day.
Here’s the thing: I am right and they are wrong. There is no reason to not shut down your computer, at the very least, at the end of the day, and boot it up fresh the next morning. Their qualms were easily batted away. Oh no, what about my tabs?!?! Every browser now has the ability to restore your last session, so you can get your stinkin’ tabs back that way. (Side note: Excessive tabs are an argument for another day.) Who cares if it runs a little slow, I don’t need my computer’s full processing power and memory to write a post. It’s much nicer when you can flit around the internet at lightning speed without your browser slowing to a crawl. You are a slave to the machines. Fine, but my machine at least runs reliably and with great speed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Pierce Turns Grim Men’s Wager Into Pleasant Men’s March]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189176</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/paul-pierce-turns-grim-mens-wager-into-pleasant-mens-march"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T14:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been a while since we last checked in with Paul Pierce, the world's foremost practitioner of the grim men's lifestyle. He does some studio work for FS1 now—that tracks—and on Wednesday's episode of Speak, he made a bold proclamation: If the Boston Celtics lost Game 2 of the Eastern Conference semifinals to the New York Knicks, he would walk to work the next day. This was quite the promise, as Pierce stated on air that he lives some 15 miles from the studio where Speak is filmed.
We all know what happened in Game 2, and we are pleased to report that Pierce seems to have actually followed through on his promise. Before sunrise on the west coast he fired up his Instagram account and posted a video of himself—wearing sweatpants, a t-shirt, and a robe—leaving his house to begin his long walk. "Welcome to this journey, here I go," he said in the dark of the early morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every Episode Of The Danny McBride HBO Universe, Ranked]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188695</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/every-episode-of-the-danny-mcbride-hbo-universe-ranked"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T14:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Righteous Gemstones' final episode aired on Sunday, closing another chapter in what has been a 16-year project by comedian-writer-creator Danny McBride and his co-creators/friends from college, Jody Hill and David Gordon Green, to tell the stories of life in the South and the fantasies of American exceptionalism. The stories of career charlatans, egomaniacal has-beens, greedy televangelists, drug-addicted hustlers, hard-living gamblers, and human volcanoes ready to burst; the kinds of people who inspire Warren Zevon or Townes Van Zandt songs. No one has captured 21st-century America with more specificity, showing the comical obsessions—with hypermasculinity and accumulation—that always threaten to destroy us.
In 2009, McBride teamed up with his friends and collaborators from the University of North Carolina School of the Arts, namely Hill, Green, and Ben Best, to create Eastbound & Down. McBride played Kenny Powers, a John Rocker-meets-Jose Canseco type of baseball superstar at the worst point in his life. All of his money and success and chances to play had burned out, reducing him to moving in with his brother Dustin (John Hawkes) and filling in as a substitute PE teacher at the elementary school where his former love April (Katy Mixon) works. Eastbound proved that McBride and his team could take what might have been a silly sitcom and elevate it to a novelistic character study of man in a spiritual battle between his worst impulses and his desires for change and human connection. It was an instant hit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Only Takes A Second]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189204</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mcdavid-draisaitl-yes-again"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:28:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the start of overtime, your mid-drowse blogger took a look at the scoresheet for Oilers–Golden Knights, and then looked again, on a different site, because he thought the first one must have been glitching or something. Four Edmonton goals, and none involved Leon Draisaitl or Connor McDavid? Not even a single measly assist? That can't be right. But it was true: For 75 minutes, including that ensuing overtime, Vegas clamped down on the Oilers' superlative-scoring duo, keeping them off the board and mostly away from any serious threats. They needed to do it for 76.
There was a lot to like about the game the Knights played, which makes the 5-4 result that much more painful. They made life miserable for Calvin Pickard, scoring four goals for the first time since Game 4 of the Wild series. They capitalized on two of their five power plays, Victor Olofsson scoring both times. Their kill was flawless, especially on a five-minute man-disadvantage in overtime. Their top skaters were buzzing, Jack Eichel contributing three assists and Mark Stone two apples of his own. They even mounted a stirring comeback, clawing back from 3-1 and then 4-2 in the third to send it to an extra frame.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Accursed Chicago Baseball Fan Base Will Get To Claim Pope Leo XIV?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189200</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/which-accursed-chicago-baseball-fan-base-will-get-to-claim-pope-leo-xiv"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T12:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would seem that The Fourteenth Leo has some clarification to make regarding his CV. Not about his papal bona fides, which we are neither fit nor inclined to judge. So far, he knows how to wave to people who like him, which is both something and maybe most of the actual job. The issue, here, is whether he grew up a Cubs fan, as originally reported, or whether he is, as his brother later told WGN News, a White Sox fan. He owes the world an answer, and that clarification better not be in Latin, or read out of some leather-bound book of ancient Hebrew—if the Pope has an opinion about DeWayne Wise, we’ll need to hear it in plain, nasally Chicagoan. Preferably while Archbishop of the 35th Avenue Diocese Harold Baines holds up a copy of the Sun-Times behind him.
It would not be unlike some surreptitious member of Big Cub, perhaps the shadowy Archbishop Bartman, to jump the gun on "Pope Durocher," as they doubtless would call him. But let's say that the former Bobby Prevost’s brother John is right. Let’s say that the man who is now the pope did grow up a White Sox fan, in a household with a Cubs fan mother and a Cardinals fan father. There would, in this case, be some signs of pre-papal equanimity in making that compromise choice between two arch-rivals, and picking the White Sox would also make sense given that meek-inheriting-the-earth lie. He could put that debate to rest for good by beginning his papacy by forgiving all the Black Sox and Arnold Rothstein, too. But we can only speculate on such matters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Trevor Richards To Minor League Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=851352</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-sign-trevor-richards-to-minor-league-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T00:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have signed right-hander Trevor Richards to a minor league deal, according to an announcement from the Omaha Storm Chasers, Kansas City’s Triple-A affiliate. The righty has been assigned to Omaha and will give the Royals some non-roster bullpen depth. Richards, 32 next week, hasn’t been in good form lately. The Twins acquired him…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A wing and a prayer]]></title>
        <id>681d11c074fb8d000119b6c9</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-316/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T22:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A dream of care and convalescence from Sam Thielman]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charisma]]></title>
        <id>681cfd9074fb8d000119b685</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/charisma/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T22:48:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summer after I turned twelve my granddad shot a dove with a BB gun and called me in a panic. 
He, that is my grandfather, was a really charismatic old guy. People always think of charisma as a sort of superpower but in my experience there’s]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Thielman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of The Onion, With Ben Collins]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189075</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-state-of-the-onion-with-ben-collins"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's not a lot of identifiably positive progress happening out there at the moment, but this week's episode does mark a short but nonetheless real step in the right direction. We first tried to book Ben Collins as a guest back when he was at NBC News, and were given a polite but definitive "maybe come back in one calendar year" from that network's press handlers. It may well have been for the best. Ben's old beat—the political version of online psychopathy, more or less—probably would have made for a compelling bummer of an episode, but it would have been a bummer for sure. While it's hard to say the broader world is doing much better now than it was then, this week's episode—which is just Ben and me, as Drew is off—is much happier. So, it seems, is Ben, who led the group that bought The Onion a year ago, and which has since overseen both an ambitious expansion and a total vibe refurbishment. Which means that, instead of talking about the absolute worst stuff online, we were talking about one of the few truly sunny-sided stories in American media.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Well, They Made A Cubs Fan The Pope]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189157</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/well-they-made-a-cubs-fan-the-pope"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T18:46:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Pope Leo XIV is truly from Chicago, he celebrated the news of his election by firing down a Malört with an Old Style chaser and eagerly accepting an invitation from the Cubs to sing "Take Me Out To The Ball Game." Otherwise, well, what's the point of the Chicago thing at all?
The first American-born pope, the Villanova-educated artist formerly known as Cardinal Robert Francis Prevost, just picked up his new gig, and within a half-hour the Pittsburgh Pirates used his election as cover to announce the firing of manager Derek Shelton, proving that Leo’s is truly the first National League Central papacy. Or it just proves that opportunism knows no season, and only the Pirates and their mudslide public relations sense could see the use in doing it this way. "The Pope has our back," you could almost hear owner Bob Nutting saying. "Let's do it now." It probably didn't happen exactly that way, but also nothing says they had to announce it then. Whatever the case, the announcement of Don Kelly as Pittsburgh’s new manager will not lead the local news this evening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Surfer’ Mostly Sputters And Flails]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189152</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-surfer-mostly-sputters-and-flails"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T18:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Hollywood, a surfer can be one of three things: a weed-smoking, wave-chasing airhead (Jeff Spicoli); a crunchy, woo-woo hippie (some of the penguins in the startlingly charming Surf’s Up); or an edgy, degenerate type, whose passion for adrenaline is paired with a generally violent demeanor (Patrick Swayze’s Bodhi in Point Break). The truth, as ever, is somewhere in between—you can expect even the gentlest of “soul-surfers” to hiss and fight over their home break. 
What, then, can we make of the unnamed protagonist (played by Nicholas Cage) in Lorcan Finnegan’s latest feature, The Surfer, beaten and humiliated in his quest to surf the Edenic waves of Luna Bay, the Australian beach where he grew up? Having been born there doesn’t grant him status as a local: “Don’t live here, don’t surf here,” goes the tag-line spat at him by the local crew. In the days leading up to Christmas, the surfer drives to the Bay to show his son the house where he grew up, which he is on the verge of buying back, if only he can outbid a competitive buyer. The surfer has long neglected his family, and a return to the wholesomeness of the beach—the beautiful surfing, the house perched on the cliff, the memory of an idyllic childhood—might help rebuild the relationships that have been sacrificed at the altar of his career.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafaela Bassili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired Web Content Manager At The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188269</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-web-content-manager-at-the-consumer-financial-protection-bureau"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T17:46:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before Chuck Sebian-Lander joined the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau as a web content manager, he knew about as much about the agency as "anybody who watched The Big Short and got really angry about it," he said. Previously, he'd worked as a proofreader and then project manager for a federal contractor that served federal health agencies, and Sebian-Lander saw this work as tremendously important, if slightly removed from his day-to-day life—"they're doing work studying diseases I've never heard of or they're treating children's cancer," he said.
Once at the CFPB, however, Sebian-Lander immediately understood how that agency's work intersected with his own life. He graduated with student debt, and he and his wife took out a mortgage to buy their home. In his work on the CFPB's website, he maintained pages that shared educational information about auto loans, bank loans, credit cards, credit reports, and credit scores, and debt. "It's all stuff that everybody has to deal with in a very existential way, even if you're a perfectly healthy person," he said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The DOGE Fencing Hearing Was Stupid And Pointless Even By Congressional Standards]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189068</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-doge-fencing-hearing-was-stupid-and-pointless-even-by-congressional-standards"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest in the long line of futile congressional sports hearings happened Wednesday. You probably missed it, as most people did. I was one of about 1,000 people watching it, according to YouTube at the time. Since then, about 12,000 people—out of a country of more than 341 million—have watched, though of course there's no way to know how many watched for more than the 30 seconds it takes YouTube to count a view. Like the sports-centered hearings that came before it, about steroids in baseball and sexual abuse in gymnastics, it was mostly political theater. Where it differed is in the intended audience. Previous hearings were about creating sound bites for television. This one was for the memes.
Officially, Wednesday's DOGE subcommittee was called to discuss the viral story about a fencer who refused to compete against another fencer in a minor competition because her opponent was a trans woman. In reality it was mostly yelling and grandstanding to be cut and clipped for the internet. The Republicans yelled at the Democrats. The Democrats yelled at the Republicans. The Republicans waved around Trump executive orders. The Democrats waved around charts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals’ Rotation Looks Stronger Than Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=851327</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/the-royals-rotation-looks-stronger-than-ever.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:40:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals had one of baseball’s best rotations in 2024. Kansas City starters posted a 3.55 earned run average that trailed only the 3.38 mark of Seattle’s star-studded staff. They logged 911 innings, again second-best in MLB behind the Mariners. Seth Lugo and Cole Ragans placed among the top four in AL Cy Young balloting. Michael Wacha and Brady…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikal Bridges Is Making A Meal Of The Celtics’ Mess]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189111</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mikal-bridges-is-making-a-meal-of-the-celtics-mess"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtics lost again, and now find themselves in an extremely precarious position: down 0-2 to the Knicks and heading to New York for the next two games of the Eastern Conference Semifinals. This is not a position that a 61-win defending champion is supposed to find itself in, so what the hell is going on here?
It can be frustrating to attempt any meaningful analysis of a Celtics loss, because the team's style of play only ever produces one answer: The three-point shot wasn't falling. The Celtics blew 20-point leads in both Game 1 and Game 2 because the shots they count on to go in simply did not. Boston set an NBA playoff record by missing 45 threes in Game 1, and lost Wednesday night's contest, 91-90, behind a 10-of-40 shooting display from behind the arc. If a few more of those shots hit at their average rate, the Celtics are up 2-0 right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allowing For Various Metaphors]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189112</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/allowing-for-various-metaphors"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the second straight game of their Eastern Conference semifinal series against the New York Knicks, the Boston Celtics blew a 20-point second-half lead, turned the ball over to Mikal Bridges at the most crucial possible moment, and lost. In his wee-hours postgame blog about this, ESPN's Brian Windhorst wrote the following sentence:
[Celtics star Jayson] Tatum didn't address the media after the game because TD Garden had to be evacuated because of a fire alarm, allowing for various metaphors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tread, Baby, Tread. Just Not On Me.]]></title>
        <id>681cbd180643d000010d33d4</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/tread-baby-tread-just-not-on-me/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T14:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bad faith of the Don't Tread On Me crowd has been fully exposed in this second Trump term]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Knicks And Maple Leafs Are Refusing To Stick To The Script]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189114</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-knicks-and-maple-leafs-are-refusing-to-stick-to-the-script"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T14:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are essentially two kinds of playoffs—the playoffs themselves, and the stranger, smaller sub-spectacle in which the New York Knicks and Toronto Maple Leafs get their fan bases excited. We have reached that second stage.
This will not be a slagging of either of those respective fan bases; first, we've already done that, and second, those fans are not responsible for the latest tandem developments. The Knicks and Leafs are now both two games to the good against the defending champions in their respective sports, and have gotten there on merit as well as through the temporary shortcomings of their alleged betters. If that isn't enough to reboot your will to live, well, you're either a Boston Celtics fan or The Dan LeBatard Show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On His Third Team Of The Season, Mikko Rantanen Is Second To None]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189086</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/on-his-third-team-of-the-season-mikko-rantanen-is-second-to-none"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T12:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right after Mikko Rantanen completed his natural hat trick en route to a 3-2 Stars win in their series-opener in Winnipeg, Stars GM Jim Nill could've been forgiven for breaking out the slip 'n' slide goal celebration. It would have been ill-advised; suite carpeting burns something fierce. But this, in Dallas's wildest dreams and the worst nightmares of the two teams who previously employed him this season, is why the Stars bet the farm and mortgaged a few drafts to lock up the 28-year-old Finn for most of the next decade. At that moment, the winger was decidedly on a heater. Six of the last seven Stars goals, dating back to Game 7 against Colorado, had come off Rantanen's stick. Six of eight scored by anybody, on either team, were his. He racked up his consecutive hat tricks in just 14:53 of ice time. It is possible no one has even been hotter.
"The chance to acquire and extend one of the best forwards in the NHL is an opportunity that we couldn’t pass up," Nill said at the time, and while it's boilerplate front-officespeak, truisms don't get to be truisms without being, you know, true. Superstars don't come available often in this league, not in their primes, not in a league that sometimes seems designed to deny us the drama of player movement. And superstars win games. And Rantanen proved the difference between Dallas going home in the first round and beating the Avs—and, for the Avs, not having him was the reason they're booking tee times. Now he's got the Stars up a game, solving home-ice Connor Hellebuyck thrice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Stephen Nogosek To Minor League Contract]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=851293</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-sign-stephen-nogosek-to-minor-league-contract.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T02:37:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals added reliever Stephen Nogosek on a minor league deal and assigned him to Triple-A Omaha. The move was announced by the affiliate. Nogosek, 30, signs out of the Mexican League. He’d made 10 appearances for the Diablos Rojos. The surface numbers aren’t all that impressive. The righty gave up 10 runs (six earned) on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A pack of villains / The comfort of the boss]]></title>
        <id>681ba76174fb8d000119a1c5</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-315/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T23:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Saward on advances in biotechnology; insights on the Latino vote from Felipe De La Hoz]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Something Dire]]></title>
        <id>681bb27c74fb8d000119a2a3</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/something-dire/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T23:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A letter to the new young wolves]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Saward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Foreman You Can Trust]]></title>
        <id>681ba7ac74fb8d000119a1d7</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/a-foreman-you-can-trust/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T23:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Texto en español
English text

Texto en español
Cada cuatro años, los comentaristas, periodistas y políticos angloparlantes perciben, como si por primera vez, que no existe tal cosa como un bloque electoral unificado de latinoamericanos en los Estados Unidos. Al igual que]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felipe De La Hoz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Still Know Babies]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188974</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-still-know-babies"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T18:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I found myself holding a baby the other day. It wasn't my baby, because I’m old and snipped. The baby in question belonged to my best friend, Howard. Howard is my age but got married late and is having his first child. Howard’s wife, Yesenia, is closer in age to him than to Jordon Hudson, so the arrival of this baby—her first child, as well—was never cleanly assured. A middle-aged pregnancy means that the mother and child are at a statistically higher risk for birth defects, miscarriage, and other terrifying complications. The mother also has to carry around a bowling ball sitting atop her bladder all day long. Tricky business.
I remember all that from when my wife I had our own kids. I remember the fear. I remember the emergency bedrest. I remember long nights in an alarmingly bustling NICU. You find out you’re expecting and your instincts force you to account for everything that can go wrong. Those instincts don’t leave you. Ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mess At Newark Airport Is Only The Beginning]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188966</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-mess-at-newark-airport-is-only-the-beginning"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T17:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is one feed—a remote line described as a "long extension cord"—that connects the radar for air traffic above Newark Airport to the air traffic controllers in Philadelphia, who make sure that planes take off and land safely. The line has gone down at least twice before, and last week, on Apr. 28, it went down again.
“We use floppy disks. We use copper wires,” Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy said on Friday. “The system that we’re using is not effective to control the traffic that we have in the airspace today.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inter Survived A War For The Ages]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188970</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/inter-survived-a-war-for-the-ages"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T17:18:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seemed impossible to top the first leg of the Champions League semifinal between Internazionale and Barcelona, a beautiful concerto of impossible goals and individual stardom. And yet, the two clubs, fighting savagely for a spot in the final, went out on Tuesday at the San Siro and not only topped it, but sent the entire tie into tournament lore. Seven goals across 120 minutes, unheralded stopgaps stepping into the spotlight, another magnificent goalkeeping display, a center back scoring the goal of his life ... the second leg had it all and more, and it was only due to a moment of nervous excellence from Inter's Davide Frattesi that the Italian side is on its seventh Champions League final, while Barcelona will rue this narrowest of missed opportunities.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qudvFiKZ6lY]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Any “Halfway Decent Person” Can Join And Own Ireland’s Oldest Gym]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188820</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/any-halfway-decent-person-can-join-and-own-irelands-oldest-gym"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T16:39:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DUBLIN — It’s raining. In Dublin this is as predictable as the phases of the moon. So predictable that I prewrote this lede. But I was right: It’s raining.
I’m in the capital chasing a fascination of mine. I turn off a modern thoroughfare and squeeze my Yaris down a narrow residential street. Older, brickwork houses and apartments stretch around a maze of similar streets ahead of me. Just before the houses, I find my quarry. The Hercules Club, founded 1935, is Ireland’s oldest gym and fully owned and operated by its members.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasper Hutson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leon Draisaitl Makes Everything Easier]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189009</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/leon-draisaitl-makes-everything-easier"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T16:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adin Hill had a bad day at the office. As the Edmonton Oilers came back from 0-2 down to take Game 1 in Las Vegas, 4-2, every goal let in by the Golden Knights netminder seemed to leave him in a slapstick position. The first Edmonton tally had Hill spinning like a turtle on his backside. The go-ahead game-winner late in the third period saw him uselessly holding up his glove like he was waving hello to an enemy who'd already sped by him at 160 kph. And the insurance tally, soon after, completely isolated Hill when the Other Connor—Brown—conjured a counterattack breakaway and enjoyed plenty of time to pick his spot.
But that's only three out of four! The best Oiler goal, to me, came from their most productive player all year. That's right: Leon Draisaitl. Expecting someone different?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rolling The 20-Sided Dice On Love]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189002</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rolling-the-20-sided-dice-on-love"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve dabbled in D&D, but I’ve never tried live action role-playing, otherwise known as LARPing. To be completely honest with you, I bet I’d be a happier person if I tried it. I suspect that LARPing shapes your spirit and tempers your character. 
Luckily for the people in this story, they won’t share my regrets. Today we’re bringing you a tale straight from Camp Gonedoor, where many a camper (and many a counselor) have come of age. What does it mean to come of age? For some, it may mean surviving your first midnight encounter with a Ouija board. For others, it may mean figuring out how to be the dungeon master of your own life. For our friend of a friend, it means finding the courage to figure out if his crush likes him back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Abundance Of Concrete]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188808</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-abundance-of-concrete"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T14:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable sources tell me that you're not supposed to judge a book by its cover. Until you actually read the thing, though, it's the only data you have to go on. So here's what I first noticed about Abundance, Ezra Klein's and Derek Thompson's zeitgeisty manifesto touting a construction-oriented liberalism: the wildlife. At risk of describing a jacket that you've already seen on a thousand podcast promo posts and airport bookstore racks, Abundance's cover depicts a planet neatly divided in two, with skyscrapers and farms and solar arrays juxtaposed against a jungly hemisphere replete with swooping birds and happy deer. It all recalls Half-Earth, the idea proposed by the biologist E.O. Wilson that 50 percent of our landscape should be devoted to the conservation of nature. So far, so good. 
Look a little closer, though, and you'll notice something odd: The animals don't really make sense, at least not on the cover of a book about American politics. The deer, which has the white spots of a fawn but the majestic rack of a trophy buck, is probably an Indian chital. The most conspicuous bird appears to be a scarlet ibis, a species native to South and Central America. Wherever you can find these fantastic beasts, it generally ain't this continent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Goldfarb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tyrese Haliburton Sure Knows How To Pick His Spots]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188924</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tyrese-haliburton-sure-knows-how-to-pick-his-spots"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cleveland's home crowd was caught chanting "overrated" at Pacers star Tyrese Haliburton during the second quarter of Tuesday night's Game 2. Donovan Mitchell, performing heroically for a severely depleted Cavaliers squad that was at that moment up 10 points, made an effort to discourage the chanting, but it persisted long enough to be picked up by TNT's microphones. This was a minor miracle: The production quality Tuesday was somehow even worse than it was Sunday. Greg Anthony's diving bell was even deeper into the Mariana Trench; the berserk home crowd's teeth-rattling clamor was reduced to an occasional slithering and shuffling; a bizarrely tuned court-side microphone managed to pick up no sound except for one Cavs fan screaming "bullshit" at key whistles. But the mics sure picked up that "overrated" chant. It's not that this is bad crowd behavior—it is, in fact, good and appropriate crowd behavior when facing a divisional foe in the playoffs—but it turned out that this was an unfortunate night to be caught on the record mocking Indiana's point guard.
Haliburton was quiet for most of the night, but it was generally the good kind of quiet, a biding of time that suited the contours of the game. The Cavs, still without Darius Garland but now also without top perimeter defender De'Andre Hunter plus literal Defensive Player of the Year Evan Mobley, ramped up their defensive intensity, threw their deeply unsexy point-of-attack defenders way the hell up the floor, and helped on dribble-penetration like absolute demons. The effort and precision of it all was downright stirring to watch, and it flustered several of Indiana's ball-handlers, and before the Pacers had developed anything like an offensive rhythm the scoreboard showed them down 20 points. Presumably the crowd was losing it, though I will need someone who was there in person to confirm this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popcorn time]]></title>
        <id>681a69cd74fb8d0001198e6b</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-314/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T00:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A.J. Daulerio predicts your summer cinema hits]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Preview of the Biggest and Best Summer Movies of 2025]]></title>
        <id>681a453774fb8d0001198e1a</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/a-preview-of-the-biggest-and-best-summer-movies-of-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T00:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Due to a fortunate birthdate, I was 11 years old during the vaunted “Summer of 1985” movie season which released heavy hitters like Back to the Future, Cocoon, Fletch, and Rambo: First Blood Part II. It was also jam-packed with many of my personal old favorites—Summer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>A.J. Daulerio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>