<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-08-02T10:19:17.263Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Be cool / Stay dry]]></title>
        <id>688d169b1a5c3900016b0fdb</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-373/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T22:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amy Chu’s surprising holiday destination, and a new story from Miles Klee and Mads Gobbo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ambassadors]]></title>
        <id>688d05291a5c3900016b0f72</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-ambassadors/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T22:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I inspected the water’s surface for scum, leaning slightly to block the light, pressing two fingers against my forehead to see if this time they might sink through the skull. There would be a dinner party next to the pool, at the wrought-iron patio table Georgia had had]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miles Klee  and Mads Gobbo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Window Unit Wanderer]]></title>
        <id>688cf10a1a5c3900016b0ee7</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/688cf10a1a5c3900016b0ee7/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T22:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salutations, weary travelers! Camoot here. I created my travel blog, The Window Unit Wanderer, to inspire solo travelers who want to follow their wanderlust to wherever the window unit blows. Here are my top five places to visit, including tips on how you can turn every day into a vacation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Chu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instant Expert On: The Economy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/instant-expert-on-the-economy-2ae3</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/instant-expert-on-the-economy-2ae3"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T21:09:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING—HUGE BBQ DEBATE EXPERTISE BEAT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jerry Dipoto Will Never Stop Doing Jerry Dipoto Things]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197378</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jerry-dipoto-will-never-stop-doing-jerry-dipoto-things"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T17:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the 2023 season, when the Mariners narrowly missed out on the playoffs despite having 90 percent odds of making it at the start of September, Jerry Dipoto traded Eugenio Suárez to the Arizona Diamondbacks in exchange for relief pitcher Carlos Vargas and White Sox legend Seby Zavala. The decision was, ostensibly, to trot out a lineup that struck out less often—Suarez's 214 strikeouts led the league. A fine explanation. Without it, the trade would have resembled a salary dump. Unrelatedly, this was also the offseason when Dipoto set his famous goal of winning 54 percent of games in a season.
Never mind that strikeout rates aren't correlated with raw offensive production. They certainly don't look very nice, and why not build a team for aesthetics if you aren't going to build one to win? If cutting down on strikeouts was the goal, trading away Suárez didn't immediately do the trick. The Mariners' overall strikeout rate went from 25.9 percent in 2023, or second-worst in the league, to 26.8 percent in 2024, which tied for worst in the league. At least the Mariners have improved in 2025—their 23.0 percent is only ninth-worst in MLB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: New Orleans Saints]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197344</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-new-orleans-saints"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T16:41:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the New Orleans Saints. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the New Orleans Saints. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: New Orleans Saints.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Emmanuel Clase Market Is Perhaps Understandably Bearish]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197298</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-emmanuel-clase-market-is-perhaps-understandably-bearish"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T15:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emmanuel Clase's paid leave has screwed up some plans. The news that the All-Star closer is involved in MLB’s sports betting investigation “did not simply deprive the Cleveland Guardians of their top trade chip,” The Athletic’s Ken Rosenthal reports, but also “ended any chance of the Guardians becoming a buyer.” Officially in sell mode, and without the guy expected to net a haul in a hot reliever market, the team flipped ace Shane Bieber to the Blue Jays and Paul Sewald to the Detroit Tigers on Thursday, and reportedly shopped around Gold Glove outfielder Steven Kwan.
Guardians execs were not the only ones with a lot staked on Clase. He’s one of seven baseball players who signed an agreement with the company Finlete, which allows fans to purchase shares in a player’s future earnings. The concept is a variation on the income-sharing agreements some young athletes sign to guard against career uncertainty, promising an investment firm a percentage of their future earnings in exchange for a cash advance. Big League Advance, now doing business as Big League Advantage, might be the best known of these firms: Fernando Tatis Jr. recently sued BLA, accusing them of using “exploitative, predatory business practices” when they signed him to one of these contracts at age 17. Overwhelmingly, the players signing income-sharing agreements are young Latin-American players, who are able to sign with MLB teams at a younger age and tend to receive lower signing bonuses than their drafted U.S.-born counterparts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Make Smart, Marginal Upgrades]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=469548</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/royals-make-smart-marginal-upgrades/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T15:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bailey Falter and Mike Yastrzemski fill key holes on the big league roster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Rosen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Journey With Lady Gaga Is Ever Wasted]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197214</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/no-journey-with-lady-gaga-is-ever-wasted"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T14:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to run the following tally for famous people with whom I shared a birthday: Vince Vaughn, also tall, famously made a movie where Las Vegas plays a big role; the poet Ada Limón, not so tall, whom I only learned of after high school, not that my friends at the time would have cared anyway; and Lady Gaga, not tall at all (see: her documentary Gaga: Five Foot Two), famously one of the few pop stars who loves Vegas and seems to take it on its own terms. To this day, at the mention of any of these people, I mutter “Birthday bestie.”
I believe we are all linked in some way, but reality has yet to bear this out. Once, Vaughn was shooting a movie down the street from my job, but I never saw him. I’ve not met Limón, though I know other poets who know her. As for Lady Gaga, the closest I’ve gotten thus far was the second night of her Mayhem Ball tour, which started this month. I felt a thrill of vindication that she chose to start the tour here, though it’s not so surprising. Gaga and Vegas go hand in hand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Fall Guys’ And ‘Among Us’ Gave 2020 The Parties It Needed]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196996</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/fall-guys-and-among-us-gave-2020-the-parties-it-needed"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T14:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to The Backlog, a series in which we will take a look back at 12 games from 2020 that, in one way or another, had a lasting impact on the video game industry. 
The summer of 2020 was a strange one. I remember spending afternoons in a park by my apartment in Brooklyn, a park that had drawn circles in the fake grass six feet apart from each other. I saw friends there, sat on picnic blankets and drank out in public, and even got a ticket for it once like an idiot. It was a beautiful summer, as far as the weather went, and for every long walk I took, I could push down a bit of the existential paranoia that crept along day-by-day as the COVID pandemic raged on with only whispers of a future vaccine to ebb the tide of disease and death.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Padres And Twins Did The Absolute Most At The MLB Trade Deadline]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197339</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-padres-and-twins-did-the-absolute-most-at-the-mlb-trade-deadline"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T13:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathtakingly unhinged baseball executive A.J. Preller wasted a lot of time this week calling every other dealmaker in Major League Baseball when all he really had to do was make one call to Minneapolis. Derek Falvey, the head of ball ops with the Minnesota Twins was clearing out his entire showroom, and all Preller would have had to do in order to facilitate his annual restock of the San Diego Padres was say, "I'll be over in 15 minutes with a tour bus. Pack lunches for everyone you want to get rid of and we'll have them off the lot before drinks."
Sadly, it didn't work that way, if only for efficiency's sake. Still the deed was there to be done, and the gods know Falvey and Preller tried in their own separate ways to make Thursday’s MLB trade deadline one of the most ludicrous redeployment festivals in the history of human arbitrage. Both Preller and Falvey succeeded in their personal missions, but they got something like two-thirds of the league involved in the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Minnesota Twins Are Finished]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197337</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-minnesota-twins-are-finished"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T13:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had an unusually hard time finding a feature photo to go atop this blog. Almost none of this is the fault of the couple of Getty photographers who hang around the Minnesota Twins. For one thing, I was on the hunt for an image of a player who is still on the team. But ahead of the Thursday trade deadline the Twins shipped out approximately 40 percent of their major-league roster, including nearly everyone of any present value, so the options were not great. For another—and I want to reiterate that I am not blaming anyone for this—photographers David Berding, Matt Krohn, Rob Tringali, and Brace Hemmelgarn show a strong preference for compositions featuring cool things happening and players being happy. I was looking for something that matched the vibes of what is left of the Minnesota Twins, but since I could find no recent images of Byron Buxton hitchhiking along I-35W, or of Joe Ryan staring at the horizon with tears streaking his face, I had to settle. That up there is the perma-crabbed Royce Lewis, looking ambiguously pensive; I am like 80 percent sure Lewis is still a Twin today, although he is never more than one misplaced banana peel away from a four-month stint on the injured list.
The Twins were not the only team that spent the past few days selling, but their version of selling was by far the most gruesome and dispiriting. They first entered the Deal Zone Monday, a rare early mover in a deadline that otherwise took a while to shake loose. Their swap of Chris Paddack and reliever Randy Dobnak to the Detroit Tigers for a surplus catching prospect down at the Florida Complex League signaled pretty definitively that the Twins would be parachuting out of the American League's wild card hunt. The fire sale did not shift into high gear, though, until Thursday, when some poor social media person spent the afternoon firing off "Thank You" posts to just about anyone on the roster that president of baseball operations Derek Falvey could exchange for a reasonably fresh ham sandwich.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Designate Joey Wiemer For Assignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=862420</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/royals-designate-joey-wiemer-for-assignment.html"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T03:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals designated outfielder Joey Wiemer earlier today, and shifted left-hander Kris Bubic from the 15-day injured list to the 60-day IL.  The moves cleared some 40-man roster space after a busy day of transactions for Kansas City, as Mike Yastrzemski, Bailey Falter, Stephen Kolek, and Ryan Bergert were all brought into the organization. Wiemer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peerless patter / Exquisite ennui]]></title>
        <id>688bd8da1a5c3900016af8eb</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/isssue-372/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T00:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Lehrer remembered by Jennie Rose Halperin; new fiction from Colin McGowan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pleasure of Your Company]]></title>
        <id>68717214d2c01800010a184e</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-pleasure-of-your-company/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T00:27:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over westward steelworks sizzling like diner flattop griddles the setting star’s glare pours through arches of summer flowers and falls as bloodsplatter across the first few rows of waiting guests.
“George Harrison sang…” Katie says, commencing the ceremony. 
The rest burns up in transit,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin McGowan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Lehrer Adjourns]]></title>
        <id>688bb9831a5c3900016af870</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/tom-lehrer-adjourns/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T00:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The musical satirist Tom Lehrer died at 97 last month, and though he claimed to have stoked rumors of his premature death to “cut down on his junk mail,” it still felt like it came too soon. By his own accounting, Lehrer only performed live 109 times, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennie Rose Halperin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HYDRANYM No. 10: Vote!]]></title>
        <id>688bf2111a5c3900016af9f1</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hydranym-no-10-vote/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-01T00:26:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by The Editors

The time has come, esteemed players of HYDRANYM, to select the victor of Game No. 10 from among the 21 best entries received this week on the theme of 
GAMBLE
HYDRANYM is the Creative Writing word game especially for Flaming Hydra subscribers (RULES appear below). Join in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Freddy Fermin Trade We’ve All Been Waiting For]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=469500</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/the-freddy-fermin-trade-weve-all-been-waiting-for/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T23:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals get two young pitchers with years of team control. The Padres get a reason to see less of Martín Maldonado and Elias Díaz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davy Andrews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Acquire Mike Yastrzemski]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=862256</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/giants-trade-mike-yastrzemski-royals.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T23:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have acquired outfielder Mike Yastrzemski from the Giants in a last-minute deadline swap. In exchange, the Giants will receive right-handed pitching prospect Yunior Marte. Mark Feinsand of MLB.com was the first to report that Yastrzemski was headed to Kansas City.  The deal is now official. Yastrzemski, 34, has slipped to a 97 wRC+…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals To Acquire Bailey Falter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=862182</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/royals-to-acquire-bailey-falter.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T21:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals are acquiring starter Bailey Falter from Pittsburgh, reports Jon Heyman of The New York Post. Lefty Evan Sisk and minor league first baseman Callan Moss are going back to the Pirates, reports Alex Stumpf of MLB.com. More to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Huge W, With Maitreyi Anantharaman]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197222</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-huge-w-with-maitreyi-anantharaman"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T20:06:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a worrying sense at the moment, present across a worryingly large swath of public life, that everything is shrinking. It is not a matter of any of those things dying so much as they are just kind of diminishing and getting worse, either out of simple neglect or as a reflection of cockeyed ideological preference or just due to your more familiar capitalist sadism. In your more speculative or spammy sectors, this is unsurprising; the people in charge of all that are not what you'd call nurturing, and get bored quickly. This feels and is bad, but it makes the few places where there is undeniable growth happening stand out that much more. In the case of the WNBA, which is growing fast and preparing to grow faster, it stands out doubly because so much of the discourse surrounding the league suggests that it is actually somehow in crisis. It's confusing. Thankfully we had an expert near at hand, and she had a podcast mic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Trade Freddy Fermin To Padres For Ryan Bergert, Stephen Kolek]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=861998</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/padres-to-acquire-freddy-fermin.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T18:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Padres are acquiring catcher Freddy Fermin from the Royals, according to a report from ESPN’s Jeff Passan. Right-handers Ryan Bergert and Stephen Kolek are headed to Kansas City in exchange for Fermin. The clubs have since announced the deal. Fermin, 30, heads to San Diego after parts of four seasons with the Royals. After…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: Carolina Panthers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197009</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-carolina-panthers"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T17:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the Carolina Panthers. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the Carolina Panthers. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: The house that David Tepper haunts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rangers Interested In Hunter Harvey, Phil Maton]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=861912</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/rangers-interested-in-hunter-harvey-phil-maton.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T17:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rangers are looking for bullpen help and Ken Rosenthal of The Athletic reports that Phil Maton of the Cardinals and Hunter Harvey of the Royals are two of their targets. Rosenthal also mentions Jake Bird of the Rockies and David Bednar of the Pirates but notes that the Rangers expect the asking price on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rafael Devers Is Living Proof That No One Knows Anything]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197274</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rafael-devers-is-living-proof-that-no-one-knows-anything"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T16:31:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is difficult to pinpoint the moment when transactions became more important than games, but it is indisputably true that fans love the movement of players and money from locale to locale for the same reason we love gambling—because it is busy, and because it is another chance to display our ignorance.
Until baseball's trade deadline brings July's annual Month of Bargains to a close later today, we can all imagine what our favorite team is going to do in lieu of delivering any actual work product; this will keep us both frothily engaged and emotionally and fiscally tied to the teams that otherwise drag us down. We love when our team is buying and hate when they are selling, because one implies belief and the other despair. Buying rocks, selling sucks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art Of Reading]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197268</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-art-of-reading"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T16:09:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brandy: This was my first read of The Art of Fielding, though I do have memories of it being like, A Book You Should Read back in the day. I’m not sure exactly what I was expecting but I found it quite winsome! It has an undeniable charm and there is a certain quaintness to it that I enjoyed a lot. Less baseball than I thought there would be, maybe. Am I the only one who was reading it for the first time? 
Maitreyi: I also read it for the first time! And I knew only very superficial things about it before—that it had to do with baseball, that it had been at the center of a major bidding war, and that it earned the author a big advance. It was a bit more folksy and commercial (in a good way!) than I expected. But it ended up being a book I was surprised I hadn’t read before, even if my feelings were a little mixed. Midwest campus baseball novel is very much my speed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minnesota Softball Has A Title IX Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197211</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/minnesota-softball-has-a-title-ix-problem"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T15:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On May 11, 2023, Ellerie Ulfers was pitching for Washburn High School against district rival Southwest in a varsity softball game in Minneapolis, Minn. The start time had been moved back 15 minutes, to 3:45 p.m., to accommodate an umpire’s schedule. But Ulfers shook it off; she was used to pitching under pressure and in less-than-ideal conditions—she’d been on the varsity team since the year before, as an eighth grader. (In Minneapolis, since most middle school sports were cut due to budget shortfalls in 2015, middle schoolers play on high school teams.) The game was tense, with the lead going back and forth, and by the end of the sixth inning, the score was tight: Southwest 15–Washburn 13. 
But instead of getting another chance to bat and close out the game, Ulfers and all the other athletes were told to go home.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maggie Mertens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Anthony Volpe Experience Will Give You Whiplash]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197236</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-anthony-volpe-experience-will-give-you-whiplash"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T14:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And not just from whipping your head around to track another one of his throws sailing past the first baseman. I'll be here all day. Try the veal.
Yankees shortstop Anthony Volpe has a problem. No one involved wants to use the dreaded Y-word. Yips are for Chihuahuas! It's a "defensive slump," according to his manager Aaron Boone. To Volpe, it's simply "this," as in, "I’ve never really experienced something like this." What this is is a newfound and inexplicable inability to throw a baseball where he wants it to go. Volpe has committed three errors in his last two games to push his season total to 16, the most of anyone in MLB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Times Clarifies That A Starving Child In Gaza Also Needs Medical Care]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197190</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-new-york-times-clarifies-that-a-starving-child-in-gaza-also-needs-medical-care"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T13:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People are starving in Gaza. They are starving because the Israeli government is not allowing enough food to enter, and because what food becomes sporadically available can be claimed only by those willing to enter the death traps engineered by the Gaza Humanitarian Foundation, an American and Israeli-backed private food distribution system. 
A recent report from the U.N.-affiliated Integrated Food Security Phase Classification, including data up to July 25, “indicates that famine thresholds have been reached for food consumption in most of the Gaza Strip and for acute malnutrition in Gaza City.” Because this crisis is so widespread, it will necessarily impact wide swathes of the population. There will be Palestinian men, women, and children who struggle to meet their minimal requirements for nutrition. This will happen to elderly diabetics and pregnant women and asthmatic teenagers. The frail bodies of children with conditions that impede muscle development will become frailer. That hunger will come for those already struggling to thrive makes the situation more horrifying, not less, provided you are a person who has not systematically shriveled your own moral instincts down to nothing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Jensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Time To Lock In On The Lynx And Liberty]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197227</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-time-to-lock-in-on-the-lynx-and-liberty"/>
        <updated>2025-07-31T13:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps you think that a rematch between two teams who played what might be the most thrilling WNBA Finals in league history should have arrived before the penultimate day of July. Sometimes it's best for these things to simmer, though, and in this case the time away served everyone well. The 2025 WNBA season has had months to settle into itself, to surface compelling narratives and interesting players, and here at the start of the stretch run there is one story that matters more than all the others: There are two great teams in this league, and then there's everyone else.
Before Wednesday night, the New York Liberty and Minnesota Lynx hadn't seen each other since Game 5 of the 2024 Finals, which brought an entertaining and hard-fought series to a sloppy and somewhat disappointing end. They have since maintained their perches atop the league—the Liberty entered last night's game in Minneapolis with a 17–8 record and a net rating of 8.2, second-best in the league. The Lynx carried with them a 23–4 record and a sparkling 13.2 net rating. The anticipation for this rematch was somewhat diminished by the absence of Breanna Stewart, who is out of the Liberty's lineup while dealing with a bone bruise in her knee. But these teams are good enough and deep enough to turn any meeting between them into a spectacle, and that's exactly what they did throughout Minnesota's 100–93 victory.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lustful solace / Faraway fellowship]]></title>
        <id>688a5178be970d000116dc6d</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-371/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-30T22:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reading therapy with Talia Lavin, and Brian Hioe on obstacles to solidarity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suspect Solidarities]]></title>
        <id>688a46d3be970d000116dc51</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/suspect-solidarities/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-30T22:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not too long ago, I organized an event with a Rohingya activist friend who was passing through Taiwan on vacation. It made me happy to be able to connect her to local Burmese activists; they were mostly ethnically Bamar, the majority ethnicity in Myanmar, or else Chinese Burmese, some of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Hioe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gay Smut Salvation]]></title>
        <id>688a9bb4be970d000116dec1</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/gay-smut-salvation/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-30T22:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problem: You are a writer who has spent most of the last ten years writing about very evil people, and you are witnessing their triumph, and you don’t have any money, and you don’t have any leads, and you don’t have any institutional clout,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Talia Lavin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gilbert Arenas Arrested For Running Illegal And Depressing Poker Games]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197194</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/gilbert-arenas-arrested-for-running-illegal-and-depressing-poker-games"/>
        <updated>2025-07-30T21:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gilbert Arenas has really gotta stay away from any card game that ain’t solitaire. The onetime Washington Wizards superstar, who tanked his basketball career in 2009 by bringing guns to a fistfight with a teammate over piddly gambling debts, has been arrested again, this time for his role in an allegedly off-the-books poker operation. 
According to the Department of Justice, Arenas was one of several card players—including a man named Yevgeni Gershman, who the DOJ describes as a "suspected organized crime figure from Israel"—taken into custody in Los Angeles today for running a recurring high-stakes game of poker at a house he owned in Encino, Calif. Details in the DOJ's release give the impression that Arenas was essentially arrested for hosting grim men's evenings:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Bad-Faith Unreality Crashes Into Reality]]></title>
        <id>688a642ef05bc90001adadc6</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/when-bad-faith-unreality-crashes-into-reality/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-30T19:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These people do not mean what they say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Men’s Health Article Hallucinates Luka Doncic With A 42-Inch Vertical]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197104</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mens-health-article-hallucinates-luka-doncic-with-a-42-inch-vertical"/>
        <updated>2025-07-30T18:18:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Luka Doncic took part in a time-honored tradition employed by many athletes before him: a news cycle about how he's in the best shape of his life. As the Lakers star made a trip to New York, showing up at Yankee Stadium and Dyckman Park to promote a shoe or whatever, Men's Health published a feature on his summer training regimen. One specific detail about his physique sounded incredible, in the literal sense of the word.
The feature, co-written by Andrew Heffernan and Ebenezer Samuel, presents an inside look at how Doncic is getting lean and strong with his trainer in Croatia. You can probably guess where this is going. He's not just getting up shots—he's lifting weights. He's working on his conditioning. He's doing something with a resistance band. He's eating better:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Have You Heard? They’re Touching It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197169</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/have-you-heard-theyre-touching-it"/>
        <updated>2025-07-30T17:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps you have given yourself over to Cucumber Season and are not paying attention to the dog days of the baseball season. It may then come as news to you that they're touching it. They're all touching it, all the time, and it is working. 
After losing 12 of 13, Tigers outfielder Riley Greene shaved off his beard but left his mustache, and since then Detroit has won three straight. Are these two things related? Is the mustache winning baseball games? Who can say. One thing we can say with absolute certainty is that they are touching it, early and often.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Sox Dance To Commemorate The Flight From Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197120</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/red-sox-dance-to-commemorate-the-flight-from-hell"/>
        <updated>2025-07-30T17:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Boston Red Sox encountered significant turbulence on a team flight to Minneapolis Sunday night. Big deal, you are saying, from the comfort of your office chair. It is at least a moderate deal. We are not talking about the zippy little Space Mountain stuff that makes passengers giggle during approach. Passengers in this case were lifted from their seats and bounced around violently, and several people barfed all over the place. The flight had to make an unscheduled landing in Detroit, so unstable was the weather, and did not finally land in Minneapolis until around 1:00 a.m. Several Red Sox players were still feeling sick and beat up the following day, and reliever Garrett Whitlock had to miss the series opener due to lingering aftereffects. Two Red Sox players and one broadcaster called it the worst turbulence they'd ever experienced, per MassLive, and these are people who do a lot of flying.
"Forty-five minutes straight of left, right, dropping down," recalled Lucas Giolito, who compared the experience unfavorably to a roller coaster. "Sitting on a plane, it was like, oh boy. At one point, I kind of flew up out of my seat. I was like, 'OK, it’s time to put the seatbelt on.'" Giolito says he was comforted by the knowledge that "commercial airline jets never crash from turbulence," information that he picked up from watching The Rehearsal, a show that I have never watched and that from my experience entirely defies explanation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: New York Jets]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197129</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-new-york-jets"/>
        <updated>2025-07-30T16:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the New York Jets. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the New York Jets. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: THEY’RE A BRICK! HOUSE!/THEY’RE NEVER RIGHTY/THEY’RE LETTIN’ IT ALLLLL HANG OUT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Favorite Part Of ‘Anna Karenina’ Is The Guy Who Can’t Stop Himself From Talking About Mushrooms]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=197117</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/my-favorite-part-of-anna-karenina-is-the-guy-who-cant-stop-himself-from-talking-about-mushrooms"/>
        <updated>2025-07-30T16:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just read Leo Tolstoy's 1870s novel Anna Karenina for the first time, and I am treating it like a real accomplishment. For basically all of my life, whenever I've heard reference to Tolstoy—OK, mostly War And Peace specifically, but whatever—it's felt like he's been hanging high above my head, his essence incomprehensible to my less-developed brain. He's so revered and so synonymous with supersized, challenging literature that he felt, basically, like the final boss of reading. 
What surprised me about Anna Karenina, however, is that on a sentence level, it isn't tough at all. It was listed under "YA" at my library, sure, but I kind of thought that was some sort of trick to lure young people into giving a classic a shot. The language in my copy was so basic and so direct about what was happening that I actually looked up the translation to make sure I hadn't accidentally grabbed some sort of "No Fear Shakespeare" version of the novel. (Apparently, Louise and Aylmer Maude were pals of Leo's back in the day, so I trust that they were faithful.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLBTR Podcast: Megapod Trade Deadline Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=861426</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/mlbtr-podcast-megapod-trade-deadline-preview.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-30T16:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest episode of the MLB Trade Rumors Podcast is now live on Spotify, Apple Podcasts, and wherever you get your podcasts! Make sure you subscribe as well! You can also use the player at this link to listen, if you don’t use Spotify or Apple for podcasts. This week, host Darragh McDonald is joined by Steve Adams and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Art Of Fielding’ Knows What’s Scary About Baseball]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196842</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-art-of-fielding-knows-whats-scary-about-baseball"/>
        <updated>2025-07-30T15:23:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can still remember the sound of the dull thud, and the scream that came after. It was a tournament game, and our pitcher, Paul, was dealing. He always did, because he could throw 80 mph as a 13-year-old, and he never missed the catcher's mitt. Games with Paul on the mound were easy; I'd just stand at my position at second or first base and watch the strikeouts accumulate while feeling sorry for the kids on the other team who had to quiver through each at-bat. Paul was the best player any of us had ever seen. During this game, though, a fastball got away from him and sailed directly into the cheekbone of the batter, Josh, a kid we all knew and were friends with. There was a sound like a mallet hitting meat, followed by the muffled ping of the bat hitting the ground just before Josh's body, and then the most upsetting scream I've ever heard.
An ambulance came for Josh (he ended up being fine, I'm not sure if he even broke a bone), and the game continued without him. Paul spent most of the delay crouched between home plate and the mound, his hat pulled down as far as it would go. Somehow he stayed in the game, and got through the next few innings while soft-tossing balls over the plate. Paul, who up until that point I could only perceive as a mythically good ballplayer, was scared. He didn't want to hurt anyone else.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Did National Geographic Disappear Its Own Documentary About A Queer Climate Scientist?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196877</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-did-national-geographic-disappear-its-own-documentary-about-a-queer-climate-scientist"/>
        <updated>2025-07-30T13:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re not a particular kind of mountain sports nerd, you might not be familiar with the Banff Centre Mountain Film Festival World Tour. But for people who live their lives in the overlapping circles of outdoor and adventure sports, environmental and conservation sciences, and nonfiction storytelling, it’s a touchstone. The parent festival has been held in Banff, Alberta, for decades—it will celebrate its 50th anniversary later this year—and the tour brings a tight selection of the featured films to more than 40 countries every year. 
Barring a true outlier like Free Solo, which made it all the way to the Oscars, getting on the Banff world tour is about as big as it gets in this corner of the filmmaking world. So it meant a lot when 600 people packed into the largest theater at the Banff Centre for Arts and Creativity on a Thursday evening last October to watch the world premiere of For Winter, a feature-length documentary from the National Geographic Society’s acclaimed Impact Story Lab.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eva Holland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feathered friends / Film fans]]></title>
        <id>68892e80be970d000116c56b</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-370/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T22:04:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A city bird reconsidered by Ben Ehrenreich; the Hydra invites readers to choose some fun movies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Praise of Pigeons]]></title>
        <id>6887b93619c0620001dfb253</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/in-praise-of-pigeons/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T22:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the second half of the second year of Israel’s genocide in Gaza, as my own country performs an astonishing act of auto-evisceration, midway through the next hottest summer since last year’s hottest summer ever, I would like to talk to you about pigeons. The birds,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Ehrenreich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HYDRANYM No. 10]]></title>
        <id>68893452be970d000116c5e9</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hydranym-no-10/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T22:02:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by The Editors

Subscribe to Flaming Hydra to play HYDRANYM! And tell your friends who love WORD GAMES because this one is fun.


[countdown to 2025-07-31 12:00am PDT]
Let's ride.
COME BACK THURSDAY, JULY 31
TO CHOOSE THE WINNER!!! 

THE RULES
Create an ENTERTAINING and APT acronym]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HYDRANYM No. 10]]></title>
        <id>68893452be970d000116c5e9</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hydranym-no-9-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T22:02:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by The Editors

Subscribe to Flaming Hydra to play HYDRANYM! And tell your friends who love WORD GAMES because this one is fun.

[countdown to 2025-07-31 12:00am PDT]
Let's ride.
COME BACK THURSDAY, JULY 31
TO CHOOSE THE WINNER!!! 

THE RULES
Create an ENTERTAINING and APT acronym]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ichiro Saved One Last Surprise For Cooperstown]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196895</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ichiro-saved-one-last-surprise-for-cooperstown"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T21:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Hall of Fame case does not get built in the same way, or out of the same things, as a legend. There are plenty of Hall of Famers who managed to build compelling cases, in the methodical and accumulative way that such cases are built, without throwing off much in the way of mythos along the way. They get plaques, too, and deserve them. They also accrue the same, inevitable sort of legend that every big leaguer attracts on the way up; everyone who ever faced Scott Rolen in high school could and probably will tell you about the experience, just as my former coworker who once served up a 450-foot homer to Orlando Hudson in a college game would invariably bring it up when even a narrow window of opportunity opened. I should be clear that I think this is absolutely the right thing to do. Even …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Body Is A Machine That Turns Money Into Posts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/my-body-is-a-machine-that-turns-money-into-posts-ca33</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/my-body-is-a-machine-that-turns-money-into-posts-ca33"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T21:21:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zaslav floats on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Designate Rich Hill For Assignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=861296</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/royals-designate-rich-hill-for-assignment.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T20:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that veteran southpaw Rich Hill has been designated for assignment.  The move opens up roster space for right-hander Thomas Hatch, whose contract has been selected from Triple-A Omaha. More to come…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The READER POLL! of Fun Movies]]></title>
        <id>68817aba19c0620001df671e</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-reader-poll-of-fun-movies/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T19:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks: Las Vegas Raiders]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196816</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-las-vegas-raiders"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T18:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the Las Vegas Raiders. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the Las Vegas Raiders. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: Las Vegas, nee Oakland, nee Los Angeles, nee Oakland Raiders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behold: A Surprisingly Beautiful Depiction Of Being Swallowed By A Toothy Penis Worm]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196640</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/behold-a-surprisingly-beautiful-depiction-of-being-swallowed-by-a-toothy-penis-worm"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T17:32:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When scientists discover new prehistoric species, the fossils alone fail to conjure the creature in the flesh. It's impossible to summon the entirety ancient shark from a single tooth, or some weird old rodent from a fragment of a jaw. This is where paleoart comes in, with illustrations that help you imagine how such an animal might have looked in its heyday. But very few of these visualizations dare to take one step further and help you imagine what it would be like to be caught, swallowed, and digested by that animal—until now.
Imagine you are a small living creature or a scrap of a dead one, drifting in the shallows over an innocuous patch of sand. But what is that? Suddenly that dimple in the sand has unfurled into a daunting pillar of a worm. But it this is not just any worm; it is Kraytdraco spectatus, an ancient penis worm that lurked in the sludge of the shallow seas swathing the Grand Canyon during the Cambrian. And K. specatus is about to eat you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OK But What If The Billionaire Is A Cool Guy?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196914</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ok-but-what-if-the-billionaire-is-a-cool-guy"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T16:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about lead singers, cooking screwups, whining children, and more.
Drew is off! I am your Dread Funbag Lord for today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Robbin’ Padres Took Away A Home Run Before Anyone Knew What Happened]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196991</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-robbin-padres-took-away-a-home-run-before-anyone-knew-what-happened"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T15:29:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Folks with fancy degrees will tell you that kleptomania is a mental illness, but I bet those doctors never watched a San Diego Padres game. On a couple of occasions already this month, Kelsey has covered how the outfielders of the Robbin' Padres so spectacularly take away would-be dingers from their opponents, almost like they have a compulsion to steal. And yet their victims persist in hitting balls to that area just above the top of the fence. The latest of these poor marks was the New York Mets, who traveled all the way to Southern California only to discover that their hosts were thieves who like nothing more than swiping taters while thousands of locals cheer them on.
San Diego's big heist came in the fourth inning of Monday's series opener—thankfully, well after any impressionable children on the east coast would have already gone to bed. Mark Vientos went the other way on some high cheese from Dylan Cease, smacking it way out to right center. But Fernando Tatis Jr. owns that territory, and if you want to do business, you gotta go through him. The SD star gathered, leaped high off the warning track, and stretched his glove over the top of the fence to reel back what had seemed like a sure-thing four-bagger. Tatis was such a stealthy, athletic robber in this instance that even Padres play-by-play man Don Orsillo had no idea what he did. First, he called it as a home run, and then when Tatis fumbled the ball on the transfer into his glove, Orsillo assumed Vientos had hit it off the wall. That's the sneakiness of all the best bandits: They stay two steps ahead of whatever you're thinking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minor MLB Transactions: 7/29/25]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=861224</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/minor-mlb-transactions-7-29-25.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T15:29:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s the latest on some players who were recently designated for assignment and cleared waivers, with all info coming from each respective player’s MLB.com profile page… Reliever Chris Devenski elected free agency rather than accept an outright assignment to the Mets’ Triple-A team.  New York designated Devenski for assignment last week, and since he has…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some More Stuff I Saw At The Tour de France]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196760</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/some-more-stuff-i-saw-at-the-tour-de-france"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T14:19:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VARIOUS CITIES (SOME ARGUABLY TOWNS), France — The Tour de France is over. I hope you enjoyed the racing and the 11 dispatches I was able to bring you from the race, on topics such as how language works in the peloton, a day in the life of a neutral service mechanic, and Tadej Pogacar's stultifying dominance. This is the last one before I go on vacation.
As I hope to have illustrated, the Tour is less a bike race than a rollicking circus that happens to have a bike race at its center. The bike race and the circus both matter, and I've tried to highlight both, though there were so many strange and delightful things that I saw, heard, and experienced that could not fit into otherwise wieldy blogposts. Instead they will fit here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christian Wilkins Saga Gains Smooch-Based Dimension]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196979</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/christian-wilkins-saga-gains-smooch-based-dimension"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T13:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defensive tackle Christian Wilkins was released by the Raiders last week, which immediately scanned as just another instance of the franchise deploying its "trip over your own feet" philosophy of roster construction. Yes, it's strange to release a guy who you just signed to a four-year deal with $84 million guaranteed last offseason, but that's how bad teams do business. 
Conscious of how a move like this would look, the Raiders had an explanation ready to be disseminated through various league insiders: Wilkins, who suffered a Jones fracture in his foot last October, was refusing to follow the team's recommendation to have a second surgery on his foot, and therefore the Raiders were not only releasing him but seeking to recoup $35.2 million of guaranteed money that remains on his contract.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Earth’s Best Logroller Has Created Her Own Greatest Rival]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194568</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/earths-best-logroller-has-created-her-own-greatest-rival"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T13:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am sitting on a dock in the Wisconsin sun. About 15 feet away, Livi Pappadopoulos and Aini Anderson are walking on water. The first and (now) second-ranked women in logrolling are sharing a No. 3 log (13 inches in diameter, No. 3 because it is third-widest) and a full conversation. "Can I flex for a second?" Livi asks. Aini says sure. "The other day I came out here alone and got a little roll in on the No. 5, probably half an hour, and then brought it back to the dock and pulled it up onto the dock all without getting wet." Though the No. 5 is the smallest, not even used by pros in competition, it would still be about 270 pounds (when dry), round, and in the situation Livi is describing, also wet and slippery. None of that seems remotely possible. It does not even occur to me to doubt her.
I got into logrolling the same way everyone does: I was hanging out in the Midwest looking for a way to kill a Saturday. On this particular weekend, the La Crosse Open was happening, so I just showed up. It was a pretty low-key, casual affair. The spectators were mostly locals who knew someone in the event, or people who didn't really know what they were looking at but were quite happy to have a beer and a brat while watching something cool for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Bloom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slow burn / Long drive]]></title>
        <id>6887743819c0620001dfb195</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-369/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T00:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Thielman on the world changed by Gaza; new poems by Kọ́lá Túbọ̀sún]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aversion Therapy]]></title>
        <id>6887d60919c0620001dfb293</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/aversion-therapy/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T00:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Israeli government treated the attacks on kibbutzim close to the Gaza border on October 7, 2023, like a starter pistol. The fantasy of extermination, it soon became clear, had an unshakable hold on the imaginations that commanded the IDF, and within days, Netanyahu’s cabinet was talking about]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Thielman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Summer Poems]]></title>
        <id>6887cb0619c0620001dfb277</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/three-summer-poems/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-29T00:32:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kọ́lá Túbọ̀sún</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Bubic To Miss Remainder Of 2025 Season With Rotator Cuff Strain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=861048</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/kris-bubic-to-miss-remainder-of-2025-season-with-rotator-cuff-strain.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T21:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Royals left-hander Kris Bubic will be out for the remainder of the 2025 season after suffering a rotator cuff strain in his most recent outing, reports Anne Rogers of MLB.com. The 27-year-old exited his start on Saturday in the third inning, later telling Rogers that “something’s not right.” He noted that he had been pitching…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leo Morgenstern</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At The Very Least, The Atlanta Dream Are Worth Watching]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196885</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/at-the-very-least-the-atlanta-dream-are-worth-watching"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T20:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 32-point, eight-rebound, seven-assist, four-steal, two-block performance is just the kind of thing you can expect from Napheesa Collier these days. She began the year favored to win MVP, and halfway through the WNBA season, she’s done nothing to sway voters in any another direction. Her Minnesota Lynx sit comfortably in first place; their biggest challengers will have to weather some time without Breanna Stewart, who left a recent Liberty game with a lower leg injury. The Lynx are still a model of steadiness, able to overwhelm opponents with sheer precision on both ends of the floor. 
Which is why a 32-point, eight-rebound, seven-assist, four-steal, two-block Napheesa Collier performance in a loss at home is just not the kind of thing you’d expect from them. Before last weekend (and excluding the Commissioner’s Cup Final), Minnesota was 14-0 in their own building this season, a franchise-record home win streak for a franchise whose records are tough to break. But it came to an end Sunday in a 90-86 loss to the Atlanta Dream, who are finally, after many years, interesting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Era Of Gaelic Football Suits David Clifford And Kerry Just Fine]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196929</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-new-era-of-gaelic-football-suits-david-clifford-and-kerry-just-fine"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T20:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Gaelic football season of massive upheaval ended just like so many others had: With Kerry winning another All-Ireland championship. The recognized all-time kings of the game, now led by David Clifford, who at 26 years old is already hailed as history’s greatest Gael footballer, blitzed Donegal early and then fairly coasted to a 10-point win, 1-26 to 0-19. The triumph, coming in front of more than 82,000 manic green-and-gold clad fans who packed Dublin’s legendary Croke Park, gave Kerry their 39th title in a competition that dates back to 1887. No other county comes close.
The 2025 tournament was the first held since the sport’s sanctioning body, the Gaelic Athletic Association, installed several momentous rule changes in hopes of opening up offenses. The alterations included forbidding back passes to goalies, and also short kickouts from goalies. But the most radical of the new edicts, and likely the most radical rule change ever foisted upon Irish football (and one which indicates Steph Curry’s sporting influence transcends the USA and basketball), came with the addition of a two-point arc 40 meters from the center of the goal line. The new line, according to the godfathers of the nationalistic pastime, would prevent coaches from stuffing the area in front of the goal with defenders, and thereby lead to both goal-scoring opportunities and long, majestic shots from play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emmanuel Clase Placed On Leave While MLB Conducts Gambling Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196903</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/emmanuel-clase-placed-on-leave-while-mlb-conducts-gambling-investigation"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T19:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Monday, ESPN's Jeff Passan reported, and the Cleveland Guardians confirmed with an official statement, that Guardians closer Emmanuel Clase has been placed on "non-disciplinary paid leave as part of MLB's sports-betting investigation" until Aug. 31. This leave comes as part of the investigation into Clase's teammate, Luis L. Ortiz, who was placed on leave earlier in the month after a betting-integrity firm flagged abnormal betting activity on two specific pitches he threw.
Clase, an All-Star and three-time American League leader in saves, has a much higher profile than Ortiz. His name has been floating around trade talks this year; as Bob Nightengale has helpfully noted, his administrative leave means he is presumably no longer on the trade block. A note on language: While being placed on leave resembles a suspension—the player is not permitted to play—it is, in the language Passan uses, explicitly non-disciplinary before the conclusion of the investigation. This is the same language used in league investigations into domestic violence cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryce Harper Opens Negotiations On MLB’s Salary Cap Proposal By Telling Rob Manfred To “Get The Fuck Out”]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196910</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bryce-harper-opens-negotiations-on-mlbs-salary-cap-proposal-by-telling-rob-manfred-to-get-the-fuck-out"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T18:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the current my-truth era everyone is not just permitted but encouraged to pretend they're right whether or not they actually are. The deranged and deranging downsides of this are obvious and everywhere, but one of the smaller of those is that heroes are by now pretty much an eye-of-the-beholder thing. For instance, our Philadelphia Bureau is pretty in on Bryce Harper because, well, because he's Bryce Harper. Even now, in a comparatively meh season—various injuries have led him to put up some fine if not quite Harperian numbers—he's pretty much whatever you make of him, as athletic golden boys in their 32-year tend to be.
Unless of course he does something like offer to throw the commissioner of baseball out of the Phillies clubhouse skidding down the hallway face first, in which case Harper becomes not a hero or even a golden boy, but a full-on god. And we say that while being fully cognizant that the baseline for godhood does not usually involve bumrushing a 66-year-old lawyer out of a room as though he were just another loud and obnoxious drunk at a corner bar. Bryce Harper is a god, period, full stop, and we are not accepting countervailing views. You want to argue? Go get in a fight with your neighbor. He's been tardy on the rosebush trimming all summer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: Jacksonville Jaguars]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196853</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-jacksonville-jaguars"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T17:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the Jacksonville Jaguars. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the Jacksonville Jaguars. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: Jacksonville Jaguars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the $5 DVD Bin at Walmart of the Trade Deadline]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=468993</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/welcome-to-the-5-dvd-bin-at-walmart-of-the-trade-deadline/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T16:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immaculate Grid just got slightly easier because of the Randall Grichuk, Gregory Soto, and Erick Fedde trades, so enjoy that while you can.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Baumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mattie Goes To A Yoga Class]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196535</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mattie-goes-to-a-yoga-class"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T16:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first time I did yoga was in a beachside studio in Ewa Beach, Hawaii in 2010. I was visiting my family there for the summer and my mom had recently become a regular at the studio. I remember the smell of incense in the stifling room and the shapes of other womens' bodies prone on their multicolored mats, completely locked into whatever physio-spiritual ritual I had stumbled into. 
I felt uncomfortable with the amount of chanting we did, but I liked the movement in the class enough to come back the next week. In the 15 years since I took that class, I've introduced several friends and romantic partners to yoga and I recognize the look of intimidation in their eyes when they first enter a studio with low light and lofi beats playing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No One’s Ever Been Better Than CC Sabathia On The Brewers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196834</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/no-ones-ever-been-better-than-cc-sabathia-on-the-brewers"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T15:41:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CC Sabathia became a star in Cleveland, and became a champion in New York, and this weekend became a Hall of Famer in Cooperstown—but I will always think of Milwaukee. Possibly the greatest midseason rental of all time, Sabathia's 17 starts that carried the 2008 Brewers to their first postseason in 26 years remains my byword for dominance. I will go to my grave swearing that his stretch was the greatest I've ever seen by a pitcher; I will brook no arguments to the contrary. Perhaps this is hagiography over historiography. Don't care! It's the Hall of Fame, not the Hall of Objectivity. Sabathia was a warhorse.
It wasn't just, or even, about being unhittable. It was about Sabathia's tirelessness—his sheer, sustained ability to take the ball and not give it up. He threw on short rest. He threw to the 27th out. He threw and threw and threw, as many as 130 pitches in one start, and then he threw some more. He strapped a big honking icepack to his left shoulder (Atlas might've envied its sturdiness) and then he threw again. He made it seem like dominance was a matter of willpower.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, July 28: When You Win, Say Nothing (Themeless)]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196848</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-july-28-when-you-win-say-nothing-themeless"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T15:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time to to wrap up the month with a challenging themeless. Keep an eye out for tricky clues and fun wordplay. This week’s puzzle was constructed by Willa Angel Chen Miller and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE. Note that our submissions are closed through July 31.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Tour de France’s New, Hardcore Paris Finale Was One For The Ages]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196809</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-tour-de-frances-new-hardcore-paris-finale-was-one-for-the-ages"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T13:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PARIS — Four hours before the final stage of the Tour de France begins, I walk the length of the last, newest climb on the race parcours. This is only possible on the course itself, as thousands of fans have packed themselves dense against the barriers, the lucky few enjoying cafe tables or spots inside second-floor apartments, the vast majority simply standing and waiting to see how the riders would contend with a Paris novelty: difficult racing. Two thirds of the way up, a group of singing French lads build to a crescendo before launching a baguette across the course. A corresponding lad on the far side takes a honking bite from the loaf, and ritually hurls it back, on and on until the baguette disappears to rapturous peals of joy. This is the Col de la Butte Montmartre.
Paris is always the end of the Tour, unless it's an Olympic year, and it's almost always a parade. Three weeks in, and every rider, mechanic, and sleep scientist with the Tour, not to mention its cheese-addled press corps, is exhausted and wants nothing more than to sleep for 36 straight hours. The final stage is usually a champagne toast on wheels, with the winners of various classifications taking turns riding to the front of the pack for photo-ops before the peloton arrives in the city and turns a few leisurely laps around the Champs-Élysées; then the sprinters duke it out one last time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simply Invent Rain Control To Ensure A Thrilling Belgian Grand Prix]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196775</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/simply-invent-rain-control-to-ensure-a-thrilling-belgian-grand-prix"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T13:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before this year's rendition of the Belgian Grand Prix, it was all feeling a little bit 2021. The Circuit de Spa-Francorchamps that year was wet and untenable. With race direction unwilling to cancel the event, the cars paraded about for two laps under the safety car before the race was red flagged and never restarted. Officially, the race was logged as lasting one lap and under seven kilometers. The points finishers, led by Max Verstappen, George Russell (in a Williams), and Lewis Hamilton, received half of the regularly allotted points. In a sport and season with no shortage of farces, the 2021 Belgian GP still managed to stand out as noticeable clown show—yet more history for one of the most beautiful, legendary, cruel tracks on the calendar.
Four years later, and spectators were getting some unfortunate flashbacks. Rain was aggressively forecast throughout the weekend, which it is wont to do in Stavelot, Belgium. On Sunday, the Formula 3 feature race was canceled. Uh-oh. Then the Formula 2 feature race managed to run in wet conditions. Joyous days! Then race control repeatedly punted the start of the Formula 1 feature race. Uh-oh, again. Then the rain petered out, and then stopped. Out of an abundance of caution, the race started under a safety car, which led for four laps. By the time it pulled in, the track was already drying.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Finalizing Extension With Seth Lugo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=860909</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/royals-finalizing-extension-with-seth-lugo.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-28T01:29:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals and Seth Lugo are in the final stages of negotiating a multi-year contract extension, ESPN’s Jeff Passan reports.  Lugo had the ability to opt out of the final season of his previous three-year, $45MM contract, but instead of facing an opt-out decision this winter, the right-hander will be staying put in Kansas City. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chloe Kelly Carried England To The Promised Land]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196779</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/chloe-kelly-carried-england-to-the-promised-land"/>
        <updated>2025-07-27T20:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After 360 minutes of knockout play, two penalty shootouts, and three comebacks, England is the back-to-back champion of Europe. Despite losing its first game of Euro 2025 against France, and despite an arduous run to the final that further extended into extra time and penalties, England held off the reigning World Cup winner Spain to lift the trophy thanks to a 3-1 penalty shootout win. It was the last gutsy victory in a line of gutsy victories, each seeing England down and out but never completely lost. The Lionesses are worthy champions, even if they only led for a total of four minutes in the knockout rounds.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=99bgTARgKD8]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Thoughts About ‘The Fantastic Four: First Steps’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196770</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/four-thoughts-about-the-fantastic-four-first-steps"/>
        <updated>2025-07-27T17:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Fantastic Four movie came out this weekend, and both Luis Paez-Pumar and Lauren Theisen went to theaters to see it. Here are four thoughts that they shared about the reboot of Marvel’s first family.
1. This is yet another superhero blockbuster, but it’s nice that it’s more about space explorers than crime fighters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Place Jac Caglianone On 10-Day Injured List]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=860791</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/royals-place-jac-caglianone-on-10-day-injured-list.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-27T15:42:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced this morning that they’ve placed outfielder Jac Caglianone on the 10-day injured list due to a left hamstring strain. His active roster spot will go to outfielder Randal Grichuk, who the club acquired from the Diamondbacks last night. Caglianone, 22, was the sixth overall selection in last year’s draft and entered the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Bubic Battling Shoulder Stiffness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=860831</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/kris-bubic-battling-shoulder-stiffness.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-27T15:12:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals appear to be inching more closely to buying than selling given their recent acquisition of Diamondbacks outfielder Randal Grichuk, but talented southpaw Kris Bubic has been a much speculated-upon trade candidate this summer nonetheless. Recent indications have been that the Royals aren’t inclined to part ways with the lefty, and that may be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tadej Pogacar And The Boredom Of Perfection]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196530</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tadej-pogacar-and-the-boredom-of-perfection"/>
        <updated>2025-07-27T14:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PARIS — Tadej Pogacar rolled across the line atop La Plagne wet and miserable. The yellow jersey appeared to weigh him down, like a suit of armor worn to guard against heavy blows which couldn't reach him anyway. His expression never shifted out of bland disgruntlement the entire way up the final summit finish of the Tour de France. With Thymen Arensman all but bleeding out a couple of seconds in front of a small group composed of this year's podium, and a stage win hanging in the balance, the sport's greediest winner sat there, indifferent. He had won four stages and built his Tour-winning margin a week ago, so what was the point of extra suffering? The race was over. What could have been gained from punishing his rivals even further? Why win more than necessary?
These are not questions Pogacar has even entertained before. Pogacar's defining trait as a competitor—the aspect that's made him not only a champion but the most feared rider on the road—is his insatiability. For the second time in his illustrious career, Pogacar has won two Tour de Frances in a row. But for the first time, the prospect of winning seems to bore him. "I'm at a point where I wonder why I'm still here," he said after La Plagne. "It's been three very long weeks. You're counting down the kilometers to Paris. I can't wait until it's over so I can have some fun things in my life again."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Acquire Randal Grichuk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=860783</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/royals-to-acquire-randal-grichuk.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-27T00:31:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Diamondbacks’ sell-off continues this evening as they’re trading outfielder Randal Grichuk to the Royals, according to a report from Steve Gilbert of MLB.com. Jon Heyman of the New York Post reports that right-hander Andrew Hoffmann is headed to Arizona in exchange for Grichuk’s services. John Gambadoro of 98.7 FM Phoenix reports that Hoffmann, who…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HYDRANYM No. 9: Vote!]]></title>
        <id>6883cecc19c0620001df97c9</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hydranym-no-9-vote/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-26T00:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by The Editors

It is your solemn duty to select the victor of Hydranym No. 9, from among the 21 best entries received this week on the theme of
MEETING
HYDRANYM is the Creative Writing word game especially for Flaming Hydra subscribers (RULES appear below). Join in by subscribing! It&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gratuitous gratuities]]></title>
        <id>6883cf6419c0620001df9806</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-368/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-26T00:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[George Orwell’s days scrambling for tips, by Diana Moskovitz]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tipping George Orwell]]></title>
        <id>68827f4e19c0620001df7c81</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/tipping-george-orwell/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-26T00:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[George Orwell was just 26 in 1929, when, the story goes, he had nearly all his money stolen from his digs in Paris. He was a middle-class, well-educated young man who could almost certainly have gotten help from his aunt Nellie, who lived in the French capital. But instead he]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need To Talk About Sloppers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/we-need-to-talk-about-sloppers-b732</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/we-need-to-talk-about-sloppers-b732"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T20:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best ever death metal bot out of Denton]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dominique Malonga Gets It Done In Small Doses]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196725</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dominique-malonga-gets-it-done-in-small-doses"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T19:58:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dominique Malonga is an unusual player in unusual circumstances for a rookie. Most lottery picks are consigned to at least one year of joker teammates, demoralizing blowouts, and moral victories only. “Being bad” is generally the reason teams end up in the lottery at all. First-overall pick Paige Bueckers, for instance, will almost surely lose more games with the Dallas Wings this year than she did in her entire UConn career. To the extent that there’s any silver lining in playing on a loser, it’s the chance to get lots of low-stakes reps in different roles and alongside different people. Bueckers is also averaging nearly 35 minutes a game, fourth-most in the league, more than the likes of Napheesa Collier, Breanna Stewart, Alyssa Thomas and A’ja Wilson, the usual workhorse suspects.
Malonga, who went second-overall to the Seattle Storm, is not quite averaging 10 minutes a game this year. That’s no huge surprise. Bueckers entered her rookie season as a polished plug-and-play guard four years Malonga’s senior. And from draft night, it was pretty clear that the timelines of the 19-year-old Malonga and of the Seattle core—Nneka Ogwumike, Skylar Diggins, Gabby Williams, and Ezi Magbegor—might be slightly misaligned. But this isn’t a terrible fit for a raw young player who’s evoked some “baby giraffe” comparisons as she gets used to the pace and intensity of WNBA basketball.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Designate Cavan Biggio For Assignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=860570</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/royals-dfa-cavan-biggio.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T19:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced Friday that infielder/outfielder Cavan Biggio has been designated for assignment. His spot on the 40-man roster will go to reliever Hunter Harvey, who has been reinstated from the 60-day injured list. Righty Jonathan Bowlan has been optioned to Triple-A. Biggio, 30, signed a minor league deal with the Royals in the offseason.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Such Brave Girls’ Wants To Trauma Bond With You]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196729</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/such-brave-girls-wants-to-trauma-bond-with-you"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T17:58:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there’s a line that sums up Such Brave Girls, it might be this one: "Remember the family crest: Ignore, Repress, Forget." The extremely British show, now in its second season on Hulu, isn’t one to let subtlety get in the way of its satire.
Such Brave Girls follows the all-girl Johnson family in the aftermath of the man of the house abandoning them after popping out for some tea bags. There’s single mom Deb (Louise Brealey), left in debt, who can't stand her cheap, moronic boyfriend but suffers through it with an eye on his huge house. There’s older sister Josie (show creator Kat Sadler) who is a lesbian with a case of clinical depression/anxiety and a simpering, actively oblivious boyfriend. And there’s younger, hyper-femme sister Billie (Lizzie Davidson), the real-life sister of Sadler and an unhinged highlight, who is chasing after her own useless drug-dealing boyfriend. “Ultimately the show is a family sitcom about trauma," Sadler has said, "but it’s more about us being narcissistic losers who are pathetically obsessed with what people think about us.” The second season opens with Josie in an art theory lecture as her mother and sister burst in, throw a hood over her head, and abduct her, only to remove the hood when they arrive at ... her wedding day. "This is the happiest day of your life, Josie," her mother says, holding up a white dress like it's a threat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is No Tour de France Without The Tour de Brands]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196720</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/there-is-no-tour-de-france-without-the-tour-de-brands"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T17:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALBERTVILLE, France — Hours before the start of Stage 19 of the Tour de France, the day's real competition is already well underway. Civilians and workers alike stalk the caravan, seeking goodies. A gendarme engages in barter with a representative from La Vache Qui Rit (the Laughing Cow). Each side wants what the other has: merch. 
Ultimately, the cop trades two official Tour de France police patches and two bananas for a dozen cycling caps adorned with the beautiful laughing cow logo and as many t-shirts. I have been trying to secure a shirt for a week, but when we beg for some, the representative offers a chagrined smile and tells us he is out, as he hands us hat after hat. On the hats is the eponymous laughing cow, wearing earrings of the brand's trademark cheese wheels, each featuring a laughing cow of their own, who is wearing the earrings as well—an infinitely recursive abyss of bovine mirth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Pursuit Of Personal Taste]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196473</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/in-pursuit-of-personal-taste"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T16:51:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Listening Habits, a column where I share the music I’ve been fixated on recently.
Like everything else in 2025, algorithms and social media deeply influence how people experience the arts, music most of all. In light of these invisible hands that more or less dictate online music exploration, and the growing desire to rebel against them as seen in the comeback of physical media, it is worth thinking about what "personal taste" really means today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What The Hell Is Going On With Marc-André ter Stegen?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196618</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-the-hell-is-going-on-with-marc-andre-ter-stegen"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T16:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, longtime Barcelona goalkeeper Marc-André ter Stegen announced via an open letter to the club's fans that he will undergo back surgery, and that as a result he will miss "about three months." A short while later, the club reportedly leaked through Catalonian radio station RAC1 that, contrary to ter Stegen's announcement, it regards his recovery time as "between 4–5 months."
An athlete announcing their own surgical recovery timetable isn't unheard of, but it is slightly unusual; typically that sort of thing goes through an organization's official communications shop. An athlete and an organization publicly disagreeing on a player's surgical recovery timetable, likewise, is pretty rare relative to the total number of pro athlete surgeries, but not really remarkable. What's interesting and worth examining in this instance is indicated by the fact that Barcelona's projected recovery timetable for ter Stegen is longer than ter Stegen's. Usually, you'd expect it to be the other way around, for easily legible reasons: The club would like its worker back at the revenue-generating part of their job as soon as possible rather than collecting paychecks for physical therapy, and the worker—the one of the parties, after all, who endures the pain and surgery and recovery, and whose career prospects are affected by injury—would like maximum security against having to go through it all again. In this case it's the player saying he'll be back in three months, and the club saying no, it'll be more like four or five. What's this all about?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Does The NFLPA Represent?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196676</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/who-does-the-nflpa-represent"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T16:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gene Upshaw would come to town once a year, usually in the middle of the week. There we were, the Denver Broncos, an NFL football team going through the routine of our football preparation, speaking football language, watching football film, taking football hits, and training our football bodies. But on this one day each year, after all the football things were done, we stayed in our seats in the team meeting room for a different type of discussion. 
Upshaw was an imposing presence. He had been a shit-kicking lineman for the Raiders for 15 seasons, and upon retirement, became the NFLPA’s shit-kicking executive director. He held the post for 25 years. We trusted him. After all, he was one of us. And yet, there he’d be, standing in front of us on a Thursday, explaining in detail some of the very important issues we had to face, including the emergence of withheld data about concussions and the impending CBA negotiations, and no one in the room was listening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Jackson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Feels Like An Occupation]]></title>
        <id>6883892319f1d000010a3432</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/it-feels-like-an-occupation/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T14:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every facet of American life is being taken over by people who recognize no limits on their power or reach]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Innovation Strikes In The Field Of Chimpanzee Rectum Adornment]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196378</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/innovation-strikes-in-the-field-of-chimpanzee-rectum-adornment"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T14:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fifteen years ago in a sanctuary in Zambia, inspiration struck a chimpanzee named Julie. She plucked a stiff blade of grass, stuck it inside her ear, and left it there. There the grass dangled as Julie played, groomed, and rested. The behavior soon spread to most of the other chimpanzees in Julie's group, called Group 4, and was adopted by her son Jack and chimps Kathy, Miracle, and Val. In the span of just one year, Julie was observed with grass in her ear 168 times; by comparison, the next most frequent observer was Kathy, with 36 grass-in-ear sightings. After Julie died in 2013, her invention lived on, with Kathy and Val carrying the torch.
Val, on trend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: New England Patriots]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196390</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-new-england-patriots"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T14:06:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the New England Patriots. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the New England Patriots. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: New England Patriots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Ugh! As If!’ Takes On The Enduring Appeal Of ‘Clueless’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196623</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ugh-as-if-takes-on-the-enduring-appeal-of-clueless"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T13:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the mid-to-late '90s, I was part of a girl gang that invaded suburban homes across the top half of New Jersey. We left our clothes strewn across various surfaces in your carpeted basements, ate your Snackwells in the wee hours, and wrote weird notes to your awkward eldest sons. Some of us stayed up all night, laughing and plotting, and some of us, inexplicably, wanted to go to bed at 9:00 p.m. For days afterwards, you would catch the faint smell of Bath & Body Works warm vanilla sugar.
It was the age of the pre-teen slumber party, and you could hear us coming from the synth riff of Kim Wilde’s “Kids in America.” It’s the song that opens Clueless, which was the preferred VHS rental for the coolest sleepovers I attended. We were the kids of America, even if we were closer to Nickelodeon’s definition than MTV’s, and Clueless offered a hopeful glimpse into life beyond middle school. We all wanted to be Cher Horowitz—beautiful, popular, rich, and, yes, even kind—and we weren’t the only ones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Annie Berke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heel, down]]></title>
        <id>6882cd8d19c0620001df7df9</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-367/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T02:42:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ian Williams, Tom Scocca, Josephine Riesman, and Maria Bustillos on the passing of Hulk Hogan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hulk Hogan, 1953–2025]]></title>
        <id>6882c3b419c0620001df7dba</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hulk-hogan-1953-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T02:39:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let me tell you something, brother]]></title>
        <id>6882bd9219c0620001df7d86</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/let-me-tell-you-something-brother/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T02:23:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pro wrestling is, in its structure, in its nature, a haven for thieves, rapists, murderers, con men, and perverts. Kayfabe—the great language and logic of pro wrestling—is, deep in its bones, based on ripping people off and making them like it. 
In related news, Hulk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hulk Hogan Is Dead]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196575</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/hulk-hogan-is-dead"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T20:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terry Bollea died on Thursday. The former professional wrestler was 71 years old. According to his longtime manager, Bollea died at his home in Clearwater, Fla.; different reports say that paramedics responded at dawn to an emergency call reporting that Bollea was suffering from cardiac arrest. He'd had some sort of recent neck surgery, and was rumored to be in failing health. Bollea's wife, Sky, recently batted away rumors that he was in a coma. Fellow washed-up wrestling luminary Jimmy Hart insisted Tuesday afternoon that Bollea was "doing phenomenal." That turned out to be not the case.
Reports of Bollea's poor health were first circulated by the radio personality Bubba the Love Sponge Clem. Followers of Bollea's post-wrestling career will recall that Clem and Bollea were once good friends and sometimes appeared together on Clem's Tampa-area radio show. In 2012, the two made headlines when Gawker reported that Clem had recorded a clandestine video of his wife, Heather, having sex with Bollea. A separate recording that became public years later captured Bollea making vile and racist remarks while in conversation with Heather.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Can You Trust? With Pablo Torre]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196525</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/who-can-you-trust-with-pablo-torre"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T19:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's just a lot to walk around with. You still have to walk around, naturally, there's stuff that needs doing and nothing is really gained by sitting around thinking about how stupid and crooked and venal everything is, and about the confluence of cultural forces conspiring to make it all dumber and nastier and worse, or about the erosion of the institutions and mores that ideally would stem that degradation. And yet, if you're the someone who thinks about that sort of thing—and if you are aware of it, it does tend to clatter around in your brain even if just as highly intrusive background noise—you can't just not think about it. The challenge, if you are aiming to remain sane, is in how you spin it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Tour de France Lunches, Reviewed]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196573</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/my-tour-de-france-lunches-reviewed"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T19:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[COURCHEVEL, France — Lunch: indisputably one of the top-three meals of the day, but at the Tour de France, not always something the intrepid reporter can afford to prioritize. Most days involve some degree of frantic scurrying between the start and finish, hitting the road early to go stand around the team buses and ask as many people as possible, "What's going to happen today?" (this often works, somehow) before scrambling to beat the peloton to the finish and ask them what happened today. Breakfast is typically one pastry, eaten in the car, and dinner is something to be taken seriously here in France, so it is good. In between, there is not much time.
However! The Amaury Sport Organization (ASO), the Tour's organizing body, provides a press room for journalists to in theory write and in practice annoy each other in like seven different languages, and the press room usually has food. I am not in the press room every day, especially on mountainous days, because it is quite often far from the finish line, which is where the interesting stuff happens. Those days, I eat either the world's driest sandwich from a French gas station or the world's least flavorful salad from a French gas station. Other days, I eat in the press room.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five Players Found Not Guilty In Hockey Canada Sexual Assault Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196539</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/five-players-found-not-guilty-in-hockey-canada-sexual-assault-trial"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T19:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five former NHL players and members of Hockey Canada's 2018 World Juniors championship team were found not guilty of sexual assault in a London, Ontario, courtroom Thursday, with the presiding judge stating, "I do not find the evidence of [the accuser] to be either credible or reliable." Dillon Dubé, Cal Foote, Michael McLeod, Alex Formenton, and Carter Hart had been accused of assaulting a 20-year-old woman in a hotel room while celebrating their tournament win on June 18, 2018.
"Having found that I cannot rely upon the evidence from [the accuser] and considering the evidence in this trial as a whole, I conclude that the Crown cannot meet its onus on any of the counts before me," Justice Maria Carroccia said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jesse Chavez Announces Retirement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=860364</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/jesse-chavez-announces-retirement.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T18:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right-hander Jesse Chavez announced his retirement on Foul Territory today. He was on the Braves’ roster until recently but was designated for assignment a week ago when that club acquired Dane Dunning. Chavez elected free agency after clearing waivers and has apparently decided to hang up his spikes in recent days. “I don’t think we’re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: New York Giants]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196442</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-new-york-giants"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T17:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the New York Giants. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the New York Giants. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: New York Giants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spain Won An Ugly Game Thanks To Moments Of Splendor]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196547</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/spain-won-an-ugly-game-thanks-to-moments-of-splendor"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T16:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's exceedingly rare to see a side enter an international tournament and manage to play its best, most aesthetically pleasing soccer for the entire month-long affair. It does happen—the Spanish men absolutely steamrolled Euro 2012, and the USWNT did the same at the 2019 World Cup—but more often than not, exhaustion, nerves, and tough matchups will force a team to win ugly on the way to the trophy. In Wednesday's Euro 2025 semifinal against Germany, Spain won ugly, as ugly as I've seen during the team's ongoing run of dominance, though La Roja did manage to sneak some real transcendence into a long and draining night in Zurich.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-Q3G9BW0Ba0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do I Find A Non-Fiction Book I Won’t Hate?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196334</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-do-i-find-a-non-fiction-book-i-wont-hate"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T15:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Ask The Book Doctor, a recurring series about books and reading them.
It can be nice to have a solid brand. For example, I always order the same drinks at the bar, so if I am running late, and I ask someone to order for me, I always get what I want, because I always want the same thing. But because I am consistent, people sometimes freak out when I choose something else. A week or so ago, I ordered a different drink at the bar, and everyone acted like I had two heads! The expectations people have of what I like, then, are determining the kinds of recommendations and information people give to me. No one told me the fancy little whiskey cocktail was so good, because no one thought I would want it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Hill Is Alive With the Sound of Scream-Grunts]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=468662</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/rich-hill-is-alive-with-the-sound-of-scream-grunts/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T15:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With songs he has sung for a thousand years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davy Andrews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat McAfee Declares Himself A “Girl Dad” In Apology To Harassed College Student]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196528</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/pat-mcafee-declares-himself-a-girl-dad-in-apology-to-harassed-college-student"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T13:27:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pat McAfee ended his daily ESPN show on Wednesday by finally addressing the role he played in ruining a college student's reputation. To nobody's surprise, he was extremely annoying about it.
Back in February, McAfee used his show to amplify a rumor about Ole Miss student Mary Kate Cornett having an affair with her boyfriend's dad. The rumor had already gone viral on social media, with Cornett's name attached, and McAfee's decision to discuss it on air—during an interview with NFL insider Adam Schefter, of all people—made things much worse for her. Cornett's phone number was posted online, her mother's house was swatted, and she received so many threats that she had to switch to online courses and move into emergency housing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get the quote / Read the book]]></title>
        <id>6881422919c0620001df650e</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-366/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T02:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Philip Bump in conversation with Maria Bustillos, and an announcement from Luke O’Neil]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking the Measure of Philip Bump]]></title>
        <id>6881680b19c0620001df6642</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/taking-the-measure-of-philip-bump/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T02:09:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Bustillos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s also quite funny to be clear]]></title>
        <id>688160a219c0620001df65fd</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/its-also-quite-funny-to-be-clear/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T02:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke O'Neil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest On Seth Lugo’s Trade Candidacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=860257</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/latest-on-seth-lugos-trade-candidacy.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T00:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seth Lugo reeled off another productive start this afternoon, tossing six innings of two-run ball to earn the win at Wrigley Field. The veteran right-hander now carries a 2.95 earned run average with a 22% strikeout rate. This was his 11th quality start in 19 appearances. Kansas City took two out of three from the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>