<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-04-13T20:16:56.134Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pauline Ferrand-Prévot’s Quick Return Makes A Great Cycling Season Better]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186731</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/pauline-ferrand-prevots-quick-return-makes-a-great-cycling-season-better"/>
        <updated>2025-04-13T18:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pauline Ferrand-Prévot was not supposed to take the start line at Paris-Roubaix on Saturday, though the framework of expectation and surprise is insufficient when applied to a rider like Ferrand-Prévot; everything about her 2025 season has been and necessarily will be a surprise. Ferrand-Prévot is back on the road this year after a six-year hiatus spent dominating the mountain biking scene. She decided to swap out her thick tires for skinny ones after winning gold in Paris at last summer's Olympics, completing the career sweep in the process, and she's returned to a very different peloton than the one she left in 2018. Ferrand-Prévot is a former road-race world champion, so it's not like she doesn't know what she's doing. But she'd never raced against latter-day crushers like Demi Vollering and Lorena Wiebes. Could PFP beat the new generation?
As it turns out: yes, with flair. Ferrand-Prévot has been one of the best riders through the early-season cobbled classic swing, taking third at Strade Bianche, second at last weekend's Tour of Flanders, and continuing her linear ascent of podia by winning Paris-Roubaix on Saturday. Each performance has been more impressive than the last: she won a small-group sprint in Italy, made the elite four-rider selection and finished second in the sprint for the win in Belgium, then escaped all alone to win at home in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Place Sam Long On 15-Day IL, Call Up Evan Sisk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=848271</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/royals-place-sam-long-on-15-day-il-call-up-evan-sisk.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-13T14:39:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that left-hander Sam Long has been placed on the 15-day injured list due to inflammation in his throwing elbow.  Fellow southpaw Evan Sisk was called up from Triple-A in the corresponding move, and Sisk will be making his MLB debut whenever he appears in his first game. Something has clearly seemed amiss…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Notes: India, Outfield, Wright]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=848243</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/royals-notes-india-outfield-wright.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-13T02:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals seem to have avoided what could’ve been a brutal blow this evening when infielder Jonathan India exited the club’s game against the Guardians due to what the club later announced was a bout of right quad tightness. After the game, manager Matt Quatraro told reporters (including MLB.com’s Anne Rogers) that the tightness India…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evil emoji / Feline friends]]></title>
        <id>67f9793d5aa1bd00010c5251</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-297/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T21:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the world’s a stage, says Zito Madu, and an announcement from Diana Moskovitz]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bad Men Are No Mystery]]></title>
        <id>67f956fd5aa1bd00010c514a</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-bad-men-are-no-mystery/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T21:52:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of the actors I’ve seen play Iago, the villain of Shakespeare’s Othello, portray him as a serpentine character—literally, as an extension of the serpent in the garden of Eden, a slippery, slithering trickster and deceiver who leads everyone to their destruction with his]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zito Madu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New: Pussycats]]></title>
        <id>67f96add5aa1bd00010c519e</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/whats-new-pussycats/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T21:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a collective of 60 writers, on fire and hard to kill]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Place Hunter Harvey On Injured List]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=848100</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/royals-hunter-harvey-injured-list-teres-major-strain.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T20:10:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[3:10pm: Anne Rogers of MLB.com relays some more info from manager Matt Quatraro. Harvey’s strain is grade 1, the lowest severity. He will be re-evaluated next week. 2:04pm: The Royals announced that they’ve placed right-hander Hunter Harvey on the 15-day injured list due to a teres major strain. Fellow righty Steven Cruz has been recalled…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bargain Vs. The Boot]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186748</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-bargain-vs-the-boot"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T19:48:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter.
Gretchen Whitmer, the Democratic governor of Michigan, went to the White House on Wednesday hoping to have a constructive policy discussion with Donald Trump about, among other things, his escalating tariff war. Beforehand, she made public remarks:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Drop’ Is Not A ’90s Thriller Because The ’90s Are Unfortunately Over]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186733</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/drop-is-not-a-90s-thriller-because-the-90s-are-unfortunately-over"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T17:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I haven’t been as excited to see a movie as I was to see Drop in possibly years. I saw the trailer a couple of months ago at the beginning of some other movie I don’t remember, and this is how the trailer goes: Ginormous house. Warm lighting. A little R&B. Meghann Fahy. “It’s just a date.” A soft halcyon vignette you know can only be prologue to a massive shitshow. Fahy leaves her cute kid with her cute kid sister at home, and now she’s wearing too much makeup and looking up at a ginormous skyscraper. The restaurant at the top of it, also ginormous, is a golden room with glowing orbs for lights and wrap-around windows overlooking a glowing city. Everything here looks like it costs $9 million. R&B picks up. A bargain-bin Indiana Jones (Brandon Sklenar, and no I don’t know who he is either) waves at her. Her date. Lame banter (“Sorry, I got a drink because I was nervous.” “I had a couple in the car on the way over.” Hahahaha.) Then. The titular drop.
Fahy’s phone buzzes, the music degrades, she starts getting AirDrops left and right, and she and Indiana Jones can’t figure out who it is. Then the music takes another dive because the AirDropper has told her to look at her security cameras and she goes from room to room until she finally sees him: THE MASKED MAN IN HER HOUSE. THIS MAN WILL LITERALLY KILL HER CUTE CHILD—THE AIRDROPPER USES CAPS A LOT—UNLESS SHE DOES ONE THING: KILL HER DATE. I mean, I’ll do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Désiré Doué Is The Coolest Of The Cool]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186663</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/desire-doue-is-the-coolest-of-the-cool"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T17:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While all of the reasons to be morally opposed to the Paris Saint-Germain sportswashing project still apply, it must be said that the team as presently constituted is exceptionally cool.
This certainly isn't the first great team of PSG's Qatar era, and even after Wednesday's 3-1 home win over Aston Villa, which has the Parisiens on the precipice of the Champions League semifinals, there's still a ways to go before it can match or possibly improve on that 2020 UCL final in terms of coming closest to finally delivering the prize its Qatari overlords have so rapaciously coveted. Almost every previous iteration of PSG has been distasteful for a variety of reasons: the chintzy Galácticos cosplay, the market-warping signings of Neymar and Kylian Mbappé, the jealousy with which they've guarded their golden-caged prisoners, the flaunting of their riches and the simultaneous anger when anyone brings up the grossness of how those riches came about, the self-righteous whining about the schadenfreude their habitual humiliations inspire in the rest of the soccer world. Nevertheless, the current team is surprisingly hard to hate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Record Store Day Became The Stupidest Day In Music]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186688</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-record-store-day-became-the-stupidest-day-in-music"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T16:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like all worthwhile endeavours, the (semi)annual celebration of independent record store culture called Record Store Day started with an idea. Specifically, it started with a dashed-off email with a subject line reading, simply, “idea.”
“[I]t could be a national event that drives people to indie stores,” Chris Brown, of Portland, Maine-based indie retailer Bull Moose Records, wrote to a consortium of colleagues. “We would need some nice licensed pieces–maybe something along the lines of the upcoming Guided By Voices rarities box…There is a huge press angle here too.  Indies rule. We haven't gone anywhere…Video, print and online testimonials from artists would run in every market to promote the event…Try to include movie stars and game developers…”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Semley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Be Insulted By These Fascists Is So Degrading]]></title>
        <id>67f926528b52b30001dcb20e</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/to-be-insulted-by-these-fascists-is-so-degrading/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T15:10:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's no game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Reacher Too Big Now? A Roundtable Discussion]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186637</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/is-reacher-too-big-now-a-roundtable-discussion"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T15:07:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Ley: Wow, I can’t believe this. After having been separated for more than a year, the Reacher Creatures have once again come back together to help each other in our time of need. The mission: Try to find something that any of us actually liked about Season 3 of Reacher. 
Roth, I believe you are the only one among us who had a good time watching this season. Perhaps you could explain to us your values? Now?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ja Morant Is Doing A New Thing, And That Thing Is Grenade]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186715</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ja-morant-is-doing-a-new-thing-and-that-thing-is-grenade"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T13:59:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good news for Adam Silver: Ja Morant is no longer pretending to shoot a gun after hitting big shots. Potentially bad news for Adam Silver: Ja Morant is now lobbing imaginary grenades into the crowd.

https://www.youtube.com/shorts/eWsgIoW9hKw]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome To The Scam Century]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186646</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/welcome-to-the-scam-century"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T13:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growing up in Florida, I have always maintained that the state as a whole should be thought of as America's id. Florida is the country's truest self, and wherever the nation is headed, it's likely that Florida was there first and rightfully mocked for it in the moment. The hard right turn into conspiracy and spite, the dismantling of education and social services, an economy built completely out of fraud and scamming—that's us, and has been us. If you were to visit Miami right now, you would see an entire city seemingly catered to fraud: credit card scams, fake medical practices, and, of course, crypto. So, so much crypto.
On Wednesday, the president of the United States backed away from some of his more extravagant tariff threats and checked down to smaller, still very dangerous tariffs—for every nation except China, that is, with which we now seem to be in full-blown trade war. While Trump claims that the tariff experiment was merely some sort of test, and his lackeys have framed it as an act of dealcraft beyond mortal comprehension, those explanations land with the same amount of sincerity as a Drake diss record. It sure looks like Trump saw the economy tanking and decided to kill two birds with one stone, readjusting the S&P and also allowing his rich friends who had shorted the economy to make a lot of money off its rebound. That's very clearly insider trading, and will also very clearly not be dealt with in any meaningful way, because consequences don't exist if you have enough money and power. Florida was early to that one, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chasing rumors / Finding the dead]]></title>
        <id>67f80f9b5aa1bd00010c3f0d</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-296/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T23:47:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arwa Mahdawi on the known unknown, and fiction (or is it?) by Sam Thielman]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Solve a Murder: Part Four]]></title>
        <id>67f7fbdf5aa1bd00010c3ea2</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/how-to-solve-a-murder-part-four/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T23:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a collective of 60 writers, on fire and hard to kill]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arwa Mahdawi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Ghosts]]></title>
        <id>67f84da85aa1bd00010c3f9b</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/some-ghosts/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T23:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a collective of 60 writers, on fire and hard to kill]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Thielman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beavises In The Code Base, With Tim Marchman]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186473</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/beavises-in-the-code-base-with-tim-marchman"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T20:13:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a longstanding workplace value at Defector not to take journalism too seriously. The work, however serious it might be from one moment to the next, is worth taking seriously and trying to do well. The industry and practitioners and accumulated lore and pomposity, on the other hand, must never get even a moment of respect. This is a little perverse, admittedly, and creates some strange internal conundrums—I find myself thinking some version of "my job, which I take seriously and try very hard to be good at, is ridiculous and often deeply stupid"—but, on balance, it is probably better than acting in the way that, say, the lead people on the New York Times politics desk act.
And there's a loophole: If you're not allowed to be too serious or even too proud of yourself and your own work, you are allowed to be impressed with others. Drew and I seized on that loophole this week to invite onto the podcast Tim Marchman, whose team at Wired has done some of the best and most important reporting about Elon Musk's ongoing vandalism campaign within the federal government. This work, at least, we are comfortable saluting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Octavio Dotel Made A Life In Baseball]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186528</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/octavio-dotel-made-a-life-in-baseball"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T19:35:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Different types of baseball careers have different kinds of shapes. Many, most, don't have any shape at all; they unfold entirely out of sight, under the waterline and in the minor leagues, and generally very quickly. Those are lives in the game, too, and the existence of even the most minor of Major League careers is a triumph simply for having existed. I remember a lot of ballplayers solely as baseball cards, one moment where a photographer caught them squinting at spring training or grimacing in bad sunglasses during a day game, and not at all as players. I never actually saw them, or if I did it was as a figure far out on a shifting sand bar, disappearing from the first moment they came into sight.
Other careers are longer and more legible; you can see a sort of story happening or almost happening over the course of years, and find a framework that puts it into a broader context. "Ah," you might say after a look at the back of a baseball card or a Baseball-Reference page, "this is kind of a Matt Lawton type of career" or "I'm getting some Terry Mulholland notes here." You might not want to say this around anyone you want to impress, but it will help you understand it—this is a type of life in baseball, one of the ways that the story can go. It is possible, in this way, to say that a ballplayer could have career that looks sort of like that of Octavio Dotel, who died on Tuesday after the roof of a nightclub in Santo Domingo collapsed during a performance on Monday night. But it would also be untrue, both because of the specific things that made Dotel's life in baseball what it was, and because no other career in baseball history ever has looked like his.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mariners Find Catharsis In A Walk-Off Walk]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186640</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-mariners-find-catharsis-in-a-walk-off-walk"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T18:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Giving up a walk is more shameful than giving up a hit. Nibbling at the edge of the zone is cowardice; the Seattle Mariners' starting rotation generally understands this fact and acts accordingly. Giving up a walk-off walk is 10 times more shameful than giving up a walk-off hit, even if that hit is a grand slam. While the Houston Astros' Bryan Abreu surely understood this fact Wednesday night, he had already thrown 29 pitches across seven batters before committing his shameful 30th. That's not what you want, especially if the guy at the plate hit a grand slam in the previous inning.
Randy Arozarena, meanwhile, had taken it upon himself to make Mariners color commentator Dave Valle happy. Prior to the eighth inning, Seattle was on track to have a repeat of Tuesday night's game, and not just in the Luis Castillo of it all. The offense was ineffective, reproducing the lack of results that had spurred Valle, in the game prior, to espouse his beliefs on the importance of hitting with runners in scoring position. His thesis was true but only in the trivial sense: All the great teams do it. With the bases loaded, Arozarena did it, turning a 5-0 game into a 5-4 game. It also improved his 1-for-11 record this season with runners in scoring position to 2-for-12.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are The Cleveland Guardians Creating A Dynamic Brand Experience That Deepens The Connection Between The Team And Its Fans, And Reflects The Team’s History, Its Commitment To Cleveland, And Its Vision For The Future, On And Off The Field?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186660</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cleveland-guardians-brand-what"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T17:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm so glad you asked. If you're anything like me, you were already wondering whether or not the Guardians' new brand platform marks a significant step in the team’s evolution of the Guardians brand, designed to deepen fan engagement, ignite excitement, and unite the club under a unified brand vision for seasons to come. Thanks to a press release (via Craig Calcaterra), we can stop wondering:
The Cleveland Guardians, in collaboration with Landor, the world leading brand consultants, today announced the launch of “Outplay Ordinary” – a bold new brand platform and refreshed visual identity set to debut in the 2025 baseball season. This initiative marks a significant step in the team’s evolution of the Guardians brand, designed to deepen fan engagement, ignite excitement, and unite the club under a unified brand vision for seasons to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ms. Rachel Is Hamas Now]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186521</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ms-rachel-is-hamas-now"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T17:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we previously checked in with Liora Rez, who runs the nuisance group StopAntisemitism, she was trying to get some flight attendants fired over a Palestinian flag pin. Between then and now, she has doubtless complained about many inanimate objects associated with Palestine, but this week she is pleading with the government to take down what she sees as a clear and present threat to national security: Ms. Rachel, the lady who sings songs for children on YouTube.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Nantz Is Being Weird About The Masters Again]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186625</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jim-nantz-is-being-weird-about-the-masters-again"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T15:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Masters is teeing off this morning, in all of its stately glory. The green jacket. The azaleas in full bloom. The soothing, piped-in bird noises. The genteel linguistic tyranny. And presiding over it all, as he has been since the 1980s,  with his collar fully erect, is Jim Nantz. You and I know all about Jim Nantz, with his burnt toast fetish and whatnot. You and I also know how disturbingly horny Nantz is for the Masters, and for golf in general. Well, I’m glad to report that the man spoke to reporters before this year’s tournament and reaffirmed just how intensely fucking WEIRD he is about this event. Jim, what does the fabled green jacket mean to you?
It’s just emblematic of excellence in golf. You’ve reached the highest level that’s achievable in the game just to be able to don a green jacket. Isn’t it refreshing, in a time in sport where all we ever hear about is money and guaranteed contracts and outrageous numbers that most people can’t relate to that at all? In fact, they’re numb to it. The numbers, it’s fantasy to them. When you have the Masters tournament, there’s never a discussion about purse money, how much you win. It’s about a jacket. It’s about a coat that you win. Tell me something else that compares to that. You won’t come up with anything that means more than just a green jacket. Yes, there’s money involved. It’s never discussed. I couldn’t even come close to telling you what first place pays at Augusta, and I don’t care. Nor do the players. You know what it is? It’s immortality in golf. You achieve it, you have found a place in history. It’s permanence. It’s forever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I’m The Idiot Who Bet Against Ovechkin]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186578</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/im-the-idiot-who-bet-against-ovechkin"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T14:46:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For somebody who followed Alexander Ovechkin's chase for as long and closely as I had, I didn’t get much fun out of his pursuit of Wayne Gretzky. A small, stupid wager I made with a buddy more than a decade ago screwed everything up. See, I bet against the Great 8. Dammit.
I was listening to the local radio broadcast on Friday night when Ovechkin scored two goals against the visiting Chicago Blackhawks to tie Gretzky at 894. Given how Ovechkin was buzzing around the net in the third period, had that game lasted another minute he surely would have gotten 895 in the only home arena he’s known in his 20-year NHL career. As it was, the record-breaker came a couple days later on the road against the New York Islanders, when Ovechkin netted a scorching wrister just 26 seconds into the Caps’ first power play of the game. The goal was his sixth in five games, but the moment was still as thrilling as it was inevitable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brand New Tour, Same Old Question]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186556</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/brand-new-tour-same-old-question"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T14:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Halloween 2006, and I’m standing in the middle of the Val Air Ballroom in Des Moines, Iowa. My bangs are side-swept and greasy, and I’m holding a newly purchased T-shirt that reads “FIGHT OFF YOUR DEMONS.” I’ve gone into the bathroom to check if my raccoon-style eyeliner looks intentionally smudged or just messy (the latter), but despite that, I’m feeling smug.
No one in this historic venue knows this band like I do. Of this, I am sure—even to this day. At that point, Brand New was still three weeks away from releasing their third full album, The Devil and God Are Raging Inside Me. For nearly a year, I’d been listening to a set of six leaked demos that I had downloaded and burned onto a cheap CD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lindsey Adler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If You’re Going To Get Food Poisoning, At Least Visit Flavortown First]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186581</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/if-youre-going-to-get-food-poisoning-at-least-visit-flavortown-first"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T13:26:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cody Bellinger was back in the Yankees' lineup on Wednesday, after a day off due to what medical experts might describe as "shitting and puking his guts out." This is a refreshingly straightforward diagnosis compared to the usual "flu-like symptoms" suffered by athletes, which I have always assumed was a mealymouthed cover for a hangover. Bellinger wanted everyone to know he was not hung over. He just ate some bad wings and embraced the toilet.
Bellinger told reporters how he ordered room-service chicken wings at his Detroit hotel, to eat while watching Monday night's NCAA men's championship game. "They were good coming in," he said, leaving to your imagination the implication of their quality while coming out. "But I woke up at 4:00 a.m. sweating and just started throwing up for a few hours."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Would Cry Too If It Happened To You]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186566</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/you-would-cry-too-if-it-happened-to-you"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T12:53:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Mavericks ran a Luka Doncic tribute video during pregame introductions ahead of their game Wednesday night against the Los Angeles Lakers. It ran about 130 seconds, featured swelling music, and opened with a clip of Adam Silver gently over-pronouncing "Doncic" from the stage of the 2018 NBA Draft. The clip worked, not just for recalling the moment of Doncic's arrival in the NBA, but because it served as a poignant reminder that the Slovenian wonderteen was still basically a foreign curiosity to North American hoops observers (and, uh, the NBA commissioner) when Mavericks fans and Dallasites first made him their guy. He stayed their guy for more than six years, growing very literally into adulthood.
That's not nothing, man! My daughter has been in her current daycare class for less than two years, and we are pulling her out for this upcoming summer session. The school's administrator recently informed me that when we re-enroll her in the autumn she might have to go to a different class, with a different teacher, run in a different classroom, one that is separated from the old one by a single wall. I am heartbroken about this, pretty well devastated. I know that I will have to clean out my daughter's cubby very soon, and I am dreading it. I'm going to need an emotional support animal when I pick her up that afternoon. Very real connections form in a hell of a lot less time than Doncic lived and worked in Dallas. "I don't know how I did it," said a still wobbly-voiced Doncic, of participating in the basketball game, after it was over. "When I was watching that video, I was like, there's no way I'm playing this game."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bad Faith Does Not Get Badder Than This]]></title>
        <id>67f6931e8b52b30001dcabb3</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/the-bad-faith-does-not-get-badder-than-this/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T11:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump regime has co-opted the language of the Civil Rights movement to advance segregationist educational policies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life in retreat]]></title>
        <id>67f6c26d5aa1bd00010c2d36</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-295/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T23:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zach Rabiroff and a Turkish artist on the wealth (or otherwise) of nations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At the Museum Near the Hospital]]></title>
        <id>67f69b125aa1bd00010c2c87</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/at-the-museum-near-the-hospital/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T23:22:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a collective of 60 writers, on fire and hard to kill]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Rabiroff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Timberwolves Collapsed In The Worst Way At The Worst Time]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186522</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-timberwolves-collapsed-in-the-worst-way-at-the-worst-time"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T18:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With 10 minutes left in the fourth quarter of the Minnesota Timberwolves' road game in Milwaukee, Donte DiVincenzo nailed a casual catch-and-shoot three-pointer to give his team a 24-point lead. This would turn out to be the final meaningful bucket scored by the Wolves Tuesday night, as Milwaukee would embark on a 23-0 run, which grew into a 39-8 run, and then concluded in a 110-103 win for the home team. The Wolves' loss was as costly as it was humiliating: Minnesota fell to eighth, one game below the four-way tie for fourth in the exceedingly tight Western Conference. At the same time, this was a fitting result for a team with a season-long inability to get out of its own way.
Blowing a 24-point lead in five minutes takes two teams, though the Wolves made things remarkably easy for the Bucks. After three quarters spent moving the ball and nailing open shots, Minnesota stagnated in the fourth, alternating between Anthony Edwards dribbling a bunch and missing a bad jumper, or one of the guards making a single pass before someone else missed a jumper. They went 4-for-20 in the fourth quarter with nine turnovers, only one of which came during the Bucks' big run. As many trailing teams have done this season, Milwaukee busted out a zone and the Wolves were totally bamboozled, unable or unwilling to make the simple passes required to overcome such a defense. On the other end of the court, Bucks guard Kevin Porter Jr. was getting into the paint at will. Once Milwaukee evened it up, they went back to man, got three steals in four possessions and blew the game open. For once, Doc Rivers's team was on the positive end of a blown lead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired USDA Program Coordinator]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=185425</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-usda-program-coordinator"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T18:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jules Reynolds grew up on a corn and soy farm in Iowa. Growing up, she imagined all agriculture looked like this—a monoculture of rows and rows of corn in one year, followed by rows and rows of soy the next. "To me, that was really beautiful," Reynolds said. "That was my backyard. That's what I played in."
When Reynolds went to college at the University of Iowa, she took classes that taught her about how monocultural farming systems impacted the environment. When you grow too many of the same plant species in one area, the crops drain the soil of its nutrients, demand more pesticide use, and diminish the biodiversity in the area. "I remember feeling this really deep tension within me," Reynolds said: how the food system that she grew up thinking was not just beautiful, but also feeding the world, was also harming the soil.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Definitive Guide To Mariners Pitchers Named Luis Castillo]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186496</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-definitive-guide-to-mariners-pitchers-named-luis-castillo"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T17:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, Mariners starting pitcher Luis Castillo battled through five scoreless innings against the Astros, before Seattle lost 2-1 in extras. This afternoon, Mariners starting pitcher Luis Castillo will face the Astros in his second-ever Major League start. This will also be his second time starting immediately after Luis Castillo.
Do not be confused and/or frightened: These are two separate Luis Castillos, who just happen to be starting pitchers for the same team, reliably pitching on back-to-back days due to their timing in the rotation. Somehow, this is not unprecedented: According to Daniel Kramer at MLB.com, Bobby Joseph Jones and Bobby Mitchell Jones pulled off the feat for the Mets, then did it again two years later for the Padres. The two Castillos have an easier run to match the record, since they're still on the same team. Depending on the performance of the second Luis Castillo this afternoon, they may well be on track to exceed it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Season 8 Kicks Off With A Couch And A Fuckboy]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186417</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/season-8-kicks-off-with-a-couch-and-a-fuckboy"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T15:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During my freshman orientation, we were told that of the three ways to pass time in college—sleeping, studying, or partying—we could only pick two. A similar framework applies to couches. Couches can theoretically be comfortable, affordable, and beautiful, but in practice you must sacrifice one attribute.
So imagine you come across a dreamily comfortable couch that could be yours for the low, low price of zero dollars. This couch also happens to be gorgeous. All you have to do is loosen your moral code a smidge, maybe screw over a former fling. You can handle that, right?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That’s Too Many Baseball Cards!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=185977</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/thats-too-many-baseball-cards"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T15:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spring training was already in full swing when Jason texted me. We mostly talk Phillies, and I figured he wanted to discuss which players would be disappointing us this season. Instead he had a question about baseball cards.
He showed me two Topps cards, for the Angels’ Niko Kavadas and the Astros’ Jeremy Peña, from the 2025 set. Each card sparkled in an uncanny way. Kavadas’s card had a reflective blue border, and Peña’s entire card glittered silver. They had the look of special cards, although Jason told me they weren’t worth anything. He just wanted to know what kind of card they were.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, Shut The Fuck Up]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186466</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/oh-shut-the-fuck-up"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T14:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hmm, it appears that the nation’s economy is collapsing at Timberwolves-like speed. That big fat trade war that the U.S. launched a few days ago has quickly proven to have the opposite of its intended(?) effect, with every market plunging and every American’s last dollar being fed into a paper shredder. Let’s see what the man responsible for starting that tariff-off has to say about the crisis at hand:
“These countries are calling us up, kissing my ass… They are dying to make a deal.” The president went on to mock the tariff-deal supplicants, pretending to be them as he pitifully pleaded in a simpering voice: “Please, Sir, make a deal. I’ll do anything. I’ll do anything, Sir.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canucks Forget They’re The Canucks For One Historic Minute]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186458</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/canucks-forget-theyre-the-canucks-for-one-historic-minute"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T14:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let us hold a moment of appreciation for those who refuse to accept the inevitable: players and teams who rage against a drama-free final couple weeks of the regular season. The Vancouver Canucks will not make the playoffs. You know this, I know this, they know this, but they don't have to act like they do. As my own team folds like origami, the Canucks are committed to playing every last one of their 60 allotted minutes until mathematical elimination. Eat shit, mathematics!
The postseason field is more or less set. The Dallas Stars are locked into a first-round match-up with Colorado. The Canucks, entering their game on Tuesday, would have been officially eliminated with a regulation loss. That sure looked like the result they'd receive after 59 minutes of play in Dallas, as they trailed 5-2 on the back of five goals by five different Stars whose first names start with M. (Mikko, Mason, Matt, Mavrik, and Mikael; I noticed this just now when looking at the box score and I'm making it everyone's problem.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal Stepped On Real Madrid’s Neck]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186439</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/arsenal-stepped-on-real-madrids-neck"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T13:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is how you beat Real Madrid in the Champions League. What Arsenal did in Tuesday's first leg of the quarterfinals was as thorough a beating as the dark magic wizards have received in recent memory, and the London side put in kill shot after kill shot en route to a dominating 3-0 victory that, perhaps ominously but mostly euphorically, could have been more. As Real Madrid's history in this competition teaches us, no team is ever truly safe until Los Blancos are fully eliminated, but the Gunners have put themselves in fantastic position to nullify whatever counter-punch might come their way.
If it sounds like I am doing some form of reverse jinx on Arsenal, allow me to dispel that notion: Arsenal is not home free yet and into the semifinal round, but my goodness did the club step up to the hardest challenge in continental soccer. From the word go, the hosts were on Real Madrid's ass, constantly pushing the defending champs back and into frantic defending. A shaky clearance from Antonio Rüdiger early on, in which a mishit of an inch the other way would have led to an own goal, served as a blaring klaxon, and even though the goals took their sweet time to arrive, the statistics were heavily slanted in Arsenal's favor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's DOGE Is Following A Familiar — And Horrifying — Playbook]]></title>
        <id>67ebf3279df7290001a3eedf</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/elon-musks-doge-is-following-a-familiar-and-horrifying-playbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T12:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk is shocking the U.S. government into a weakened state so it can be rebuilt in his image]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Reimer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moral panic / Dangerous complacency]]></title>
        <id>67f587385aa1bd00010c18ca</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-294/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T23:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Parker Molloy on comic book burnings, and Kọ́lá Túbọ̀sún on an old academic crisis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Folk Devils Keep Changing]]></title>
        <id>67f5668b5aa1bd00010c1850</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-folk-devils-keep-changing/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T22:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[... but the Panic Stays the Same]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Parker Molloy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Certain Parallels]]></title>
        <id>67f593f05aa1bd00010c1927</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/certain-parallels/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T22:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meeting ended with a majority pledge of allegiance to the new University Credo. Confident that it now had the support, or complaisance of the majority of the University, the Government issued fresh orders. All those who had resigned should be… ejected from the University at once. Twenty-four hours&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kọ́lá Túbọ̀sún</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Malone And Calvin Booth Lose Their War Over The Soul Of The Nuggets]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186414</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/michael-malone-and-calvin-booth-lose-their-war-over-the-soul-of-the-nuggets"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T20:22:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Denver Nuggets are all fucked up. After losing four straight games and getting dragged into the Western Conference tar pit in which the current fourth through eighth seeds are desperately trying to escape the play-in tournament, the team's short-term outlook is as bad as its been during the Nikola Jokic era. On Tuesday, the team confirmed that anyone making dour proclamations about the current state of the franchise was not overstating things in the slightest: Both head coach Michael Malone and general manager Calvin Booth are gone with just three games left to play in the regular season.
The departures themselves are perhaps less interesting than the fact that they were announced simultaneously. For the past few seasons, the off-court story of the Nuggets has been about the power struggle between Booth and Malone. Booth, who was always a little too willing to talk up his roster-building acumen, had his mind set on keeping Denver's contention window open by developing late draft picks into useful starters. He envisioned turning players like Jalen Pickett, Peyton Watson, Julian Strawther, and Zeke Nnaji—often sarcastically referred to as the Booth Boys by Nuggets fans—into steady contributors. He believed in this plan so much that he gave Nnaji a four-year, $32 million extension, making him the fifth-highest paid player on the roster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Western Conference Is Heading Into A Week Of Glorious Chaos]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186415</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-western-conference-is-heading-into-a-week-of-glorious-chaos"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T18:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For all the carping about the NBA's multitude of failings—ask Shaquille O'Neal if you need the full bill of complaints—the end of this regular season has become a thoroughly organic motherlode of chaos, in ways that can only be good. Not necessarily for the sport in some macro sense, mind you; these things tend to even out after the second round, anyway. But the chaos in the Western Conference is inarguably good for the fan who wants games that matter at a point in the season when games almost always don’t.
And no, we are not talking about the lineups that the tanking teams are trotting out nightly to guarantee the success of that night's tactical failure ritual. The nightmarish tapestry of the worst eight teams is a thing to behold, and lopsided defeats have been weaponized as never before. Utah has lost 19 of its last 20 games, by an average of 17 points per game; this includes losses in the last two weeks alone of 38, 37, 36, 29, 28, and 26 points. Philadelphia is 3-27 over their last 30, Brooklyn is surfing a 4-18 skid, Charlotte a 6-20 one. Washington is 4-12 in its last 16 games and might be the most dignified of the turbotankers, and when the Wizards aren't the worst team in any department, you've got yourself a whopper of an anomaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Octavio Dotel Dies In Roof Collapse Tragedy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=847723</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/octavio-dotel-dies-in-roof-collapse-tragedy.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T17:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former major leaguer Octavio Dotel has died in a tragic accident, per multiple sources out of the Dominican Republic, including Diario Libre. The roof of the Jet Set club in Santo Domingo collapsed in the early hours of Tuesday morning. Full details of the tragedy are still emerging but Diario Libre says at least 27…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grocery Shopping Is Meditation]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186370</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/grocery-shopping-is-meditation"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T17:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about grill pans, born again Dookies, Woodstock, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stumbling Minnesota Twins Struggle With Clocks, Gizmos, Rules, And Authority]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186361</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/stumbling-minnesota-twins-struggle-with-clocks-gizmos-rules-and-authority"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T15:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simeon Woods Richardson, starting pitcher for the Minnesota Twins, was preparing to throw his 108th pitch of the evening Monday night when something went wrong. Before we get there, I'd just like to say that this was gutsy, heroic shit from Woods Richardson, who had only once before topped 100 pitches in a major-league appearance. He was not having a particularly good time Tuesday night, having allowed 12 base runners and four runs, but the Twins are playing like crap, and their bullpen is pretty well shredded. Baseball tradition sometimes makes it the job of a starting pitcher to climb back up the mound, at or past the best-if-used-by date of their throwing arm, and guile their way to another out or two, not to win a game but simply to bring a game that much closer to completion, while sp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[American Freedom]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186365</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/american-freedom"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T15:23:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On March 26, the official White House Twitter account posted a photo of Vice President JD Vance aiming a military rifle with the caption “Just the Vice President of the United States sending some freedom seeds downrange. Doesn’t get more American than that.” Presumably this image inspired the millions of Americans who love guns and wanted to see a ranking executive shoot them, just as previous administrators inspired Americans who love golf (W. Bush), jogging (Clinton), and coercive sex (Clinton). 
“Freedom seeds,” though, caused at least one American to shrivel up inside. I would call it a euphemism, but a euphemism is supposed to sound better than what it replaces. “Freedom seeds” manages to sound both dumb and effortful at the same time, committing the cardinal sin of written communication by calling attention to the writer’s “cleverness”—here I am making scare quotes so hard that the dog has run out of the room—at the expense of clarity. Readers can understand what the White House is trying to say, but we have to waste a second to supply the shorter and more familiar word “bullets.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Brooks</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Title IX Is Now A Weapon In The Trump Administration’s Culture War]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186122</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/title-ix-is-now-a-weapon-in-the-trump-administrations-culture-war"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T14:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Education announced on Friday that it will be creating what it called a "Title IX Special Investigations Team" that would be dedicated to swiftly resolving complaints about trans female athletes in sports. It was the sort of announcement the Trump administration has made nearly every day since taking office months ago—high-flown, vague, aligned with a conservative media fixation, and ominous. Just as telling as anything in the announcement was what was missing from it: facts.
The announcement contained no information about exactly how many complaints the department had received about trans athletes. (Two? Five? Twenty?) It did not say who filed these complaints. (Parents? Students? Teachers?) It did not say when those complaints were received. It did not even bother to say what those complaints were about, beyond some extremely ambiguous, predictably overheated language referring to "pernicious effects of gender ideology in school programs and activities." Anyone looking for something as basic to democracy as public accountability from a public agency would have to look elsewhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MC Ktrine’s Rapping Is A Gift To Brazilian Funk]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186092</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mc-ktrines-rapping-is-a-gift-to-brazilian-funk"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T14:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilian funk, at least out on the radical, thrilling, ear-frying, brain-scrambling fringes, is primarily a producer's genre. It's not that the songs are mostly instrumental. Vocals are a critical part of the sound, the defining examples being the endlessly repeated stabs of short words or phrases—"Vai, vai"; "Toma, toma"; "Fode, fode"; "Pega, pega"; "Vuk vuk" (maybe don't look up what those last few mean in English if you're at work)—that basically are to funk what the hi-hat triplet is to trap. In addition to those stock adlibs and the omnipresent DJ drops, funk tracks typically feature at least one and usually a few vocalists rhythmically croaking out verses beneath the chirps and blares and clangs of the beat, and certain sub-scenes, like funk ostentação, are in fact rapper-centric.
Nevertheless, vocals are primarily a resource for the funk DJ/producer. You can see this even in how the music is made. Listen to enough funk, and you'll inevitably find a verse you first encountered in one song showing up elsewhere, and potentially several different elsewheres. This is because the custom is for rappers to upload a cappellas online for free, which DJs then take and edit as they please. The consistency of funk's rhythmic patterns makes this kind of splicing together of various verses pretty seamless, and there's no stigma to reusing a good a cappella that someone else has gotten to first. But as is their approach to music more generally, funk producers love to deconstruct vocals and play with parts. DJ Ramemes mentioned in an interview once that rappers are sometimes annoyed when they learn he's used one of their verses for a song, as he is prone to snip out all but a couple choice lines, distort them, rearrange them, and weave the frayed strands into his frenzied aural tapestries. And Ramemes is closer to the norm in funk, where the DJ is almost always sovereign.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida Didn’t Lose The National Championship]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186358</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/florida-didnt-lose-the-national-championship"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T13:19:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The end of Monday's NCAA National Championship Game between Florida and Houston had brief moments of retrograde brilliance but ended as an entirely justified mess. This can reasonably be said of many if not most college basketball games, but in this last college basketball game of the season there was one reason that superseded all the others. 

https://bsky.app/profile/houstonchronicle.com/post/3lmbfkxyrh22q]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Diceman cometh / Bunny business]]></title>
        <id>67f3e8ae5aa1bd00010c0562</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-293/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T22:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Pendarvis on Tinseltown; flash fictions by Luke O’Neil]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy to do]]></title>
        <id>67f442645aa1bd00010c065f</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/easy-to-do/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T22:24:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updates from my backyard March 2005 
Technically speaking it wasn’t quite spring just yet but this little rabbit didn’t know that. It was running undisciplined routes across the yard like a rookie slot receiver and now came back around for another sniff of the dead]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke O'Neil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ace Goes to Hollywood: Episode 3]]></title>
        <id>67f433b95aa1bd00010c05bb</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/ace-goes-to-hollywood-episode-3/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T22:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ace Goes to Hollywood is a continuing transcript of a ride from Oxford, Mississippi, to Memphis, Tennessee, during which Jack Pendarvis interviewed Ace Atkins about his work on the Pauly Shore film Jury Duty.

Episode 3: Ace’s Big Break!
JACK: Let’s talk about some of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Pendarvis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Is Time To Close Down The White Lotus]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186337</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/white-lotus-season-3-finale-belinda"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T20:02:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third season of The White Lotus ends with guests speeding away from the resort on a boat while the staff wave at them, placid and obliging. In Season 1, Natasha Rothwell’s Belinda was among the staff charged with sublimating their identities to avoid being “too specific as a presence,” as Murray Bartlett’s Armond explains in the pilot. “It’s a Japanese ethos where we are asked to disappear behind our masks as pleasant, interchangeable helpers.” 
By the end of the third season, though, it’s Belinda who is on the boat, pockets newly deep, speeding away from a crew of waving staff members stranded on the beach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amen Thompson Breaks The Game]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186292</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/amen-thompson-breaks-the-game"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T18:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the fourth quarter of last Friday's Thunder-Rockets game, Shai Gilgeous-Alexander executed perhaps the NBA's single most-executed action and drove to the basket. One aspect of OKC's double-big lineup that makes defending the group particularly demanding is the unique threat that each of the two bigs presents as a screener; you can see on the following play how Isaiah Hartenstein's ghost screen forces Amen Thompson out to Gilgeous-Alexander's outside hip, and how he and Chet Holmgren arcing down to the block keeps either Alperen Sengun or Jabari Smith Jr. from helping. This action forces one player to defend Gilgeous-Alexander's drive from a disadvantageous position, which has been a death sentence for almost every single defender, all year.
Not Thompson. He stuck with the slithery Thunder guard, kept him from fully turning the corner or baiting a foul, and rejected his midrange jumper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wrestling Shows Don’t All Have To Aim For “Epic”]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186253</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/wrestling-shows-dont-all-have-to-aim-for-epic"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T17:49:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA - When I was first getting into wrestling, as a wee lad of about nine or ten, I had to beg my parents to let me buy the big pay-per-views in what was then the WWF. The names are still synonymous with Big Wrestling Pay-Per-View: Royal Rumble, SummerSlam, Survivor Series, WrestleMania. These shows felt like the biggest events in my young world, and I was always enraptured for the entire duration. I was too young to discern things like "match quality" and "pacing," and too excited to care. I just wanted to see Stone Cold Steve Austin beat the shit out of Vince McMahon. Even with the boundless energy of a kid, my emotions ran so high that I would be exhausted just from watching. After I stayed up somewhat late on a Sunday night for a PPV, the following Monday at school was split evenly between yapping with my friends about the show and wanting to take a nap.
I bring all this up because it now seems almost quaint that a three-hour WWF/E show used to induce a placid state of overawed sleepiness. As I write this, the morning after I attended to All Elite Wrestling's Dynasty show at Temple University's basketball arena on Sunday night, I am struggling for something like the opposite reason. Dynasty is safely considered a B-show for AEW; it's between two of its own big shows, March's Revolution and Memorial Day Weekend's Double or Nothing, and as such it should be okay for Dynasty to serve more as an exhibition than an all-time great show. That clearly wasn't the aim from wrestling's no. 2 company, and the over-stuffed, near-endless show that we got on Sunday delivered exhausting proof of that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Friend Has Been Naming Shitty TV Characters After Me For 20 Years]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=185908</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/my-friend-has-been-naming-shitty-tv-characters-after-me-for-20-years"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T16:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not much of a TV guy. Sure, I’ll grab the remote and a seat on the couch for any live sports broadcast. But the last scripted series I watched was Derry Girls, and only because I had a pending work trip to Ireland and hoped it would prepare me for the brogues I’d encounter. (Not much. But, what a show!)
But I broke my fast to watch Zero Day, the prestige TV poli-sci-fi thriller starring Robert DeNiro and Angela Bassett. Nothing against the Oscar winners, but they weren’t what drew me. I was only there for the return of Dave McKenna. Or, rather, "Dave McKenna."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Victor Robles Demonstrates What Trying Can Get You]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186290</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/victor-robles-demonstrates-what-trying-can-get-you"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T16:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Victor Robles of the Seattle Mariners was carted off in the ninth inning of Sunday's game against the San Francisco Giants. Robles tracked a fly ball off the bat of Patrick Bailey deep into the right-field corner, sprinting 113 feet in just over six seconds and then laying out into the netting over the wall in foul territory. Incredibly, Robles somehow came down with the ball, although the catch had to survive a replay challenge from the Giants. This was an amazing feat of athleticism, to say nothing of bravery and hustle and all the rest.
Robles's catch did not make MLB's daily top plays compilation, and I can think of two possible reasons why: For one, by crashing into the netting to haul down a foul ball, Robles made it possible for San Francisco's Luis Matos to tag and advance on what would've otherwise been a dead ball. This wound up mattering a lot one pitch later, when Wilmer Flores chopped a grounder through the right side of the infield and Matos trotted home to score what would be the game-winning run. For another, and more importantly, Robles fucked himself up pretty bad on the catch and had to be carted off the field; it was everything he could do after coming down to flip the ball in the direction of the infield and prevent Matos from coming all the way around to score on the fly-out. Perhaps MLB's clip editors aren't very comfortable adding to a celebratory highlight compilation a play that ends with a guy writhing in agony:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, April 7: Block By Block]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186171</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-april-7-block-by-block"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T15:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buckle up: It's time for the Monday crossword. This week's puzzle was constructed by Brian Callahan and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Brian (he/him) is a pub trivia fan and dog dad from Chicago. In addition to editing and mentoring for AVCX’s midi arm, Lil AVCX, he occasionally posts puzzles on his blog, oliogrids.com
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE. Note that we're pausing open submissions until April 18.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Algorithm's Economic Unreality]]></title>
        <id>67f3e17e8b52b30001dc9a83</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/the-algorithms-economic-unreality/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T15:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How did Americans vote for a man who pledged to collapse the global economy? The algorithm told us to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Ovechkin Scores]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186240</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/alex-ovechkin-scores"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T14:14:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You could tell he wanted this. Not that he ever made much secret of that—he's got a goalscorer's heart, and the logical conclusion of scoring goals, if you're great and prolific and ageless, is that you end up with more goals than anyone else has ever scored. But as Alexander Ovechkin finally passed Wayne Gretzky in the marathon chase that never stopped being a sprint, he let his desire and pleasure say it all. There was a little extra oomph in his wrister, from his office in the top of the left circle, off a cross-ice feed to beat Ilya Sorokin through traffic. A little extra violence as he uncoiled, a little extra body English on the follow-through, because an extra mile per hour or two can be the difference between a score and a save, and he smelled blood, and he wanted to finish it there and then. Then, when goal 895 was safely in the twine, Ovechkin allowed himself to take his eyes off goal, turned back up ice, and sprawled on his stomach as the Capitals swarmed him at center ice.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9xd8pB72yMQ]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azzi Fudd And The Huskies Finally Got Their Crowning Moment]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186232</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/azzi-fudd-and-the-huskies-finally-got-their-crowning-moment"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T13:39:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TAMPA, Fla. — On the keen, soulful UConn women’s basketball internet, Azzi Fudd is “the people’s princess.” She carries herself with regal grace. She’s kind to her young superfans. By teammates’ accounts, she can do no wrong in the eyes of Geno Auriemma. But even fairytales have dark beginnings. A poison apple (or poison Brussels sprouts) marred Fudd’s first trip to the national championship game in her freshman season. As a junior, she was cursed with a second ACL tear in five years, this one right after teammate Paige Bueckers tore hers. “To say that these four years have not gone according to plan or according to how we thought it would go, I would say, is to put it lightly,” Fudd said with a chuckle on Saturday afternoon, calm but hungry before the national championship game. 
On Sunday, the princess rescued herself and brought some peace to the kingdom. Fudd logged 24 points, five rebounds and three steals in an 82-59 win over South Carolina that gave UConn the program’s 12th NCAA championship and its first in nine years. For her vital two-way play in Sunday’s game and in Friday’s game against UCLA, the redshirt junior was voted the Final Four’s Most Outstanding Player.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Matter The Car, Max Verstappen Is Inevitable]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186170</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/no-matter-the-car-max-verstappen-is-inevitable"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T13:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The focus would have been on the Red Bulls no matter the outcome of the Japanese Grand Prix, but thankfully for Christian Horner and company, Max Verstappen at least dragged the attention, however briefly, away from the mess made in the second seat. His weekend was an instant classic on a track that the commentators repeatedly referred to as "historic" and "old-school." You could almost forget that Red Bull had dumped Liam Lawson for Yuki Tsunoda just two races into the season. For just one moment, this weekend wasn't about that.
Verstappen had some help along the way. Suzuka made it easy; his McLaren competitors behind him made it easier. The earlier sessions of the weekend were marked by constant red flags due to grass fires, but on the day of the race, rain poured heavily. The rain didn't stick around long enough for a wet weather race, but it did cool track temperatures until tire degradation was barely a concern—as an added bonus, the cars were running the three hardest compounds of tire available to them—and the probability of grass fires was down to zero. The historic nature of the track was evident in its lone DRS zone and narrow breadth. Both made it difficult for drivers to overtake and turned the race into an exceedingly polite formality; there wasn't much race to go around.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Leaf Tip Ain’t Big Enough For The Two Of Us]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186167</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-leaf-tip-aint-big-enough-for-the-two-of-us"/>
        <updated>2025-04-06T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two-lined hooktip moth lays its eggs in even rows on twigs and leaves of birch and alder trees. When the eggs hatch, almost inscrutably small larvae emerge, some as short as half a millimeter. But the newborns, called warty birch caterpillars, have a serious task at hand. Despite not even being snack-sized, the caterpillars are easy pickings. Unlike other caterpillars, they do not build shelters, live in groups, or live inside leaves like the extremely flat larvae or some other fliers. Instead, newborn warty birch caterpillars march their itty-bitty bodies to a leaf of their own, which they will defend against any intruder, adult or baby, who happens to wander by.
At least, this is what Jayne Yack, a neuroethologist at Carleton University in Ottowa, suspected. In a 2008 paper, Yack and colleagues observed that freshly hatched warty birch caterpillars lived alone on leaves and produced two kinds of vibrations, which they employed in minutes-long duels with other caterpillars. Now, in a paper recently published in the Journal of Experimental Biology, Yack and a team of researchers have confirmed the unusually territorial nature of the caterpillars and described their vibrational defense mechanisms, which are surprisingly feisty for a creature smaller than a grain of rice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Houston Showed Why You Play To The Final Buzzer]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186151</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/houston-showed-why-you-play-to-the-final-buzzer"/>
        <updated>2025-04-06T21:54:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was no question it would be Cooper Flagg's shot. How could it not be? In a season where the Duke freshman was celebrated as one of the best players in the country, a prospect with boyish charm and a monster on both ends of the court, there was no question who would have the ball in his hands as Duke's national title hopes were on the line with less than 18 seconds left in the semifinal.
Flagg came off a screen and took the pass from Kon Knueppel just above the three point line, but Houston's J'Wan Roberts was with him step for step. Fighting his way into the paint, Flagg rose for a jumper from the elbow that met its end at the front of the rim, another Cougars defensive rebound on the night.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What It Means To Fund Studies in Transition “Regret”]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186143</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-it-means-to-fund-studies-in-transition-regret"/>
        <updated>2025-04-06T19:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a month of dismantling more than $180 million in national research on trans health, meaning research in support of the health of trans people, the White House has reportedly directed the National Institutes of Health to conduct "research" on the "regret" people may feel after transitioning, Max Kozlov reported Friday in Nature. I say "research" because this directive will not actually fund any research, but rather spawn propaganda. Matthew Memoli, an infectious diseases researcher who served as acting director of the NIH, who, incredibly, at one point refused to be vaccinated against COVID-19, wrote an email to the NIH directing that new research be funded in "a few specific areas," including the “chemical and surgical mutilation” of children and adults—the conservative colloquialism for gender-affirming care and surgery—and social transition, in which a person transitions with no medical intervention.
It feels almost stupid to state the obvious—which feels increasingly less like a risk, as no major national publication has covered this new directive after Nature's scoop—this is not how research is done. This is not bad science; it's not science. Science is driven by open inquiry, not fixed outcomes. Funneling money into "research" to find evidence of a predetermined belief will not result in any actual science, but rather disinformation disguised as science. It feels equally stupid to point out the irony that the Department of Health and Human Services told Kozlov that, "NIH is prioritizing research that serves the best interests of public health, not ideological agendas, and will continue to support studies that provide clear, objective data — particularly regarding the long-term effects of gender transitions." The ongoing research on trans health was not ideological, as HHS claims, but rather driven by curiosity and a fundamental belief that all people deserve to live healthy lives. Whatever results emerge from this directive will not only be ideological, it will be a sham.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sarah Strong Doesn’t Act Her Age]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186140</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/sarah-strong-doesnt-act-her-age"/>
        <updated>2025-04-06T15:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TAMPA, Fla. — Sarah Strong is so over it. She floats above the Final Four action with just the smallest hint of facial expression, a wry quarter-smile like she’s trying to hold in a laugh. And when the freshman big drives past a defender for an easy scoop layup or slips in the perfect spot for a rebound, it really can feel like that’s what’s happening: Sarah Strong is in on this joke and you’re not. 
To retake their place at the top of women’s basketball in Sunday afternoon’s national championship game against South Carolina, the UConn Huskies are turning to a young star but an old soul. UConn’s rout of No. 1 overall seed UCLA on Friday night was the team at its best and deadliest. Azzi Fudd found her shooting form after a rough offensive first half in the Elite Eight. Paige Bueckers got to her midrange spots. Jana El Alfy, a redshirt freshman center, poked entry passes away from Lauren Betts. Geno Auriemma has called this a less-balanced team than he’s used to coaching. “We rely so much on our perimeter game, and not as much on our interior game,” he said. Lucky for him, though, he has the piece to make it work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Acquire Nick Gordon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=847409</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/royals-acquire-nick-gordon.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-05T17:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have acquired Nick Gordon from the Orioles, FanSided’s Robert Murray reports.  Baltimore’s end of the trade return isn’t yet known.  Gordon signed a minor league deal with the O’s last winter, and he’ll now join the team that his father Tom pitched with from 1988-95. Drafted fifth overall by the Twins in 2014,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ovechkin Skates Down Gretzky]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186100</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ovechkin-skates-down-gretzky"/>
        <updated>2025-04-05T14:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It might have seemed like excessive prudence to send the traveling party out that early. The full suite of people on hand for the Capitals' game in Carolina on Wednesday, in anticipation of Alexander Ovechkin chasing down Wayne Gretzky's all-time goalscoring record, included Ovechkin's family, Gary Bettman and a host of NHL executives, and Gretzky himself. At the time, Ovechkin was three goals away from tying, four from passing; it raised the specter of an extended chase that would see the traveling party fruitlessly jetting around the country for weeks, waiting for goals. But the prudence was warranted. This is Alex Ovechkin. You don't threaten Gretzky's mark without, you know, scoring a lot of goals.
Ovechkin scored No. 892 on Wednesday, and on Friday at home against the Blackhawks, put up a pair of goals to tie Gretzky at 894. It was his fourth and fifth goals in his last four games; the 39-year-old has looked invigorated by the chase. Which in itself is a tribute to his otherworldliness: energy and desire are all well and good, but it is still very difficult to score a goal, yet in 2025 as in 2005, Ovechkin makes it look like a matter of will.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New warmth / Old hotness]]></title>
        <id>67f0599304f5080001bae87b</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-292/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T23:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Saward at home in Chicago; A.J. Daulerio looks back in disbelief at 2005]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Like It HOT 100]]></title>
        <id>67f04dc604f5080001bae7cb</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/some-like-it-hot-100/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T23:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months ago, a friend sent me several boxes of god-knows-what he’d been storing for me in a relative’s basement for almost seven years after I left my Brooklyn apartment. The boxes were expensive to send, and my friend didn’t have enough money]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>A.J. Daulerio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where I’m Thawing From]]></title>
        <id>67f060b204f5080001bae8b2</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/where-im-thawing-from/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T23:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[winter in Chicago leaves town]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Saward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Lie The Phoenix Suns, Who Did It All Wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=185958</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/here-lie-the-phoenix-suns-who-did-it-all-wrong"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T19:08:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The time has come to bury the Phoenix Suns, who barely lived and are now dead. When they made the Finals three years ago and then got sold to an aggressive, engaged billionaire, it seemed as if they would perch atop the Western Conference for years to come, a position they attempted to consolidate by moving as aggressively as possible. Instead of winning anything of value, they're drawing dead in a conference that has passed them by and now face one of the bleakest futures in the NBA. They are quite the cautionary tale.
This all starts in the summer of 2020, when a Devin Booker–led Suns team ranked 13th in the West got invited to the Orlando pandemic Bubble and—helped along by a good deal of Cam Payne nonsense—won every one of its eight games there. The basic idea that a team built around Booker could win a bunch of games that mattered had been unproven until the Bubble: He'd scored 70 points in a game before, in a meaningless March 2017 loss (only two Suns who played that night are now still in the league, while another two are active assistant coaches), but had never even cracked 30 wins in any of his four pro seasons to that point. That tiny segment of Mickey Mouse pandemic basketball is the strongest case against Bubble hoops being a flimsy, inconsequential construct rather than a real end to a real season, as the Suns did build on the foundation by trading for Chris Paul.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick McAfee You Are 37 Years Old]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186068</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/patrick-mcafee-you-are-37-years-old"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T18:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In late February, I caught wind of a salacious rumor involving students at Ole Miss. Obviously, since I do not make a habit of keeping apprised of the sex lives of college students, it came to my attention because it had already garnered a lot of attention online. The rumor was spreading via a photo of a paragraph of text from someone’s Snapchat DMs that had gone viral on YikYak, a social media app primarily used by students. 
Which makes sense, since this was exactly the sort of rumor that spreads like wildfire on a college campus. It has all the hallmarks: a sorority girl breaking a sexual taboo and being called a slut for it. Anyone who has ever been 18 has heard some version of a rumor like this, they rival crypto as the favored currency among those too young to legally drink. There is not a fully-formed pre-frontal cortex to be found in these situations. Most people that age haven’t seen the damage that kind of rumor can do, or they don’t care, and so off it goes into the ether, to live as a vaguely remembered story you once heard about someone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ja Morant Will Not Stop Doing His Little Gun Thing]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186066</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ja-morant-will-not-stop-doing-his-little-gun-thing"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T18:16:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is not ridiculous to say that one of Ja Morant's professional goals should be trying to end his association with firearms. Whether or not you agree that an NBA player should be suspended multiple times for being eager to show people his gun, it cannot be denied that this man's affinity for guns has had negative consequences on his career. "Stop being the gun guy" perhaps does not belong at the very top of a list of Morant's aspirations, but it shouldn't be at the bottom, either.
The NBA is hoping a $75,000 fine will encourage Morant to find something other than guns to be interested in. Morant was hit with that fine this morning because during Thursday night's nationally televised game against the Heat—which Morant won at the buzzer—he celebrated a made three-pointer by pretending to shoot a gun. This is objectively a strange thing for a player to fined for; NBA players pretend to shoot stuff after hitting a big shot every night, and this is something that Morant had done several times already throughout the season. The reason he got fined today is that he also did the gun gesture during Tuesday's game against the Warriors, to the great annoyance of Steph Curry, and the NBA warned him to knock it off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are The Pittsburgh Pirates Really In Dire Straits?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186011</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/are-the-pittsburgh-pirates-really-in-dire-straits"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T18:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defector has partnered with Baseball Prospectus to bring you a taste of their work. They write good shit that we think you’ll like. If you do like it, we encourage you to check out their site and subscribe.
This story was originally published at Baseball Prospectus on March 26.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Normandin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good News: The EU Wants To Censor Elon Musk]]></title>
        <id>67f012c46edde70001bb554c</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/good-news-the-eu-wants-to-censor-elon-musk/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T17:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why we have to break free from a right-wing, individualistic interpretation of free speech]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[West Sacramento Has The A’s, Whether They Want Them Or Not]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186060</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/west-sacramento-has-the-as-whether-they-want-them-or-not"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T17:18:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The West Sacramento Athletics have been in existence as a viewing experience for three days and one full home stand, and already they have accomplished something of note. It’s this: They have already made 2,800 people disappear.
Beginning their indeterminate layover in Yolo County with a three-game series against the Chicago Cubs, they announced consecutive attendance figures of 12,119, 10,095, and 9,345. Those people were entertained by defeats of 18-3, 7-4, and 10-2. The baseball part of all this, we can presume, will take care of itself; the crowds, on the other hand, offer hints of just how aggressively unmoved the A’s new town seems to be by the presence of an actual Major League Baseball team in their midst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baltimore Sues DraftKings And FanDuel For Exploiting Gamblers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=186036</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/baltimore-sues-draftkings-and-fanduel-for-exploiting-gamblers"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T14:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The city of Baltimore filed a lawsuit against FanDuel and DraftKings on Thursday, alleging that both companies have violated city's consumer protection ordinance by targeting and exploiting gamblers. 
The specific allegations made in the suit—that these sports books hook gamblers with misleading promotions, use proprietary data to profile and target problem gamblers for further exploitation, and seek only to extract as much lifetime revenue as possible from each customer—are all allegations that have been made before in other lawsuits and by people whose problem gambling has been exacerbated by access to online sports books.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With An Epidemiologist Who Lost Her Job Because Of The DOGE Layoffs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=185597</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-an-epidemiologist-who-lost-her-job-because-of-the-doge-layoffs"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T14:35:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump administration is going full steam ahead on its terrifying project of dismantling the country's defenses against HIV. In February, it gutted the U.S. Agency for International Development, which plays a crucial role in supplying other countries with HIV treatments. On March 21, the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services terminated the Adolescent Trials Network, or ATN, which is the only national research network focused on adolescents and young adults who live with, or are at risk for, HIV. The National Institutes of Health terminated grants related to PrEP, medications that can prevent HIV infection. And this week, the administration laid off scores of workers at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention who focused on HIV prevention.
Since its formation in 2001, ATN has enrolled more than 30,000 people in over 150 studies, many of which focus on the ongoing HIV epidemic, and expanded access to PrEP. But it has a more expansive remit, also studying the rising incidence of STIs, and mental health and substance abuse disorders in young people. Nevertheless, the network's termination letter used the same language seen in letters from the National Institutes of Health that intend to eradicate "diversity, equity, and inclusion" in scientific research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gangsta Grillz Is Forever]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=185777</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/gangsta-grillz-is-forever"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T14:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Listening Habits, a column where I share the music I’ve been fixated on recently.
We are currently in a moment of 2000s nostalgia. I suppose it was inevitable. After spending 20 years stuck in the '90s, it's about time the culture finally moved on to the next decade. This may have brought us an even worse version of George W. Bush era politics and the #RETVRN of white male angst content, but it has also given us something good: a revival of the mixtape DJ. The most prominent recent example of this type of call back to the DatPiff era of DJ-hosted records is Playboi Carti's new album Music, where Swamp Izzo goes around shouting his name all over the place as if it were 2011 again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Silence Surrounding Sedona Prince Is A Look Into Sports’ Future]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=185120</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-silence-surrounding-sedona-prince-is-a-look-into-sports-future"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T13:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sedona Prince's college basketball career ended quietly, and with a loss. The TCU center put up four points, an assist, and nine rebounds before fouling out in the fourth quarter of a 58-47 defeat in the Elite Eight against one-seed Texas. Prince didn't shine much in the prior game, either, a TCU victory that mostly belonged to teammate Hailey Van Lith. Prince had been one of the faces of the push for women's equality in college sports, and then became the subject of accusations from women who said Prince had assaulted or abused them.
In total, five women have either talked to reporters, or to law enforcement, or filed documents with a court describing some form of sexual assault or physical violence by Prince. The first woman spoke out on TikTok several years ago; the most recent was in police reports filed earlier this year. Back in August, Prince said on TikTok "I have never abused anybody in my life." In response to recent police reports in Texas, her lawyer, A. Boone Almanza, said Prince herself was an assault victim that day, kicked and hit in the head repeatedly "when a former friend entered her house uninvited." What happened, Almanza said, "was a traumatic event for Sedona."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re Littering The Earth With Space Trash]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=185965</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/were-littering-the-earth-with-space-trash"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T13:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alizee Zimmermann and her husband were rinsing off their dive gear on a relatively muggy January evening when the sky exploded with a dozen shimmering fireballs. “We saw the trails as it started to lose control,” Zimmermann told me. “Then we heard the booms.”

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NIe5Ao6R39s]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paola Rosa-Aquino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>