<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-02-07T06:22:13.683Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encpipe – encryption tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141838</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/encpipe-encryption-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T21:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Encpipe is billed as the simplest encryption tool in the world. 
The post Encpipe – encryption tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Eagles Fan Version Of Personal Growth, With Dan McQuade]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180646</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-eagles-fan-version-of-personal-growth-with-dan-mcquade"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T21:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have other stuff to talk to my therapist about, luckily, but there is a part of me that feels churlish and a little silly about not appreciating Sunday's upcoming Super Bowl matchup. Yes, we've gotten somewhere between plenty and more than enough of both these teams in the monitors over recent years; yes, some of this grumpiness is surely due to the fact that there were more novel and compelling options than these two very good but very familiar teams. I didn't write that I felt wrong in my churlishness, though. I felt, and still feel, faintly silly about it—about my inability to get especially excited about a game between these two extremely good and evenly matched teams, each of which dominated their respective conferences throughout the season and both of which make for pretty fascinating counterpoints to the other. I think the game will be good, but I can't quite feel what I probably should be feeling about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rouge – elegant, extendable code highlighter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141760</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/rouge-elegant-extendable-code-highlighter/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T21:02:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rouge is a pure Ruby syntax highlighter. It can highlight over 200 different languages, and output HTML or ANSI 256-color text. 
The post Rouge – elegant, extendable code highlighter appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone Thinks They Have A Shot]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180707</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/everyone-thinks-they-have-a-shot"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T20:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My first thought upon seeing that the Lakers had traded a haul for Hornets center Mark Williams was that Rob Pelinka had never bothered to tab over to the "games played" section of Williams's permanently mangled Basketball-Reference page. The second was that the Western Conference playoffs are going to be incredible this year.
The majority of the eight teams in the bottom half of the playoff race made win-now trades ahead of Thursday afternoon's trade deadline. The talent scramble somehow gets fiercer the further you go down the standings; four of the five teams between eighth and 12th, at least two of which will not even make the play-in field, pushed their chips in. Why would this many ailing teams further over-leverage themselves for a chance to fight their way into the playoffs? I'd argue that this is proof that the play-in is working as intended and keeping more teams than ever before from tanking, but more to the point, the teams at the bottom of the race are battle-tested while the teams at the top are not. They're not just pushing for a playoff spot due to some clever incentives or because it's the right thing to do. They're doing it because they think they've got a shot at taking out one of the variously green teams currently atop the standings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoBang – QR code and barcode snanner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141892</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/cobang-qr-code-barcode-scanner/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T18:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CoBang is a native QR Code and barcode scanner application for the Linux desktop.
The post CoBang – QR code and barcode snanner appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Last Living Bedwardite]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180481</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-last-living-bedwardite"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T18:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AUGUST TOWN, Jamaica — It's not simple to get to August Town, but it is easy. Anyone can take the road into this Kingston suburb, founded as a haven for freedmen. Its name refers to Emancipation Day of Aug. 1, 1838, which is celebrated as a national holiday. On the way in, one can see a beautifully preserved mural of two 20th-century men who capture the ethos of Caribbean black liberation: Marcus Garvey and Haile Selassie. Selassie's legacy is more contentious—the Rastafari people who venerate the late Ethiopian emperor are not universally loved, even here—but there's little controversy about Garvey, whose likeness appears on the $20 coin.
At the time, I had no idea that Garvey would soon be pardoned by Joe Biden in one of his last acts as president, plastering Garvey's name in American headlines for the first time in decades. He was convicted on trumped-up mail fraud charges in 1923, a prosecution less about any crime than it was about Garvey's towering stature as an activist who founded the Universal Negro Improvement Association and advocated for black people's rights in the U.S., Jamaica, and around the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Wizards Have Forgotten How To Lose]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180650</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-washington-wizards-have-forgotten-how-to-lose"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T18:01:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A week ago when we explained the historical badness of the Washington Wizards, we were on solid mathematical and historical ground. The team was on pace to become one of the very worst teams ever; if you squinted into the police cruiser spotlight, as you no doubt have done at least once in the last year, they had an outside chance at being the very worst; if you watched them play, the case only became more convincing.
But because these are the Wizards, they couldn't even get the stink right. And because we want to be fair (this is a lie; we never want to be fair), we must now note that the Wiz are on a rare-for-them three-game winning streak during which they have lowered their margin of defeat to a terrible but not hideous 13.8 points per game, and now cannot finish with the worst record in NBA history. In fact, their 119-102 win over Brooklyn last night was their second most decisive victory of the season, a celebration of sorts after the already completely forgotten deal that sent Kyle Kuzma to Milwaukee for Khris Middleton, an athletic rookie, and a pick swap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YunoHost – Linux distribution simplifying server administration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141939</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/yunohost-linux-distribution-simplifying-server-administration/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T17:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YunoHost is a Debian-based Linux distribution which aims simplify server administration and democratize self-hosting.
The post YunoHost – Linux distribution simplifying server administration appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Want To Focus On My Salad]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180673</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-want-to-focus-on-my-salad"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T17:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
It’s the early 2000s and lifestyle magnate Martha Stewart has done a very bad thing. The Securities And Exchange Commission just opened a far-ranging investigation into biotech firm ImClone after its founder, Sam Waksal, divested himself of company stock right before the FDA announced that it had rejected ImClone’s application for a drug called Erbitux. Ever considerate, Waksal tipped off a number of fellow investors to dump their shares before the news hit. Stewart was one of those investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PixelViewer – cross-platform image viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141972</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pixelviewer-image-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T16:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PixelViewer is a cross-platform image viewer supports reading raw Luminance/YUV/RGB/ARGB/Bayer pixels data from file and rendering it.
The post PixelViewer – cross-platform image viewer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vv – image viewer for sixel terminals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142024</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/vv-image-viewer-sixel-terminals/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T16:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vv is different from the vast majority of image viewers. It's a small command-line program to view images from the terminal.
The post vv – image viewer for sixel terminals appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Think River Dolphins Don’t Piss On Each Other? Urine For A Surprise]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180604</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/think-river-dolphins-dont-piss-on-each-other-urine-for-a-surprise"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T15:58:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most majestic water shows in the world cannot be found in front of the grand casinos of Las Vegas or Macao. Instead, it can be seen, sporadically, in the brown waters of the Amazon and other South American rivers occupied by the river dolphins also called botos. As the botos grow, their bodies blush a pale pink, a color that is particularly evident in males. When the male dolphins need to defecate, they do so without any fuss:emptying their bowels directly into the river. But when the males pee, they sometimes get a little fancy with it.
In such cases, a male boto will slowly roll onto his back, exposing his belly to the surface. Then, like a hoisted flag, his penis will gradually emerge from its usually sheathed position. And finally, the boto will begin to pee in one mighty stream that reaches as high as three feet in the air. The powerful arc of the boto's pee sails over his own head and eventually plummets into the water several feet beyond the tip of the dolphin's long snout, or rostrum. Once the boto has peed all its pee, he will slowly roll over once again and resume swimming. With a show like this, who wouldn't want a front-row seat?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Setting up for multiple snows (THU-2/6)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3816695</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-setting-up-for-multiple-snows-thu-2-6/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T15:43:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is the potential for at least four inches of snow early next week with multiple rounds of snow expected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boxes – view, access, and manage remote and virtual systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141969</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/boxes-view-access-manage-remote-virtual-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T15:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boxes is a simple GNOME application to view, access, and manage remote and virtual systems.
The post Boxes – view, access, and manage remote and virtual systems appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Warriors And Jimmy Butler Are Trying To Stop The Clock]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180661</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-warriors-and-jimmy-butler-are-trying-to-stop-the-clock"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T14:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is almost sad that this week will likely be remembered as the Luka Doncic trade deadline, if only because the single weirdest trade of the week and maybe the decade happened four days later. That one involved more teams, players, personalities, and wrecked preconceptions than the one that saw the Mavericks bail on their generational star. Which is why the gods in their infinite chicaneries came up with this four-torsoed, five-headed beauty that centers around the skull-melting notion of Jimmy Butler, Stephen Curry, and Draymond Green as teammates for what might be their last serious run at incandescence.
The Doncic-Anthony Davis deal, which nobody saw coming on Saturday and still inspires conspiracy theories about who screwed whom and for what reasons this long after the deal, has the advantage both of happening first and involving the Los Angeles Lakers. But before there was Luka—before anyone other than Miriam Adelson even imagined that there could be a deal involving Luka—there was Jimmy. Good lord,  was there Jimmy. There was Jimmy staging a month-long one-man palace revolt that he surely could not win against septuagenarian strongman Pat Riley, which played out through a series of suspensions and recriminations long past the point of caring. But credit where due: Butler’s monomaniacal persistence in the face of the oddest NBA trade deadline in memory finally got him both the escape route and the raise that he wanted, even if the team he went to is actually further behind in the standings than the one he left.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Baker And The NCAA Roll Over For Donald Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180664</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/charlie-baker-and-the-ncaa-roll-over-for-donald-trump"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T14:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, Donald Trump signed an executive order seeking to ban trans athletes from competing in girls and women's sports. A few hours later, NCAA president Charlie Baker showed everyone just how little moral courage he has.
Like all of Trump's executive orders, the one he signed yesterday does not actually change the law of the land, nor does it create a clear path for enforcement. The executive order relies on a new and perverse interpretation of Title IX—the federal law that prevents schools that receive federal funding from discriminating on the basis of sex—arguing that schools that allow trans people equal opportunities to participate in sports are actually in violation of Title IX. The Trump administration is now threatening to pull federal funding from schools that protect the rights of trans people. The administration's interpretation of Title IX will certainly be challenged in court, and it's not clear how the administration plans to identify schools that are running afoul of this executive order.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sesdiff – generates a shortest edit script]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141822</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/sesdiff-generates-shortest-edit-script/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T13:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sesdiff is a shortest edit script diff that's written in the Rust programming language.
The post sesdiff – generates a shortest edit script appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XEphem – Serious Interactive Astronomical Software Ephemeris]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141944</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/xephem-serious-interactive-astronomical-software-ephemeris/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T10:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XEphem is a Motif based ephemeris and planetarium program for Unix-like operating systems including Linux.
The post XEphem – Serious Interactive Astronomical Software Ephemeris appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chloe Lula]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/chloe-lula-caa</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/chloe-lula-caa"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T08:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Chloe Lula, a Berlin-based cellist and electronic musician.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ONLYOFFICE Docs 8.3 released: stamps and multi-page selection in PDF files, enhanced collaboration in sheets, Shape Merge and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141998</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/onlyoffice-docs-8-3-released-stamps-multi-page-selection-enhanced-collaboration/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T07:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The developers of ONLYOFFICE Docs have released version 8.3, bringing a fresh wave of enhancements.
The post ONLYOFFICE Docs 8.3 released: stamps and multi-page selection in PDF files, enhanced collaboration in sheets, Shape Merge and more appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliShell – like IntelliSense, but for shells]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141738</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/intellishell-like-intellisense-but-for-shells/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T23:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliShell acts like a bookmark store for commands. No need to have a clean history to find something useful with CTRL + R.
The post IntelliShell – like IntelliSense, but for shells appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snip – simple snippet manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141778</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/snip-simple-snippet-manager/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T20:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Snip is a simple snippet manager for your predefined Ultisnips Snippet Directory.
The post Snip – simple snippet manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Dipshit And His Strike Team Of Greasy Beavises Are Stripping The Wires From The Federal Government]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180358</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/billionaire-dipshit-and-his-strike-team-of-greasy-beavises-are-stripping-the-wires-from-the-federal-government"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T19:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most important thing to know about both the chittering Renfields gnawing through the ductwork of the American administrative state and the billionaire sociopath they serve is that they don't care. Every bit of damage they have done and will do springs from and follows this fundamental fact. They don't know anything about what they're wrecking, naturally—these are creatures that do and eat and shit on things, not ones that know—but it is more salient that they don't care enough even to try to know anything about it. They are busy and stupid in a way that mirrors their rancid imago—hardcore in a way that is mostly just erratic and impatient, secretive but grandiose, prissily paranoid, conducting their nasty business on an amphetamized and whimsical timetable—but they are also not really doing anything for the reasons that people or institutions do things.
They do not care about or understand the state because they do not acknowledge that it is valid; they do not care about or understand public service or public servants because they refuse the premise that such things could even exist. This goes beyond the private sector's familiar and self-flattering disdain for the public sector, which amounts to the load-bearing assumption that everything and everyone operating outside of the free market is somehow the minor leagues. There is another opposition at work here, a crabbed and curdled worldview that reflects libertarianism's signature balance of ideological resentment and pure childish certitude, and which is defined by the smash-and-grab anti-ethos of the vandal, but which is finally simpler and stupider than either.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yankees Claim Braden Shewmake]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840551</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/yankees-claim-braden-shewmake-waivers-royals.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T19:17:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Yankees announced Wednesday that they’ve claimed infielder Braden Shewmake off waivers from the Royals. He’ll bring their 40-man roster to capacity, meaning New York will now need to make a roster move once lefty Tim Hill’s deal is finalized. Kansas City designated Shewmake for assignment last week. They’d claimed him off waivers from the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NWSL To Pay $5 Million To Abused Players As Part Of Settlement]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180615</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nwsl-to-pay-5-million-to-abused-players-as-part-of-settlement"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T18:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NWSL will have to pay $5 million to players who were abused and submit regular accounts detailing how it is addressing reports of harassment and discrimination following a joint investigation by the attorney generals of New York, Illinois, and Washington D.C., the offices announced Wednesday. 
The news followed an investigation by all three attorneys general that found—like the other investigations before it—that the league failed to prevent or adequately respond to player reports of harassment and sexual misconduct. From the purview of the attorneys general, this also put the league in violation of Title VII of the Civil Rights Act, which prohibits employment discrimination based on race, color, religion, or national origin, as well as in violation of each state’s human rights act.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lesley Ryder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nets Sabotage Their Own Tank With Thrilling Upset Of Rockets]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180590</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nets-sabotage-their-own-tank-with-thrilling-upset-of-rockets"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T18:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday night's game between the Houston Rockets and Brooklyn Nets had the spirit of March Madness, and I'm not sure whether I intend that in a complimentary or derogatory way. Both teams were struggling to make free throws, finish layups, or just hold onto the ball long enough for an actual shot to go up. It was, at times, a very rough watch. But the finish made up for all of it.
The sloppiness was a key factor in how Brooklyn, a team that likely won't make the play-in, snatched a 99-97 win away from Houston. Walking out of the arena afterward, one fan within earshot compared it to Reggie Miller's eight points in nine seconds against the Knicks. That comparison felt a bit too ambitious, but "six points in six seconds from two players" is tough to capture eloquently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Would Think Nothing Of Being Shot In The Chest With This Plasma Cannon]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180584</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-would-think-nothing-of-being-shot-in-the-chest-with-this-plasma-cannon"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T17:29:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Leyh likes to screw around with voltage and electric fields and plasma. In his time he's built some of the world's biggest Tesla coils, huge towering transformers that throw off terrifying webs of crackling electricity. Working for a decade out of the since redeveloped American Steel Studios space in West Oakland, and now just plying his plasma skills wherever there's an empty tarmac, Leyh has imagined and tested and fabricated and tinkered with many a device that you or I might reasonably mistake for a doomsday weapon. One of these projects, which Leyh has been working on for 30 years, is a by-God plasma cannon, a huge gun that fires a 180,000-volt blast of hell-fire a distance of about 35 feet. 
Plasma, as you know, is at the extreme bitchin' end of all science. You can make it in your microwave if you don't mind blowing up your microwave, and possibly your home, but it is also the stuff they brew up inside of tokamak reactors. Plasma is what kerplodes out of a fuel-stuffed diamond-lined hohlraum after it's been bombarded by 192 freakin' lasers. It's what forks out of a thunderstorm with annihilating fury and chases every living thing for miles around under cover. In China last month researchers at the EAST nuclear fusion reactor fired up a plasma hotter than the interior of the Sun and held it in a steady state for just shy of 18 minutes, making that plasma more than twice as old as the second-oldest human-made plasma of this kind ever to have existed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-Highlight – powerful syntax highlighter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141867</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/re-highlight-powerful-syntax-highlighter/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T17:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Re-Highlight is a powerful syntax highlighter, which is a sub-module of the Reqable project. 
The post Re-Highlight – powerful syntax highlighter appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLB Loses Its Best Umpire To Sports Gambling]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180523</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mlb-loses-its-best-umpire-to-sports-gambling"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T17:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major League Baseball announced on Monday that umpire Pat Hoberg, who is famous for calling a perfect game in the 2022 World Series, was officially fired for violating the league's gambling policy. The news that Hoberg would be disciplined broke in June last year, though he appealed the decision then, denying that he bet on baseball.
According to MLB's investigation, Hoberg had shared a legal sports betting account with a friend he met at a poker tournament in 2014, and, after sports betting was legalized in Iowa in 2019, asked his friend to place non-baseball bets for him. His friend, a professional poker player, did bet on baseball, and later shared his account log-in with Hoberg. (Communication was done over Telegram; both Hoberg and his friend deleted their conversation logs after MLB's investigation began, because, according to Hoberg, he was embarrassed by the volume of his bets.) When Hoberg opened a sports betting account in his own name, the operator flagged that Hoberg's device was also associated with another account that had bet on baseball, and MLB opened an investigation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freeze – generate images of code and terminal output]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141872</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/freeze-generate-images-code-terminal-output/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T16:15:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freeze generates PNGs, SVGs, and WebPs of code and terminal output alike.
The post Freeze – generate images of code and terminal output appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Of Negative Thinking]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180529</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/erik-baker-make-your-own-job-interview"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T16:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Self-help literature is ubiquitous in American culture: A staple of airport bookstores, grocery magazine aisles, as well as its own separate category on the New York Times Nonfiction bestseller list (under Advice, How-To & Miscellaneous). The lifestyle trade, which props up actual scientists, amateur life coaches, and shameless grifters alike, thrives and shifts with each new social fad. Think Robert Greene. Think Malcolm Gladwell, Peggy Orenstein, Brene Brown, Thich Nhat Hanh, Eckhart Tolle. Atomic Habits. How To Win Friends & Influence People. The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People. 
Perennial topics include: body positivity, mental health, relationship advice, why gender essentialism is or isn’t true, pseduo-scientific/spiritual explanations for a bad or good personality, and, since the very beginning, guides to navigating the workplace. Books about how to make money are so popular they could constitute a separate genre. It might seem as if this appetite for self-improvement and creative enlightenment is baked into America itself. Moreover, one could be tricked into believing that the self-help industry’s constant focus on managerial expertise, adversarial competition, and a phrenology-like fixation on types of people is a reflection of objective truth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: An icy start (WED-2/5)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3815314</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-an-icy-start/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T14:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not the prettiest of mornings out there. The precipitation, which is so fine and light that it has barely shown up on the radar, has created a mess on bridges and overpasses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: An icy start]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3815314</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-an-icy-start/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T14:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not the prettiest of mornings out there, the precipitation, so fine and light that it's barely showing up on radar, has created a mess on bridges and overpasses. I didn't notice any pre-treatment on any of the overpasses last night on the way home on the major roads...so we start this morning with a mess [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On The Road With The Monte Carlo Ice Crews, Who Keep Disaster At Bay]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180528</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rally-monte-carlo-ice-crews"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T14:02:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The race, which starts in Monaco and loops 1,012 miles into the Alps and back over the finish line in the Principality, presents its drivers with the most treacherous stages of any rally on Earth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raphael Orlove</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Wing Café’s saucy wings & Exclusive Jerk’s bold Caribbean bites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=869556</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-wing-cafes-saucy-wings-exclusive-jerks-bold-caribbean-bites/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T14:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wing Cafe Northland // Photo By Tiffany Watts Wing Cafe As a dedicated wing enthusiast and firm believer that the saucier the wing, the better, I recently found myself at Wing Cafe’s Northland location on a quick lunch break with my mom. I went all in, ordering a 12-piece wing combo ($23.00): six Cajun Buffalo and six Durango, because, let’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Best Free and Open Source Linux Photo Management Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=3818</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/photomanagement/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T13:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo management software is a type of computer application that helps users to organize their digital image collection.
The post 8 Best Free and Open Source Linux Photo Management Software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qreator – create your own QR codes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141888</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/qreator-create-qr-codes/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T11:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qreator enables you to easily create your own QR codes to encode different types of information in an efficient and compact way.
The post Qreator – create your own QR codes appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tucana – Linux distribution built for customization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141851</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tucana-linux-distribution-customization/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T09:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tucana is an ultra customizable distro built entirely from scratch.  Essentially Tucana is a Build-Kit where you can share you customizations.
The post Tucana – Linux distribution built for customization appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[upsammy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/upsammy-c43</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/upsammy-c43"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T08:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to upsammy, a Dutch electronic musician.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[20 Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to the Top Utility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=5172</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alternativestotop/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T07:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[top is a small, venerable utility that offers a dynamic real-time view of a running system. We identify alternatives to top that offer more control in managing processes on a running system.
The post 20 Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to the Top Utility appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rotary Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3047/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3047/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greenbone Vulnerability Manager – central management service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141820</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/greenbone-vulnerability-manager-central-management-service/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T23:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Greenbone Vulnerability Manager is the central management service between security scanners and the user clients.
The post Greenbone Vulnerability Manager – central management service appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jalen Brunson Plays Like A Rolling Rock]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180522</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jalen-brunson-plays-like-a-rolling-rock"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T22:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NBA is always getting taller, longer, springier, stronger. The league's future might lie in lithe titans like Victor Wembanyama and Evan Mobley. We now have the technology to imbue stick figures with strength, mobility, and guard skills. You'd be hard-pressed to identify an elite prospect under 6-foot-4. In such a world, the best player on the New York Knicks seems almost like an act of defiance. Small, dense, and inexorable, Jalen Brunson is a rock tumbling down a hill. He'll kick up off a tree root, squash a small weed, and get jostled by the changing curve of the slope. But he'll always create a path through any resistance.
I'm convinced that Brunson's official 6-foot-2 listing is one of the league's many fake measurements. He might land two inches shy of that, and has approximately the bodily proportions of a thumb. He doesn't get too high off the ground, and he doesn't run all that fast. What he does is weaponize what must be the lowest center of mass of any NBA star. He hunches over the ball, protecting it with the cave of his body, backing his way into the post. When he turns to face up, he'll use his shoulders to batter and dislodge his bigger opponents; where necessary, he will even use a noggin so big that his teammates wear colossal hats to mock it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PGPTool – encrypt and decrypt files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141841</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pgptool-encrypt-and-decrypt-files/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T22:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PGPTool is a Java-based desktop GUI application for easy and regular PGP decryption/encryption.
The post PGPTool – encrypt and decrypt files appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eye of MATE – simple graphics viewer for the MATE Desktop Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141965</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/eye-of-mate-simple-graphics-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T21:33:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eye of MATE (or eom) is the official image viewer for the MATE Desktop Environment. 
The post Eye of MATE – simple graphics viewer for the MATE Desktop Environment appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL No Longer Interested In Ending Racism]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180496</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nfl-no-longer-interested-in-ending-racism"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T19:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many other American companies catering to bigots by abandoning their DEI programs, the NFL has decided to rearrange the furniture before President Donald Trump's planned appearance at Super Bowl 59 this Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help! I’m Worried The Government Will Stiff Me On My Paycheck!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180452</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/help-im-worried-the-government-will-stiff-me-on-my-paycheck"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T17:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about boring high school classes, fucking on gondolas, Kendrick Lamar, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jaren Jackson Jr. And The Memphis Grizzlies Are Leveling Up]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180450</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jaren-jackson-jr-and-the-memphis-grizzlies-are-leveling-up"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T16:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NBA's Western Conference is being weird right now. The two teams that made last year's conference finals—both younger teams thought to be on the rise—have now made themselves sharply worse with trades: The Timberwolves, by swapping Karl-Anthony Towns for a couple of grumpy and ill-fitting Knicks role-players; and now the Mavericks, by dumping the future of their franchise for a few post-prime* years of the broadly unreliable Anthony Davis. The Kings, Suns, and Warriors are in various states of crisis; the Nuggets are being hunted down by math; and the two Los Angeles teams are stalled out in also-ran-hood, pending unlikely runs of good health. Even the Spurs, who seemed a month ago to have arrived at feistiness ahead of schedule, are lately sagging back into lottery territory. 
*Here's a wild statistic, from Dan Devine of Yahoo Sports: Since Davis's arrival in Los Angeles in 2019, the Lakers have outscored opponents by just four total points in the nearly 4,600 minutes that Davis has played without LeBron James on the court beside him.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scrumlens – agile retrospective tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141805</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/scrumlens-agile-retrospective-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T16:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scrumlens is an agile retrospective tool. Real-time, and designed to make your team's voice heard loud and clear.
The post Scrumlens – agile retrospective tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Artist’s Way’ Week 4: We Are Deprived]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180415</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-artists-way-week-4-we-are-deprived"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T16:29:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To what do you give your attention? What does giving that attention away do for you? These are the questions Julia Cameron asks us to ponder in Week 4 of The Artist's Way in the form of reading deprivation. The book was originally published in the 1990s so contemporary readers will often refer to this challenge as "media deprivation" to encompass all the ways we can now distract and upset ourselves using the tiny computers in our pockets.
We talked about how we each engaged with the challenge in our own ways—or not at all–in the latest iteration of The Artist's Way book club. If you're just joining us now, you can start from the beginning of the process here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Music Club Travels Back To M.A.A.D City]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180438</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-music-club-travels-back-to-m-a-a-d-city"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T15:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Defector Music Club, where a number of our writers get together to dish about an album. Today, Tom Ley, Patrick Redford, Luis Paez-Pumar, and Israel Daramola explore Kendrick Lamar's second album and major label debut good kid m.A.A.d city.
Israel Daramola: Kendrick Lamar just won a bunch of Grammys and is about to play in the freakin' Super Bowl halftime show. As a headliner! After ostensibly taking over rap over the past year. And it all started here, more or less, on his major-label debut good kid m.A.A.d city, a totemic record out the gate that people wanted to give instant classic status. But before we get into all of that, let's start with our personal relationships to this album back when it was first released in 2012.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bregging the Question]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=456114</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/bregging-the-question/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T15:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Which teams stand to gain the most by signing Alex Bregman?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Szymborski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Ice and snow risks over the next week (TUE-2/4)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3813901</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-ice-and-snow-risks-over-the-next-week-tue-2-4/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T15:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City is in a cold weather pattern where we may get some ice on Wednesday, with more snow and ice risks through the next week]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Microsoft Windows Media Player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141957</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-microsoft-windows-media-player/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T14:26:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Media Player is a video and audio player. We recommend the best free and open source alternatives for Linux.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Microsoft Windows Media Player appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chroma – general purpose syntax highlighter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141864</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/chroma-general-purpose-syntax-highlighter/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T14:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chroma takes source code and other structured text and converts it into syntax highlighted HTML, ANSI-coloured text, and more.
The post Chroma – general purpose syntax highlighter appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The De’Aaron Fox Trade Is A Bet On Victor Wembanyama]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180376</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-deaaron-fox-trade-is-a-bet-on-victor-wembanyama"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T14:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two seismic NBA trades that took place over the weekend involved four Western Conference teams scattered across the standings. What links the deals together is that they both represent, to different degrees, bets on Victor Wembanyama.
The San Antonio angle is more obvious, but let us first consider the temporal rejiggering aspect of the Luka Doncic–Anthony Davis turbodeal. One theory of the Mavericks' decision to trade the best player on a team that made the Finals eight months ago is that they would be better set up to win big this year with Davis, as old as he is, than with Doncic, as injured as he currently is. Dallas clearly peeked up the standings, saw a largely untested Oklahoma City team that struggles with size—I'd note this premise is flawed since Chet Holmgren and Isaiah Hartenstein have yet to be healthy at the same time this season, but we are adopting the Nico Harrison position for this exercise, so—followed by the even more untested Rockets, a bizarro Grizzlies team that plays a Eurobasket style untested in the playoffs, the somewhat rickety Nuggets, and a bunch of teams with a bunch of old guys, and concluded that they could make a real run at contention right now. I don't think it's a stretch to think that Dallas also peeked down the standings and felt motivated to slam down the accelerator given the looming threat of Wembanyama, especially now that his Spurs are operating like a contender instead of a purpose-built lottery dweller.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gum – tool for glamorous shell scripts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141845</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gum-tool-glamorous-shell-scripts/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T10:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gum lets you leverage the power of Bubbles and Lip Gloss in your scripts and aliases without writing any Go code.
The post Gum – tool for glamorous shell scripts appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EasyOS – experimental Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141801</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/easyos-experimental-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T09:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EasyOS is an experimental Linux distribution made in Australia. While using Easy, everything happens in RAM. 
The post EasyOS – experimental Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QIV – Quick Image Viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=129</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/qiv/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T08:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Image Viewer (QIV) is a very small and pretty fast open source gdk/imlib image viewer.
The post QIV – Quick Image Viewer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flow State Ep. 263: Ghostly Label Edit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-ep-263-ghostly-label-edit</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-ep-263-ghostly-label-edit"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T08:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s mix is all music from Ghostly International in honor of their recent reissue of Studio’s 2006 record, West Coast. Thanks to Sam Valenti IV for the assistance (check out his newsletter, Herb Sundays]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minisign – sign files and verify signatures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141772</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/minisign-sign-files-verify-signatures/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T23:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minisign is a very simple tool to sign files and verify digital signatures.
The post Minisign – sign files and verify signatures appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emails Show How Saints Leadership Offered To Help Local Clergy With Damage Control Amid Sexual Abuse Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180355</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/saints-pelicans-clergy-abuse-emails-released"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T22:04:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just how much help did the leadership of the Saints and Pelicans provide to the archdiocese of New Orleans as it was forced to acknowledge its own role covering up sexual abuse for decades amid in the global Catholic church sex abuse crisis? Four news outlets—WWL Louisiana, The Guardian, the Associated Press, and The New York Times—fought for the release of emails between local Catholic leadership and the Saints. The emails were first obtained through a clergy abuse lawsuit brought against the archdiocese, but the Saints and the church wanted them kept private. The Saints and the church lost their court battle, and recently the four news outlets were finally given copies of the emails.
All four outlets wrote about what they discovered and published stories Monday; each report is worth your time. If one thing is made clear from the emails that were released, it is how easy it is for one powerful organization, when in crisis, to turn to another for help, and receive it with few questions asked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beef-Ending Trade Of J.T. Miller Leaves Vancouver Sports Media With Nothing To Talk About]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180323</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/j-t-miller-elias-pettersson-canucks-beef-update"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T21:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The only way forward seemed to be for the Canucks to get rid of either Miller or Pettersson, and indeed that's what happened: Miller was traded to the Rangers on Friday evening. Let’s see how they got there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No But Seriously, Why Did The Mavericks Trade Luka?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180324</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/no-but-seriously-why-did-the-mavericks-trade-luka-doncic"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T20:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty much right away, late on Saturday night when the Luka Doncic trade was first announced, I was convinced there had to be something wrong. Not just that I thought Shams was hacked—which I did—but even after we found out it was legit. Not to get all conspiracy-brained, but none of it passed the smell test, and it didn't help that various commentators seemed to have the same talking points explaining the trade, all of it revolving around Luka Doncic being so fat that when he sits down, he swallows the whole arena, or something. There is just no way to convince me that "conditioning" is why the Mavericks had to trade a 25-year-old superstar that just took them to the Finals last season. To that end, I would like to dissect some of the talking points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Times Call For More Trade Chaos]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180334</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/these-times-call-for-more-trade-chaos"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T18:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can say it with some certainty now: whoever thought that the NBA trade deadline would work best when fit into Superb Owl Week is a genius. Assuming politics in the league office work as they do in every other corporate structure, with credit flowing upward towards the Monopoly Guy reclining in the fattest chair, that would make Adam Silver a super-genius.
And credit where it’s due: it worked. Nothing else could have kept us from our preordained position—face down in the gutter, licking up the two main themes of this championship week, the referees taking a knee for the Chiefs, and Patrick Mahomes Legacy Talk. Nothing else would have elevated our attention beyond the please-just-play-the-stinking-game-now mantra that hits like clockwork on Big Game Thursday. Nothing else would have spared us from the ceaseless bleating of the Owl Nobody Wanted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[17 Best Free and Open Source GUI Matrix Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=75460</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-matrix-clients/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T18:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix is an open standard for interoperable, decentralised, real-time communication over IP.  Here's our recommended free and open source GUI Matrix clients.
The post 17 Best Free and Open Source GUI Matrix Clients appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mirage – fast and simple GTK+ image viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141908</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/mirage-fast-simple-gtk-image-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T18:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mirage is a fast and simple GTK+ image viewer which only depends on PyGTK.
The post Mirage – fast and simple GTK+ image viewer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Jhon Durán Ever Be Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180043</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/will-jhon-duran-ever-be-back"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T16:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friday afternoon saw the official announcement of the latest coup Saudi Arabia has struck against the traditional soccer establishment. Jhon Durán, Aston Villa's impossibly cool backup striker, is headed to Saudi Pro League club Al-Nassr, which has acquired the Colombian's services for a reported transfer fee of €77 million. The move is just the latest escalation of an ongoing trend that has seen dozens of legitimately top-level talents eschew Europe's big leagues in favor of Saudi Arabia's big bucks. Like all those other moves, this one sucks ass.
The word "unprecedented" has already been attached to several previous transfers into the SPL, but it needs to be trotted out once again to describe the Durán move. This one's a lot like the Gabri Veiga transfer, only much, much more significant. Veiga was (and I guess still is?) a young prospect with genuine potential to one day reach the elite of the elite, but was not yet of serious interest to the top clubs as anything other than a flier. Durán, in contrast, has already gotten the big boys' tongues wagging. He's proven his scoring prowess in the best league in the world. He's played, and played well, in the Champions League. He's probably the single best U23 striker prospect in the world. West Ham and Chelsea both came close to signing him last summer, and his star has only risen since then. Aston Villa didn't hesitate to slap down the £57 million bid West Ham sent for Durán about a week ago, no doubt expecting that in a mere matter of months even bigger clubs—the likes of Chelsea, Paris Saint-Germain, and Barcelona have all reportedly been keeping a close eye on him—would come offering even bigger money. Anyone who pays attention to this stuff would've predicted that, by this time next year, Durán would have been either the face of Aston Villa's attack or the splashy new signing of one of Europe's perennial contenders. Veiga could've maybe, eventually gotten to where Durán is now, right on the doorstep of the soccer elite. And yet Durán, like Veiga, turned away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cade Cunningham Will Beat You Up]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180232</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cade-cunningham-will-beat-you-up"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T16:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luka Doncic spent his final game as a Dallas Maverick on the bench watching a coronation and a tribute act. Days after Cade Cunningham was named an all-star for the first time, Adam Silver came to Detroit to chat about the possibility of WNBA expansion, toast Cunningham, and join the besweatpantsed Laker-to-be in watching the newly minted all-star throw down a Doncic-esque 40-pointer. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BQ1b-ZVQaNE]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Feb. 3: Space Jam]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180315</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-feb-3-space-jam"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the crossword. This week's puzzle was constructed by Shannon Rapp and Will Eisenberg, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Shannon is a research administrator at Washington University in St. Louis. Will is a French horn player and music teacher in the Twin Cities. As a constructing duo, they've collaborated for every branch of AVCX and many other venues. They enjoy visiting new places, dining well, and solving and making crosswords together.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Apple Universal Control]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141833</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-apple-universal-control/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T15:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Universal Control is software which lets you use the keyboard and mouse to control up to two other nearby Mac or iPad devices.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Apple Universal Control appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drawing – simple image editor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141902</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/drawing-simple-image-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T15:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drawing is a basic raster image editor is similar to Microsoft Paint, but aiming at the GNOME desktop. 
The post Drawing – simple image editor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s A Supercut Of Groundhog Day In Punxsutawney]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180291</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/heres-a-supercut-of-groundhog-day-in-punxsutawney"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T14:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday was Groundhog Day, the annual weirdo holiday where weather-prediction rodents and other animals come out of hibernation and pretend to tell us what the weather will be like over the next few weeks; people stand around and cheer while this happens. I do not understand any of this and I am sure I never will. But that does not mean I don't like it.
Two years ago, Quebec meteorologist/rodent Fred la Marmotte was found dead on the morning of Groundhog Day; he had likely died the previous year. But organizers in Val-d’Espoir went along with the ceremony anyway, announcing “la mor du Fred” to the crowd right before he was to make his prediction. A new Fred made it to Feb. 2 this year and said we’d get six more weeks of winter, though the CBC reports that Canada's weather oracles were at odds: Lucy the Lobster, Shubenacadie Sam, and Fred agreed, but Wiarton Willie said we’d get an early spring. Soon, these predictions will cost 25 percent more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Winters ugly return (MON-2/3)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3812565</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-winters-ugly-return-mon-2-3/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T14:27:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, our January to February thaw is almost done. One more day from KC of nice and mild temperatures before the step down to colder wintry weather commences. Yesterday was phenomenal with highs in the lower 60s, and today will follow suit -- maybe even cracking 70° farther south of the Metro. A cold front [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal Did To Manchester City What Manchester City Used To Do To Everyone Else]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180233</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/arsenal-did-to-manchester-city-what-manchester-city-used-to-do-to-everyone-else"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T14:02:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This version of Manchester City must hate the entirety of North London. After losing 4-0 to Tottenham back in November, and the subsequent run of bad form that followed, City went into Arsenal's home ground on Sunday riding a bit of a high, relatively speaking. Though it had choked away a 2-0 lead to Paris Saint-Germain in the second-to-last Champions League league phase match, City has actually been on a bit of an upswing recently, winning six of its last eight matches across all competitions. In its most-recent match, a must-win against Club Brugge, City gave up the opener but ended up winning convincingly 3-1, thanks to a steady and ruthless second half. While I wouldn't have said that City is all the way back to its world-conquering ways, I wouldn't have been shocked if it went into North London and beat Arsenal, something it had done 12 times in a row in Premier League play between 2017 and 2023.
That being said, I am also not shocked at how the match actually went, as Arsenal played the most brutal of hosts—eat your heart out, Walder Frey—and stomped on City's slowly reanimating corpse to the tune of 5-1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[grype – vulnerability scanner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141818</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/grype-vulnerability-scanner/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T12:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[grype is a vulnerability scanner for container images and filesystems. 
The post grype – vulnerability scanner appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clear Linux OS – Linux distribution optimized for performance and security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141795</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/clear-linux-os-linux-distribution-optimized-performance-security/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T09:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clear Linux OS is an open source, rolling release Linux distribution optimized for performance and security.
The post Clear Linux OS – Linux distribution optimized for performance and security appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to popular CLI tools: grep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=105280</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alternatives-popular-cli-tools-grep/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T08:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article spotlights alternative tools to grep, a utility that searches for patterns in each file.
The post Alternatives to popular CLI tools: grep appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chick Corea & Béla Fleck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/chick-corea-and-bela-fleck</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/chick-corea-and-bela-fleck"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T08:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Chick Corea & Béla Fleck, an American pianist and American banjoist, respectively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[bower – curses frontend for the Notmuch email system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141809</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/bower-curses-frontend-notmuch-email/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T07:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[bower is a curses frontend for the Notmuch email system. There are two main views: the index, and the combined thread/pager.
The post bower – curses frontend for the Notmuch email system appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stromatolites]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3046/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3046/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Other Competitive Balance Round Draft Picks Could Be Traded This Winter?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840183</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/what-other-competitive-balance-round-draft-picks-could-be-traded-this-winter.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T04:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Competitive Balance Rounds are a pair of bonus rounds within the MLB draft, designed to give an extra pick to the game’s smaller-market teams.  Teams that fall within either the bottom 10 in revenues and market size are eligible, and since 2017, the league determined the eligible teams based on a formula involving market…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Witch Hunt]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180125</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-witch-hunt"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T01:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of January the president sat impatient on a Zoom call from his garish, gilded estate in Florida, slumped and flustered as his lawyer idled next to him. Even his makeup reflected the mood, with his face daubed to a dull flaxen hue instead of his typical defiant goldenrod. Whatever it was that Judge Juan Merchan was saying from his courtroom in New York during Donald Trump's sentencing that day faded into a dull whistling sound. When the time finally came for him to speak, Trump strung together the same phrases he has uttered every time the subject of his criminal history comes into question. He had suffered an "injustice," been through a "very terrible experience," before landing on one of his favorites: "It's been a political witch hunt." Persecuted and yet unbound, 10 days later the convicted felon was re-inaugurated to the most powerful political office on earth.
I've been thinking of this moment a lot in the last two weeks as Trump, or his cadres of sycophants and sympathetic oligarchs and associated corps of sunlight-deprived grifters, have set about dismantling the American project with the speed and enthusiasm of a contestant on Supermarket Sweep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Way – code snippets manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141720</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/the-way-code-snippets-manager/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T23:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[the-way is a terminal-based code snippets manager.Record and retrieve snippets you use every day, or occasionally, without starting a browser.
The post The Way – code snippets manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland Moves Toward Historic Rugby Three-peat While Humiliating Failed Imperialist Nation Where Rugby Was Invented]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180247</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ireland-defeats-england-rugby-six-nations-2025"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T22:32:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody has ever won three consecutive outright titles in the Six Nations Championship. That’s a rather stupendous stat, considering that this annual round-robin affair for Europe’s top national rugby teams, which kicked off this weekend, dates all the way back to the nineteenth century. But maybe this is the year: Ireland, the reigning two-time defending champs, took a step toward history on Saturday night in Dublin by pounding England, 27-22, in the opening round of the 2025 tournament. Don’t be fooled by the final score: A pair of garbage-time tries from England covered up Ireland’s actual dominance. 
Heading into the matchup against its most despised rival on and off the pitch, Ireland is currently ranked second in the world (behind only South Africa) and has the highest-rated squad in this year’s all-Euro Six Nations field.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pygments – generic syntax highlighter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141756</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pygments-generic-syntax-highlighter/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T21:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pygments is a generic syntax highlighter suitable for use in code hosting, forums, wikis or other applications.
The post Pygments – generic syntax highlighter appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can’t Be Headbutting Dudes On The Basketball Court]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180236</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/you-cant-be-headbutting-dudes-on-the-basketball-court"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T20:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With just under three minutes left, Arizona pulled away from Arizona State to win the Grand Canyon-adjacent rivalry game, 81-72, on Saturday. It had been a sleepy start to the game, with both teams combining to hit a mere 23 shots and commit 19 fouls in the first half. Basheer Jihad kicked some life into the Sun Devils at the beginning of the second half with a pair of dunks and a three-pointer to grab a five-point lead. Alas, it was not meant to be. Caleb Love, last seen hitting a ridiculous half court three to force overtime on way to a win against Iowa State Monday night, led the comeback hitting multiple threes as the Wildcats went on a run.
Things were almost wrapped up with about 30 seconds left on the clock when Love was jawing with Arizona State's BJ Freeman under the hoop during an out of bounds play and, well, Freeman replied ... headfirst. Both were ejected, and Arizona State Coach Bobby Hurley yanked his team from the floor as the final buzzer sounded, bypassing the handshake line and customary pleasantries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kryptor – simple, modern, and secure file encryption and signing tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141727</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/kryptor-file-encryption-signing-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T19:27:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kryptor lets you encrypt multiple files/directories with a passphrase, symmetric key, or asymmetric keys.
The post Kryptor – simple, modern, and secure file encryption and signing tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>