<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-11-05T10:17:56.244Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chicago Bulls Unveil United Center-Inspired City Edition Uniforms]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83183</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/05/chicago-bulls-unveil-united-center-inspired-city-edition-uniforms/basketball/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T07:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although the rest of the league isn’t set to officially reveal their City Edition uniforms until Nov. 14, the Chicago Bulls unveiled their new United Center-inspired design over the weekend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Independence’s historic Twin Drive-In movie theater to close after 60 years of screenings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859482</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/independences-twin-drive-in-movie-theater-to-close-after-60-years-of-screenings/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T04:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This morning, the historic B&B Theatres Twin Drive-In announced in a Facebook post that it will be turning its lights off permanently on Nov. 17.  For 60 years, the cinema has provided a variety of movies to the Kansas City area as one of the only drive-in theaters in Missouri.  The company took to Facebook to share the news, saying...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Luck Trying To Get A Remote Biglaw Job — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076991</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/good-luck-trying-to-get-a-remote-biglaw-job-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T00:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want To Work Remotely? Well, you probably can't.
Biglaw Gets Fuzzy On The Lessons From Dewey's Collapse: Lateral partner guarantees are back, baby!
The Supreme Court Is Scary! But make it Halloween.
The Latest In The GOP's Election Nonsense: From Georgia.
Don't Speculate About Your Lawyer's Pregnancy (Or Anyone's): They'll tell you when they're ready, *IF* you need to know.
The post Good Luck Trying To Get A Remote Biglaw Job — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Department Of Justice Is Going To Be Real Busy On Election Day]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076985</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-department-of-justice-is-going-to-be-real-busy-on-election-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T00:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DOJ's election day schedule is intense.
The post The Department Of Justice Is Going To Be Real Busy On Election Day appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk’s Henchmen Testify There Was No Illegal Lottery, Just Good Old Fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076979</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/musks-henchmen-testify-there-was-no-illegal-lottery-just-good-old-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T23:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peanut the squirrel would be so disappointed. 
The post Musk’s Henchmen Testify There Was No Illegal Lottery, Just Good Old Fraud appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reminder: Stop Gossiping About Your Coworkers’ Fertility]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076987</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/reminder-stop-gossiping-about-your-coworkers-fertility/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T22:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not a good look.
The post Reminder: Stop Gossiping About Your Coworkers’ Fertility appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giants Loss Marked By Anti-Irish Playcalling]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172343</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/giants-loss-marked-by-anti-irish-playcalling"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T22:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why does Brian Daboll hate the Irish? 
Among the many failed decisions the soon-to-be-former Giants head coach made on what was a bloody awful Sunday for his home side, none were more noticed than Daboll’s bypassing extra-point kicks in favor of two-point conversions in the fourth quarter—not once, but twice. Daboll kept kicker Jude McAtamney on the sidelines, only to watch poor and poorly supported quarterback Daniel Jones muck things up both times, and see his team lose precious points in a 27-22 loss to the Commanders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, Trump Supporters! Just Who Thinks You’re Deplorable?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076965</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/hey-trump-supporters-just-who-thinks-youre-deplorable/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T21:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How does Trump view your intellect as it relates to tomorrow's election?
The post Hey, Trump Supporters! Just Who Thinks You’re Deplorable? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Herrmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOP Demands Judge Throw Out Legitimate Ballots In Georgia Because Of Poll Workers’ Error (There Was No Error)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076973</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/gop-demands-judge-throw-out-legitimate-ballots-in-georgia-because-of-poll-workers-error-there-was-no-error/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T21:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They lost in state court. But what if you make the same argument in federal court while shouting EQUAL PROTECTION?
The post GOP Demands Judge Throw Out Legitimate Ballots In Georgia Because Of Poll Workers’ Error (There Was No Error) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Lateral Partner Compensation Guarantees Are All The Rage Again]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076972</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/biglaw-lateral-partner-compensation-guarantees-are-all-the-rage-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T20:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dewey Know What's The (Old) New Hotness In Partner Compensation?
The post Biglaw Lateral Partner Compensation Guarantees Are All The Rage Again appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The São Paulo Grand Prix Was A Wet And Wild Max Verstappen Masterclass]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172262</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-sao-paulo-grand-prix-was-a-wet-and-wild-max-verstappen-masterclass"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T19:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many reasons, the São Paulo Grand Prix is my favorite weekend of any in Formula 1. The track is the best, or at least my favorite, on the ever-more-bloated calendar, and its traditional position towards the end of the season makes it appointment viewing any time there is a semblance of a title race. Throw in the possibility for rain, given that the race almost always takes place in São Paulo's wet season, and the stage is often set for chaos, drama, and all-timer performances. The 2024 edition at the Autódromo de Interlagos might end up the most memorable weekend of all, if not for the pure quality on display, then for the sheer chaos that altered the schedule, upended the grid both before and during the race, and left the only man who could have won this race at the top of the podium, and within millimeters of another world title.
Let's start with that man, Max Verstappen. While last weekend in Mexico brought out some of Verstappen's worst impulses en route to a penalty-aided sixth-place finish that kicked Lando Norris' title charge and its corresponding narrative into overdrive, Sunday's race was Verstappen at his absolute best. That's not to say he had a great Sunday altogether; thanks to heavy rain on Saturday, qualifying was postponed to Sunday morning, under still wet conditions. Thanks to poorly timed red flag in the second part of qualifying, Verstappen was mired in 12th place for the start of the race, and a five-grid penalty, due to adding in a new internal combustion engine, pushed him further back to 17th. To make matters worse, Norris nabbed pole position, giving the McLaren driver hope of a not just a big points finish but also the possibility that Verstappen wouldn't get many points of his own, shrinking the drivers' championship gap further.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Athletics Officially Change Name, Introduce Logos for Sacramento]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83173</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/04/athletics-officially-change-name-introduce-logos-for-sacramento/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T19:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Oakland Athletics are no longer. The club officially announced today that they are now known simply as Athletics. The new location-less name will stick for as long as the team plays in Sacramento, which looks like it will be for the next three seasons before they move to Las]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Creamer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Elite Litigation Boutique Where Associates Gain Early Trial Experience And Learn By Doing]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076958</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/holwell-shuster-goldberg-elite-litigation-boutique-where-associates-gain-early-trial-experience-and-learn-by-doing/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T19:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Holwell Shuster & Goldberg is committed to developing the finest associates by putting complete trust in them at the earliest opportunity, allowing them to grow exponentially as litigators.
The post An Elite Litigation Boutique Where Associates Gain Early Trial Experience And Learn By Doing appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Political scientists lay out how abortion views could impact the vote]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859450</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/political-scientists-lay-out-how-abortion-views-could-impact-the-vote/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T19:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday, Nov. 5, is Election Day — the last day for Americans to cast their ballots. In 10 states, voters could reinstate or expand abortion rights, or add further protections. (John Partipilo/Tennessee Lookout) Political scientists and pollsters who have been studying attitudes on abortion since Roe v. Wade was overturned in June 2022 told States Newsroom that abortion has become...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sofia Resnick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of the classical cover song with the Vitamin String Quartet ahead of their Kauffman gig]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859433</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/the-art-of-the-classical-cover-song-with-the-vitamin-string-quartet-ahead-of-their-kauffman-gig/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T18:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vitamin String Quartet. // image courtesy the artist Instrumental interpreters of popular music Vitamin String Quartet have been making music for 25 years. Their classical versions of pop hits have not only sold a million copies, but also found their way onto the soundtracks of shows like Bridgerton, Gossip Girl, and Westworld. VSQ’s versions of songs feel timeless and, given...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working Remotely As A Biglaw Associate Is Sadly A Thing Of The Past]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076976</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/working-remotely-as-a-biglaw-associate-is-sadly-a-thing-of-the-past/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T18:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Associates were very successful when they worked remotely during the pandemic, but in-person requirements are the newest normal.
The post Working Remotely As A Biglaw Associate Is Sadly A Thing Of The Past appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women’s Pro Baseball League Set to Launch in Summer 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83168</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/04/womens-pro-baseball-league-set-to-launch-in-summer-2026/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T18:27:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[League co-founded by Justine Siegal — first woman to coach a pro men's team and to throw batting practice in MLB — aims to ride wave of women's sports by throwing out first pitch in summer 2026 with six teams primarily in northeast United States]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raiders Fire Three Coaches For Lack Of Anything Else To Do]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172307</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/raiders-fire-three-coaches-for-lack-of-anything-else-to-do"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T18:23:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFL is becoming weirder with every week. If you doubt that, let us present Saquon Barkley's airborne rear end as the first thing you see when he and it sail over your head. It's becoming too hard to keep up with all of the concussion-infused nonsense in this league, especially in a week in which two teams with one win on the season triumphed on the same day.
But then, just as your disorientation is threatening to swallow you whole, there are the Las Vegas Raiders. To call them a pillar of stability would be inaccurate, but damn if they aren’t reliable. Their gift for ass-backwardness (hello again, Saquon) is overwhelming, and after a loss on Sunday they defenestrated three of their most prominent offensive coaches—nine months after those coaches were hired, and nine games into the current season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recent safeguards should quash efforts to overturn election results, experts say]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859442</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/recent-safeguards-should-quash-efforts-to-overturn-election-results-experts-say/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T18:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two election observers watch election workers at the Milwaukee Election Commission’s warehouse south of downtown during the August primary. The post-election period in swing states, including Wisconsin, will be closely watched as local officials certify results (Matt Vasilogambros/Stateline) Recent sweeping changes to how the nation handles election results should prevent a repeat of the near-constitutional crisis four years ago. For...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Vasilogambros</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How The Newest Supreme Court Justices Compare: A Look At Each Of Their Respective First Two Years On The Court]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076971</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/how-the-newest-supreme-court-justices-compare-a-look-at-each-of-their-respective-first-two-years-on-the-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T18:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overall, these justices reflect the ideological spectrum of the Supreme Court.
The post How The Newest Supreme Court Justices Compare: A Look At Each Of Their Respective First Two Years On The Court appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Adam Feldman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Keeps Voters Interested With Surprise Cameo Appearance On SNL]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076891</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/kamala-harris-keeps-voters-interested-with-surprise-cameo-appearance-on-snl/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T17:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[End the drama-la and vote for Kamala!
The post Kamala Harris Keeps Voters Interested With Surprise Cameo Appearance On SNL appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Grief Cards’ Madison Clark]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858541</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-grief-cards-madison-clark/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T17:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Madison Clark When Madison Clark quietly launched her specialized brand of sympathy cards late last year, she was hopeful they’d find an audience. Born and raised in Kansas City, Clark experienced a tremendous loss at 15 years old when her big brother Garrett was killed in a car accident at only 18 in 2008. Clark went on to travel the world, teaching in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Tech-Savvy GCs Can Overcome Governance And Productivity Challenges [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076710</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/how-tech-savvy-gcs-can-overcome-governance-and-productivity-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T16:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['The Modern CLO & Legal Ops Toolkit' provides a road map to excel in an evolving landscape. 
The post How Tech-Savvy GCs Can Overcome Governance And Productivity Challenges appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LITERA AND ABOVE THE LAW</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eagles Take One Giant Leap Backwards In Win Over Jaguars]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172245</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/eagles-take-one-giant-leap-backwards-in-win-over-jaguars"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T16:23:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hurdle only gained the Eagles five more yards, on a drive that ended with a field goal. But it was one of the weirder things you could ever see on a football field; until it happened, it wouldn't have even seemed to be on the menu. It will be in Eagles highlight packages forever. Early in the second quarter on Sunday, Saquon Barkley took a pass from Jalen Hurts in the flat. He juked one defender to pick up a first down, then spun away from another. Now with his back to the end zone, Barkley jumped into the air and over Jacksonville Jaguars cornerback Jarrian Jones and landed on his feet. It was a play that had Eagles color commentator Mike Quick screaming. “It was the best play I’ve ever seen,” head coach Nick Sirianni said.
Eagles beat reporter Zach Berman wrote that down the line, this is the play you will first remember from this game. That makes sense, and not just because the play was unique and incredible. When the Eagles honored LeSean McCoy at halftime yesterday, they showed some of his runs in the Blizzard Bowl. Nobody remembered that the Eagles trailed 14-0 in that game, or that they gave up punt and kickoff return touchdowns. They only cared that the Eagles came back to win 34-20, with McCoy rushing for a franchise-record 217 yards. (People tailgating yesterday will probably also remember that Robert De Niro and John Kerry were there.) The Eagles beat the Jaguars on Sunday, although what was once a laugher came down to the wire. Barkley's hurdle will be remembered a lot longer than that, and deservingly so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wacha Won’t Walk: Michael Wacha Signs Three-Year Deal To Stay in Kansas City]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=450260</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/wacha-wont-walk-michael-wacha-signs-three-year-deal-to-stay-in-kansas-city/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T16:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After arguably the best season of his career, Wacha will return to the Royals for at least three years are $51 million. A better writer would have figured out how to wedge a Fozzie Bear joke into the headline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davy Andrews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Nov. 4: Rock Group]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172254</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-nov-4-rock-group"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T16:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ll have a blast doing our Monday crossword. This week's puzzle was constructed by Adam Simpson, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Adam is a game designer living in San Francisco's colorful Castro neighborhood. When he's not making crosswords, Adam enjoys watching horror movies, playing Metroidvanias, and cuddling with his black cat named Rook.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Halloween House Of Horrors Channels Supreme Court]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076968</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/halloween-house-of-horrors-channels-supreme-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T15:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The true Courthouse of Horrors.
The post Halloween House Of Horrors Channels Supreme Court appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Favorite Influencer Is In Her 60s]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171965</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/my-favorite-influencer-is-in-her-60s"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T15:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heidi Clements jolted me out of a glaze-eyed scrolling spiral one night a few months ago. A typical video of hers starts with her bending over toward her camera and then stepping back to reveal her starting point, a bra and pants. Then she builds an outfit while a voiceover shares a funny or heartbreaking or inspiring nugget of wisdom, like "If you don't ask for what you want, you probably won't get it," and "You may say you have nothing to wear, I say: just get dressed. Even if you have nowhere to go, just get dressed. Even if you don't like how your body feels right now, just get dressed."
Clements has amazing style. It's androgynous and playful, a little punk, a little Stevie, California-easy with a heavy silver chain or a black leather bag. Her arms are covered in tattoos and she has a shaggy haircut I've been trying to learn to cut via internet videos. Her nose is pierced with a silver hoop and she loves a red lip. She's an influencer; she has more than 600,000 followers on both TikTok and Instagram and her manager's information is in her bio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Election Day Looms, What Trump And Harris Presidencies Will (And Won’t) Mean For Defense]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076950</id>
        <link href="http://breakingdefense.com/2024/11/as-election-day-looms-what-trump-and-harris-presidencies-will-and-wont-mean-for-defense/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T15:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While analysts told Breaking Defense a Trump administration would likely be a more unpredictable one, they also said that equally, if not more important, will be whichever party controls the houses of Congress where the defense budget is crafted.
The post As Election Day Looms, What Trump And Harris Presidencies Will (And Won’t) Mean For Defense appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VALERIE INSINNA - BREAKING DEFENSE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jaguars Junction: Week 9]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172261</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jaguars-junction-week-9"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T14:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you get to the stadium for the NFL game and suddenly soul singer Ronald Isley walks out to midfield. The lights go down and someone hands him a microphone. He strikes a pose and begins to sing: 
Hey Moo Dang, 
Sit and speak to me brother
You're moving too fast
Life is more than eating grass]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamilton Nolan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: More rain today and later this week (MON-11/4)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3717284</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-more-rain-today-and-later-this-week-mon-11-4/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T14:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drought breaking rains are still coming for the region over the coming days, including today as our system(s) output continues to create needed rains for the region. Many areas have had 1-2 1/2" worth, perhaps more a bit farther south of KC since everything started and today's rain will add to that as it moves [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 11.04.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076959</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/morning-docket-11-04-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T14:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Car crashed into law firm office Halloween night. Too bad it wasn't a DWI firm. [KOAT]
* Second Circuit affirms that "Thinking Out Loud" is not "Let's Get It On." You could say they didn't even see any Blurred Lines when considering their similarities. [Law360]
* Considering potential Harris and Trump judicial nominations. [ABA Journal]
* Another Biglaw salary bump... in London. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Law firm converting a bar into their new office. One stop shopping! [KTAR]
* Class action targets company charging big transaction fees for school lunch payments. CFPB already found that the company has charged parents $100 million in "junk fees." [NJ Law Journal]
* Eric Adams trial set for April. [Courthouse News Service]
The post Morning Docket: 11.04.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cowboys Are In The Pain Zone]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172233</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-cowboys-are-in-the-pain-zone"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T14:01:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the second quarter of their game against the Cowboys, the Atlanta Falcons faced fourth-and-3 from the Dallas 36-yard line. What played out once Kirk Cousins got the ball snapped to him was a pristine example of two interrelated statistical probabilities coming true at the same time. The Cowboys' pass defense allows the most yards per attempt in the NFL, and had given up the second-highest number of plays of 40 yards or more even before Trevon Diggs tore a muscle in his calf. Falcons wide receiver Darnell Mooney, meanwhile, leads the NFL in receptions of 20 or more yards. As three Cowboys defenders bumbled into each other, with Diggs raising his hands in disbelief, Mooney ran into a pasture of space and sauntered in for an easy touchdown.
That play was one of the many embarrassments suffered by the Cowboys as they lost, 27-21, and fell to 3-5. Their year is less than halfway over and they already have as many losses as they had in each of the past three seasons. The football Mike McCarthy's team is playing has him smashing tablets on the sideline, Ezekiel Elliott is only nominally on the team, and they have to play through a brutal schedule without several key players, including possibly Dak Prescott. The NFL's highest-paid player hurt his hamstring on a run in the third quarter and was quickly taken out of the game, leaving Cooper Rush to see out the loss. After three losses in a row, things are suddenly looking dire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smoke This Now: STIIIZY vape cartridges are now available to the Missouri cannabis market]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859247</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/smoke-this-now-stiiizy-vape-cartridges-are-now-available-to-the-missouri-cannabis-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T14:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of STIIIZY STIIIZY—a cannabis brand that originated in Los Angeles—has recently expanded to the Missouri market. Popular for its vape cartridges, 12 different strains of cartridges are now in your local dispensaries.  Among the 12 strains are indicas Watermelon Z, OG Kush, Skywalker OG, and King Louis XIII, sativas Blue Dream, Super Lemon Haze, Sour Diesel, and Strawberry...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Ellett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOP outrage sparked Missouri decision to make it harder to change gender on licenses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859462</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/gop-outrage-sparked-missouri-decision-to-make-it-harder-to-change-gender-on-licenses/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T13:24:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wayne Wallingford, the director of the Missouri Department of Revenue, speaks to reporters in December 2021 (photo: Missouri Governor’s Office) The emails started showing up on Aug. 1 into the inboxes of Missouri Department of Revenue officials, signaling growing outrage from GOP officials over what they were seeing on social media. A transgender woman in Ellisville was using the women’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Annelise Hanshaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Alan Jackson says goodbye to KC on his ‘Last Call’ tour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859306</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-alan-jackson-says-goodbye-to-kc-on-his-last-call-tour/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T21:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Jackson. // photo by Allison Scavo Alan Jackson with Jon Pardi and James Carothers T-Mobile Center Saturday, October 26 Alan Jackson brought a night to remember at the T-Mobile Center in Kansas City last Saturday blending heartfelt emotions with country charm. Jackson kept fans on their feet while tugging at their heartstrings. He set the tone for an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Scavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Dopapod at recordBar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859309</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-dopapod-at-recordbar/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T21:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dopapod. // photo by Allison Scavo Dopapod recordBar Wednesday, October 23 Dopapod are as weird as they are fun. They combine funk, metal, jazz, and more to create a musically diverse and unique jam band. Having formed in 2008, Dopapod has become a recognized staple in the jam band scene. Their energetic live shows, improv jams, and electronic additions give...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Scavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Milwaukee Bucks Are Playing Like Milwaukee Butt]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172199</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-milwaukee-bucks-are-playing-like-milwaukee-butt"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T20:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first five or so games of an NBA season can only give you so much quantitative data about how the next 77 or so will go—e.g. the Warriors might not be this great without Steph Curry because they have mostly played bad or injured teams; the Nets are not going to remain this competent, as Dennis Schröder will at some point miss a shot—but they are useful as qualitative exercises. Shots will go in or not go in at aberrant rates in the short term, which doesn't tell you much, but the processes by which teams generate good shots and prevent their opponents from doing so tell you plenty. Some qualities, then, that the Milwaukee Bucks have shown through five games: unconnected, slow, stinky, creatively adrift, thin, and generally miserable.
The Bucks are 1-5, winners in Philadelphia on the second night of the season and then losers of five straight, with double-digit losses to the Bulls and Nets in there. They lost a heartbreaker to the Cavs on Saturday as Donovan Mitchell nailed a tough game-winner. The vibes are not great: Doc Rivers is all but openly wailing on the sidelines; Giannis Antetokounmpo is sitting through garbage time in a daze; Khris Middleton, who had surgery on both ankles this summer, has not played yet this season; Darvin Ham is on the bench; and the guy he brought with him from L.A., Taurean Prince, is giving quotes like, "I just feel like defensively, our IQ has to go up." They are currently the biggest disappointment in the NBA, under circumstances that are not altogether that surprising.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Michael Wacha To Three-Year Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=829045</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/royals-sign-michael-wacha-to-three-year-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T19:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced this afternoon that they’ve signed right-hander Michael Wacha to a three-year contract with a club option for the 2028 season. Per ESPN’s Jeff Passan, the deal guarantees Wacha $51MM and can max out at $72MM if the option is exercised, as Passan goes on to note that the 2028 option rises from…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL Week 9 Uniform Schedule: Giants, Eagles, Packers Wearing Throwback Uniforms]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83163</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/03/nfl-week-9-uniform-schedule-giants-eagles-packers-wearing-throwback-uniforms/football/nfl/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T16:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our weekly series that looks at every uniform matchup across the NFL continues with the New York Giants, Philadelphia Eagles and Green Bay Packers all wearing throwback uniforms on Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Isn’t Always Enough For The Ballon d’Or]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172215</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-best-isnt-always-enough-for-the-ballon-dor"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T16:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the issues that arise from the Ballon d'Or stem from misaligned expectations. Even after almost 70 years of footballers winning the thing, it's still unclear to many what exactly soccer's most prestigious individual prize is actually for. Is it meant to go to the single best player in the world? The best player on the best team? Should the winner have scored the most goals? Won the most trophies? How do you weigh club performances with national team ones? Does it even make sense to try to isolate and award an individual in what is an indivisibly collective sport? Is this whole affair so stupid, the criteria so unclear, the voters so random, the concept so flawed, that nobody should even care about it in the first place?
For better and for worse, the answer to all of those questions is "it depends." Sometimes it's easy, when the best player in the world wins literally everything for club and country and there's no need for a multifactorial analysis. Other times, as was the case for the men's Ballon d'Or this year, no candidate's case is undeniable, and so you're forced to wade into the subjectivity muck. It's these non-obvious Ballon d'Or years that bring the controversy, but also make it more interesting by sharpening what exactly the award is getting at. And this year's men's BdO was one of the most controversial ones ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joel Embiid Shoves Author Of Weird Column About Him Shaming The Memory Of His Dead Brother]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172212</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/joel-embiid-shoves-author-of-weird-column-about-him-shaming-the-memory-of-his-dead-brother"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T15:25:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hours after the Philadelphia 76ers lost at home to the Memphis Grizzlies on Saturday night, news broke that Sixers star Joel Embiid dislodged Philadelphia Inquirer columnist Marcus Hayes in some way during a confrontation in the locker room over a rotten, cynical piece of work Hayes published this past week. That is as determinate of a statement as can be made on the interaction, as the story broke via a series of confusing and contradictory reports that first characterized it as an assault. It doesn't seem nearly that severe, but the NBA has confirmed it is investigating the matter.
"We are aware of reports of an incident in the Sixers locker room this evening and are commencing an investigation," an NBA spokesman said. The public first became aware when Keith Pompey, in the most egregiously out-of-order manner possible, tweeted, "Oh, boy, people will remember the Sixers season for all the wrong reasons. The team just dropped to 1-4 and Joel Embiid assaulted a reporter in the locker room." In a deleted reply to a fan asking for clarification of what exactly Embiid had done to the unnamed reporter, Pompey said Embiid "punched him." Twenty minutes later, ESPN's Shams Charania confirmed that an "altercation" took place, noting that Embiid took issue with Hayes's latest and clarifying, "Embiid shoved the columnist. No punch." Charania's colleague Ramona Shelburne provided the detail that the "shove was to the reporter's shoulder."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QMJHL’s Quebec Remparts Pay Homage to Beloved Quebecois Movie With Special Jerseys]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83144</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/02/qmjhls-quebec-remparts-pay-homage-to-beloved-quebecois-movie-with-special-jerseys/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerseys worn Friday vs. Sherbrooke Phoenix inspired by 1997 hockey comedy "Les Boys," which spawned three sequels, a prequel and a TV show that lasted five seasons]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon Ducks Unveil Final “Generation O” Uniform Combination]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83134</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/02/oregon-ducks-unveil-final-generation-o-uniform-combination/college/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T05:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oregon unveiled the fifth and final combination of its new “Generation O” uniforms earlier this week in preparation for Saturday’s game at Michigan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Illinois Fighting Illini Unveil Military Appreciation Helmets]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83155</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/02/illinois-fighting-illini-unveil-military-appreciation-helmets/college/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T04:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illinois will wear a special helmet design during Saturday’s Military Appreciation Game against Minnesota that honors the former football players, students and alumni who lost their lives in WWI, WWII or the Vietnam War.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve Moved Well Past Fighting Words — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076932</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/weve-moved-well-past-fighting-words-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T23:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fighting For Speech Is One Thing: But fighting during free speech is worth breaking up.
Law Firm Hopes To Make Gold In Denver: Best of luck to Vinson & Elkins!
Georgia's Longest Criminal Trial Is Over With: Jeffrey Williams takes probation after years of legal trouble.
3 Cheers For The Top 30!: These are the 30 largest law firms in Europe.
Spook Us By Sunday!: Send us your four-word combinations that would terrify the average lawyer.
The post We’ve Moved Well Past Fighting Words — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Biglaw Firm Combines Social Impact And Prestige For A Winning Formula]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076909</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/this-biglaw-firm-combines-social-impact-and-prestige-for-a-winning-formula/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T22:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This firm is rising up the ranking.
The post This Biglaw Firm Combines Social Impact And Prestige For A Winning Formula appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[honeybee bring saturn return EP to NKC Fall Fest on Saturday afternoon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858581</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/honeybee-bring-saturn-return-ep-to-nkc-fall-fest-on-saturday-afternoon/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T22:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[honeybee. // Photo by Haley Mullenix As an increasingly old rock’n’roll fan, I still haven’t complained that concerts are getting too loud. I’m fairly certain the shows in my youth destroyed the frequencies that would allow me to be bothered by all that. But increasingly, I join in with the public that clamors for concerts where a headliner might actually...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stat(s) Of The Week: Employment Law And Election Day]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076886</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/stats-of-the-week-employment-law-and-election-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T21:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does your state have a law giving workers time off to vote? 
The post Stat(s) Of The Week: Employment Law And Election Day appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Barker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk Gets Tossed Back To PA State Court In Lottery Case, Just In Time For Election]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076937</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/musk-gets-tossed-back-to-pa-state-court-in-lottery-case-just-in-time-for-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T21:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes gambits work.
The post Musk Gets Tossed Back To PA State Court In Lottery Case, Just In Time For Election appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Could The Election Mean For Data Interoperability?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076889</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/10/election-data-healthcare-interoperability/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T20:46:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Americans don’t understand how an administration's view on healthcare data sharing interoperability could directly impact them, pointed out Arcadia CEO Michael Meucci. More requirements around data sharing could lead to better care continuity, improved outcomes and lower costs.
The post What Could The Election Mean For Data Interoperability? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KATIE ADAMS - MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Bezos Could Do For The Media What Musk Did For Free Speech,’ Says Law Professor Unironically]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076911</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/bezos-could-do-for-the-media-what-musk-did-for-free-speech-says-law-professor-unironically/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T20:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a wild guess.
The post ‘Bezos Could Do For The Media What Musk Did For Free Speech,’ Says Law Professor Unironically appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many Law School Applicants Should Consider Careers In Finance]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076633</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/many-law-school-applicants-should-consider-careers-in-finance/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T19:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Students should not consider attending law school merely because a law degree can lead to a stable income.
The post Many Law School Applicants Should Consider Careers In Finance appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Rothman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dodgers Set World Series Sales Records]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83141</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/01/dodgers-set-world-series-sales-records/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T19:22:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Los Angeles Dodgers set a series of merchandise records following the 2024 World Series Championship this week]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Creamer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Way To Scare A Lawyer, Using Only 4 Words]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076916</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-best-way-to-scare-a-lawyer-using-only-4-words/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T19:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is getting terrifying! Send us four words to scare a lawyer by SUNDAY, NOVEMBER 3, at 11:59 PM.
The post The Best Way To Scare A Lawyer, Using Only 4 Words appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Select Evan Sisk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=828813</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/royals-select-evan-sisk.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T19:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that they have selected the contract of left-hander Evan Sisk. He was set to become a minor league free agent but the Royals will keep him in the organization by giving him a 40-man spot. More to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Douglas County vineyard was just named one of the best disc golf courses in the world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859261</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/a-johnson-county-vineyard-was-just-named-one-of-the-best-disc-golf-courses-in-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T19:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tasting Room // Photo courtesy of White Tail Run Winery, Vineyard, & Disc Golf Course UDisc, the largest global resource for disc golfers, named Edgerton, KS’s White Tail Run Winery, Vineyard, & Disc Golf Course the ninth-best “winery disc golf course” in the world.  Though co-owner Dan Fuller Sr. started making wine in 2003, disc golf wasn’t part of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Takes Overly Aggressive Stance On School Board Issue, Gets Admonished For His Efforts]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076924</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/judge-takes-overly-aggressive-stance-on-school-board-issue-gets-admonished-for-his-efforts/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T18:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He's very passionate about his high school.
The post Judge Takes Overly Aggressive Stance On School Board Issue, Gets Admonished For His Efforts appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Sues CBS For Tortious Editing And Violating His Rights As A Texas Consumer]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076921</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/trump-sues-cbs-for-tortious-editing-and-violating-his-rights-as-a-texas-consumer/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T18:20:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good luck getting Melania to move to Dallas.
The post Trump Sues CBS For Tortious Editing And Violating His Rights As A Texas Consumer appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Time To Vote]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172182</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-time-to-vote"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T17:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter, examining the apocalyptic politics and coverage of Campaign 2024.
I voted. That was the one thing I knew I could do. I didn't get the "I VOTED" sticker because they were all out of them; it was the last hour of the first day of early voting and the line was out the door of the high school gym when I got there. It looked like they were printing out fresh ballots for each new person, to keep up with the demand, but the man who handed me my ballot was too busy to hear me ask him if the thing that looked like a printer was in fact a printer, and I didn't want to break the flow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conquering Conferences: Enjoying Small Victories]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076883</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/conquering-conferences-enjoying-small-victories/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T17:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the small steps and the individual moments that create the most memorable experiences.
The post Conquering Conferences: Enjoying Small Victories appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEJAL PATEL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bring Back Weird Halloween Candies]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172164</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bring-back-weird-halloween-candies"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T17:36:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't give out candy, or anything else, on Halloween. Not for reasons of miserliness or whatever; I simply live in a spooky-looking (at night) log cabin at the end of a very long and dark driveway branching off of a winding and hilly forest road in a low-density area. If any trick-or-treaters have visited my home in the seven Halloweens I've lived here, they were very small, dressed very convincingly as squirrels and raccoons, and left without knocking on the door.
I've had occasion, nevertheless, to form Halloween candy opinions and judgments in that time, from taking my own kids trick-or-treating. Raising kids in an area ("neighborhood" would be inappropriate, here; it's just a road with some houses alongside) where trick-or-treating basically does not happen, you learn where the good nearby trick-or-treating districts are, and you travel to them. This means that pretty much by definition, for the past seven years my kids have trick-or-treated on Halloween only in places known to be especially good for the practice, where there are lots of decorated houses, lots of costumed trick-or-treaters, and lots of friendly people giving out lots of candy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Tribute To PATCO, The Little Rail Line That Could]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172092</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-tribute-to-patco-the-little-rail-line-that-could"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T17:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My fascination with PATCO was pure: I had no reason to go into South Jersey, and so, for a long time, all of those subway stations I passed when walking around Philadelphia were little mythical pockets of alternate existence from which people occasionally emerged. Sure, I could come up with a reason for a day trip to say, Collingswood or Haddonfield, but that hardly felt legitimate enough to forfeit the mystique. Judging by the dress of the people who left the stations, PATCO served commuters; when I eventually rode the PATCO Speedline, it should be to commute.
I'll admit, I was appalled when the prospect of a Defector Atlantic City retreat cropped up. But while Atlantic City offered to my colleagues sportsbooks and blackjack and craps and a sense of glamour, it offered me something much less sick in the head: an opportunity to ride a new and mysterious transit line. Once I realized this fact, I was, shall we say, on board.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 30 Largest Law Firms In Europe (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076898</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-30-largest-law-firms-in-europe-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T16:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because size matters in the legal profession. Which are the largest law firms in the EU? You may be surprised by how many are U.S.-based.
The post The 30 Largest Law Firms In Europe (2024) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In David Peace’s ‘Munichs,’ The Dead Are Everywhere You Look]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171137</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/in-david-peaces-munichs-the-dead-are-everywhere-you-look"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T16:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open up any novel by David Peace and you will find ghosts, and people beset by ghosts. The haunted are almost always from the north of England, except for the ones in post-World War II Tokyo. They are obsessive and prone to paranoia, as the haunted tend to be; their self-destructive streaks are galvanic and inescapable. The worse things get—things always get worse—the hauntings become propulsive, dissociative experiences. It’s fitting that the late Mark Fisher, high priest of Hauntology, was a big fan. “You are not living with the dead. You are living with the living,” Philip Roth wrote in Sabbath’s Theater. Peace’s characters aren’t afforded such merciful clarity. As one of the many disordered minds in 1977 muses repeatedly: 
“This is why people die.
This is why.”
This is why people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Segall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The YSL RICO Trial Is Finally Done With!]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076918</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-ysl-rico-trial-is-finally-done-with/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T16:15:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a Halloween miracle! 
The post The YSL RICO Trial Is Finally Done With! appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Metaphor: ReFantazio’ Is The Bullshit-Free RPG I’ve Been Waiting For]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170449</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/metaphor-refantazio-is-the-bullshit-free-rpg-ive-been-waiting-for"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T16:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese RPGs (JRPGs for short) do a lot of things right, but one thing they are not particularly known for is respecting the player's time. Whereas Western AAA games like Horizon: Zero Dawn, Assassin's Creed, or even the newer Legend of Zelda entries, pad their runtimes with open-world shenanigans, JRPGs usually earn their 100-plus hour runtimes the old-fashioned way: with a slow pace, lots of cutscenes and dialog, and grinding monsters for experience. At times, playing a JRPG can feel like watching a particularly engaging anime, if during every commercial break had you complete a puzzle or fight a monster before getting back to the show.
Metaphor: ReFantazio (let's get this out of the way: the name is dumb) isn't immune to this, especially at the beginning. The newest game from Japanese developer Atlus, makers of the Persona series as well as the more hardcore Shin Megami Tensei series, is a bit of a slow burn. Like their breakthrough masterpiece Persona 5 before it, the first couple of hours of Metaphor are an extended tutorial, which in practice boils down to doing scripted fights in between grand cutscenes that lay out the setting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STIIIZY’s Darren Blair on the brand’s commitment to providing quality cannabis to the Missouri market]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859176</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/stiiizy-leans-on-consumer-culture-and-lifestyle-in-missouri-cannabis-market-expansion/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T16:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of STIIIZY STIIIZY—a cannabis brand that originated in Los Angeles—has recently expanded to the Missouri market. Popular for its vape cartridges, 12 different strains of vape cartridges are now in your local dispensaries.  Among the 12 strains are indicas Watermelon Z, OG Kush, Skywalker OG, and King Louis XIII, sativas Blue Dream, Super Lemon Haze, Sour Diesel, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Ellett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Appealing Weekly Roundup]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076907</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/how-appealing-weekly-roundup-93/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T15:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The week in appellate news.
The post How Appealing Weekly Roundup appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ivory The Contraband-Sniffing Giant African Pouched Rat Gets It Done]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171927</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-ivory-the-contraband-sniffing-giant-african-pouched-rat-gets-it-done"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T15:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Species around the world are threatened by the illegal wildlife trade, which peddles in wares such as pangolin scales, elephant tusk, rhino horn, and rare woods. Smugglers stow these artifacts, or even the wildlife themselves, inside large shipping containers, which are too expensive and time-consuming to scan with an X-ray. To help sleuth out these objects, scientists at the Belgian nonprofit Anti-persoonsmijnen ontmijnende product ontwikkeling (which roughly translates to Anti-Personnel Landmines Removal Product Development, or APOPO in Flemish) are turning to a rat with an extraordinary sense of smell. Giant African pouched rats have been trained to sniff out landmines in the ground, tuberculosis in mucus samples, and even survivors in disaster zones. Can the eight trained rats of APOPO—Marty, Attenborough, Irwin, Betty, Teddy, Ivory, Ebony, and Fossey—rise to the occasion, and help stave off their neighbors' endangerment, or even extinction? We sat down with Ivory, who lives in the town of Morogoro in Tanzania, to learn about the smell of poaching, her itty-bitty uniform, and what kind of treats she likes most as a reward; here's how she gets it done.
On carving her own path:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>A. Giant Pouched Rat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vinson & Elkins Opens Its Doors In Denver, Hoping To Cash In On Corporate Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076892</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/vinson-elkins-opens-its-doors-in-denver-hoping-to-cash-in-on-corporate-clients/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T14:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Biglaw firm’s new location in the Mile High City will be its thirteenth office worldwide.
The post Vinson & Elkins Opens Its Doors In Denver, Hoping To Cash In On Corporate Clients appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: A big dose of rain coming (FRI-11/1)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3715074</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-a-big-dose-of-rain-coming-fri-11-1/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T14:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There will be a wet system in the Kansas City region from Saturday night into early Tuesday, and another one likely later next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands Turn Out For Nonexistent Halloween Parade Promoted By AI Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172132</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/thousands-turn-out-for-nonexistent-halloween-parade-promoted-by-ai-listing"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T14:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands of Dubliners showed up for the city's much-anticipated Halloween parade on Thursday evening. They lined the streets from Parnell Street to Christchurch Cathedral, waiting for the promised three-hour parade that would "[transform] Dublin into a lively tapestry of costumes, artistic performances, and cultural festivities." A likely story. There was no parade, and never was one. 
Would-be revelers started getting suspicious about an hour after the parade was supposed to begin, according to one attendee. The Gardaí, Ireland's national police service, tried to disperse the crowds and put out the message on social media that "contrary to information being circulated online, no Halloween parade is scheduled to take place in Dublin city centre this evening or tonight."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4th Circuit Shoots Down ‘Unite The Right’ Protester’s Attempt To Turn The Consequences Of His Own Actions Into A Constitutional Violation]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076905</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/4th-circuit-shoots-down-unite-the-right-protesters-attempt-to-turn-the-consequences-of-his-own-actions-into-a-constitutional-violation/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T14:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the better-be-doing-right-before-you-complain-about-your-rights dept
The post 4th Circuit Shoots Down ‘Unite The Right’ Protester’s Attempt To Turn The Consequences Of His Own Actions Into A Constitutional Violation appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Techdirt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Red Rooms’ Is Too Fucked Up To End]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171938</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/red-rooms-is-too-fucked-up-to-end"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T13:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's the most upsetting thing you can imagine existing on the internet? How about two videos—one 28 minutes in length, the other 31—each depicting a masked man methodically torturing, and then killing, a teenage girl. The videos, which feature dismemberment via power tool and an eyeball being slit open by an exacto knife, were broadcast live on the dark web to a paying audience of snuff-film enthusiasts.
Relax. You won't see any of that in Red Rooms, a French-Canadian psychological thriller directed by Pascal Plante, which does not feature any gore or violence. But it begins with something that is perhaps worse: A thorough description, even more detailed than the one I provided above, of the snuff films at the center of its plot. The descriptions are delivered to a silent courtroom, by a prosecutor who is trying a man named Ludovic Chevalier (Maxwell McCabe-Lokos) for the murder of three teen girls. All three murders were recorded, but the location of the third recording is unknown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 11.01.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076902</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/morning-docket-11-01-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T13:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* For you civil procedure fans: Florida resident sues Delaware corporation doing business in New York in..Northern District of Texas -- Amarillo to secure a 1-in-1 chance of scoring a judge loyal to the plaintiff. [Reuters]
* After the Supreme Court blessed purging voters within days of the election, Iowa is following Virginia's suit. [Courthouse News Service]
* YSL trial stayed true to form and couldn't even get a plea deal done without bizarre and unnecessary drama. [NPR]
* Former first minister of Scotland apologizing for calling lawyer a "Tory f*ckwit." Though, unlike American conservatives clutching pearls over the idea that one of their comedians was called garbage, the UK lawyer responded, "No offence is taken." [RollonFriday]
* Profiling the lawyers on the Harris transition team, which is heavy on Biglaw. [National Law Journal]
* CFPB considering action against Meta over financial ads. [Law360]
* "Antitrust Zeal to Morph but Won’t Fade Under Next President." In that Trump may use it to punish companies he doesn't like and Harris will openly defy her most vocal deep pocketed donors?Not so sure about this, but here's hoping. [Bloomberg Law News]
The post Morning Docket: 11.01.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anora’s writer-director Sean Baker on sex work, endings as beginnings, and mainstream acclaim]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859226</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/anoras-writer-director-sean-baker-on-sex-work-endings-as-beginnings-and-mainstream-acclaim/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T13:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anora behind the scenes. // Courtesy Neon For years, Sean Baker has made a name for himself with low-budget independent films about life on the margins. Baker’s first film, Take Out, was about an illegal Chinese immigrant working as a deliveryman in New York. 2012’s Starlet explored an unexpected friendship between two women — one younger, one elderly — in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gambling Industry’s Cynical Play For Your Vote]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172100</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-gambling-industrys-cynical-play-for-your-vote"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T13:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was originally published by The Lever, an investigative newsroom. If you like this story, sign up for The Lever's free newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amos Barshad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Art Bytes podcaster Kathleen Leighton]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857690</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-art-bytes-podcaster-kathleen-leighton/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T13:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Kathleen Leighton Kathleen Leighton never set out to work at a museum. Originally from Minneapolis, Leighton started her long legacy as a journalist, jumping from radio to TV, where she had a storied career as a news anchor. “At that point, I’d been in television for several decades and I was burned out,” she says. “I still...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hunter Renfroe, Chris Stratton Exercise Player Options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=828711</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/hunter-renfroe-chris-stratton-exercise-player-options.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T00:28:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Outfielder Hunter Renfroe and reliever Chris Stratton triggered player options in their deals with the Royals, reports Mark Feinsand of MLB.com (X links). Kansas City declined its end of a mutual option on infielder Adam Frazier, per Feinsand. In other Royals’ news lefty reliever Josh Taylor elected free agency, according to the MLB.com transaction log. Kansas City evidently ran…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even The Lawyers Are Scared! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076876</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/even-the-lawyers-are-scared-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T23:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Four Words You Can't Say To Counsel: What are the scariest four words you could hear?
Time To Wow The Audience!: Send your submissions for our 15th annual Legally Themed Halloween Costume Contest!
Sir Elton Is One Thing, But Sir Alito?: Did you know Justice Alito was knighted? Did you know that that's literally unconstitutional?
The Value Of AI Can Be Overhyped, But At Least Do Your Research: This company is ready to replace your $2000/hr paralegals. If you have 'em.
Fighting Over Basics: NYC Bar steps in to clear up misinformation.
The post Even The Lawyers Are Scared! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wishing A Happy Halloween To Our Advertisers]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076859</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/wishing-a-happy-halloween-to-our-advertisers-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T22:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boo! We love working with you.
The post Wishing A Happy Halloween To Our Advertisers appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>