<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-12-22T14:13:15.448Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USC women’s basketball coach Lindsay Gottlieb channels Gregg Popovich with short in-game interview]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686009</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-basketball/lindsay-gottlieb-usc-uconn-in-game-interview.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T13:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For some coaches, in-game interviews don’t seem to be a big issue. Other coaches, though, are still getting used to them. Lindsay Gottlieb, USC’s women’s basketball coach, is firmly in the second group. Gottlieb’s No. 7 USC team took on No. 4 UConn on Saturday in a game that could well be a Final Four Read more...
The post USC women’s basketball coach Lindsay Gottlieb channels Gregg Popovich with short in-game interview appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday Notes: Pondering Pedroia, Wright, and a HoF Ballot Dilemma]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453392</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/sunday-notes-pondering-pedroia-wright-and-a-hof-ballot-dilemma/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T12:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus Baltimore's Matt Blood on draft decisions, a 2005 conversation with Brian Bannister, Tomoyuki Sugano, Jeremy Zoll on Minnesota's promotions, facts and stats galore, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Laurila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vrite – collaborative developer content platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139941</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/vrite-collaborative-developer-content-platform/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T07:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vrite is a collaborative space to create, manage, and deploy product documentation, technical blogs, and knowledge bases.
The post Vrite – collaborative developer content platform appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Herbstreit rips Ohio State’s ‘lunatic fringe,’ ESPN’s ‘First Take’ in defense of Ryan Day]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686027</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/kirk-herbstreit-first-take-ohio-state.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T05:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first round of the College Football Playoff produced virtually no on-field suspense, as all four favorites cruised to a double-digit victory. That included Ohio State, who wrapped up the first round on Saturday night with a 42-17 win against Tennessee. But while there was no on-field drama, Kirk Herbstreit made some comments in the Read more...
The post Kirk Herbstreit rips Ohio State’s ‘lunatic fringe,’ ESPN’s ‘First Take’ in defense of Ryan Day appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Field Pass alternate cast of Ohio State-Tennessee CFP game with ‘The Pat McAfee Show’ was off the rails]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=686000</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/pat-mcafee-show-alternate-broadcast-cfp-ohio-state-tennessee-nut-busting-comment.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T04:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those who decided to tune into ESPN2 Field Pass alternate cast of the CFP First Round matchup between the Ohio State Buckeyes and the Tennessee Volunteers starring the cast of The Pat McAfee Show got a very unique experience that certainly toed the line of controversy when some improper conversation broke out about “nut-busting.” Through Read more...
The post Field Pass alternate cast of Ohio State-Tennessee CFP game with ‘The Pat McAfee Show’ was off the rails appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Media pundits heavily critique Tom Brady on call of Steelers-Ravens Week 16 game]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685966</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/tom-brady-criticized-numerous-mistakes-ravens-steelers-broadcast.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T02:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thus far, Tom Brady has perhaps expectedly had a hard time living up to the incredibly lofty expectations for his broadcasting career following his legendary NFL career. And while some have argued that he has shown growth throughout the season, his performance on the call of the Steelers-Ravens Week 16 game was perhaps a bit Read more...
The post Media pundits heavily critique Tom Brady on call of Steelers-Ravens Week 16 game appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Utah Hockey Club alternate broadcast reverse-jinxed a goal]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685829</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nhl/utah-hockey-club-goal-reverse-jinx.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T01:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There have been a lot of announcer jinxes over the years, where commentators say something and are immediately proven wrong. But the field of reverse jinxes is perhaps more interesting, where announcers say something will happen and then it does. A data-focused alternate broadcast for the NHL’s Utah Hockey Club in their game against the Read more...
The post Utah Hockey Club alternate broadcast reverse-jinxed a goal appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wisconsin announcer Matt Lepay defends CFP, cites previous blowouts in four-team era]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685930</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/matt-lepay-cfp-blowouts-wisconsin-announcer.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T00:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since this is the first season of the 12-team format, the CFP is under a microscope. It doesn’t help that Indiana and SMU, regarded as two of the shakier teams going into the CFP, lost largely noncompetitive games to Notre Dame and Penn State, respectively. But as Matt Lepay, the radio voice of Wisconsin football and Read more...
The post Wisconsin announcer Matt Lepay defends CFP, cites previous blowouts in four-team era appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sports media pays tribute to late MLB legend Rickey Henderson]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685918</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/media-members-pay-tribute-rickey-henderson-death.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T00:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Saturday, baseball lost one of its most important figures with the passing of all-time stolen base leader, Rickey Henderson. The Hall of Fame outfielder died on Friday after a bout with pneumonia at 65 years of age. Shortly after the unfortunate news broke, countless sports media members weighed in with some of their favorite Read more...
The post Sports media pays tribute to late MLB legend Rickey Henderson appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joel Klatt roasts Lane Kiffin over CFP post: ‘If your team played half as well as you tweet you would likely be in’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685907</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/joel-klatt-roasts-lane-kiffin-cfp-post.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T23:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years, Ole Miss Rebels’ head football coach Lane Kiffin has drawn a lot of attention for his social media posts. His latest of note came on X Saturday, where he joined the chorus of people criticizing the College Football Playoff Committee for selections of Indiana and SMU after those teams’ disappointing playoff performances. Read more...
The post Joel Klatt roasts Lane Kiffin over CFP post: ‘If your team played half as well as you tweet you would likely be in’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2025 Royals Top Prospects]]></title>
        <id>https://farmtofountains.com/?p=6602</id>
        <link href="https://farmtofountains.com/2025-royals-top-prospects/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=2025-royals-top-prospects"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T22:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Royals prospects just outside the latest Top 30 update: Logan Martin, RHP: Martin offers a lot of the same notes as Ryan Ramsey (below). He’s an older prospect for his level, clouding just how real his season production was. He offers a four-pitch mix with great command. There’s enough strikeout stuff to notice, but doing […]
The post 2025 Royals Top Prospects appeared first on Farm to Fountains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Farr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Famed Red Wings/Tigers host John Keating retiring after 45 years of broadcasting]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685771</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/local-networks/john-keating-famed-red-wings-tigers-host-retiring.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T22:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As local sports broadcasts bring familiar faces into the homes of countless viewers, some personalities become as integral to the experience as the teams they cover. For John Keating, whose voice and presence have shaped Detroit sports coverage for over two decades, all of that’s true. Keating is set to retire after the Detroit Red Read more...
The post Famed Red Wings/Tigers host John Keating retiring after 45 years of broadcasting appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dick Vitale calls out Lane Kiffin, CFP critics after Indiana, SMU losses]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685910</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/dick-vitale-cfp-indiana-smu-lane-kiffin.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T21:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dick Vitale does not want to hear complaints about who did not make it into the College Football Playoff. To be blunt, the first-ever 12-team playoff started with a couple of duds. Despite surrendering two cosmetic touchdowns in the final two minutes of the game, Notre Dame had little trouble with Indiana in a 27-17 Read more...
The post Dick Vitale calls out Lane Kiffin, CFP critics after Indiana, SMU losses appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tank Dell’s injury created a tough situation for the NBC NFL broadcast]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685909</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nbc/tank-dell-injury-noah-eagle-todd-blackledge-texans-chiefs.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T21:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFL games see plenty of injuries, and even a notable amount of serious injuries. And any injury poses challenges for a broadcast team. But the one to Houston Texans’ wide receiver Tank Dell in Saturday’s game against the Kansas City Chiefs was particularly rough on a few fronts. One, it came as he caught a Read more...
The post Tank Dell’s injury created a tough situation for the NBC NFL broadcast appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Post, TMZ confirm Rickey Henderson’s death, hours after reports from Dave Winfield, Ozzie Guillen, others]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685877</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/rickey-henderson-death-early-reports-eventually-confirmed.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T20:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest case of unusual reporting involves the passing of former MLB legend Rickey Henderson at 65. That news officially came out early Saturday afternoon, with the New York Post and TMZ key early sources there: Rickey Henderson, Hall of Famer and MLB’s all-time stolen bases leader, dead at 65 https://t.co/e554V5CzCU pic.twitter.com/IwUTZnZZQ0 — New York Read more...
The post New York Post, TMZ confirm Rickey Henderson’s death, hours after reports from Dave Winfield, Ozzie Guillen, others appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Best Free and Open Source Shutdown Timers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=96721</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-shutdown-timers/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T20:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux is blessed with an abundance of useful utilities. We feature interesting shutdown timers. Open source goodness as you'd expect.
The post 4 Best Free and Open Source Shutdown Timers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Herbstreit: Visiting Tennessee fans ‘by far the most’ in his 29-year ‘College GameDay’ history]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685792</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/kirk-herbstreit-tennessee-fans-college-gameday.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T20:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t long ago that Kirk Herbstreit apologized to Tennessee fans; now he’s praising them. The College GameDay star, who had his quote about Volunteers’ fans taken out of context, offered some praise — and then some on Saturday. Herbstreit was recently a guest on Barstool Sports’ Pardon My Take and doubted that the Volunteers Read more...
The post Kirk Herbstreit: Visiting Tennessee fans ‘by far the most’ in his 29-year ‘College GameDay’ history appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[littleutils – utilities for file compression, file manipulation, text cleanup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139935</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/littleutils-utilities-file-compression-file-manipulation-text-cleanup/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T19:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[littleutils include duplicate file finders, image optimizers, file rename tools, archive recompressors, a tempfile utility, and others.
The post littleutils – utilities for file compression, file manipulation, text cleanup appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joel Klatt calls out ‘partisan bias’ in college football narratives]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685802</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/joel-klatt-partisan-bias-college-football-narratives.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T19:40:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joel Klatt didn’t need to name names — his message was crystal clear. In the aftermath of Notre Dame’s 27-17 victory over Indiana, revisionist history was in full swing. Kirk Herbstreit suggested that the Hoosiers didn’t belong on the field, implying that teams like Alabama, Ole Miss, South Carolina, or even Miami might have been Read more...
The post Joel Klatt calls out ‘partisan bias’ in college football narratives appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[kleur – Node.js library for formatting terminal text with ANSI colors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139930</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/kleur-node-js-library-formatting-terminal-text/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T19:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[kleur bills itself as the fastest Node.js library for formatting terminal text with ANSI colors. It's written in JavaScript.
The post kleur – Node.js library for formatting terminal text with ANSI colors appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Penn State’s early dominance against SMU got SEC Network personalities mad over Mustangs’ CFP selection over Alabama]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685843</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/league-networks/penn-state-smu-sec-network-personalities-cfp.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T19:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regardless of how any particular version of the College Football Playoff actually plays out, many are always going to use its results to argue that other teams would have been better picks. That happened during and after Indiana’s 27-17 first-round loss to Notre Dame Friday, and it’s already going strong in the SMU-Penn State game, Read more...
The post Penn State’s early dominance against SMU got SEC Network personalities mad over Mustangs’ CFP selection over Alabama appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legendary Mississippi State voice Jim Ellis retires after 46 years calling their baseball team]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685744</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/ncaa/jim-ellis-mississippi-state-baseball-broadcasting-legend.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T19:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sports broadcasting world is no stranger to turnover, making it all the more remarkable when someone spends over four decades in the same role. Jim Ellis, the long-time voice of Mississippi State Bulldogs baseball, is one such rare talent, having called the team’s games for an incredible 46 seasons. Ellis announced this week that Read more...
The post Legendary Mississippi State voice Jim Ellis retires after 46 years calling their baseball team appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best Free and Open Source Replacements for ls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=70404</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-replacements-ls/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T18:48:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When invoked without any arguments, ls lists the files in the current working directory. We recommend some great replacements.
The post 10 Best Free and Open Source Replacements for ls appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Herbstreit, Nick Saban retroactively lobby for Cam Ward and Miami over Indiana in playoffs]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685795</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/nick-saban-kirk-herbstreit-cam-ward-miami-cfp-indiana.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T18:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Sunday, Dec. 8, before the College Football Playoff rankings reveal show, ESPN CFB analyst Kirk Herbstreit appeared on the network seemingly to discuss who’d be in and out but actually chose to offer no take. There, he said “After last year, I have learned, I have no opinions about anything.” But following the Indiana Read more...
The post Kirk Herbstreit, Nick Saban retroactively lobby for Cam Ward and Miami over Indiana in playoffs appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shutdown Scheduler – schedule shutdown and restart tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139925</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/shutdown-scheduler-schedule-shutdown-restart-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T18:15:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shutdown Scheduler is a simple cross-platform application that uses system utilities for scheduling shutdown and restart tasks.
The post Shutdown Scheduler – schedule shutdown and restart tasks appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Titans’ QB Will Levis roasted after bashing ESPN Fortnite branding for CFP]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685724</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/titans-qb-will-levis-roasted-fortnite-espn-branding-cfp.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T18:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Broadcast sponsorships have long been a source of awkwardness, but ESPN/ABC’s latest for this year’s College Football Playoff might take the cake. During Friday’s Notre Dame-Indiana game, the network heavily promoted its “Fortnite OG Kickoff” sponsorship, with announcer Sean McDonough repeatedly mentioning it on air. “You’re watching the Fortnite OG Kickoff.” pic.twitter.com/lDYQx1S9gl — Awful Announcing Read more...
The post Titans’ QB Will Levis roasted after bashing ESPN Fortnite branding for CFP appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Herbstreit: ‘Outclassed’ Indiana [shouldn’t] have ‘been on that field’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685708</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/kirk-herbstreit-indiana-outclassed-field.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T17:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rece Davis might have said that performance doesn’t validate or invalidate these selections, but that doesn’t mean everyone on the College GameDay set has to fall in line. Kirk Herbstreit tried not to frame Indiana’s 27-17 loss as a knock on the Hoosiers, but the GameDay analyst didn’t exactly shield them from criticism, either. In Read more...
The post Kirk Herbstreit: ‘Outclassed’ Indiana [shouldn’t] have ‘been on that field’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals, Junior Fernández Agree To Minor League Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=835404</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/12/royals-junior-fernandez-agree-to-minor-league-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T17:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have signed right-handed pitcher Junior Fernández to a minor league deal, the team announced. He last pitched in MLB during the 2022 season. Fernández signed with the Cardinals as an international free agent in 2014 and made his MLB debut in St. Louis five years later. Unfortunately, he was never able to establish…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leo Morgenstern</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Pasch is still chasing ‘a whole new way of broadcasting’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685456</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/dave-pasch-chasing-new-way-broadcasting-walton.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T17:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You always play for the touchdown. That’s what Dave Pasch insisted with Arizona State on the verge of punching its ticket to the Big 12 championship game in late November at home. “You win the game if you get in the end zone,” Pasch said on the ESPN broadcast. “Go score.” Yet with the ball Read more...
The post Dave Pasch is still chasing ‘a whole new way of broadcasting’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mac McClung on Bronny James performing despite pressure: ‘He’s doing a great job’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684940</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/mac-mcclung-bronny-james-performing-pressure.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T16:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bronny James has been the center of attention this season, with plenty of buzz about the Los Angeles Lakers’ plan to have him split time between their NBA squad and their G League affiliate, the South Bay Lakers. One player who’s in somewhat of a similar situation is Mac McClung. McClung is the reigning G Read more...
The post Mac McClung on Bronny James performing despite pressure: ‘He’s doing a great job’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix orders documentary about Broncos great John Elway]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685556</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/documentary-john-elway.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T16:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Somewhat overshadowed at different times during his Hall of Fame career by Joe Montana, Troy Aikman, Brett Favre, and Steve Young, Denver Broncos great John Elway is getting the star treatment from Netflix. Elway, who led the Broncos to five Super Bowl appearances, winning two to cap his record-breaking NFL career,  will be the focus Read more...
The post Netflix orders documentary about Broncos great John Elway appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Keeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to sports media rights, it’s better to buy than rent]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685219</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/sports-media-rights-buyer-renter.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T15:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In looking for a place to live, the decision to rent or buy a place can be among the most difficult parts of the process. Both options have inherent pros and cons. Renting a place requires less capital, allows for flexibility in terms of not being tied down in a certain location long-term, and is Read more...
The post When it comes to sports media rights, it’s better to buy than rent appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indiana’s Curt Cignetti tries to explain sad surrender punt]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685696</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/curt-cignetti-surrender-punt-explanation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T15:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a coach who likes to talk the talk, Curt Cignetti sure didn’t walk the walk. Clichés aside, everything that got Indiana to South Bend disappeared the second Cignetti saw his breath. The aggressiveness that saw the first-year head coach earn Coach of the Year honors and turn one of the worst football programs in Read more...
The post Indiana’s Curt Cignetti tries to explain sad surrender punt appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City's oldest restaurants: Where you can still eat your way through city history]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2024-12-21/oldest-restaurants-kansas-city-barbecue-history</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2024-12-21/oldest-restaurants-kansas-city-barbecue-history"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T14:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some restaurants across the Kansas City metro are still running strong after more than 100 years in business, serving up delicious meals and defining the culinary landscape for generations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hannah Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark DeRosa: ‘MLB Central’ offers ‘safe space’ to ’empower’ players]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685454</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/mark-derosa-empower-players.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T14:40:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MLB Central celebrates its 10th birthday in 2025, and the MLB Network show has become must-see TV for many baseball fans. San Diego Padres radio broadcaster Sammy Levitt talked to MLB Central co-host Mark DeRosa during the Winter Meetings about the show’s success through the years. In addition to the camaraderie of DeRosa and co-hosts Read more...
The post Mark DeRosa: ‘MLB Central’ offers ‘safe space’ to ’empower’ players appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Would sluggish CFP ratings be a blessing in disguise for TNT?]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685535</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/would-sluggish-cfp-ratings-blessing-disguise-tnt.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T14:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A feast of football awaits this Saturday with a trio of College Football Playoff games to go with a marquee NFL doubleheader. Much has already been said about the circumstances surrounding the crowded schedule. College football loyalists are upset that the NFL would dare to schedule such high-octane matchups on a Saturday — a day Read more...
The post Would sluggish CFP ratings be a blessing in disguise for TNT? appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sean McDonough calls out Indiana, questions CFP’s Big Ten bias]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685688</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/sean-mcdonough-indiana-big-ten-bias.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T13:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sean McDonough wasn’t having it. The veteran announcer, who, alongside Greg McElroy, ranked second in Awful Announcing’s 2024 college football announcer rankings, was in rare form Friday night as he took the Hoosiers to task. In a game that gave him and his partner little to work with, McDonough didn’t hold back, calling it exactly Read more...
The post Sean McDonough calls out Indiana, questions CFP’s Big Ten bias appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL social media team deletes Jalen Hurts shoes post after league fines QB]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685601</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/twitter/social-media-deletes-jalen-hurts-shoes-fine.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T13:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFL uniform violations usually fly under the radar in the news, but an infraction involving Jalen Hurts this week raised eyebrows for a bizarre reason. The NFL fined the Philadelphia Eagles quarterback $5,628 for a uniform and equipment violation in last Sunday’s win over the Pittsburgh Steelers. Hurts wore shoes that were mismatched shades of Read more...
The post NFL social media team deletes Jalen Hurts shoes post after league fines QB appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Schaap calls Boomer and Gunnar Esiason E:60 ‘one of the best things we’ve done’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685400</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/jeremy-schaap-boomer-gunnar-esiason-e60-best-things.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T13:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boomer and Gunnar Esiason’s work to find a medical miracle against cystic fibrosis is a story Jeremy Schaap is excited to tell on an upcoming edition of E:60. Earlier this week, ESPN announced The Boomer & Gunnar Esiason Story: Second Wind, an E:60 set to premiere at 7 p.m. ET next Tuesday on Christmas Eve. Read more...
The post Jeremy Schaap calls Boomer and Gunnar Esiason E:60 ‘one of the best things we’ve done’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matchroom’s Eddie Hearn sees Fury-Usyk 2 as chance for boxing fans to enjoy ‘real fights’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685139</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/boxing/eddie-hearn-matchroom-dazn-fury-usyk-tyson-paul.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T12:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A discussion of “boxing” can conjure quite different images at the moment. For some, that’s fights like 27-year-old YouTuber Jake Paul’s highly-publicized exhibition defeat of 58-year-old Mike Tyson in November. For others, the interest is more in actual title fights, such as the Oleksandr Usyk vs. Tyson Fury heavyweight title rematch (for the WBC, WBA, Read more...
The post Matchroom’s Eddie Hearn sees Fury-Usyk 2 as chance for boxing fans to enjoy ‘real fights’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 21, 2024 (Part II): how to watch the NFL doubleheader]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685682</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/viewing-picks/december-21-2024-part-ii-watch-nfl-doubleheader.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T12:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All Times Eastern Golf Exhibition PNC Championship, Ritz-Carlton Golf Club, Orlando, FL Day 1: Scramble — Golf Channel/Peacock, 11 a.m. Day 1: Scramble — Peacock, 12:30 p.m. Day 1: Scramble — NBC/Peacock, 4 p.m. Golf Central Pregame — Golf Channel, 10 a.m. DP World Tour Mauritius Open, Mont Choisy Le Golf, Grand Baie, Mauritius Final Read more...
The post TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 21, 2024 (Part II): how to watch the NFL doubleheader appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 21, 2024 (Part I): how to watch the CFP QF tripleheader]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685559</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/viewing-picks/december-21-2024-part-i-watch-cfp-tripleheader.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T12:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All Times Eastern Bundesliga Matchday 15 Eintracht Frankfurt vs. 1. FSV Mainz 05 — ESPN+, 9:20 a.m. Holstein Kiel vs. FC Augsburg — ESPN+, 9:20 a.m. SV Werder Bremen vs. 1. FC Union Berlin — ESPN+, 9:20 a.m. TSG Hoffenheim vs. Borussia Mönchengladbach — ESPN+, 9:20 a.m. VfB Stuttgart vs. FC St. Pauli — ESPN+, Read more...
The post TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 21, 2024 (Part I): how to watch the CFP QF tripleheader appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Best Free and Open Source GUI Tools for System Resources Monitoring in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139904</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-gui-tools-system-resources-monitoring/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T08:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tools featured in this roundup are targeted at a desktop user who wants to monitor resources being used on their machine.
The post 6 Best Free and Open Source GUI Tools for System Resources Monitoring in Linux appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effectively Wild Episode 2260: What We Might Remember About 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453378</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/effectively-wild-episode-2260-what-we-might-remember-about-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T06:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Lindbergh, Meg Rowley, and Pebble Hunting’s Sam Miller banter about Michael Lorenzen embracing an Effectively Wild hypothetical, Ben and Sam’s past predictions about baseball in the 2020s, and Paul Skenes and the ERA title, then discuss what will be remembered about baseball in 2024 (plus a postscript). Audio intro: Daniel Leckie, “Effectively Wild Theme” Audio outro: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Lindbergh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curt Cignetti boasts Indiana beats ‘s***’ out of Top 25 teams, then punts game away]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685621</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/curt-cignetti-boasts-hoosiers-notre-dame-punt-conservative.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T04:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indiana head coach Curt Cignetti baffled fans and even ESPN announcers Friday night with a conservative game plan as Notre Dame defeated the Hoosiers, 27-17, in the College Football Playoff. Complicating matters, that game strategy stood in sharp contrast to Cignetti’s pregame boasts on College GameDay, when he said he and the Hoosiers “beat the Read more...
The post Curt Cignetti boasts Indiana beats ‘s***’ out of Top 25 teams, then punts game away appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coach whose team lost to Kentucky at home shades Indiana’s CFP inclusion]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685651</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/lane-kiffin-ole-miss-lost-kentucky-indianas-inclusion-cfp.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T04:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The unfortunate thing about the Indiana Hoosiers’ loss to the Notre Dame Fighting Irish in the College Football Playoff on Friday night is that it opened the door for every angle critics want to take about their inclusion. If you wanted to argue Indiana didn’t deserve to be included in the CFP despite finishing 11-1, Read more...
The post Coach whose team lost to Kentucky at home shades Indiana’s CFP inclusion appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Keeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Thrill Was Never There]]></title>
        <id>https://tedium.co/2024/12/20/punk-rock-mba-youtube-quitting/</id>
        <link href="https://feed.tedium.co/link/15204/16925582/punk-rock-mba-youtube-quitting"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T03:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Takeaways from a punk-rock creator who says he doesn’t like punk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ernie Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local holiday music drops for when you need to rock around the Xmas tree]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865956</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/local-holiday-music-drops-for-when-you-need-to-rock-around-the-xmas-tree/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T03:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As demonstrated from coverage in years past, we’re big fans of Christmas music here at The Pitch, and love nothing more than to see that some local musicians have tried their hand at holiday fare. Here’s a selection of this year’s releases, with moods to suit every taste. Mark Murtha’s Christmas Party in Kansas City In addition to his work with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN’s new CFP scorebug heaped with praise, except when paired with BottomLine]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685615</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/scorebug-college-football-playoff-bottom-line.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T03:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s hard to explain to a non-sports fan just how much people love to analyze and discuss scorebugs. But trust us, we’re well aware. So we were not surprised to see ample discussion about ESPN’s new College Football Playoff scorebug, which debuted Friday night during the Notre Dame-Indiana game. ESPN debuts a new scorebug and Read more...
The post ESPN’s new CFP scorebug heaped with praise, except when paired with BottomLine appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Keeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Hanson apologizes for using commercial-free catchphrase during NFL RedZone with ads]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685606</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/scott-hanson-apologizes-commercial-free-catchphrase-redzone.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T03:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many NFL fans, their game-viewing experience hasn’t truly started until NFL RedZone host Scott Hanson welcomes them with a promise of “seven hours of commercial-free football.” This past Sunday, that promise was broken when RedZone viewers were treated to multiple commercials throughout the day. An NFL Media spokesperson later confirmed that RedZone’s most recent Read more...
The post Scott Hanson apologizes for using commercial-free catchphrase during NFL RedZone with ads appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Keeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nick Saban has perfect response for Shane Gillis’ ‘cheating’ joke]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685550</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/college-gameday-shane-gillis-nick-saban-paying-players-alabama.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T02:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comedian Shane Gillis appeared as the celebrity guest picker on College GameDay Friday night, but one of his jokes might have gotten under the skin of analyst Nick Saban. The CGD crew set up in South Bend ahead of the Notre Dame-Indiana game, and Gillis, a big Fighting Irish fan, told Pat McAfee that the team Read more...
The post Nick Saban has perfect response for Shane Gillis’ ‘cheating’ joke appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nick Saban: Angry Ohio State fans ‘need to quit all this negative bull****’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685519</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/nick-saban-college-gameday-ohio-state-angry-negative.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T02:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Ohio State fans are down on Ryan Day heading into the College Football Playoff, but the head coach found a surprising defender Friday night in Nick Saban. The former Alabama coach and now College GameDay analyst went after Ohio State fans who have vented their frustration with Day. While the Buckeyes are in the Read more...
The post Nick Saban: Angry Ohio State fans ‘need to quit all this negative bull****’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fox airing Bill Belichick-Madden Cruiser road trip special before Super Bowl]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685429</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/bill-belichick-madden-cruiser-road-trip.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T01:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fox will air a one-hour special, The Madden Cruiser: A Bayou Adventure with Bill Belichick, ahead of its Super Bowl LIX pregame show, and that title alone should be enough to capture the attention of many sports fans. The legendary coach will ride in the iconic RV made famous by broadcaster John Madden, traveling through Read more...
The post Fox airing Bill Belichick-Madden Cruiser road trip special before Super Bowl appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arthur Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astros Get Early Christian-mas Present]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453360</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/astros-get-early-christian-mas-present/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T01:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This nerd favorite fills a massive need in Houston.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Baumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nick Saban, who left LSU before its bowl game, says players shouldn’t be allowed to leave before bowl games]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685523</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/nick-saban-players-shouldnt-be-allowed-leave-before-bowl-games.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T01:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[College football has always had something of a Wild West quality to it. Conferences and schools have been tweaking the rules in their favor since the sports began. The bowl system makes no logical sense when you stop and think about it with 2024 eyes. We’ve lost count of how many times a school promised Read more...
The post Nick Saban, who left LSU before its bowl game, says players shouldn’t be allowed to leave before bowl games appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Keeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirby Smart mixing up Indiana with ‘Purdue’ was a tough scene]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685426</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/kirby-smart-indiana-purdue-mix-up.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T00:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Indiana manages to beat Notre Dame and Georgia, perhaps we’ll look back at Kirby Smart’s College GameDay appearance as the turning point. Playing with house money, the Hoosiers enter Friday’s matchup in South Bend as clear underdogs. But anything feels possible with the expanded College Football Playoff in full swing. Since Friday’s game marks Read more...
The post Kirby Smart mixing up Indiana with ‘Purdue’ was a tough scene appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Desmond Howard: Ohio State brass put ‘too much pressure on’ Ryan Day to win]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685462</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/desmond-howard-ohio-state-ryan-day.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T00:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that Michigan has beaten Ohio State for a fourth consecutive season, Desmond Howard has finally wrapped up his victory laps. The former Heisman winner turned College GameDay analyst, however, now seems to feel a twinge of sympathy for Ryan Day. And during Friday’s GameDay broadcast from South Bend, Howard took up a collection for Read more...
The post Desmond Howard: Ohio State brass put ‘too much pressure on’ Ryan Day to win appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN’s Seth Greenberg takes up for Doug Gottlieb amid criticism: ‘Coaching isn’t easy’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685391</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-basketball/seth-greenberg-doug-gottlieb-criticism.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T23:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Gottlieb doesn’t exactly have a lot of allies in the media right now. The head men’s basketball coach at the University of Wisconsin–Green Bay is getting humbled — in more ways than one — to say the least. After engaging in a war of words with Adam Schefter, who implored Gottlieb to spend less Read more...
The post ESPN’s Seth Greenberg takes up for Doug Gottlieb amid criticism: ‘Coaching isn’t easy’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Al Michaels reflects on broadcasting future beyond 2025: ‘As long as I have the passion, I’ll continue’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685384</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/amazon/al-michaels-broadcasting-future-passion-continue.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T23:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Al Michaels has already committed to returning as the voice of Amazon Prime Video’s Thursday Night Football in 2025. But what about after that? That question came up Friday during an appearance on The Dan Patrick Show, where Patrick likened the 80-year-old Michaels to a legendary head coach like Joe Paterno or Bill Belichick and Read more...
The post Al Michaels reflects on broadcasting future beyond 2025: ‘As long as I have the passion, I’ll continue’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Job Posting: MLB Draft League / Appalachian League – Data Coordinator]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?post_type=instagraphs&amp;p=453367</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/instagraphs/job-posting-mlb-draft-league-appalachian-league-data-coordinator/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T22:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MLB Draft League is hiring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Appelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cris Collinsworth sheds light on why Buccaneers-Cowboys isn’t flexed out of primetime]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685360</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/cris-collinsworth-buccaneers-cowboys-flex-primetime.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T22:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you were asking yourself why the NFL didn’t flex the Dallas Cowboys out of Sunday Night Football, you might want to ask yourself that again. For better or worse, ‘America’s Team’ gets ratings — and Cris Collinsworth wasn’t kidding when he said NBC would air 17 Dallas Cowboys games if it could. The network Read more...
The post Cris Collinsworth sheds light on why Buccaneers-Cowboys isn’t flexed out of primetime appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals sign RHP Fernandez to Minor League Contract]]></title>
        <id>https://farmtofountains.com/?p=6597</id>
        <link href="https://farmtofountains.com/royals-sign-rhp-fernandez-to-minor-league-contract/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=royals-sign-rhp-fernandez-to-minor-league-contract"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T22:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kansas City Royals have added their second minor league free agent of the week. First, it was Taylor Clarke, followed by RHP Junior Fernandez on Friday. Fernandez, 27, started his professional career in the St. Louis Cardinals organization. He was signed as an international free agent before the 2014 season and went on to […]
The post Royals sign RHP Fernandez to Minor League Contract appeared first on Farm to Fountains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Farr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix Women’s World Cup deal keeps streaming dominant for U.S. soccer fans]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685285</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/soccer/netflix-fifa-womens-world-cup-streaming-soccer-american-fans.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T22:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Netflix shocked American soccer fans when they closed a busy 2024 of sports rights acquisitions by buying rights to the 2027 and 2031 FIFA women’s world cups. Unlike other sports streaming deals that offer global exclusivity, Netflix will now carry the event, which has been dominated by the U.S. women’s national team most Read more...
The post Netflix Women’s World Cup deal keeps streaming dominant for U.S. soccer fans appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Pederson struggles to find answers to Mac Jones question]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685333</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/doug-pederson-mac-jones-question.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T21:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s been no greater rivalry in the NFL this year than Doug Pederson and press conferences. When he’s not criticizing his own players or members of the media, Pederson is finding ways to dance around questions being asked. Like the latter of the example, in which he refused to explain a play to reporters, claiming Read more...
The post Doug Pederson struggles to find answers to Mac Jones question appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Herbstreit apologizes to Tennessee fans after quote taken out of context]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685282</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/kirk-herbestreit-tennessee-fans-viral-quote.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T21:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anytime Kirk Herbstreit says something that can even slightly be perceived as a jab at a college football fanbase, he immediately finds himself under the microscope. Florida State fans’ longstanding grievances with the “Mayor of College Football” are well-documented, and Herbstreit is no stranger to criticism. But, in this instance, he has a legitimate gripe Read more...
The post Kirk Herbstreit apologizes to Tennessee fans after quote taken out of context appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cam Newton scolds Stephen A. Smith over Lamar Jackson: ‘Watch what you say’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685264</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/cam-newton-stephen-a-smith-lamar-jackson.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T20:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cam Newton is accusing Stephen A. Smith of holding Lamar Jackson to a different standard than he holds Josh Allen. Friday morning on First Take, Smith, Newton and Canty were previewing this week’s Baltimore Ravens-Pittsburgh Steelers matchup by assessing whether a win would be a bigger statement for Jackson or Russell Wilson. According to Smith, Read more...
The post Cam Newton scolds Stephen A. Smith over Lamar Jackson: ‘Watch what you say’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Draymond Green goes statless in loss to Memphis, whose head coach he called ‘softie’ on his podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685262</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/draymond-green-memphis-grizzlies-statless-loss-taylor-jenkins-softie.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T20:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In mid-November after a loss to the Memphis Grizzlies, Draymond Green took to his podcast to called the opposing head coach a “softie” who was teaching his team bad habits by complaining to the media about foul calls in defeat. “You got janky Taylor Jenkins, who’s a softie,” Green said at the time. “Guess what, Read more...
The post Draymond Green goes statless in loss to Memphis, whose head coach he called ‘softie’ on his podcast appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Howard Eskin announces abrupt exit from WIP after 38 years]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685346</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/radio/howard-eskin-announces-exit-wip.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T20:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After nearly four decades with Philadelphia’s SportsRadio WIP, Howard Eskin announced he is parting ways with the station. Eskin made the announcement Friday afternoon, where the 73-year-old sports personality made it clear his departure from WIP should not be considered a retirement. After 38 years I am moving on from Sportsradio WIP where I launched Read more...
The post Howard Eskin announces abrupt exit from WIP after 38 years appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion: Inspecting Kansas and Missouri power players at the heart of the far-right’s porn censorship bid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865845</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/opinion-kansas-missouri-officials-at-the-heart-of-the-far-rights-porn-censorship-bid/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T20:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abode Images It’s no secret that I have many bones to pick with our state’s elected officials. I told the lot of them in a previous column for The Pitch to go fuck themselves for instilling a “MAGA virus” and far-right Christian nationalism throughout Missouri. This time around, there is just more evidence to share that several leaders in Missouri...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael McGrady Jr.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg McElroy uses ‘Mean Girls’ reference to describe Texas quarterback situation]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685267</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/greg-mcelroy-mean-girls-reference.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T19:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don’t know whether Greg McElroy wears pink on Wednesdays. But we do know how he feels about Texas’ current quarterback situation. Ahead of the Longhorns’ first-round matchup against Clemson in the College Football Playoff, McElroy — who will be on the call for the game — appeared on ESPN’s Get Up. And during the Read more...
The post Greg McElroy uses ‘Mean Girls’ reference to describe Texas quarterback situation appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix Reloaded: December 20, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453233</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/matrix-reloaded-december-20-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T19:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was far less hectic than the Winter Meetings last week, but there are still plenty of Matrix updates to go over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Becker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cubs beat writer defends Russell Martin Hall of Fame vote]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685226</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/cubs-beat-writer-defends-russell-martin-vote.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T19:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russell Martin had a good — even great — Major League Baseball career. Not many, however, would call it Hall of Fame worthy. But as it turns out, there is at least one exception when it comes to Martin’s Cooperstown candidacy. Taking to X on Thursday, Chicago Tribune Cubs beat writer Meghan Montemurro shared her Read more...
The post Cubs beat writer defends Russell Martin Hall of Fame vote appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RosterResource Chat – 12/20/24]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453351</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/rosterresource-chat-12-20-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T18:42:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Martinez and Jon Becker answer questions related to projected rosters and playing time, team needs, payroll, free agency, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Martinez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rival exec accuses NFL of being ‘slanted’ towards Amazon, Thursday Night Football]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685220</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/rival-exec-accuses-nfl-of-being-slanted-towards-amazon-thursday-night-football.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T18:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t long ago that famed sportscaster Al Michaels was openly making fun of his own Thursday Night Football schedule on Amazon Prime Video and the number of stinkers that he and Kirk Herbstreit had to call. My how things have changed. The NFL can giveth and taketh away when it comes to schedules and Read more...
The post Rival exec accuses NFL of being ‘slanted’ towards Amazon, Thursday Night Football appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing Gets Jim Harbaugh’s Motor Running Like An Obscure Rule]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176965</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jim-harbaugh-cameron-dicker-fair-catch-kick"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T18:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Harbaugh has this look about him that screams dotty uncle—the blinky eyes behind the old-man glasses, the slightly slack jaw, the refusal to employ the newfangled play-sheet-and-face-shield look. He's perfectly cast for a man who thinks Lawrence Welk is the cutting edge.
Thus, it was right and proper that he be the one to return the fair catch kick to our notice by stealing a last-second three-banger right before halftime of last night's Amazonapalooza in which Harbaugh's Los Angeles Chargers defeated the almost as old but not nearly so physically arresting Sean Payton and the Denver Broncos. An arcane enclave of the rulebook which was successfully employed as recently as 1976, when Harbaugh was spiritually already in his mid-40s, the fair catch kick can be employed only on a fair catch as time expires, or a penalty on a fair catch, which the Broncos' Tremon Smith gifted the Chargers on a punt that Derius Davis tried to collect with no time left on the clock. The 15-yard penalty took the ball from the Charger 38 to the Bronco 47 and offered an untimed play to provide the punishment for the penalty that would otherwise go unpunished—why, you could hear the oldey-timey gears in a million old coaches' heads at the possibilities. “It’s my favorite rule in football,” Harbaugh said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timothée Chalamet wants to play TNT’s Ernie Johnson in a biopic]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685136</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/pop-culture/timothee-chalamet-play-ernie-johnson-biopic.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T18:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By this point, it’s become well-established that Timothée Chalamet knows ball. But while Chalamet previously showcased his sports bona fides while serving as the guest picker on College GameDay and by waxing poetic about MLS stars, the depths of his sports fandom are still being revealed. That includes an apparent affinity for Inside the NBA‘s Read more...
The post Timothée Chalamet wants to play TNT’s Ernie Johnson in a biopic appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Babygirl’ Wants To Know Your Fantasy]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176871</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/babygirl-wants-to-know-your-fantasy"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Babygirl, a movie written and directed by Dutch filmmaker Halina Reijn and starring Nicole Kidman and Harris Dickinson, is about facades. It's also about sex, but less about sex itself and more about what sex says about a person, and the ways we suppress our sexual appetites in order for it to say nothing about us at all. Babygirl, Reijn's second English-language film after 2022's Bodies Bodies Bodies, taps into a conservative cultural moment that is firmly anti-sex while still being in sex's thrall. It is the subject everyone wants to talk about but no one wants to see, or seemingly even have.
The movie follows tech CEO Romy Mathis (Kidman), an unabashed, all-caps GIRLBOSS who nominally "has it all": a powerful job, a big office, an eager assistant who looks up to her, a seemingly well-adjusted family that includes two daughters and a hot theater director for a husband (Antonio Banderas). But there is a restless beast inside of Romy, and vanilla sex with her husband can't appease it—so much so that Romy often finds herself having to watch dom-play porn in the bathroom afterwards in order to actually reach an orgasm. When a much younger intern for the company arrives, Samuel (Dickinson), she slowly finds herself ensnared in his web, and discovers that he is up for taming that beast. Both in spite and because of the power dynamics and the threat their affair poses to her life and career, they begin an ill-advised relationship that is hot and steamy, but most importantly effective and passionate. Romy finds her sexual needs met for the first time, which, in this movie, is as important as the tension or thriller aspects at play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even ‘Jeopardy!’ is pilling on the Jets’ misery]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685157</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/final-jeopardy-jets-super-bowl.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There aren’t many teams in professional sports that have had a more disappointing 2024 than the New York Jets. Ok, except maybe the Chicago Bears. And even the beloved game show Jeopardy! is taking stock of the franchise’s woes. Sports categories and clues on Jeopardy! can always be hit or miss. Ok, it’s mostly misses Read more...
The post Even ‘Jeopardy!’ is pilling on the Jets’ misery appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blob-Headed Fish Sets New Standard Of Fishy Blobbiness]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176910</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/blob-headed-fish-sets-new-standard-of-fishy-blobbiness"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:32:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the narrow, highly specialized field of fish with blob-like attributes, one fish has dominated for decades: One would hardly dare imagine a blobbish fish without first thinking of the blobfish. But has a new blobby fish emerged to unseat this age-old champion of blobdom?
Today, a group of researchers from the nonprofit Conservation International published a report of 27 new species discovered in Alto Mayo, a region in the Peruvian Amazon. Each of the species was a singular delight: the amphibious mouse that dwells in palm swamps called aguajales; the small, stubby chestnut-colored salamander that climbs trees. But as I scrolled through the report, one species was a clear standout—a born star, never readier to accept its place in the spotlight. This, of course, was the blob-headed fish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A guide to ESPN’s College Football Playoff studio coverage]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684958</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/college-football-playoff-studio-shows.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN has rolled out its official plans for extensive studio coverage of the College Football Playoff, and there’s a lot to parse through. The expanded 12-team playoff also means expanded coverage plans for the Worldwide Leader, who will deploy several studio teams across its various networks. ESPN’s flagship college football studio show College GameDay will Read more...
The post A guide to ESPN’s College Football Playoff studio coverage appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JAWS and the 2025 Hall of Fame Ballot: Brian McCann]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453284</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/jaws-and-the-2025-hall-of-fame-ballot-brian-mccann/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though he was a seven-time All-Star, McCann was somewhat underappreciated until the value of his elite pitch framing came to light.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Jaffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eat This Edible: Honeybee’s Queen Bee delivers a high-potency and piquant palate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865942</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/eat-this-edible-honeybees-queen-bee-delivers-a-high-potency-and-piquant-palate/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Proper Cannabis In November, Honeybee Edibles—an edible brand underneath the St. Louis-based cannabis company Proper Cannabis—released a new edible in the Missouri market. The gluten-free and vegan Queen Bee is now giving consumers an easier route to their high, compacting 100mg of THC and 100mg CBD into just a couple easy-going bites. Similar to Grön’s MEGA edible...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Ellett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More difficult days ahead for Nike as they re-invest in sports marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685133</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/sports/nike-sports-marketing-difficult-days.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T17:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elliott Hill has been the new CEO of Nike just around 60 days now, taking over for the beleaguered company whose stock is down 27 percent this year, an inverse of the broader market. After a whirlwind tour of Nike offices and meeting athlete and league endorsers, Hill outlined some of his plans on an Read more...
The post More difficult days ahead for Nike as they re-invest in sports marketing appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kaplan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Longenhagen Prospects Chat: 12/20/24]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453335</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/eric-longenhagen-prospects-chat-12-20-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T16:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Prospect Impresario is in Philadelphia for the holidays. Will he draw from the energy of his homeland and be extra salty in chat? Bring a snowball and find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Longenhagen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN’s Dan Graziano eviscerates ‘con artist’ and ‘narcissist’ Aaron Rodgers]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685205</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/dan-graziano-aaron-rodgers-unsportsmanlike-rant.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T16:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It isn’t often — if ever — that the cast of ESPN Radio’s Unsportsmanlike finds itself speechless. Only that’s exactly what happened on Friday morning, as Dan Graziano engaged in an epic rant regarding Aaron Rodgers. Graziano’s skewering of the 41-year-old quarterback came as the show discussed The Athletic’s recent report regarding the New York Read more...
The post ESPN’s Dan Graziano eviscerates ‘con artist’ and ‘narcissist’ Aaron Rodgers appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Awfulies: The best in sports radio & sports media podcasts]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684706</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/orig/2024-awfulies-best-sports-radio-media-podasts-ourand-kay-canty.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T16:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we’re celebrating the highs, lows, best, and worst of the year with The Awfulies. Started in 2022 and expanded in 2023, the Awful Announcing staff has cast its votes for who we think should take home the coveted golden microphone. Keep an eye on category and winner reveals all week long. And be sure to let Read more...
The post The 2024 Awfulies: The best in sports radio & sports media podcasts appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Keeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Is Nolan Arenado Anymore, and How Can He Be Traded?]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453266</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/who-is-nolan-arenado-anymore-and-how-can-he-be-traded/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T16:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will Arenado loosen up his no-trade list and save a mediocre joke that was 10 years in the making?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Baumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Unionizing Protect Contestants From The Reality Of Reality TV?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176872</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/could-unionizing-protect-contestants-from-the-reality-of-reality-tv"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T15:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an industry-wide first, the National Labor Relations Board argued last week that contestants participating in Netflix’s hit reality TV dating show Love Is Blind should be classified as employees. If implemented into policy—which, admittedly, seems unlikely given the fact that Donald Trump is expected to fire the current NLRB general legal counsel—the filing could not only give more on-set protection to participants of shows like Love Is Blind but potentially allow them to unionize. 
Since its oddly prescient premiere in February 2020, which saw 15 men and 15 women dating, falling in love and eventually getting engaged sight unseen, Love Is Blind has faced allegations of mistreatment and coercion. Early contestants have accused producers of plying them with alcohol while regularly denying them food and water; one contestant alleged that production pushed her to continue filming even after she told them that she was experiencing suicidal ideation and wanted to leave. Over the past four years and seven seasons, the two production companies behind Love Is Blind—Kinetic Content and Delirium TV—have faced multiple lawsuits from former contestants. One of them alleges “inhumane working conditions” while another accuses Kinetic and Delirium of negligence, false imprisonment and sexual assault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shane Gillis is ‘College GameDay’ guest picker for Notre Dame-Indiana]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685199</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/shane-gillis-college-gameday-guest-picker-notre-dame-indiana.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T15:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even though College GameDay has only one game to cover on Friday when they kick off the newly expanded 12-team playoff in South Bend, they aren’t taking a pass on inviting in a guest picker with comedian Shane Gillis joining the fun. College GameDay is pulling an ultra-rare doubleheader this weekend with the first ever Read more...
The post Shane Gillis is ‘College GameDay’ guest picker for Notre Dame-Indiana appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeLinuxCo Workstation – Manjaro spin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139890</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/delinuxco-workstation-manjaro-spin/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T15:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The goal and purpose of DeLinuxCo is to have a workstation experience right from the start. It's a spin of Manjaro.
The post DeLinuxCo Workstation – Manjaro spin appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Inside the NBA’ crew send condolences to Ernie Johnson: ‘We definitely feel his pain’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685154</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/charles-barkley-shaq-kenny-smith-inside-the-nba-condolences-ernie-johnson.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T15:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Lefkoe, Charles Barkley, Kenny Smith and Shaquille O’Neal opened Inside the NBA with somber news about Ernie Johnson and his family Thursday night. Filling in for the longtime host of Inside the NBA, Lefkoe informed the audience Johnson was absent after his sister Christine died from cancer this week at the age of 72. Read more...
The post ‘Inside the NBA’ crew send condolences to Ernie Johnson: ‘We definitely feel his pain’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Awfulies: Best & worst in sports television]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684325</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/tv/2024-awfulies-best-television-inside-nba-first-things.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T15:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we’re celebrating the highs, lows, best, and worst of the year with The Awfulies. Started in 2022 and expanded in 2023, the Awful Announcing staff has cast its votes for who we think should take home the coveted golden microphone. Keep an eye on category and winner reveals all week long. And be sure to let Read more...
The post The 2024 Awfulies: Best & worst in sports television appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod, Sam Neumann and Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2025 ZiPS Projections: Detroit Tigers]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453248</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/2025-zips-projections-detroit-tigers/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T15:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tigers right now look like a .500 team, but that makes them an AL Central contender.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Szymborski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix wins 2027, 2031 Women’s World Cup rights]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685168</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/netflix/netflix-wins-2027-2031-womens-world-cup-rights.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T14:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix is officially a player in live sports thanks to a stunning victory in winning Women’s World Cup rights for the next two tournaments in 2027 and 2031. The streamer has long been on the outside looking in at live sports while big tech competitors like Amazon, YouTube, and Apple entered into the space. But Read more...
The post Netflix wins 2027, 2031 Women’s World Cup rights appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Hater’s Guide To The Williams-Sonoma Catalog]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176334</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-2024-haters-guide-to-the-williams-sonoma-catalog"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T14:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[walks out to greet you as you pull into my circular driveway]
There you are! Oh my goodness, look at you! You look so festive! Why don't you leave your bags in the breezeway for now and come on in? And MERRY CHRISTMAS! My gosh, I can finally say it! No more "happy holidays" or any of that nonsense. Doesn't it feel great? You and I can talk like normal people again! Oh, it was AWFUL for a while, wasn’t it? We just got Andley back from Conn College and you can't say boo to that girl without her telling you that you're the worst person alive! Good luck trying that on your boss when you start your internship at Credit Suisse, young lady! You can't invest in pronouns!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chicago Cubs Top 37 Prospects]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453142</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/chicago-cubs-top-37-prospects/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T14:05:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As this system stands right now, it's a shade below average in terms of both depth and high-end impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Longenhagen and Travis Ice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caitlin Clark’s Time interview is just what the WNBA needed]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684542</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/wnba/caitlin-clark-time-interview-outspoken.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T14:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Was there a more obvious pick for Time 2024 Athlete of the Year than Caitlin Clark? Not only did she break the NCAA scoring record in her final year of college just weeks before going first overall in the WNBA Draft, but she made the WNBA All-Star Team and won the WNBA’s Rookie of the Read more...
The post Caitlin Clark’s Time interview is just what the WNBA needed appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katie Lever</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charles Barkley doesn’t believe in adults getting Christmas presents: ‘It’s for the kids’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685069</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/tnt-sports/charles-barkley-christmas-presents-for-the-kids.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T13:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charles Barkley has shared his fair share of controversial takes over the years. But perhaps none will upset and divide more people than his take shared on Thursday about Christmas. People all over the world have differing opinions about Christmas and how the day should be celebrated. Some use the day as a way to Read more...
The post Charles Barkley doesn’t believe in adults getting Christmas presents: ‘It’s for the kids’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Al Michaels says he ‘wasn’t allowed to’ talk Super Bowl XXIX spread]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685079</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/al-michaels-super-bowl-xxix-spread.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T13:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fascinating part of NFL broadcasting over the years has been the league’s relationship with gambling, and specifically the way its broadcasters are allowed (or not allowed) to discuss gambling. Betting on NFL games has long been a thing, even long before that was legal in most jurisdictions, and so have been some levels of Read more...
The post Al Michaels says he ‘wasn’t allowed to’ talk Super Bowl XXIX spread appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 20, 2024: how to watch Indiana-Notre Dame CFP QF]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684971</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/viewing-picks/december-20-2024-watch-indiana-notre-dame-cfp-qf.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T12:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All Times Eastern Bundesliga Matchday 15 Bayern München vs. Red Bull Leipzig — ESPN Deportes/ESPN+, 2:20 p.m. College Basketball Men’s HBCU Challenge HBCU Doubleheader, Mohegan Sun Arena, Mohegan Sun Resort & Casino, Uncasville, CT Norfolk State vs. Grambling State — ESPNU, 4 p.m. Delaware State vs. Alabama State — ESPNU, 6:30 p.m. Valparaiso at Western Read more...
The post TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 20, 2024: how to watch Indiana-Notre Dame CFP QF appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plasma System Monitor – monitoring tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139897</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/plasma-system-monitor-monitoring-tool/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T11:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plasma System Monitor provides an interface for monitoring system sensors, process information and other system resources.
The post Plasma System Monitor – monitoring tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awful Announcing Podcast: Jeff Marek on Sportsnet, NHL expansion, J.T. Miller]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685094</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/orig/podcast-jeff-marek-sportsnet-nhl.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T11:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week’s episode of the Awful Announcing Podcast, host Brandon Contes interviews former Sportsnet NHL host and current host of The Sheet with Jeff Marek, Jeff Marek. Brandon and Jeff discuss a wide range of topics including his dismissal from Sportsnet, which cities are prime for an NHL expansion team, his thoughts on J.T. Read more...
The post Awful Announcing Podcast: Jeff Marek on Sportsnet, NHL expansion, J.T. Miller appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Bupp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bogdan Raczynski (Interview)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/bogdan-raczynski-interview</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/bogdan-raczynski-interview"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T08:02:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Friday so we’re listening to something more upbeat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[picocolors – tiny and fast library for terminal output formatting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139887</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/picocolors-tiny-fast-library-terminal-output-formatting/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T07:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[picocolors is billed as the tiniest and the fastest library for terminal output formatting with ANSI colors.
The post picocolors – tiny and fast library for terminal output formatting appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusion Principle]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3027/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3027/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lakers’ coach JJ Redick blames critical NBA broadcasters, social media discourse for ratings slump]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685054</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/lakers-jj-redick-broadcaster-criticism-ratings.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T04:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s been a lot of discussion out there around the NBA’s ratings this year. On Thursday, former ESPN analyst and podcaster and current Los Angeles Lakers head coach JJ Redick waded in. And he attributed some of the decline to criticism of the on-court product from broadcasters, as The Athletic’s Sam Amick shared on Bluesky: Read more...
The post Lakers’ coach JJ Redick blames critical NBA broadcasters, social media discourse for ratings slump appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Gottlieb blasts ESPN for taking ‘Nobody U’ comment out of context]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685013</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/radio/doug-gottlieb-blasts-espn-out-of-context-nobody-u-comment.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T04:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CBS Sports Radio host and Green Bay Phoenix men’s basketball coach Doug Gottlieb has found himself at the center of controversy in recent days on a number of different fronts. On Thursday, Gottlieb not only defended himself but also took aim at his many critics, including ESPN. On Monday, Gottlieb responded to a report from Read more...
The post Doug Gottlieb blasts ESPN for taking ‘Nobody U’ comment out of context appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buster Olney seemingly slams Cubs for handling of Sammy Sosa]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684850</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/sammy-sosa-cubs-apology-buster-olney.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T03:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thursday marked a significant repair in the relationship between the Chicago Cubs and Sammy Sosa. ESPN MLB insider Buster Olney does not seem pleased with how things happened. Sosa last played with the Cubs in 2004 and retired following the 2007 season. While his career numbers are undeniably worthy, Sosa—like other stars of his era Read more...
The post Buster Olney seemingly slams Cubs for handling of Sammy Sosa appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former NBA player John Amaechi goes off on Stephen A. Smith for ‘creepy’ viral video about women in Miami]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=685000</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/meadowlark/john-amaechi-stephen-a-smith-creepy-viral-video.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T03:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN’s Stephen A. Smith has always been unapologetically himself in front of a camera. Even when it perhaps toes the line of inappropriate, which Smith’s recent comments did in the eyes of former NBA player John Amaechi earlier this week. On Tuesday’s edition of The Stephen A. Smith Show, Smith answered a question from a Read more...
The post Former NBA player John Amaechi goes off on Stephen A. Smith for ‘creepy’ viral video about women in Miami appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Kornheiser says CFP and NFL scheduling competing games is ‘football on football crime’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684937</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/tony-kornheiser-cfp-competing-games-football-on-football-crime.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T02:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFL and college football typically go to great lengths not to program against each other. Save for some low-wattage Thursday night college football games on ESPN competing with Thursday Night Football on Amazon, football fans are generally able to watch every important game—college or pro—without worrying about missing another. That can all be thrown Read more...
The post Tony Kornheiser says CFP and NFL scheduling competing games is ‘football on football crime’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Kornheiser says CFP and NFL scheduling competing games is ‘football on football crime’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684937</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/tony-kornheiser-cfp-nfl-competing-games-football-on-football-crime.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T02:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFL and college football typically go to great lengths not to program against each other. Save for some low-wattage Thursday night college football games on ESPN competing with Thursday Night Football on Amazon, football fans are generally able to watch every important game—college or pro—without worrying about missing another. That can all be thrown Read more...
The post Tony Kornheiser says CFP and NFL scheduling competing games is ‘football on football crime’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dan Marino on potential return to broadcasting: ‘I think I could if I wanted to’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684956</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/dan-marino-potential-return-broadcasting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T02:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hall of Fame quarterback Dan Marino last served as an NFL studio analyst over a decade ago. But in a recent interview, he shared that he is still very capable of serving in his old role again if he decides to do so in the future. Marino, of course, served as a studio analyst on Read more...
The post Dan Marino on potential return to broadcasting: ‘I think I could if I wanted to’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your 2024 NFL Week 16 announcing schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684932</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/schedules/nfl-week-16-announcing-schedule.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T01:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a look at the announcing assignments for Week 16 of the NFL season, including a Saturday doubleheader. That includes some discussion of a featured game or games in each slot based on broadcasters, matchups, or both. All times are Eastern. Thursday, Dec. 19 Featured/only game: Denver at LA Chargers Prime Video 8:15 p.m. Al Read more...
The post Your 2024 NFL Week 16 announcing schedule appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Williams returning to mornings on Golf Channel]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684830</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/golf/gary-williams-returning-mornings-golf-channel-5-clubs.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T01:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Golf Channel is adding some new morning programming to its lineup which will feature the return of a familiar face. Longtime Golf Channel broadcaster Gary Williams will return to the network’s morning lineup as part of a new one-hour morning show titled 5 Clubs on Golf Channel that will debut Monday, Jan. 6th. Williams helped Read more...
The post Gary Williams returning to mornings on Golf Channel appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Johnson blames NBA ratings decline on stars yukking it up: ‘They don’t hate each other’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684839</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/magic-johnson-blames-ratings-decline-stars.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T00:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With NBA TV ratings in decline, Magic Johnson believes players from opposing teams need to get back to hating each other. Everybody has a theory on why NBA viewership is down. Commissioner Adam Silver blames the demise of cable television, Shaquille O’Neal faults the three-point shot, Mike Francesa points to load management, Joe Mazzulla blames Read more...
The post Magic Johnson blames NBA ratings decline on stars yukking it up: ‘They don’t hate each other’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Marchand and John Ourand both predict Tom Brady will return for second season as Fox NFL analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684872</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/andrew-marchand-john-ourand-tom-brady-return-second-season-analyst.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T00:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One and done for Tom Brady at Fox? Not so fast, say sports media insiders Andrew Marchand and John Ourand. In their latest conversation on the Marchand Sports Media podcast, both put a stake in the ground predicting that the new lead NFL on Fox game analyst will return for the second season of his record 10-year, Read more...
The post Andrew Marchand and John Ourand both predict Tom Brady will return for second season as Fox NFL analyst appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Finebaum: My ‘legacy’ will be showing college football elites ‘where the country really is’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684841</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/paul-finebaum-show-legend-representation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-20T00:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN college football analyst and radio host Paul Finebaum is synonymous with his callers. None more so than an Alabama superfan known as “Legend.” In a new episode of the Pablo Torre Finds Out podcast heading into the College Football Playoff, Finebaum appeared to discuss his connection to those callers and the impact of his radio Read more...
The post Paul Finebaum: My ‘legacy’ will be showing college football elites ‘where the country really is’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Kelce rips anti-flag planting legislation: ‘I don’t like it. I’m not gonna lie’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684769</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/travis-jason-kelce-ohio-flag-planting-bill.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T23:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An anti-flag planting bill proposed by Ohio state Rep. Josh Williams has earned two more prominent critics — Jason and Travis Kelce. After Michigan’s upset win over Ohio State in November, some of the Wolverines attempted to plant a Michigan flag at midfield at Ohio Stadium — which triggered a fight with some of the Read more...
The post Jason Kelce rips anti-flag planting legislation: ‘I don’t like it. I’m not gonna lie’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NBA Cup Final viewership down big versus Lakers’ win last year]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684862</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/cup-final-viewership-down-big.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T23:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Viewership for the second ever NBA Cup championship game declined significantly compared to last year’s debut, but still proved to be a substantial upgrade versus a normal regular season game. Tuesday’s NBA Cup Final between the Milwaukee Bucks and Oklahoma City Thunder averaged 2.99 million viewers on ABC, per Jon Lewis of Sports Media Watch. Read more...
The post NBA Cup Final viewership down big versus Lakers’ win last year appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new Kansas City program steers residents to mental health or drug care rather than custody]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865975</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/a-new-kansas-city-program-steers-residents-to-mental-health-or-drug-care-rather-than-custody/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T23:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Riders wait for the Prospect Max bus at the 31st Street stop, in the first corridor to be included in the REACH program. (Mili Mansaray/The Beacon) You see someone in the midst of a mental breakdown, or high on drugs. Call 911 and they may get arrested. Things could get worse from there. They might lose their job, their apartment....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mili Mansaray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeff Marek on dismissal from Sportsnet: ‘It was bizarre’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684796</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nhl/jeff-marek-dismissal-sportsnet-bizarre.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T23:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five months after an abrupt dismissal from Sportsnet following 13 years with the network, Jeff Marek is excited for the next chapter of his career. One of the most well-known NHL analysts, Marek recently partnered with The Nation Network and the Daily Faceoff to launch his new show, The Sheet. In July, Marek was let Read more...
The post Jeff Marek on dismissal from Sportsnet: ‘It was bizarre’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Awful Announcing NFL/CFB rules analyst rankings]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684754</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/2024-football-rules-analyst-rankings.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T22:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The votes are in for the top broadcast football rules analysts. We asked Awful Announcing readers to grade nine rules analysts working on NCAA and NFL football broadcasts across a wide selection of networks, and received responses from more than 400 voters, similar to what we received for our scorebug rankings earlier this year. As Read more...
The post The 2024 Awful Announcing NFL/CFB rules analyst rankings appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13 Best Free and Open Source Tools for Novelists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=486</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/novelists/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T22:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing is one of the essential skills in modern society.
The post 13 Best Free and Open Source Tools for Novelists appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Mike Tomlin interview nearly gave Erin Andrews a ‘panic attack’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684751</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/erin-andrews-mike-tomlin-panic-attack.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T22:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Tomlin feels like an easy guy to root for, especially for Erin Andrews. Sure, he can come across as abrasive, like he did after the Pittsburgh Steelers’ 27-13 loss to the Philadelphia Eagles in Week 15. Tomlin might’ve told an official to “Get the f*ck” out of his face and snapped at a reporter Read more...
The post Why Mike Tomlin interview nearly gave Erin Andrews a ‘panic attack’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to popular CLI tools: tree]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=105876</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alternatives-popular-cli-tools-tree/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T22:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article spotlights alternative tools to tree, a utility that lists the contents of directories in a tree-like format.
The post Alternatives to popular CLI tools: tree appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN reveals new graphics package for College Football Playoff]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684808</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/reveals-new-graphics-package-college-football-playoff.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T22:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new playoff format means a new graphics package for ESPN. The Worldwide Leader will debut a brand new set of graphics on Friday when the Indiana Hoosiers visit South Bend to take on the Notre Dame Fighting Irish in the first ever game of the expanded College Football Playoff. To celebrate, ESPN dropped a Read more...
The post ESPN reveals new graphics package for College Football Playoff appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feeling Like Ozymandias, With Susie Banikarim]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176553</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/feeling-like-ozymandias-with-susie-banikarim"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T21:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no reason for a normal person to know who Carlos Watson is. This is why I have made it my business to reach as many members of the normal-person community with the Good News about the disgraced and deliriously scammy founder and figurehead of Ozy Media, who was sentenced to nearly 10 years in prison for various oafish and common financial crimes earlier this week. I understand that my personal grievances with, say, Vice Media founder Shane Smith are my own, and my own problem; I understand, too, that there is no reason for really anyone to know who Jim Spanfeller is, although I have not always honored that. I get all this.
But it is my belief that Watson's baroquely thirsty and fraudulent public arc, while powered by the specific scamminess and scuzz of online media during the previous decade, is wild and weird enough to resonate even with people lucky enough to have avoided working in that field during that time. We put that to the test this week by having our buddy and former GMG executive editor Susie Banikarim on to talk about her new podcast about Watson's rise and fall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kylie Kelce doesn’t want to ‘feed any conflict’ after dethroning Joe Rogan atop podcast charts]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684757</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/kylie-kelce-joe-rogan-podcast-charts.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T21:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kylie Kelce is the latest member of her family to launch a hit podcast, and it took her no time at all to find an audience. As the wife of Philadelphia Eagles legend turned ESPN star Jason Kelce, she was already in the spotlight before she debuted Not Gonna Lie in partnership with Wave Sports + Read more...
The post Kylie Kelce doesn’t want to ‘feed any conflict’ after dethroning Joe Rogan atop podcast charts appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Tirico advocates for NFL schedule flexibility, calling for Premier League-inspired approach]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684688</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/podcasts/mike-tirico-nfl-schedule-premier-league.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T21:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether through New Year’s resolutions or a fresh perspective on long-standing traditions, everyone is searching for change. It’s that time of the year. We already saw Joel Klatt voice that Army-Navy should be moved to Week 0. And that idea seemed better in his head than in actuality. Meanwhile, Mike Tirico has his own proposal Read more...
The post Mike Tirico advocates for NFL schedule flexibility, calling for Premier League-inspired approach appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: New York Jets Plagued By Woody Johnson’s Meddlesome Teen Sons]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176739</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/report-new-york-jets-plagued-by-woody-johnsons-meddlesome-teen-sons"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T20:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a beloved media tradition: when a dysfunctional team's dysfunctional season reaches its dysfunctional end, reporters covering that team are permitted to write one big notebook-dumping explainer/eulogy. With a few outré exceptions, no one cares enough about bad teams to justify two such stories; with a few outré exceptions, no team is quite dysfunctional enough to fill out more than one. If you are a Tennessee Titans fan, to take one example, this is more or less the one big thing you have left to look forward to this season. You already know the team is lousy, inert, soggy and sodden and miserable; in a few weeks, once everyone goes home, you will find out whether that has anything to do with Tony Pollard's insistence upon letting his pet puma wander around the locker room or some such thing. That is how it usually works.
But the New York Jets are different. Everyone always and already knows about the pumas wandering around the locker room. Every week their ulcerous and increasingly haggard quarterback joins Pat McAfee's ESPN show via Zoom, seemingly from the Black Lodge, and starts Speaking Real Words about the germ theory of disease or whatever else is troubling him; this week, Aaron Rodgers testily demanded that critics of his (terrible!) recent play disclose their vaccination status, either as an indication of their bias or just as proof that they lack the courage that permitted Rodgers to self-immunize against infectious disease, possibly by eating hundreds of small, smooth rocks. This is just how the Jets are, and more or less how they have been since the pharmaceutical heir Woody Johnson bought the team 25 years ago. That they have the longest streak in American pro sports without a playoff appearance is not surprising given all that, but also feels somehow incidental to the organization's broader project, which under Johnson's blithely buttheaded stewardship has mostly been to generate news about people getting fired.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Best Free GUI Tools to Find and Delete Duplicate Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=56056</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-tools-find-delete-duplicate-files/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T20:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We feature free and open source software that lets you find and remove the duplicate files.
The post 6 Best Free GUI Tools to Find and Delete Duplicate Files appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kirk Herbstreit addresses why son committed to Michigan and reaction from Ohio State fans]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684721</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/kirk-chase-herbstreit-ohio-state-michigan.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T20:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Dan Katz (Barstool Big Cat) pointed out, Kirk Herbstreit’s son, Chase, committing to the University of Michigan — his father’s alma mater’s fiercest rival — stirred up some serious waves. And rightfully so. For the first time publicly, Kirk addressed his son’s decision to commit to the University of Michigan, joining $10 million man Read more...
The post Kirk Herbstreit addresses why son committed to Michigan and reaction from Ohio State fans appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen A. Smith cringes at Dan Orlovsky’s mayonnaise admission]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684718</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/food/stephen-a-smith-cringes-dan-orlovsky-mayonnaise-admission.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T20:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN should be used to Dan Orlovsky dropping bad food takes by now, but this latest one really seemed to irk Stephen A. Smith. There are mayonnaise eaters and mayonnaise lovers. Consider Orlovsky among the latter. Because according to the former NFL quarterback, mayonnaise and more mayonnaise is all you need to make a great Read more...
The post Stephen A. Smith cringes at Dan Orlovsky’s mayonnaise admission appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eat This Now: Cookies at Sweet Kiss Brigadeiro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865750</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/eat-this-now-cookies-at-sweet-kiss-brigadeiro/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T20:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cookie at Sweet Kiss Brigadeiro // Photo by Sarah Sipple These cookies are less like a sweet kiss and more like a giant smooch! Sweet Kiss Brigadeiro bakes large, filled cookies in classic and creative flavors.  But what is a brigadeiro?   The Brazilian sweet is a truffle, known as brigadeiro. These bite-sized balls come in a variety of flavors including...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eat This Now: Cookies at Sweet Kiss Brigadeiro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865750</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/eat-this-now-cookies-at-sweet-kiss-brigadeiro/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T20:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cookie at Sweet Kiss Brigadeiro // Photo by Sarah Sipple These cookies are less like a sweet kiss and more like a giant smooch! Sweet Kiss Brigadeiro bakes large, filled cookies in classic and creative flavors.  But what is a brigadeiro?   The Brazilian sweet is a truffle, known as brigadeiro. These bite-sized balls come in a variety of flavors including...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Francesa scoffs at Adam Silver blaming NBA ratings problem on cable]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684689</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/mike-francesa-adam-silver-rating.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T19:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NBA has a ratings problem and Mike Francesa is convinced commissioner Adam Silver has no clue what it is. Silver addressed the league’s ratings dip this week while speaking to reporters ahead of the NBA Cup championship game. Reluctant to blame the product, Silver instead pointed to the trend of declining cable viewership. But Read more...
The post Mike Francesa scoffs at Adam Silver blaming NBA ratings problem on cable appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gtree – generate trees and directories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139766</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gtree-generate-trees-directories/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T19:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[gtree is a CLI-based utility which uses Markdown to generate directory trees and directories itself, and also verifies directories.
The post gtree – generate trees and directories appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Lawson Enters The Red Bull Second-Seat Gantlet]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176741</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/liam-lawson-enters-the-red-bull-second-seat-gantlet"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T19:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the news that everything was thinking about, Mercedes announced Thursday morning that Valtteri Bottas would be returning to the team as its reserve driver. Bottas spent the past three years as an unfortunate, i.e. racing for Alfa Romeo–turned–Kick Sauber, but up until 2021, Bottas had represented everything a championship-winning team needed in a second driver: fast enough to ensure 1-2 finishes, good enough in qualifying to occasionally beat Lewis Hamilton, not quite good enough to disrupt a clear 1-2 hierarchy. The full circle continues what has been considered one of the kinder arcs for a second driver post-eviction: freed from the pressure of one-year contracts and matching up against literally Lewis Hamilton, Bottas grew a mullet and a mustache, posted ass, and then managed to return to Mercedes with zero expectations.
If Sergio Pérez has half that, he will be fortunate. Red Bull announced yesterday that Pérez would be leaving the team after three seasons. Pérez is already missing out on the clean end-of-term-into-multi-year-contract-with-another-team sequence that Bottas got. Lest anyone forgets, Pérez's contract was initially due to expire at the end of the 2024 season, but six months ago, Red Bull Racing announced that they had extended his contract by two years. This was a baffling decision at face value, but could be explained by the disaster of Red Bull leadership, McLaren evading consideration as legitimate Constructors' Championship contender, Daniel Ricciardo still being in the second VCARB seat, and Pérez having a far worse second half of the season compared to his first—he had four podiums prior to the extension, and zero after. In the end, Red Bull had to worm its way out of an easily avoidable extension, and took a no doubt expensive route to an inevitable result; Sergio Pérez lasted for longer than expected, but he, too, fell victim to the curse of the second Red Bull seat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Woody Johnson reportedly shares links from Jets blogs with top football decision-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684638</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/woody-johnson-blogs-jets-x-factor.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T19:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, it’s well-known that Woody Johnson perhaps pays too much attention to the media. He’s not totally at fault for the New York Jets’ shortcomings. As previously outlined, the media narrative absolving now-former general manager Joe Douglas of blame misses the mark. But there’s a common denominator her, as best exemplified by the team Read more...
The post Woody Johnson reportedly shares links from Jets blogs with top football decision-makers appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Several bars and restaurants may not carry Netflix’s Christmas Day NFL games]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684616</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/netflix/several-sports-bars-wont-carry-christmas-day-games.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T18:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent surge in sporting events being exclusive to streaming services has led to many questions about the ability of bars and restaurants to carry such games. But while most establishments seem to have found ways to carry those games — albeit often at a hefty price — it doesn’t appear that will be the Read more...
The post Several bars and restaurants may not carry Netflix’s Christmas Day NFL games appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revisiting the Kirby Index]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453088</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/revisiting-the-kirby-index/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T18:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the current state of quantifying command?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Rosen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Mazzulla takes blame for declining NBA ratings: ‘I would rather watch something else’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684614</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/joe-mazzulla-blame-declining-ratings.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T18:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the NBA attempts to deal with its ratings problem, don’t expect much help from Boston Celtics head coach Joe Mazzulla. We’re not even through December yet and commissioner Adam Silver has already been asked to address the NBA’s declining TV ratings on several occasions. But now, even NBA coaches are being asked to address Read more...
The post Joe Mazzulla takes blame for declining NBA ratings: ‘I would rather watch something else’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skribisto – writing tool for Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139782</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/skribisto-writing-tool-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T17:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Skribisto project manager and rich text editor for writers in a quest of a complete, yet simple, way of writing and organizing their work.
The post Skribisto – writing tool for Linux appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I’ll Be Home For Christmas]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176720</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ill-be-home-for-christmas"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T17:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
I have not lived year-round with my parents since I was 14 years old. I went to boarding school for sophomore year (I was already a year younger than all of my classmates), and then college and professional life followed. So while I have an ample memory bank of the time before I left the nest, I have just as many memories of returning home from my travels out in the big, wide world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carmelo Anthony in talks with Amazon, NBC and ESPN for NBA analyst role]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684673</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/carmelo-anthony-emerges-media-roles.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T17:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Amazon and NBC prepare to add the NBA to its airwaves in 2025, Carmelo Anthony has emerged as a candidate for both broadcasters’ coverage plans. According to Front Office Sports’ Michael McCarthy, the 10-time All-Star is “talking to everybody” about possible studio and game analyst roles. That includes not only Amazon and NBC, which Read more...
The post Carmelo Anthony in talks with Amazon, NBC and ESPN for NBA analyst role appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: Festive foodie finds, two closures, and a moment for the olives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865931</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-festive-foodie-finds-two-closures-and-a-moment-for-the-olives/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T17:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Life in KC is pretty delicious. In fact, there is often so much going on that it can be hard to decide where to go and what to try. That’s where I come in.  I’ve curated this weekly list of events, openings, deals, and celebrations to keep you in-the-know. Cheers! Something New Bar Medici: I need...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: Festive foodie finds, two closures, and a moment for the olives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865931</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-festive-foodie-finds-two-closures-and-a-moment-for-the-olives/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T17:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Life in KC is pretty delicious. In fact, there is often so much going on that it can be hard to decide where to go and what to try. That’s where I come in.  I’ve curated this weekly list of events, openings, deals, and celebrations to keep you in-the-know. Cheers! Something New Bar Medici: I need...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pickleball leads the way in women’s sports pro salaries as sport continues growth]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684568</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/tennis/pickleball-womens-sports-pro-salaries-growth.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T17:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick question; which sports league paid female players the most on average in 2024, the year women’s sports finally broke through?  Was it the Caitlin Clark-infused WNBA? (Sorry Sheila Johnson, but like it or not Clark is the top reason for the surge in popularity.) Maybe the National Women’s Soccer League, which has seen skyrocketing Read more...
The post Pickleball leads the way in women’s sports pro salaries as sport continues growth appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kaplan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brooks Lee Embraces the Art of Hitting]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453169</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/brooks-lee-embraces-the-art-of-hitting/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T17:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The promising young Minnesota Twins infielder has learned a lot from his father, a longtime college coach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Laurila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review: Taco Bell Crispy Chicken Nuggets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.brandeating.com/2024/12/review-taco-bell-crispy-chicken-nuggets.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.brandeating.com/2024/12/review-taco-bell-crispy-chicken-nuggets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taco Bell's Crispy Chicken Nuggets feature white-meat chicken bites marinated in jalapeno buttermilk," breaded with a mix of breadcrumbs and tortilla chips, and then deep-fried.

A 10-piece order included two dipping sauces and cost me $7.49. I went with the new Bell Sauce and Hidden Valley Fire Ranch.
There was quite a bit of variance in the size of the nuggets. The smallest piece was about half the size of the largest piece:



The breading was fairly thick with an almost knobby texture to it. I could see bits of tortilla chips sporadically embedded in it and some odd dark patches on the surface. It was lightly crispy but super crunchy when a piece of chip was encountered. The chicken inside was moist and decently tender. There was a lightly seasoned flavor to the nuggets and just a hint of spicy heat. Quality-wise, it's about the same level as frozen breaded chicken bites heated in the air fryer.



The new Bell Sauce offered a sweet tomato flavor and a distinct pepper note to go with a fair amount of spices, a mild heat, and a creamy, tangy mayo base.
The Hidden Valley Fire Ranch is a mixture of Hidden Valley Ranch and Fire Sauce. It was more run-of-the-mill versus the Bell Sauce. It offered the creamier buttermilk tang and herbiness of Hidden Valley ranch with an additional hit of tang and a moderate heat from Taco Bell's Fire Sauce.



I found both sauces enjoyable but preferred the Bell Sauce as it was more complex and interesting.
At the end of the day, Taco Bell's Crispy Chicken Nuggets made for a decent but middling fast-food chicken nugget offering but with some added novelty from the new sauces.
Nutritional Info - Taco Bell Crispy Chicken Nuggets (10 pieces)
Calories - 670
Fat - 33g (Saturated Fat - 3.5g)
Sodium - 1840mg
Carbs - 20g (Sugar - 0g)
Protein - 72g
Read more at Brand Eating!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brand Eating. Your Daily Fast Food Reading.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presenting The 2024 Shams Charania Award For Excellence In Divulging Of Information Through Syntax Comprehended By Many]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176547</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/presenting-the-2024-shamsy"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T16:51:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was an eventful year for our award's namesake. Shams Charania's mentor-turned-rival Adrian Wojnarowski left ESPN in September to take a job in college basketball. Just three weeks later, Charania left The Athletic and assumed Woj's place as "Senior NBA Insider." This was perhaps always his destiny, since he was a news-breaking teenage prodigy: to speak his beautiful sentences on linear TV, to appear in a little photo inset for news graphics. In November, Charania was granted an award for basketball writing besides ours: first place in the Professional Basketball Writers Association's 2024 Blumenthal Memorial Writing Contest, for his co-bylined work with The Athletic's Jon Krawczynski. If any of the other awardees are reading this post, please reach out: We're curious to know what it's like to learn that you have won an award for good writing, and then, within the same sentence, learn that Shams Charania has also won it.
It is momentous to present the Shamsy in this strange year of "artificial intelligence." Sometimes critics compare the scoopster prose style to the output of a large language model; I find this funny, but off the mark. While often factually wrong and semantically hollow, an LLM's sentences typically scan like sentences that real humans might produce. Perhaps lazy or thoughtless humans trying to cheat on their homework, but real ones. These models are, after all, trained on a huge corpus of human writing. But the compositions of Shamsy award winners are compelling precisely because they deviate from default human rhythms. Man has not yet devised an intelligence that can report a Jarred Vanderbilt injury in such a disorienting fashion. For now, the human mind is more flavorfully stupid than its technological successors. That's what makes these nominees some of the most innovative writers working today, and that's why we're grateful to sift through these submissions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen A. Smith warns Aaron Rodgers amid Ryan Clark feud: ‘You don’t want to go at [him]’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684619</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/stephen-a-smith-ryan-clark-aaron-rodgers-feud.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T16:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there’s any feud involving a sports media member — particularly an ESPN personality — you can set your watch to Stephen A. Smith (and us at Awful Announcing) chiming in. Smith uses The Stephen A. Smith Show platform to talk about subjects he wouldn’t necessarily be afforded to on ESPN’s airwaves. Not that weighing Read more...
The post Stephen A. Smith warns Aaron Rodgers amid Ryan Clark feud: ‘You don’t want to go at [him]’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Neumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A First Look At Statcast’s Stolen Base Leaderboards]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453118</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/a-first-look-at-statcasts-stolen-base-leaderboards/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T16:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No, we didn’t use that photo of Rays legend Tommy Pham because he’s good at stealing bases. Or maybe he is. It’s complicated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davy Andrews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bold sports media predictions for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684556</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/orig/bold-sports-media-predictions-for-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T16:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, Awful Announcing presented the biggest sports media storylines and trends to watch in 2025. Common themes emerged, from insiders paying close attention to ESPN’s impending launch of its direct-to-consumer streaming service called Flagship, to the continued growth of the creator economy and personality-driven media and production companies. Now, let’s take a look at sports media experts’ big, bold Read more...
The post Bold sports media predictions for 2025 appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark J. Burns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Apple Clock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139691</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-apple-clock/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T15:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Clock helps you manage your time. We recommend the best free and open source alternatives.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Apple Clock appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[lscoltui – change the colors of ls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139773</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/lscoltui-change-colors-ls/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T15:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[lscoltui is a TUI program that lets you configure the colors of ls.
The post lscoltui – change the colors of ls appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jets’ Woody Johnson reportedly nixed Jerry Jeudy trade due to Madden rating]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684602</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/woody-johnson-jets-jerry-jeudy-madden.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T15:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By this point, it’s been well established that Jerry Jeudy is a polarizing player. But while the criticism that Mark Schlereth and Steve Smith Sr. have directed toward the wide receiver in recent years has typically come as a result of his play on the field, it was another factor that resulted in New York Read more...
The post Jets’ Woody Johnson reportedly nixed Jerry Jeudy trade due to Madden rating appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Strong front to blast in tonight (THU-12/19)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3764460</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-strong-front-to-blast-in-tonight-thu-12-19/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T15:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A frosty start to the day today in KC as temperatures flatlined last night after initially falling into the mid to upper 20s. We tanked to 24° at 2AM then immediately rose from there to around 32° by 7AM as south winds transported the colder air from yesterday away from the region. The winds today [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Strong front to blast in tonight (THU-12/19)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3764460</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-strong-front-to-blast-in-tonight-thu-12-19/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T15:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A frosty start to the day today in KC as temperatures flatlined last night after initially falling into the mid to upper 20s. We tanked to 24° at 2AM then immediately rose from there to around 32° by 7AM as south winds transported the colder air from yesterday away from the region. The winds today [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Awfulies: Best media personalities of the year]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684316</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/2024-awfulies-best-media-personalities.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T15:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we’re celebrating the highs, the lows, the best, and the worst of the year with The Awfulies. Started in 2022 and expanded in 2023, the Awful Announcing staff has cast its votes for who we think should take home the coveted golden microphone. Keep an eye on category and winner reveals all week long. And be sure Read more...
The post The 2024 Awfulies: Best media personalities of the year appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod, Sam Neumann, and Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2025 ZiPS Projections: Chicago Cubs]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453136</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/2025-zips-projections-chicago-cubs/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T15:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ZiPS is exuberantly happy about the Cubs lineup, especially the team's defense.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Szymborski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Ritz Bits Spicy Queso Cracker Sandwiches Arrive]]></title>
        <id>https://www.brandeating.com/2024/12/new-ritz-bits-spicy-queso-cracker-sandwiches.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.brandeating.com/2024/12/new-ritz-bits-spicy-queso-cracker-sandwiches.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ritz Bits get a new flavor with the launch of new Spicy Queso cracker sandwiches.

The bite-sized cracker sandwich variety features a layer of "rich, creamy cheese flavor with a bold, spicy kick." It is the first brand-new flavor of Ritz Bits in almost a decade.
You can find new Spicy Queso Ritz Bitz starting this month at convenience stores across the country in 3-oz snack-sized bags. Larger 8.8-oz boxes are set to arrive at major grocery retailers starting in February 2025.
Photo via Ritz.
Read more at Brand Eating!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brand Eating. Your Daily Fast Food Reading.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System Monitor – view and manage system resources]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139763</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/system-monitor-view-manage-system-resources/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T14:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[System Monitor is a process viewer and system monitor with an attractive, easy-to-use interface.
The post System Monitor – view and manage system resources appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Up With The Rangers?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176692</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-is-up-with-the-rangers"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T14:43:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Rangers are in free-fall. They are 3-11 over the last month. There is intrigue in the front office, discontent in the locker room, and two disgruntled players have been shipped out of town in as many weeks, after Kaapo Kakko became Kaapo Kraken on Wednesday, with more threatening to come. There are a lot of moving parts to this implosion, and we thought you might have questions.
When did all the problems start?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Gottlieb on no good, very bad week: ‘You start losing games, everybody wants to have their turn’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684593</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-basketball/doug-gottlieb-losing-games-criticism.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T14:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not too many Division I basketball coaches have had a worse week than Wisconsin-Green Bay head coach and Fox Sports radio host Doug Gottlieb. Gottlieb has had the unfortunate distinction of getting embarrassed both on and off the court. First, there was his viral run-in on X with ESPN’s Adam Schefter, where Schefter ended an Read more...
The post Doug Gottlieb on no good, very bad week: ‘You start losing games, everybody wants to have their turn’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creature Feature: Meet handsome Houston]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865811</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/creature-feature-meet-handsome-houston/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T14:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Scott Poore Meet the handsome Houston. He is a four-year-old boxer mix and kind of a beefcake at around 80 pounds. (We’d argue that it’s all muscle, too.) One of the things he wants most is a forever home with a human friend to hang out with, not doing anything in particular, just a couple of pals...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Poore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Seiya Suzuki BABIP Polka]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453210</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/the-seiya-suzuki-babip-polka/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T14:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Other teams want him. The Cubs are listening to offers. How good is Seiya Suzuki really?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Baumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hailey Davidson Loves Golf, And Golf Wants To Get Rid Of Her]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176654</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/hailey-davidson-loves-golf-and-golf-wants-to-get-rid-of-her"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T14:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hailey Davidson can’t resist popping what she calls “phone pimples”: those nagging little red notification dots that indicate new messages. So on Dec. 4, when she was at her home golf course near Orlando, waiting with a friend to tee off on the fourth hole, she squeezed one.
“It numbed me at first,” said Davidson, 32, in early December. “It’s almost like I didn’t know where I was for a few minutes.” Though she zoned out during her tee shot that followed, the ball still landed within four feet of the par-3 hole.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julie Kliegman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charles Barkley wants NBA season to start on Christmas Day]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684553</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/charles-barkley-wants-nba-season-to-start-on-christmas-day.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T14:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suddenly everybody’s favorite talking point is that the NBA is irrevocably broken and on the verge of collapse.. or something like that. With ratings down this year and growing discontentment about the league’s three-point heavy style of play, it seems like everybody has an idea about how to “fix” the league. Naturally, one of those Read more...
The post Charles Barkley wants NBA season to start on Christmas Day appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Danny Parkins isn’t sold on Mike Vrabel as Bears coaching candidate: ‘This leader of men stuff is grossly overrated’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684539</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/fox/danny-parkins-mike-vrabel-grossly-overrated.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T13:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This coming offseason, the Chicago Bears have the important decision of who they will bring in to be the head coach of the organization for the second season of 2024 first overall pick Caleb Williams. And on Wednesday, FS1 personalities Colin Cowherd and Danny Parkins shared two very different suggestions for what type of candidate Read more...
The post Danny Parkins isn’t sold on Mike Vrabel as Bears coaching candidate: ‘This leader of men stuff is grossly overrated’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlanta Braves reach deal to simulcast 15 games over-the-air]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684499</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/mlb/atlanta-braves-reach-deal-simulcast-15-games-over-the-air.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T13:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Atlanta Braves and Gray Media, a television broadcast company that owns or operates 180 channels nationwide, have agreed to a multi-year deal that will see 15 games simulcast on Gray television stations in Atlanta and surrounding markets each season. The announcement comes on the heels of the Braves’ new media rights agreement with the Read more...
The post Atlanta Braves reach deal to simulcast 15 games over-the-air appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Job Posting: Los Angeles Angels – Full Time Analyst, Research and Development]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?post_type=instagraphs&amp;p=453228</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/instagraphs/job-posting-los-angeles-angels-full-time-analyst-research-and-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T13:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Los Angeles Angels are hiring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Appelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Mannix on Sports Illustrated shift from Arena to Minute: ‘There’s a lot more emphasis on quality.’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684293</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/si/chris-mannix-sports-illustrated-shift-arena-minute.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T12:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the start of 2024, there were regular headlines about the latest disastrous news at Sports Illustrated. That particularly came around publishing license holder Arena Group’s January move to lay off more than 100 employees, which came around SI owner Authentic Brands Group revoking Arena’s license to publish SI. But, after that revocation and announced Read more...
The post Chris Mannix on Sports Illustrated shift from Arena to Minute: ‘There’s a lot more emphasis on quality.’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sty – string styling for your terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139759</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/sty-string-styling-terminal/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T11:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sty provides a simple, customizable and performant string styling markup, which is decoupled from color palettes and terminal implementations.
The post sty – string styling for your terminal appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Food recs: Kansas City's best desserts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2024-12-19/food-recs-kansas-citys-best-desserts</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2024-12-19/food-recs-kansas-citys-best-desserts"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got a sweet tooth for the holidays? Here's a guide to the Kansas City metro's most decadent cakes, divine chocolates, creative baked goods and more treats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Ellison, Claudia Brancart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluefin – Fedora based Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139754</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/bluefin-fedora-based-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T08:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bluefin is an immutable, developer-focused, Cloud-native Linux distribution that's based on Fedora.
The post Bluefin – Fedora based Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seconds - Fascinating Stuff (Flow State Records 009)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/seconds-fascinating-stuff-flow-state</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/seconds-fascinating-stuff-flow-state"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T08:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Seconds, an electronic musician based in Los Angeles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effectively Wild Episode 2259: Rated Rooker]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453218</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/effectively-wild-episode-2259-rated-rooker/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T07:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Lindbergh and Meg Rowley banter about the Cody Bellinger trade, the Yankees’ and Cubs’ next moves, Guaranteed Rate Field changing to Rate Field, and the results of MLB’s inquiry into pitcher injuries. Then (31:39) they bring back A’s slugger Brent Rooker to discuss his monster 2024, his work as a World Series correspondent, misconceptions […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Lindbergh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘College Football 25’ becomes best-selling sports video game ever]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684482</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/gaming/ea-sports-cfb-25-best-selling-sports-video-game-ever.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T03:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After an 11-year hiatus, EA Sports decided to bring back their incredibly popular College Football series with College Football 25 thanks to the implementation of compensation for student-athletes introduced in 2021. And for EA Sports, this decision to bring the series back has paid off in a major way. EA Sports of course stopped making Read more...
The post ‘College Football 25’ becomes best-selling sports video game ever appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sonic 3 doubles down on Jim Carrey to deliver one of the year’s best family flicks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865838</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/sonic-3-doubles-down-on-jim-carrey-to-deliver-one-of-the-years-best-family-flicks/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T03:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paramount Pictures The first thing to be said about Sonic 3 is that it’s a big dumb flurry of fun. That’s capital D and capital F. While it does stretch some comedic beats a bit too far, it’s the kind of exciting family spectacle that used to rule the summer box office. The action is kinetic and colorful. The heroes...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Torres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ohio State roasted for celebrating Ryan Day Coach of the Year semifinalist honor]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684509</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/ohio-state-ryan-day-coach-of-the-year-semifinalist.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T03:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no hotter seat in America than Ryan Day as head coach of the Ohio State Buckeyes. And apparently everyone gets this except for Ohio State themselves. The Ohio State program enters each year with three stated objectives – 1) Beat Michigan, 2) Win the Big Ten, 3) Win a National Championship. Day is Read more...
The post Ohio State roasted for celebrating Ryan Day Coach of the Year semifinalist honor appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Award winner Ezra Edelman says current state of sports documentaries ‘border on branded content’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684470</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/meadowlark/ezra-edelman-sports-documentaries-branded-content.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T02:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are more sports documentaries than ever before. But the question is how many of them are actually good? At this point, it seems like almost everyone who has ever had a cup of coffee in the big leagues has had a documentary made about them. Years ago you could count the number of media Read more...
The post Award winner Ezra Edelman says current state of sports documentaries ‘border on branded content’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Dennis Jr. gets deducted 501 points on ‘Around the Horn’ for Bill Belichick-UNC cold take]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684443</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/david-dennis-jr-around-the-horn-incorrect-bill-belichick-prediction.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T01:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2024 marks the final full calendar year where Around the Horn will be on ESPN programming. And with only a few weeks left before the start of 2025, Around the Horn regular David Dennis Jr. blew a 200-point lead on the year in epic fashion after he was rightfully called out for his incorrect take Read more...
The post David Dennis Jr. gets deducted 501 points on ‘Around the Horn’ for Bill Belichick-UNC cold take appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Army-Navy posts largest audience since at least 1990]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684461</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/army-navy-posts-largest-audience-since-at-least-1990.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T01:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although pretty much everything in college football has changed over the last couple seasons, one thing that remains constant is the unique tradition of the Army-Navy game. While there are some calls to tinker with the tradition of playing the game after conference championship games and move it to Week 0 (looking at you Joel Read more...
The post Army-Navy posts largest audience since at least 1990 appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An underrated trade acquisition for the Royals]]></title>
        <id>https://farmtofountains.com/?p=6585</id>
        <link href="https://farmtofountains.com/an-underrated-trade-acquisition-for-the-royals/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=an-underrated-trade-acquisition-for-the-royals"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T00:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kansas City Royals kick-started their offseason nearly a month ago. The team sent RHP Brady Singer to the Reds in exchange for second baseman Jonathan India and outfielder Joey Wiemer. India was the real focus of the return for the Royals, with good reason. India was named the NL Rookie of the Year in […]
The post An underrated trade acquisition for the Royals appeared first on Farm to Fountains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Farr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Titans head coach on question about team being soft: ‘You can shove that right up your ass’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684422</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/titans-head-coach-question-team-being-soft-shove-that-right-up-your-ass.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T00:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Questioning the toughness of an NFL team is typically a fools errand. These are some of the biggest and baddest dudes in the world, and it’s pretty difficult to go pro in the sport of football without being tough. One reporter, however, did not get that memo during a press conference with Tennessee Titans head Read more...
The post Titans head coach on question about team being soft: ‘You can shove that right up your ass’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alabama transfer Damon Payne confuses reporters with voided commitment to Michigan]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684395</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/college-football/damon-payne-michigan-commitment-voided.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-19T00:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the current landscape of college football where players are moving teams more than ever in the transfer portal, reporting on college recruiting has become an incredibly difficult job. But on Wednesday, Alabama transfer Damon Payne and his agency made things even more difficult with his commitment to Michigan, which was voided in the span Read more...
The post Alabama transfer Damon Payne confuses reporters with voided commitment to Michigan appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Gottlieb absent from radio show after losing to D2 school]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684392</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/radio/doug-gottlieb-absent-from-afternoon-radio-show-after-d2-loss.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T23:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who could have seen this coming? It turns out, coaching a Division I basketball team and hosting a daily nationally syndicated radio program simultaneously may be a tough gig. University of Wisconsin Green Bay head coach Doug Gottlieb is learning that the hard way so far this year. Gottlieb, the longtime radio host and former Read more...
The post Doug Gottlieb absent from radio show after losing to D2 school appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A hater’s guide to all the problems people have with the NBA right now]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684290</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/haters-guide-issues-viewership-popularity.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T23:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NBA is one of the most popular sports leagues in the world and just shocked everyone with a massive 11-year, $76 billion media rights deal. Yet if you look at the media landscape around the NBA, the vibe is quite different. Nobody is celebrating the league’s record incoming revenues or the enormous depth of Read more...
The post A hater’s guide to all the problems people have with the NBA right now appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Gottlieb Humbled By Michigan Tech, Life]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176625</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/doug-gottlieb-humbled-by-michigan-tech-life"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T22:46:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fox Sports ding-dong Doug Gottlieb has experienced ongoing humiliation in his first year as the head coach of the Green Bay Phoenix, which is rough for him but great for everyone else. The 2-11 team's season in the Horizon League has been dismal, though it hit a notable new low for Gottlieb this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Certified ball-knower Timothée Chalamet flexes knowledge on…MLS?]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684337</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/podcasts/certified-ball-knower-timothee-chalamet-flexes-mls-knowledge.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T22:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timothée Chalamet may just be the surprise sports media story of the year. After the A-lister’s masterclass appearing as a guest picker on College GameDay, Chalamet showed off another side of his sports knowledge on This Past Weekend hosted by comedian Theo Von.   I certainly didn’t have Timothée Chalamet dapping up Alex Muyl on Read more...
The post Certified ball-knower Timothée Chalamet flexes knowledge on…MLS? appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ALLCITY CEO Brandon Spano talks layoffs: ‘The shows have to be profitable.’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684331</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/online-outlets/allcity-ceo-brandon-spano-layoffs-profitable.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T22:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, numerous employees across the ALLCITY network of local sports websites and shows took to social media to note that they’d been laid off. Awful Announcing spoke to ALLCITY CEO Brandon Spano about this Wednesday afternoon, and confirmed that about seven percent of the company’s workforce has been laid off in an attempt to Read more...
The post ALLCITY CEO Brandon Spano talks layoffs: ‘The shows have to be profitable.’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bucholtz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nick Wright proclaims NBA Cup title now ‘a thing you have to have on your resume if you’re a great player’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684353</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/nick-wright-cup-title-great-player.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T21:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NBA Cup is openly mocked among old-school media who dislike new things, but FS1’s Nick Wright thinks it matters a lot. Discussing the Milwaukee Bucks’ victory in the NBA Cup final on Wednesday’s edition of First Things First, Wright argued that the accolade is quickly becoming an important part of a player’s legacy. That’s because Read more...
The post Nick Wright proclaims NBA Cup title now ‘a thing you have to have on your resume if you’re a great player’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The age of Sports Bluesky is upon us]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684239</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/tech/sports-bluesky-age-twitter-x.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T21:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re familiar with Bluesky, the upstart social media platform vying to replace X/Twitter, you might be aware that it hasn’t always been synonymous with sports. For a while, in fact, there was a stretch when the sheer lack of sports talk on it was something of a running gag on the platform. Paul Frazee, Read more...
The post The age of Sports Bluesky is upon us appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Devin Raab</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Falcons Choose Buyer’s Remorse Over Kirk Cousins]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176608</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/falcons-choose-buyers-remorse-over-kirk-cousins"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T20:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This spring, the Atlanta Falcons made the bold decision to bring in an old quarterback with a worrisome injury history. What made the decision bold was that a month earlier, they’d signed Kirk Cousins to a four-year, $180 million contract with a no-trade clause—and $100 million of it guaranteed. (Zing!)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Clark fires back at Aaron Rodgers in scathing video criticizing QB’s ‘hypocrisy’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684319</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/ryan-clark-fires-back-aaron-rodgers-scathing-video-criticizing-hypocrisy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T20:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The war of words between Aaron Rodgers and Ryan Clark was stoked once again on Wednesday, this time due to a scathing video released by Clark criticizing the New York Jets quarterback’s “hypocrisy” and general lack of self-awareness. The nearly five-minute long video posted to Clark’s social media channels shows the ESPN analyst take direct Read more...
The post Ryan Clark fires back at Aaron Rodgers in scathing video criticizing QB’s ‘hypocrisy’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s So Confusing Sometimes To Be A Bird]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176564</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-so-confusing-sometimes-to-be-a-bird"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T20:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(bird, bird, bird, bird)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruthie Ozonoff paints us the big picture in The Pitch Questionnaire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865819</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/ruthie-ozonoff-paints-us-the-big-picture-in-the-pitch-questionnaire/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T20:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Ruthie Ozonoff Ruthie Ozonoff is a Kansas City-based designer and muralist. Known for her bold, colorful designs, Ozonoff has created iconic murals throughout the city, including the “Kansas City I’m So In Love” mural in the Crossroads Arts District, the Minsky’s Pizza murals at 51st & Main St. and Southwest Blvd., and the UMKC Welcome Center murals....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking ahead to the biggest sports media stories of 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684233</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/orig/looking-ahead-to-the-biggest-sports-media-stories-of-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T20:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While we’re nearing the end of 2024, Awful Announcing wanted to take stock of the sports media industry and see what are the biggest stories and trends keeping insiders’ attention over the next 12 months. In 2025, we’ll see the NBA begin its 11-year deal with Prime Video, which has already reportedly started signing talent for its Read more...
The post Looking ahead to the biggest sports media stories of 2025 appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark J. Burns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bart Scott, Chris Carlin reuniting for daily radio show on ESPN New York]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684296</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/radio/bart-scott-chris-carlin-reunite-espn-new-york.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T19:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN New York announced its new radio lineup with Michael Kay leaving the afternoon show, and it features a familiar tandem in middays. Seven years after they were tasked with helping to fill the void left by Mike Francesa on WFAN, Bart Scott and Chris Carlin are reuniting on ESPN New York, taking over the Read more...
The post Bart Scott, Chris Carlin reuniting for daily radio show on ESPN New York appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former rural Kansas prosecutor charged with felony perjury and witness intimidation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865876</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/former-rural-kansas-prosecutor-charged-with-felony-perjury-and-witness-intimidation/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T19:10:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Thuston hands his wedding ring to his wife before being handcuffed following a Sept. 4, 2024, hearing in Neosho County District Court. (Sherman Smith/Kansas Reflector) TOPEKA — Former Neosho County Attorney Linus Thuston, who was jailed for misdemeanor convictions earlier this year, now faces six felony charges of perjury and witness intimidation. Special prosecutor Branden Bell filed the charges...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sherman Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen A. Smith calls for Ohio State to hire Deion Sanders due to Coach Prime’s ‘sizzle’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684295</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/stephen-a-smith-ohio-state-hire-deion-sanders.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T19:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Ohio State prepares to host Tennessee in a first-round matchup in the College Football Playoff, there’s been no shortage of speculation regarding Ryan Day’s job status. But while most of that conversation has focused on the possibility of Mike Vrabel returning to Columbus to coach his alma mater, Stephen A. Smith has another former Read more...
The post Stephen A. Smith calls for Ohio State to hire Deion Sanders due to Coach Prime’s ‘sizzle’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carlos Watson Played The Wrong Game And Lost]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176600</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/carlos-watson-played-the-wrong-game-and-lost"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T18:50:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, former digital media entrepreneur and self-styled criminal justice reform activist Carlos Watson was sentenced to almost 10 years in prison in the federal financial conspiracy case over his startup, Ozy Media. Watson and Ozy Media were both convicted in July of conspiracy to commit securities fraud and conspiracy to commit wire fraud and aggravated identity theft. 
Last year Watson was indicted after New York Times reporting revealed that former Ozy Media Chief Operating Officer Samir Rao impersonated a YouTube executive on a conference call with Goldman Sachs. Both Watson and Ozy were indicted, and both pleaded not guilty throughout the trial, with Watson claiming instead that the entire trial was racially motivated, biased, and corrupt. He and his team raised more than $60,000 since March 2023 on this argument through a website titled “Too Black for Business,” and last month, supporters released a two-part, three-hour docuseries on YouTube called “The Troubling Case of Carlos Watson.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Mangold’s Bob Dylan flick A Complete Unknown will get your dad’s approval, but paints-by-numbers as a music biopic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865852</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/james-mangolds-bob-dylan-flick-a-complete-unknown-will-get-your-dads-approval-but-paints-by-numbers-as-a-music-biopic/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T18:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Searchlight Pictures Perhaps the only review that matters is this: I took my dad to see A Complete Unknown, and he enjoyed himself. He hummed along with the songs, we laughed at a few things, and while we both agreed that I’m Not There is a better movie about Bob Dylan’s artistic identity and legacy, we had a good...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Francesa doesn’t buy reports of Bill Belichick’s interest in Jets]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684272</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/mike-francesa-bill-belichick-jets-report.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T18:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Belichick was reportedly interested in burying the hatchet with Woody Johnson and the New York Jets, but Mike Francesa doesn’t buy it. Last week, Dianna Russini of The Athletic stunned the NFL world by reporting Belichick’s camp reached out to the Jets about their head coaching vacancy earlier this month. This is the same Read more...
The post Mike Francesa doesn’t buy reports of Bill Belichick’s interest in Jets appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bucks Rode A Big Third Quarter To An NBA Cup Win They Definitely Care About]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176566</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/milwaukee-bucks-win-nba-cup-horray-i-guess"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T17:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hottest NBA action on Tuesday night was in Las Vegas, as the second Airline NBA Cup Championship Final Where They Award A Trophy pit the Milwaukee Bucks against the Oklahoma City Thunder at the Cell Phone Arena Earmarked For A Future NBA Team, Probably. Granted, it was the only NBA action on Tuesday night, thanks to the league's ongoing effort to make its in-season tournament seem important. Still, though, a game between the two hottest teams in the NBA is usually worth the price of listening to Richard Jefferson speak for a couple of hours.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kBFRMjFpY8Q]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JAWS and the 2025 Hall of Fame Ballot: Russell Martin]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453102</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/jaws-and-the-2025-hall-of-fame-ballot-russell-martin/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T17:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Framing the case for an elite receiver.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Jaffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13 Best Free and Open Source Java Micro-Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=82513</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/free-open-source-java-microframeworks/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T17:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article examines the best Java micro-frameworks. Micro means the framework is small, with little or no tools and libraries.
The post 13 Best Free and Open Source Java Micro-Frameworks appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix announces docuseries covering 2024 SEC football season]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684260</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/netflix/netflix-announces-docuseries-covering-2024-sec-football-season.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T17:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this year, The Athletic reported that Netflix was closing in on a deal with the Southeastern Conference for a docuseries on the league’s football season. On the eve of the first-ever 12-team College Football Playoff, the project is now official, with Netflix announcing that an unnamed docuseries featuring the SEC’s 2024 season will be Read more...
The post Netflix announces docuseries covering 2024 SEC football season appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Max McGee was reportedly let go from ESPN after complaint from female employee]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684226</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/max-mcgee-reportedly-let-go-complaint-female-employee.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T17:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Max McGee’s departure from ESPN earlier this year largely flew under the radar. But it appears we now know the reason behind the former SportsCenter anchor’s exit in February, with The Athletic reporting that it came “after the company received a complaint about him from a female employee, according to ESPN sources.” While The Athletic’s Read more...
The post Max McGee was reportedly let go from ESPN after complaint from female employee appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruby Mae Johnson & Friends’ A Very Ruby Christmas lights a joyful candle in the dark of winter with holiday variety spectacular]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865764</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/a-very-ruby-christmas-lights-a-joyful-candle-in-the-dark-of-winter/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T17:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those of you feeling as though your holiday season came down to the wire, Ruby Mae Johnson’s upcoming Christmas spectacular, A Very Ruby Christmas–A Holiday Extravaganza with Ruby Mae and Friends, came together in less than two months. The show takes place this Friday, December 20, at Liberty Hall, and the idea only came to the Lawrence poet and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hostess Updates with New Logo and Packaging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.brandeating.com/2024/12/hostess-snack-cakes-new-logo-and-packaging.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.brandeating.com/2024/12/hostess-snack-cakes-new-logo-and-packaging.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Snack cake brand Hostess reveals a new logo and packaging design as part of a brand refresh. Hostess describes the change as more modern to "enhance appeal with new consumers while engaging current fans." Smuckers acquisition of the brand in 2023 probably also played a part.

The new logo still includes a heart but features a "more playful font style and a brighter color palette." There's also a cloud-shaped border to reflect the "light and airy quality of every Hostess snack."
As far as the new packaging goes, it includes new stylized typography, updated product photography, and updated product descriptions." 
According to Hostess' consumer testing, the updated logo and new packaging were preferred 2 to 1 over the previous look.
What do you think of the new look? Is it better? Worse? Here's the previous packaging for references:

Photos via Hostess.
Read more at Brand Eating!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brand Eating. Your Daily Fast Food Reading.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[as-tree – print a list of paths as a tree of paths]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139745</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/as-tree-print-list-paths-tree/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T16:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[as-tree is a command-line utility that prints a list of paths as a tree of paths.  It's written in Rust.
The post as-tree – print a list of paths as a tree of paths appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Play-By-Play: What’s up with the NBA? Bill Belichick to UNC and another Caitlin Clark controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684211</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/podcasts/the-play-by-play-nba-bill-belichick-caitlin-clark.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T16:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s time for another episode of The Play-By-Play, Awful Announcing’s weekly sports media news podcast. On the latest episode, Awful Announcing’s Ben Axelrod and Brendon Kleen discuss: The state of the NBA. Bill Belichick to North Carolina. Kyle Shanahan trade rumors. Angst regarding the college football transfer portal. The latest Caitlin Clark controversy. The Play-By-Play is available Read more...
The post The Play-By-Play: What’s up with the NBA? Bill Belichick to UNC and another Caitlin Clark controversy appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charles Barkley reveals he’s undecided on ESPN future and has met with NBC and Amazon]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684242</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/charles-barkley-undecided-espn-nbc-amazon.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T16:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN may have reached an agreement to license Inside the NBA from TNT, but that agreement doesn’t include Charles Barkley just yet. After talking openly about Warner Bros. Discovery losing NBA rights for TNT for months and repeatedly preaching his desire to see Inside the NBA remain intact, Barkley has been curiously quiet about the Read more...
The post Charles Barkley reveals he’s undecided on ESPN future and has met with NBC and Amazon appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Contes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hornets Cruelly Bait-And-Switch Child By Promising PS5 But Giving Him PS5 And Hornets Tickets]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176560</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/hornets-cruelly-bait-and-switch-child-by-promising-ps5-but-giving-him-ps5-and-hornets-tickets"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T16:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Charlotte Hornets scheduled a Christmas-themed on-court skit for a break in the second quarter of their home loss Monday to the depleted 76ers. The setup involved Hugo, the mascot of the Hornets, learning what a couple of participating children most want for Christmas, and then delivering the goods. The payoff, as far as I can tell, was supposed to come with the final wish: A kid tells Hugo, sadly, that his father is moving the family to Philadelphia, and Hugo saves the day by producing a new father, clad in a Hornets jersey, to keep the family in Charlotte. You're rolling your eyes now, but someone at the Hallmark Channel is rubbing their hands together greedily while their assistant speed-dials Luke Macfarlane.
To set up this joke, the skit had to first demonstrate that Hugo had Santa-like powers. The second and penultimate child to interact with Hugo, a 13-year-old named Jack, asked for and received a Playstation 5. In the same way that the children in the punchline did not get to keep the actor in the Hornets jersey, Jack was never intended to keep the Playstation 5; the expensive hardware was meant to establish Hugo's generosity, in order to set up the gag about how a Hornets-loving dad, to replace your regular, crappy one, would a great and wonderful gift. The Hornets were giving the gift of entertainment, to the audience, with a skit! They were not giving a PS5 to a child. Alexei Phillips, Jack's uncle, told Queen City News that after the skit the Hornets took back the PS5, and instead gave his nephew a Hornets jersey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tigers and Twins Winter Meetings Notes]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453019</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/tigers-and-twins-winter-meetings-notes/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T16:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Derek Falvey, Scott Harris, A.J. Hinch and Rocco Baldelli address questions from the media.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Laurila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saints linebacker Demario Davis leads way in making community activism part of NFL’s growth story]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684143</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/saints-linebacker-demario-davis-community-activism.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T16:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Orleans Saints linebacker Demario Davis is an All-Pro both on and off the field. And with the NFL more popular than ever before, Davis is hopeful that the work players do in their local communities is always part of the story. At 35, Davis’ career has aged like fine wine. He signed with the Read more...
The post Saints linebacker Demario Davis leads way in making community activism part of NFL’s growth story appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Yoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL earns massive combined audience for Sunday’s big slate]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684086</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nfl/massive-combined-audience-sunday-double-doubleheader.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T15:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A pair of high-wattage games in the late afternoon window led the NFL to a huge audience on Sunday. Deploying its first “double-doubleheader” of the season in which both CBS and Fox aired nationally televised games in the 4:25 p.m. ET window, the NFL drew nearly 40 million viewers on Sunday afternoon. The CBS broadcast Read more...
The post NFL earns massive combined audience for Sunday’s big slate appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Cold, warmer, colder, warmer (WED-12/18)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3763177</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-cold-warmer-colder-warmer-wed-12-18/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T15:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudy Wednesday morning, becoming mostly sunny this afternoon with highs near 40 degrees]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Cold, warmer, colder, warmer (WED-12/18)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3763177</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-cold-warmer-colder-warmer-wed-12-18/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T15:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudy Wednesday morning, becoming mostly sunny this afternoon with highs near 40 degrees]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tyson Foods cut contracts with Missouri farmers and is working to silence their legal fight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865861</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/tyson-foods-cut-contracts-with-missouri-farmers-and-is-working-to-silence-their-legal-fight/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T15:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A farm near Sikeston on April 17 where the owner raised chickens before market changes (photo by Daniel Byrd, for Investigate Midwest) This story was produced by the Watchdog Writers Group in collaboration with Investigate Midwest.  DEXTER – On an early August morning in 2023, Shawn Hinkle received a call from one of his technicians at Tyson Foods who, through...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Egan Ward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Awfulies: Best & worst sports media moments of the year]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684137</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/orig/2024-awfulies-best-worst-sports-media-moments-year.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T15:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we’re celebrating the highs, the lows, the best, and the worst of the year with The Awfulies. Started in 2022 and expanded in 2023, the Awful Announcing staff has cast its votes for who we think should take home the coveted golden microphone. Keep an eye on category and winner reveals all week long. And be sure Read more...
The post The 2024 Awfulies: Best & worst sports media moments of the year appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Keeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orioles Sign NPB Legend Tomoyuki Sugano To One-Year Pact]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453071</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/orioles-sign-npb-legend-tomoyuki-sugano-to-one-year-pact/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T15:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My favorite one-year deal of the winter so far asks an interesting question: What does 80-grade command look like without overpowering stuff?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Clemens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashburger Offers Buy-One-Get-One-Free Burger Deal Through December 24, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.brandeating.com/2024/12/smashburger-buy-one-get-one-free-burger-deal-through-december-24-2024.html</id>
        <link href="https://www.brandeating.com/2024/12/smashburger-buy-one-get-one-free-burger-deal-through-december-24-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a holiday promotion, fast-casual burger chain Smashburger is offering a limited-time, buy-one-get-one-free deal on any of its burgers through Tuesday, December 24, 2024.

The deal is available in-store only at participating locations (you can find a list of participating locations on the Smashburger website here). The deal is good on both single-patty and double-patty versions of the chain's various burgers.
Interestingly enough, the deal is not limited to one use (i.e. one free burger) per person so you can buy something like four burgers and get four burgers free. The relevant fine print reads as follows:

"For each burger or sandwich purchased in a transaction, receive one (1) complimentary order of any burger or sandwich (protein substitutions available) (not including applicable taxes) on the menu that is of equal or lesser value to the item purchased.  Must use promo code 4031 at checkout to redeem this offer in person at a participating location.  No limit on number of qualifying complimentary items that may be redeemed with coupon in a single transaction.  Offer valid only for item of equal or lesser value."

Photo via Smashburger.
Read more at Brand Eating!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brand Eating. Your Daily Fast Food Reading.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Lee Fitting’s abrupt ESPN departure came after HR investigation into behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684202</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/lee-fitting-hr-investigation-the-athletic.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T14:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The timing of Lee Fitting’s departure at ESPN raised plenty of questions, as it came just weeks ahead of the 2023 college football and NFL seasons. But while those questions appeared to have been answered with the ensuing College GameDay Emmy fraud scandal that was made public months later, it appears there was more to Read more...
The post Report: Lee Fitting’s abrupt ESPN departure came after HR investigation into behavior appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Axelrod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Clock 5 – modern digital clock application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139701</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/digital-clock-modern-digital-clock-application/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T14:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Clock 5 is billed as a very customizable and beautiful clock. It lives up to its billing and more besides.
The post Digital Clock 5 – modern digital clock application appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shams Charania again refutes Jimmy Butler’s agent: ‘Probably the most vetted story I’ve ever put out’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684011</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/shams-charania-jimmy-butler-trade-report-most-vetted-story.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T14:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past week, ESPN’s lead NBA insider Shams Charania’s reputation has been dragged through the mud by Jimmy Butler’s agent Bernard Lee over the validity of his reporting. On Tuesday, Charania made it clear during an appearance on The Pat McAfee Show how strongly he stands by his reporting. Charania first reported that the Read more...
The post Shams Charania again refutes Jimmy Butler’s agent: ‘Probably the most vetted story I’ve ever put out’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Warming up at Blue Bird Bistro and KC Craft Ramen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865793</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-warming-up-at-blue-bird-bistro-and-kc-craft-ramen/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T14:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blue Bird Bistro // Photo By Tiffany Watts Blue Bird Bistro In Kansas City’s eclectic food scene, Blue Bird Bistro stands out as a neighborhood gem dedicated to local and organic fare. It’s the kind of place where wholesome ingredients meet creative flavors, and recently, it served as the perfect spot for a little team bonding with the Pitch team....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Warming up at Blue Bird Bistro and KC Craft Ramen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=865793</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-warming-up-at-blue-bird-bistro-and-kc-craft-ramen/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T14:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blue Bird Bistro // Photo By Tiffany Watts Blue Bird Bistro In Kansas City’s eclectic food scene, Blue Bird Bistro stands out as a neighborhood gem dedicated to local and organic fare. It’s the kind of place where wholesome ingredients meet creative flavors, and recently, it served as the perfect spot for a little team bonding with the Pitch team....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2025 ZiPS Projections: Boston Red Sox]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453039</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/2025-zips-projections-boston-red-sox/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T14:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Red Sox have gained enough ground on the Yankees and Orioles to make them sweat, at least a little.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Szymborski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Watches A Christmas Movie: ‘The Christmas Quest’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176152</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/christmas-movie-the-christmas-quest"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the time of year when the best, biggest, and most ambitious movies come out. Not Oscar season, but rather that stretch when the halls of streaming services are decked with the brightly lit, thinly disguised advertisements that are the year's new Christmas movies. There are more than 100 new Christmas films to watch this holiday season, and whether that number horrifies or excites you depends upon how much of a freak you are for the festive. Sabrina is proud to say they are a real Christmas freak, and this year they asked some of their colleagues to watch some of the most, uh, available new holiday movies. The fifth movie in our lineup is The Christmas Quest, a movie that pushes the boundary of what a neckline can be.
Sabrina Imbler: I’m so excited to talk with both of you about Hallmark’s first and potentially last foray into the special kind of love that stems from a mutual interest in Icelandic antiquities. Before we talk about the movie, I would love to learn more about your relationship with archaeology and the rich cultural traditions of Iceland. What interested you in watching this movie in particular? Had you heard of the Icelandic Yule Lads, or Jólasveinar, before?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN sees massive audience growth for NCAA Volleyball Regionals]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684140</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/massive-growth-ncaa-volleyball-regionals.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T13:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[College volleyball continues to be a rocket ship property for ESPN. The NCAA Volleyball Regional semifinals and finals both scored big increases versus last year. Per ESPN PR, 2024 was the most-watched NCAA Volleyball Regionals on record, averaging 401,000 viewers per telecast. That’s up 98% versus last season’s regionals. ’24 @NCAAVolleyball Regionals were the MOST-WATCHED Read more...
The post ESPN sees massive audience growth for NCAA Volleyball Regionals appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Brianna Chickenfry podcast co-host Grace O’Malley leaves Barstool Sports]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=683999</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/barstool/grace-omalley-leaves-plan-bri-uncut-brianna-chickenfry-lapaglia.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T13:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is more change coming at Barstool Sports around star host Brianna “Chickenfry” LaPaglia, as her now-former Plan Bri Uncut cohost Grace O’Malley announced her departure from Barstool this week. In a note on her Instagram story, O’Malley wrote that it was “not a mutual decision” and that she was “heartbroken” to see the show come Read more...
The post Former Brianna Chickenfry podcast co-host Grace O’Malley leaves Barstool Sports appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon Kleen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vernon Davis, Omar Bolden to star in mockumentary on podcasting]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684170</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/podcasts/vernon-davis-omar-bolden-star-podcasting-mockumentary.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T13:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Podcasting, perhaps the most mockable medium out there, is getting the mockumentary treatment. According to The Hollywood Reporter, former NFL stars Vernon Davis and Omar Bolden will star in an upcoming mockumentary style comedy series titled Match Point. The former Denver Broncos teammates will play the lead roles Max (Davis) and Anthony (Bolden), two former Read more...
The post Vernon Davis, Omar Bolden to star in mockumentary on podcasting appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 18, 2024: how to watch Boca Raton and LA Bowls]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=683981</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/viewing-picks/tv-and-streaming-viewing-picks-for-december-18-2024-how-to-watch-boca-raton-and-la-bowls.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T12:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All Times Eastern Bundesliga Bundesliga Weekly — ESPN+, 5:30 p.m. Carabao Cup Knockout Round Quarterfinal, St. James’ Park, Newcastle upon Tyne, England, United Kingdom Newcastle United vs. Brentford — CBS Sports Network, 2:45 p.m. CBS Sports Golazo Matchday — CBS Sports Golazo Network, 2 p.m. College Basketball Men’s Jumpman Invitational Day 2, Spectrum Center, Charlotte, Read more...
The post TV and Streaming Viewing Picks for December 18, 2024: how to watch Boca Raton and LA Bowls appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Fang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[zpaqfranz – deduplicating archiver with encryption and paranoid-level tests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139730</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/zpaqfranz-deduplicating-archiver-encryption-paranoid-level-tests/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T11:52:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[zpaqfranz is a deduplicating archiver with encryption and paranoid-level tests. 
The post zpaqfranz – deduplicating archiver with encryption and paranoid-level tests appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla – extensible CSS framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139727</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/vanilla-extensible-css-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T08:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla Framework is an extensible CSS framework, built using Sass and is designed to be used either directly or by using themes.
The post Vanilla – extensible CSS framework appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ambient Country Episode 39: Dave Harrington]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/ambient-country-episode-39-dave-harrington</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/ambient-country-episode-39-dave-harrington"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T08:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On today’s episode of Ambient Country, host Bob Holmes of SUSS is joined by Dave Harrington of Darkside to discuss Dave's music, his latest releases with Nicole McCabe & Yuka Honda for the Across the Horizon music series]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effectively Wild Episode 2258: 99 Manfred Balloons]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=453104</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/effectively-wild-episode-2258-99-manfred-balloons/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T05:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Lindbergh and Meg Rowley banter about the qualifications for being a superstar, the Kyle Tucker trade from the Astros’ and Cubs’ perspectives, the Devin Williams trade from the Yankees’ and Brewers’ perspectives, and various other transactions, including the A’s trading for Jeffrey Springs and the Orioles signing Tomoyuki Sugano, plus thoughts on Caleb Durbin’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Lindbergh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linear Sort]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3026/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3026/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Gottlieb acknowledges fault in Adam Schefter social media beef: ‘I understand my tone was pretty negative’]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684119</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/radio/doug-gottlieb-takes-blame-adam-schefter-beef.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T04:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Monday, ESPN’s Adam Schefter and Fox Sports Radio host Doug Gottlieb got into a war of words on social media that quickly turned into personal jabs at their respective professional careers. The interaction all started when Schefter reported that Sacramento State, currently an FCS program, had targeted Michael Vick to be the next head Read more...
The post Doug Gottlieb acknowledges fault in Adam Schefter social media beef: ‘I understand my tone was pretty negative’ appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals sign RHP Taylor Clarke to minor-league deal]]></title>
        <id>https://farmtofountains.com/?p=6580</id>
        <link href="https://farmtofountains.com/royals-sign-rhp-taylor-clarke-to-minor-league-deal/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=royals-sign-rhp-taylor-clarke-to-minor-league-deal"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T04:08:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals are bringing back a familiar face to the organization, signing relief-pitcher Taylor Clarke to a minor league contract. After spending his first three major league seasons with the Arizona Diamondbacks, Clarke signed with the Royals prior to the 2022 season where he found some success. That season, he held a 4.04 ERA in […]
The post Royals sign RHP Taylor Clarke to minor-league deal appeared first on Farm to Fountains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zac Miller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix announces new Mike Tyson docuseries]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684044</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/netflix/mike-tyson-docuseries-announcement.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T03:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month, Netflix broke streaming records with its first major foray into live sports for the Mike Tyson-Jake Paul boxing match. On the back of this event, Netflix officially announced that Tyson will be the subject of a new docuseries on the platform. While the Tyson-Paul broadcast did have its fair share of issues, it Read more...
The post Netflix announces new Mike Tyson docuseries appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals, Taylor Clarke Agree To Minor League Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=834960</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/12/royals-taylor-clarke-agree-to-minor-league-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T03:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals agreed to a minor league contract with right-hander Taylor Clarke last week, according to the MLB.com transaction log. The 31-year-old returns to the organization after spending one season in the Milwaukee system. Clarke, a former Diamondbacks draftee, pitched with Kansas City in 2022 and ’23. The former was the best season of his…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers opens up about strained relationship with family in new docuseries]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684088</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/netflix/aaron-rodgers-strained-family-relationship-new-docuseries.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T03:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday, the new Aaron Rodgers docuseries called Aaron Rodgers: Enigma premiered on Netflix. And during episode two of the docuseries, Rodgers dove into the longstanding and messy relationship with his family members. Rodgers has become one of the most polarizing figures in sports for his conspiracy theories and recent inability to accept criticism for Read more...
The post Aaron Rodgers opens up about strained relationship with family in new docuseries appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reice Shipley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hubie Brown to call final NBA game on February 9th]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684116</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/hubie-brown-call-final-game-february-9th.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T02:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legendary NBA coach and broadcaster Hubie Brown will call his final game in February, ESPN announced Tuesday night. The news was first reported by the New York Post‘s Ryan Glasspiegel. Brown will call the Philadelphia 76ers and Milwaukee Bucks on February 9th at 2:00 p.m. ET on ABC. The game is the same day as Read more...
The post Hubie Brown to call final NBA game on February 9th appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doris Burke misses NBA Cup Final for illness, not blackjack losses]]></title>
        <id>https://awfulannouncing.com/?p=684104</id>
        <link href="https://awfulannouncing.com/nba/doris-burke-misses-cup-final-illness-blackjack-losses.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-18T02:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second ever NBA Cup Final is up for grabs on Tuesday night, and one of ESPN’s lead commentators isn’t there to call it. ESPN’s lead NBA game analyst Doris Burke is not on the call as the Milwaukee Bucks and Oklahoma City Thunder battle for the NBA Cup title in Las Vegas. Instead, lead Read more...
The post Doris Burke misses NBA Cup Final for illness, not blackjack losses appeared first on Awful Announcing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Lerner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>