<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-06-17T06:27:14.750Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crowded tent / Empty words]]></title>
        <id>6850875f475bb700010aff9a</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-341/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T23:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Osita Nwanevu on growing the antifascist coalition; Hydranym victors; Tom Scocca consults the dictionary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking Your Meaning]]></title>
        <id>68509388475bb700010affba</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/taking-your-meaning/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T23:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My eighth-grader showed up in the doorway of the kitchen with a sheet of vocabulary words he wanted to go over. They were reading Night, by Elie Weisel, so they were being quizzed on words written in adult literary diction—billeted and manacled and conflagration—and while I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome, Antifascists!]]></title>
        <id>6850330d475bb700010afe9e</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/who-goes-anti-nazi/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T23:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The president’s combination birthday celebration, army anniversary, and Flag Day parade on Saturday was, perhaps predictably, a total bust. Forty-five million dollars might buy you time and tanks from the US Army, but it cannot, it turns out, buy you grandeur. And as bemusing as it was to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Osita Nwanevu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weenie Centrist Legislator Faceplants Hard At Weekend Protest Event]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192688</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/weenie-centrist-legislator-faceplants-hard-at-weekend-protest-event"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T19:50:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April McClain Delaney, House representative for Maryland's 6th congressional district, did not get off to a hot start in her address to Frederick, Md.'s modest-sized but otherwise energetic and very positive "No Kings" protest on Saturday. As soon as she took the microphone, a few people on the back side of the little pavilion at the center of Mullinix Park began heckling her; at first, a whole crowd away and out of sight from the hecklers, I thought they were pro–Donald Trump counterprotesters, but I made my way over there and found that they were actually anti-Trump protesters, perhaps the anti-Trump-iest people there, and were mad specifically at the congressperson.
When McClain Delaney spoke of the need to stand up to the Trump administration's terrorism of immigrant communities, one of the hecklers shouted "Then don't thank ICE!" This seemed like it was probably a reference to her vote in favor of a congressional resolution expressing "gratitude to law enforcement officers, including U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement personnel, for protecting the homeland." I didn't get a chance to ask any of them, but I'd wager they were also unhappy with McClain Delaney's vote for the Laken Riley Act calling on ICE to detain and deport immigrants arrested for—but not convicted of or even charged with—nonviolent offenses. Or her vote for a Republican-sponsored bill overturning the city of Washington, D.C.'s immigration laws and forcing its officials to cooperate with DHS and ICE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How You Should Vote in the New York City Democratic Party Primary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/how-you-should-vote-in-the-new-york-city-democratic-party-primary-4a25</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/how-you-should-vote-in-the-new-york-city-democratic-party-primary-4a25"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T19:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is NOT an endorsement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Good Marriage Plot Needs Real Stakes]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192613</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-good-marriage-plot-needs-real-stakes"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T19:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A romantic comedy often opens with a scene where the protagonist demonstrates that she's not like other girls. In Legally Blonde, that's Reese Witherspoon slipping her freshly painted toenails into wedge heels with a heart on them, before she heads out to the date that will ruin all her plans. In Pride & Prejudice (2005), that's Keira Knightley reading while she walks outside, and returning home to her chaotic family. In Materialists—the new Celine Song movie released over the weekend—Dakota Johnson applies lip gloss in a mirror and runs out onto the New York City streets, her high ponytail swinging. She passes a tall man, stops him, and offers him her card. She's a matchmaker named Lucy, and he's tall and rich and would be great for her clients.
But that's not the first scene in Materialists. The movie opens with a vast red-rocked canyon filling the screen. It is beautiful and immense. Then we watch a long-haired prehistoric man chop a bushel of daisies, put it into a backpack, and carry it to a cave where a woman waits for him. They do not speak. The man then twists the stem of one of the daisies into a ring and slips it onto the cave woman's left ring finger. Get it? It's not a diamond. It's just a flower. That's love, baby.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dodgers Innovate Watchable June Bullpen Game]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192616</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/shohei-ohtani-dodgers-pitching-return"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T18:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shohei Ohtani has not pitched in a game since 2023, when in addition to leading the league in all the cool batting stats he also struck out 11.4 per nine with a 1.061 WHIP in 23 starts. I was a witness to one of them.
On April 3, 2023, my now-ex and I had tickets to see Shohei. The Angels were bringing him to Seattle for a three-game series, and we weren't going to miss him. He did not disappoint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Bloom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lando Norris Fails To Find One Gap, Widens Another]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192610</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lando-norris-fails-to-find-one-gap-widens-another"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T17:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen, your two unfortunates of the past weekend: Lando Norris and local wildlife. The Circuit Gilles Villeneuve, host site of the Canadian Grand Prix, encircles an island in Montreal. It is a gorgeous circuit, featuring the close-hewn walls of a street race, a run through lush greenery rivaling even the aesthetics of the Circuit de Spa-Francorchamps, and marmots. Groundhogs, specifically, who have found a circuit raised upon their homes and stayed put, to infrequent risk of extreme bodily harm, i.e. decapitation or bisection.
On turn 13, Lewis Hamilton hit a groundhog that was on track with his Ferrari. The remainder of the groundhog stayed as debris on the track, shown a few times throughout the race. Hamilton was smartly not informed of this fact during the race, which, thanks to resulting floor damage and poor pit-stop timing, he spent largely treading water on an island in P6. The nature of automobiles leads to somewhat flippant and/or nervously hysterical reactions to loss of animal life—during the weekend's running of 24 Hours of Le Mans, the delirious night session commentators' processing of a local rabbit death included a (unobserved?) moment of silence and the term "derabbitized"—but the vegan Hamilton was naturally upset after the race. There may be a crude metaphor in there for how things are going at Ferrari this year, though it remains to be seen who exactly is the groundhog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, June 16: Swing Both Ways]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192657</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-june-16-swing-both-ways"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T16:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Look on the bright side: There's a new crossword for you to solve! This week's puzzle was constructed by Hanh Huynh and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Hanh is a bankruptcy attorney who lives in Brooklyn, N.Y. with his wife and two kids.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE. Note that our submissions are closed through July 31.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[J.J. Spaun’s Last Shot Was The Shot Of His Life]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192627</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/j-j-spauns-last-shot-was-the-shot-of-his-life"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T16:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Open is a notoriously difficult tournament even under normal circumstances, but forcing professional golfers to play in the kind of weather that tormented the greater Pittsburgh area on Sunday was a televised exercise in humiliation. Battling relentless rain that essentially gave Sunday's action an extended halftime break, contending players like Adam Scott and Sam Burns sunk themselves with final-round scores of 78 and 79 respectively, as a course saturated with water worked to make their lies as miserable as possible. To put golfers in these conditions is like trying to make Sabrina Ionescu shoot threes in a wind tunnel, or Harry Kane take a penalty with a ball made of lead. It stops being about "Who's the best?" and starts being about "Who can survive?"

https://bsky.app/profile/jm539581.bsky.social/post/3lroojuwuy22j]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals Have Lost Cole Ragans for Awhile]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=465990</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/the-royals-have-lost-cole-ragans-for-awhile/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T15:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 27-year-old lefty, an AL All-Star last year, could miss months with a rotator cuff strain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Jaffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Melissa Hortman Didn’t Play Republican Games]]></title>
        <id>68502533c602f50001a83702</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/melissa-hortman-didnt-play-republican-games/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T15:13:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hortman was unbending in her advocacy for a more free and fair United States. For that she was killed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Sox Fans Chopped Up And Cooked On The Hot Stove]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192590</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/red-sox-fans-chopped-up-and-cooked-on-the-hot-stove"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T14:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the Red Sox closed out their three-game series at home against the Yankees on Sunday afternoon, spirits were high. The win made for a sweep of their division rivals and put the Red Sox half a game back of a wild card spot. A middling rotation haunted Boston for much of the season and especially in early June, but now they’d won on the strength of their pitching, which held Yankees bats to four total runs all weekend. 
At the start of the week, Roman Anthony, the top prospect in baseball, joined Kristian Campbell and Marcelo Mayer in the big leagues to complete the arrival of the team’s long-awaited ‘Big Three’ prospect trio. If these young, promising lads weren’t exactly contributing “hits” as they adjusted to MLB pitching, they still kept the vibes all nice and hopeful. It doesn't get much better than this, some fathers and their children celebrating at Fenway may have thought, as they watched Rafael Devers clobber an insurance solo homer onto the ledge of the Green Monster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finals Good As Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192583</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/finals-good-as-hell"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T14:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a defensible reading of Game 4 of the NBA Finals as an aesthetic disappointment, a slugfest of a game defined by Bennedict Mathurin missing a bunch of free throws in the final minute and the Oklahoma City Thunder shooting a collective 3-for-16 from three-point range and recording a collective 11 assists, both season lows. Certainly, if you wanted to read the game through the lens of individual offensive brilliance, you'd find the text lacking, though to do so would be to voluntarily step back from the bleeding edge of basketball. Game 4 was not only the best game of what has been a great series, but a klaxon from the future, the highest-level example of the sort of collective, pure-pressure hoops that's been the story of this season.
The ghastly 3-for-16 figure is an instructive place to start, as it is an extremely aberrant statistic. What it shows is not so much a Thunder offense that played poorly, but a Pacers defense that strung together a near-perfect night of defense. The most thoughtfully articulated concerns about the ubiquity of the three-pointer in modern NBA basketball arrive at the point that the three makes NBA offense fundamentally unstoppable, the spatial advantages of parking a bunch of guys on the perimeter rendering the game into a mere shooting contest. The defense played by both the Pacers and the Thunder makes a mockery of that assertion, as both units managed to shut down the opponents' long-range shooting without surrendering open looks at the rim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Orlando Magic Have Acquired A Big Dog]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192589</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-orlando-magic-have-acquired-a-big-dog"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T13:12:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first big trade of the NBA offseason arrived yesterday, and it was one that no one saw coming: Memphis Grizzlies shooting guard Desmond Bane has been shipped off to the Orlando Magic in exchange for Kentavious Caldwell-Pope, Cole Anthony, and four unprotected first-round picks.
Four first-round picks for a guy who as never made an all-star tea—shhhhh. I am going to keep my index finger pressed to your lips until you finish hearing what I have to say: Yes, a bushel of first-round picks is the kind of thing you expect to see included in a trade package for a real-deal superstar, which Bane is not. But to call this an overpay by the Magic would be to ignore how deals actually get done in the NBA. Players of a certain status are able to heavily influence and in some cases entirely dictate their own movements in the trade market, meaning that if a team like Orlando wants to hoard a pile of first-round picks until a true franchise savior becomes available to them, they are likely to be sitting on those picks forever. You can only play in the corner of the market that's available to you, and Orlando found a big prize in theirs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thank God Jalen Brunson And Josh Hart Are Kind Of Boring]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192331</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/thank-god-jalen-brunson-and-josh-hart-are-kind-of-boring"/>
        <updated>2025-06-15T20:35:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wasn't sure what to expect when I started listening to Roommates, the gambling-sponsored podcast hosted by New York Knicks Jalen Brunson and Josh Hart. My familiarity with the two is recently acquired—a friend introduced me to them and their fellow Villanova alumni Mikal Bridges and Donte DiVincenzo back during the headiest days of the "Nova Knicks" phenomenon, before DiVincenzo was traded to the Minnesota Timberwolves for Karl-Anthony Towns. Admittedly, my interest waned once the quartet became a trio. But that was before the Knicks entered the playoffs and New York City exploded.
Seemingly overnight, the city was covered in blue and orange. Suddenly, I couldn't go to the gym without someone uttering phrases that might as well have been code: pick-and-roll, bing bong, double overtime, Reggie Miller. If I'm being honest, it wasn't until the Knicks started their third playoff series against the Pacers that I finally understood that Game 5 is actually closer to Game 20 for these players. But by the time my older brother told me he was planning to come to New York if the Knicks won the whole thing, my curiosity had officially been piqued.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protests Big]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192510</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/protests-big"/>
        <updated>2025-06-15T16:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All across the United States and beyond on Saturday, millions of people got together and expressed—to put it in probably the most broadly acceptable terms to everyone who went—that Donald Trump needs to get out of everybody's business. Coming after days of anti-ICE protests in Los Angeles, as the community there fights to protect immigrants from kidnapping and torture, the "No Kings" demonstrations contrasted with a dull, dorky military parade Trump held for his own amusement on the same day in Washington D.C.
Protesters in Los Angeles, specifically, faced yet more violence from police, who charged at a crowd on horseback, beat people with batons, fired projectiles, and used tear gas. In Minnesota, protesters gathered after that day's assassination of Democratic state Rep. Melissa Hortman and attempted killing of Democratic state Sen. John Hoffman by a person, still at large, who allegedly impersonated a police officer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Panther Machine Never Breaks]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192507</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/panther-machine-never-breaks"/>
        <updated>2025-06-15T15:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brad Marchand. Again. As if the Florida Panthers taking a 3-2 series lead in front of a passionate Edmonton Oilers crowd wasn't brutal enough, it had to be the NHL's premier pest who orchestrated the 5-2 win in Game 5 on Saturday night. After scoring the team's last two goals in Game 2's OT win and following that up with the play that kicked off a blowout in Game 3, the 37-year-old trade deadline pickup from Boston scored Nos. 9 and 10 of his playoffs to help the Panthers to within one win of their second straight Stanley Cup. All Edmonton could do in response is curse him and pray for two straight victories.
With Game 4's exhilarating comeback win, the Oilers took back home-ice advantage in this series, and the fans flaunted it with a beautiful "O Canada" singalong before puck-drop. But what followed was pretty depressing from start to finish, and it began with Marchand's opening goal 10 minutes into the first, which came from pure hustle and speed. Watching a face-off after an out-of-play, Marchand pounced on what was technically a Draisaitl win before any other Oilers could get to the puck. He was so quick, and in such good position, that he instantly eliminated most of the opposing skaters from the play. Taking the puck right down the middle, he swerved around one defenseman and protected himself from the other, lasering a shot high on a Calvin Pickard that had gone low.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trevor Richards Elects Free Agency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=855707</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/06/trevor-richards-elects-free-agency.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-14T15:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that right-hander Trevor Richards has become a free agent after clearing outright waivers.  Kansas City designated Richards for assignment earlier this week, and since he has been previously outrighted in his career, Richards had the ability to reject an outright assignment to Triple-A in favor of re-entering the open market. As a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mechanical learning / Man of Steel]]></title>
        <id>684c48fb475bb700010ae600</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-340/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T23:56:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Misha Angrist on the allure of AI; Sam Thielman and Joe MacLeod nerd out on Superman]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suspended Sentence]]></title>
        <id>684cac65475bb700010ae763</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/suspended-sentence/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T23:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fifteen years ago I taught a freshman seminar entitled “The Secret of Life: DNA, Property Rights, and Human Identity.” We read What is Life? by Erwin Schrödinger, The Double Helix, and a brand-new book called The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks. We watched Jeff Goldblum portray]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Misha Angrist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PODCAST Round Table! Episode 10: Supernerds]]></title>
        <id>684c982d475bb700010ae6e1</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/podcast-round-table-episode-10-supernerds/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T23:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Thielman flies in to the podcast studio to discuss his recent Flaming Hydra post My Ten Favorite Superman Stories with Joe MacLeod.
Listen on Apple/Spotify/RSS/plus more options at pod.link

Episode 10: Supernerds
Joe MacLeod and Sam Thielman discuss Sam’s Flaming Hydra]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Thielman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angels Call Up Christian Moore As Infield Crisis Counselor]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192457</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/angels-call-up-christian-moore-as-infield-crisis-counselor"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T21:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2025 Angels have been startlingly okay thus far. Mike Trout hasn't looked himself and is currently the everyday DH, but he's been doing better lately. The various castoffs that make up the rotation are mostly pitching acceptably, and the franchise's strategy of immediately calling up their '22 and '23 first rounders has looked real smart. Continuing this philosophy, on Friday the club called up their 2024 first rounder, second baseman Christian Moore.
Normally, when a team brings a highly touted 22-year-old to the show, you can write something about him like "this guy's been tearing up the minors." But Moore's stats are actually pretty startling. He's striking out 27 percent of the time down there. And his defense has been terrible. What is Perry Minasian thinking? Well, when he looks at his infield, what he's probably thinking is Oh no. Here's a rundown of the Angels' non-Moore infielders this season. They've been, well, unique. In order of plate appearances:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Bloom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stick With ‘Dept. Q’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192468</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/stick-with-dept-q"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T17:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s been this ongoing concern, I mean like in the air, for a while now, about people’s attention spans. I find it even creeping into my conversations. "Is this boring?" I'll ask a few minutes into a story. "Am I boring you?" People usually laugh and say something like, You'll know if I'm bored. But I never used to do that. I never used to be self-conscious about, I don't know, wasting time? I was listening to a podcast recently and Loyle Carner, this British musician, mentioned how grateful he was that this author he had read had basically summarized her whole book in the first chapter, because even when he has every good intention, he won't always finish the entire thing. He sounded sheepish about it. I don't know why. The fact that he reads is rare enough, right? 
"Stick with it," my brother said when I started watching Dept. Q. "It's a slow burn." I mean, that's one way to put it. The first episode of Dept. Q is a SLOG. I was really excited going in—a Scottish show about a basement-dwelling trio of cold-case detectives starring a scruffy Matthew Goode and the amazing-faced actress Kate Dickie as his long-suffering boss? Yes, it sounds a little like Slow Horses, but how is that a bad thing? But then I started watching it and thought: Is this an assignment? This show looks like no one wants to be here, down to the set designer. Goode is phoning it in, the flashbacks are excessive, the pacing is so glacial it's basically stagnant. It was all so ... uninspiring, so generic, like someone fed "dark uk detective series" into an AI model. I couldn't figure out why this was happening: Did they not have much money? Was this Netflix's fault? I texted my brother midway through that first episode: "Are you using slow burn as a euphemism for boring?" He texted back: "Stick with it."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired Unaccompanied Children Ombuds]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191536</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-unaccompanied-children-ombuds"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T16:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Mary Giovagnoli was in law school, she spent a year working as a junior public defender representing people accused of misdemeanors. "I really liked the work, but it was emotionally devastating, because you got very wrapped up in your clients' cases," Giovagnoli said. She felt that only the prosecutors held real power; Giovagnoli would make her clients' cases, but the final decision was out of her hands. Then something clicked. "I realized that public service for me probably meant trying to be within the government to improve things," she said.
With this in mind, Giovagnoli became an attorney for the U.S. Immigration and Naturalization Service and spent the next two decades switching between jobs with the government and nonprofits, eventually focusing on the welfare of unaccompanied children, meaning any child under 18 who arrives in the United States without a parent or guardian. Since 1997, a legal settlement called the Flores agreement has enshrined basic rights and protections for children held in federal immigration custody. "The agreement acknowledged that children have unique needs and response and we have a unique responsibility to them," Giovagnoli said. "That the goal should not be to keep children in detention, but to release them to a family member as quickly and as safely as possible, keep them in as least restrictive a setting as possible."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Krabbe’s ‘The Rider’ Won Us Over By Losing]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192463</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tim-krabbes-the-rider-won-us-over-by-losing"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:48:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brandy: Let me start by saying thank you, Patrick, for picking this book. I enjoyed it enormously. I will also now immediately display ingratitude by ignoring what you said in your lovely introductory essay and say that I read this book as a metaphor. Specifically, it felt to me of a piece with another genre of slim, semi-autobiographical volume from a European writer: an account of a woman being driven to madness by an obsession for which she is willing to suffer, by which I mean, of course, being catastrophically in love with some guy. The way Krabbé is alternately so clear-eyed and willing to lie to himself, the debasement followed by the self-aggrandizement, the devotion unto despair… these all felt quite familiar to me as a fan of that other genre of book!
Kathryn: It’s funny, Brandy, because I also experienced it as a semi–psychological horror, though for the same reasons that Patrick mentions in his essay, in terms of how narrow the focus of the novel is on the act of competition. Absent projection or meaning-making, the emotional extremes of competitiveness wind up being so petty and ugly and ignoble—which is useful to be reminded of as I’ve gotten into more of the fucked up, suffering-based sports out there (tennis, the concept of Marc Márquez in MotoGP). Though I am also beginning to believe that cycling is just psychological horror.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michelle Cooper Is Always Ready To Pounce]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192447</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/michelle-cooper-is-always-ready-to-pounce"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:22:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michelle Cooper took her time. When Temwa Chawinga sent a slow ball to the space in front of her—a ball Chawinga only had because of a turnover Cooper had caused—she moved laterally with it, waiting for it to come across her body. She timed her steps and her shot perfectly. The moment she arrived to the ball was when she had maximum space from both Emily Sonnett and Ann-Katrin Berger, who were moving toward her from opposite directions. But once each piece was aligned—Berger and Sonnett out of the way, the ball on her preferred right foot, and her body faced up toward the net—she pounced. Without any superfluous touches, she slotted the ball inside the far post, past Berger’s desperate reach. 
She could afford to be patient. It was only the third minute of the match.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abigail Segel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Posts From The Glorious Future: How Texas Was Won]]></title>
        <id>684c3175c602f50001a82ba0</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/blog-posts-from-the-glorious-future-how-texas-was-won/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T14:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We faced terrible choices in the early days of the Great Redo. I was in charge of picking the least terrible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Had A Baby And Now I Can’t Read! What Do I Do?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192305</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-had-a-baby-and-now-i-cant-read-what-do-i-do"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T14:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Ask The Book Doctor, a recurring series about books and reading them.
It's natural to fall out of reading simply because of circumstance. Every time I am on vacation, I devour books—put me on a plane, any plane, and I'll finish a book. But plop me back in my normal life where the shelves are dusty and the groceries need to be bought and my friends are going to a bar after work, and the appeal of picking up a book diminishes. It is easy to allow yourself to build a world in your mind when you have space there. It is much harder to make the words on the page into pictures when your mind is far too busy with other obligations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calvin Pickard Saved The Day]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192412</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/calvin-pickard-saved-the-day"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T13:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Edmonton Oilers' maddening, decade-long goalie controversy is over ... for the next week, anyway. As that next week contains the entirety of what is now a best-of-three Stanley Cup Final, it feels like a mercy. Calvin Pickard, after two periods and most of an overtime of effective relief in Thursday's absurd 5–4 win, will be the man between the pipes, as there is simply not enough time left to survive any sort of disaster that might tempt head coach Kris Knoblauch to go back to Stuart Skinner.
This is not necessarily the ideal situation. (Say what you will about Sergei Bobrovsky and his contract and his very good but not elite play—there's something to be said for just not having to ever worry about the position.) It's certainly not a normal one for a team two wins from a Cup, to be still figuring out its best netminder. But nothing these Oilers do is normal. They became just the seventh team in NHL history, and the first since 2006 to come back from three goals down to win a Cup Final game. They became the first team ever to do it after digging that three-goal deficit in the first period. They couldn't have squirmed (clawing is for Panthers) back into it without Pickard. They might not have made it out of the first damn round.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oilers-Panthers Isn’t A Rivalry, It’s A Saga]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192435</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/oilers-panthers-isnt-a-rivalry-its-a-saga"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T13:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to figure out how Leon Draisaitl's game-winning goal found glory when it barely found 30 mph is a waste of your time. What you should be noticing instead in the wake of Edmonton's wonderfully absurdist 5–4 overtime victory over Florida in Game 4 of the Stanley Cup Final is how delightfully it fits into the broader theme these two teams have crafted over two seasons. Namely, that they are the perfectly weighted rivalry for our time: two teams that when they attempt to be their own best selves adhere to each other, separated only when one team or the other loses its way and tries to be the other team's opponent rather than the idealized version of itself.
So ignore for a moment the sheer dumb luck of Draisaitl's rush that resulted in a modest backhand that ever so slightly deflected off Florida defenseman Niko Mikkola and past Florida goaltender Bob. The result, which evened the series at two wins apiece, and the time, 11:36 p.m. Eastern Daylight Time, are the explanation. Well, unless you think Taylor Swift had something to do with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cole Ragans To Go For Second Opinion On Injured Shoulder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=855554</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/06/cole-ragans-to-go-for-second-opinion-on-injured-shoulder.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T02:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems the Royals will be without Cole Ragans for a while. Manager Matt Quatraro tells Anne Rogers of MLB.com that the lefty will go for a second opinion on his ailing shoulder next week. Kansas City placed Ragans on the 15-day injured list with a rotator cuff strain yesterday. Quatraro indicated that the team does…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young and free / Baby chimps]]></title>
        <id>684af4ece36b2c0001a46c39</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-339/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T22:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amy Chu on the Linda Lindas, and zoological conjectures with Jack Pendarvis. Plus HYDRANYM voting!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, The Sky Is Falling For The Sky]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192192</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/yes-the-sky-is-falling-for-the-sky"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T21:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watch basketball games for a living and you develop a certain tolerance for garbage—a fondness, even. Bad teams make visible all the neat and complicated parts of the sport. In an “I can fix them” sort of way, these teams are sometimes the most endearing. It's hard to look at even the WNBA’s worst without finding something to grasp, some little thread of hope. 
Alas, I’m drawing a blank with the Chicago Sky, who are 2-6, both of those wins over the league-worst 1-10 Dallas Wings. In retrospect, the Sky’s disastrous start to the season makes perfect sense. An offense that ranked near the bottom of the league in 2024 lost its leading scorer in the offseason. At the trade deadline last year, it also lost its second-best scorer. The Sky locker room might be more functional for the absence of Chennedy Carter and Marina Mabrey, but the two of them did score points! It is also a team theoretically built to feature two non-shooting bigs, one of whom is currently the league’s worst finisher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hydranym No. 3: Vote!]]></title>
        <id>684ae424e36b2c0001a46c03</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hydranym-no-3-vote/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T21:35:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE VICTOR OF HYDRANYM NO. 3 will ascend from this flock of the 21 most scintillating entries received this week, as judged by the editors. Consider well, and make your choice.
It won’t be easy! these are superexcellent entries.
HYDRANYM is a word game for Flaming Hydra subscribers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ace Goes to Hollywood: Episode 7]]></title>
        <id>684ae685e36b2c0001a46c0f</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/ace-goes-to-hollywood-episode-7/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T21:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ace Goes to Hollywood is a continuing transcript of a ride from Oxford, Mississippi, to Memphis, Tennessee, during which Jack Pendarvis interviewed Ace Atkins about his work on the Pauly Shore film Jury Duty.
Episode 7: Tortoises and Chimps
JACK: Oh! The reason I mentioned earlier, when I was, like,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Pendarvis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Girling and Growing Up]]></title>
        <id>684b2c62e36b2c0001a46d08</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/girling-and-growing-up/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T21:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amy Chu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone’s Changing So Much]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/everyone-s-changing-so-much-8fb9</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/everyone-s-changing-so-much-8fb9"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T21:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intrigued AND demure? ¿En esta economia?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Let Drew Cook]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192322</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/we-let-drew-cook"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T19:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last fall, Defector R&D announced another paradigm-disrupting plan for Year 5. We would once again run a Tip Jar drive to top off our Pay Forward A Subscription fund, but this time we’d give one lucky entrant the opportunity to have Drew Magary come cook them a meal. We drew that winner in early December, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monorail: Origins, With Alan Siegel]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192270</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/monorail-origins-with-alan-siegel"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T19:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is not a boast and not an apology, but simply an assertion of fact: I could be awakened from a deep sleep, abducted from public transit, or otherwise put under extreme duress and still happily be able to talk about The Simpsons for a solid hour. I am fortunate, I think, that my youth overlapped with a period of time during which The Simpsons was basically the wildest and most innovative television programming that anyone had ever seen. I write "I think," there, because I am aware that all those bits and songs and in-jokes are taking up space in my brain that might otherwise be occupied by, say, "things I learned in college." Still, I can't say I really regret it. If you have to fill your brain up with anything, it might as well be the funniest stuff that's ever been on TV.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metallica Is Forever]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192313</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/metallica-is-forever"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T17:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was a time in my youth where the anticipation of a concert was better than the concert itself. I saw a whole lot of incredible acts back then, but my memories of those shows are largely confined to their buildup. I remember waiting for hours—in a line that wrapped around the local Dayton’s department store—to score tickets to Van Halen, feeling like a prince when I reached the window and they still had seats left. I remember the giant, Hysteria-themed scrim that shielded Def Leppard’s in-the-round stage, and the band, from view before they went on. I remember standing on the main floor before a Poison concert with my friend Tony, gawking at all the women in attendance who had dressed themselves with the intent to score an invite backstage. Great moment to be a ninth grader.
Above all else, I remember the excitement. The electrical current inside of my body, growing to a crescendo as showtime drew nearer and nearer. The energy I intuited from everyone else in the arena as we endured the wait for the headliner to take the stage. The music blasting through the PA that kept getting louder and louder, to prime everyone for the real thing. And finally, the lights going off and all of us breaking into a spontaneous roar, a roar so loud that I couldn’t hear my own screams through it. I remember all of that, and in some ways that’s enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Whole NBA Is Telling James Dolan To Piss Off]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192337</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-whole-nba-is-telling-james-dolan-to-piss-off"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T17:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is visible in most coaching searches is largely iceberg-ish in nature, in that we see 10 percent of the process and then, mostly out of self-aggrandizement, measure it at 90 percent from there. But let's play the game anyway and laugh the fit of our trousers off at the number of teams that have received requests from the New York Knicks to talk to their coaches about a new job and responded with an emphatic "Shove off, Guitar Boy."
To date, Dallas, Minnesota, Houston, and Atlanta have all refused Knicks chief ball guy Leon Rose and owner Jimmy Dolan permission to discuss their vacancy with, in order, Jason Kidd, Chris Finch, Ime Udoka, and Quin Snyder. Of those four, Atlanta's refusal was described as "emphatic." One presumes that is code for "shove off," but it could have been “no way,” “get bent,” or something more profane. Possibly much more profane. Again, there’s just so much about this process that is invisible to the public.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why ‘The Rider’ Is The Best Sports Book I’ve Ever Read]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191857</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-the-rider-is-the-best-sports-book-ive-ever-read"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T16:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sports are simple. That is perhaps their most crucial property, the attribute that makes sports interesting to write and read about yet simultaneously makes doing so depend, to greater or lesser degrees, on mistranslation. The French Open final, an afternoon Golden State Valkyries game, Stage 20 of the Giro d'Italia: These are all rich texts that can be mined for pathos, meaning, and critical perspectives on gender, pan-European identity in the 21st century, or whatever, but at their core, none of them are "about" anything larger than their competitive structure. The games happen on their own terms and are projected outward for us, the non-competing public, to contextualize them as we see fit. But what is lost in any such act of projection?
That's one of the questions raised and dealt with in Tim Krabbe's The Rider, a work that achieves transcendence via fidelity. Krabbe's semi-autobiographical novel, translated from the Dutch by Sam Garrett, is extremely simple. He tells the story of the Tour de Mount Aigoual, "the sweetest, toughest race of the season," taking the reader kilometer-by-kilometer through the race, using its climbs, weather systems, and intrapeloton dynamics as entry points to write about the theory, practice, and what could fairly be characterized as the esoteric mysticism of road cycling. Krabbe is a somewhat tragic figure, a chess player who only became a rider in his early 30s, someone who had the talent to win more frequently and at a higher level than he ever was able to but started too late to be anything more than a very good amateur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Wilson Was The Sound of Something Just Out Of Reach]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192296</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/brian-wilson-was-the-sound-of-something-just-out-of-reach"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T15:29:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's impossible for me to think about Brian Wilson, who died on Wednesday, without picturing myself awake in my teenage bedroom at some sort of goblin hour. I still have very late nights, but they look a lot different—healthier, more organized. If I lose sleep now, it's because I'm so busy. If I lost a lot of sleep then, it was ... well, I guess you'd just call it anxiety. I wouldn't be able to sit still, or relax my brain, because my body just didn't want to shut off. I'd write jittery little poetry in my notebook, and pace around what little space I had, and listen to the Beach Boys.
I don't remember a specific moment where I was introduced to them, but at some point in my teen years, as I developed both taste in music and an interest in drugs, I got a burned-CD copy of Pet Sounds. Rounding out the collection soon after was the download of a sprawling Beach Boys greatest hits album from the library, and a more questionably obtained digital copy of The Smile Sessions, a big set devoted to the almost mythical, partially failed studio work that followed up the band's arrival on the absolute cutting edge of modern pop. That was my Beach Boys canon, and there were a few tracks in particular that I'd cycle through again and again when it felt like nobody else was awake. "Surf's Up," a delicate piano ballad that flips the whole fun-loving simplicity of the group's signature tunes on its head. "Caroline, No," a plaintive longing for eternal love. And of course, "God Only Knows," this divine wind that blows into your ears and leaves you (or at least me) forever changed, stunned by the possibility of melody and arrangement. I'd listen to these and write, but maybe more often I'd listen and just focus intently on them, my unslowing brain wrapping itself around every note. Hearing Wilson's songs, I felt separate from the world I knew.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Wilson Was A Sad Genius Who Brought Joy To The World]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192266</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/brian-wilson-was-a-sad-genius-who-brought-joy-to-the-world"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T13:39:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Wilson, the guy behind some of the happiest sad songs in pop history, is dead. 
Take “Wouldn’t It Be Nice,” which I’d say is my favorite Beach Boys tune if you asked me right now, the day after Wilson died at 82 years old. The song, the first track from Pet Sounds, the band's peerless 1966 album which Wilson produced, arranged, and wrote most of, finds a young man wanting more out of life and love than he’s getting, and hoping a day comes when he gets it.  Wouldn’t it be nice to be happy?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not So Funny When Someone’s Doing That Shit To You, Is It?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192283</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/not-so-funny-when-someones-doing-that-shit-to-you-is-it"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T13:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Indiana Pacers left the devil at home on Wednesday night. They didn't need him to beat the Oklahoma City Thunder, 116–107, and take a 2-1 lead in the NBA Finals.
Throughout these playoffs, the Thunder have always felt like the constant in the equation that makes up any one game. We could head into every game assured that the Thunder were A) going to apply immense pressure on the other team through physical and aggressive defensive play, and B) make plenty of room for Shai Gilgeous-Alexander to turn the screws at the other end with his shotmaking, driving, and foul-drawing. Those things always happening didn't necessarily mean that the Thunder would always win, but if they lost it was because an unexpected variable showed up somewhere else. Maybe the other team managed not to turn the ball over, or got unsustainably hot from three; maybe Mark Daigneault overthought his rotations or his late-game strategy; maybe someone hit a miracle shot at the buzzer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get together / Play a show]]></title>
        <id>6849fe08e36b2c0001a45676</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-338/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T00:32:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tommy Craggs on foxhole solidarity, and Rax King at the Dew Drop Inn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Hands]]></title>
        <id>6849f6f4e36b2c0001a4562e</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/all-hands/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T00:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first hour or so of Ryan Coogler’s Sinners is a classic of that unnamed but easily recognized film genre which we’ll call “the Squad Assembles.” We follow the Moore twins, both played by Michael B. Jordan, in and around Clarksdale, Mississippi, as they]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tommy Craggs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sexfaces Live in D.C.]]></title>
        <id>6849f7f0e36b2c0001a45646</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/sexfaces-live-in-d-c/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T00:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the sticky floor of Washington D.C.’s Dew Drop Inn, Sexfaces’ drummer/vocalist Jacky Cougar paused between songs to pay a touching tribute to Pere Ubu’s recently departed frontman David Thomas. “I hear he was kind of a prick,” Cougar said affably.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rax King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Place Cole Ragans On IL With Rotator Cuff Strain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=855374</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/06/royals-place-cole-ragans-on-il-with-rotator-cuff-strain.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T20:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced a series of roster moves today. Right-hander Lucas Erceg has been reinstated from the 15-day injured list and righty Jonathan Bowlan has been recalled from Triple-A Omaha. In corresponding moves, right-hander Trevor Richards has been designated for assignment while lefty Cole Ragans has been placed on the 15-day IL due to a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Psychiatric Nurse Whose Research Funding Was Cut By The Trump Administration]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191779</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-psychiatric-nurse-whose-research-funding-was-cut-by-the-trump-administration"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T19:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laura Mata López was born and raised in a low-income community in San José, Costa Rica. Some of her earliest memories were of the impact poverty and a lack of support for mental health had on her neighbors. Mata López's mother and grandmother had migrated to Costa Rica from Colombia during the Colombian civil war, severing them from their roots and family. For a period of time, Mata López's family was undocumented in Costa Rica, although their route to citizenship there was fairly easy. "Even then, I always had this identity of being a migrant and being an other," Mata López said.
When Mata López was 12 years old, she immigrated to New York City, where her mother cleaned houses. When she started school, Mata López became selectively mute, a condition she could not name at the time. She was overcome with a knot in her throat when her mom dropped her off at school, only regaining the ability to speak when she returned home and spoke with her family in Spanish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chicago Man Wears White Sox Cap To Work]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192237</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/chicago-man-pope-leo-xiv-wears-white-sox-cap-to-work"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T18:33:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pope Leo XIV celebrated his weekly general audience in St. Peter's Square this morning, so you might assume he donned a White Sox ballcap at the request of one of his parishioners. I think it much more likely he just wears this around all the time, even to formal events where it's entirely inappropriate. Have you met people from Chicago? He probably sold his mitre to buy a sandwich.
This fairly definitively puts to bed any lingering debate about which accursed Chicago franchise gets to claim the Pope, though the Cardinals and Padres could still make a case. In any event, the former Robert Prevost surely claims the White Sox—that is the face of a man who just heard that Jerry Reinsdorf might not sell the team until 2034.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats Should Simply Remove The Stumbling Block]]></title>
        <id>68498fd6d75ada00010709c9</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/democrats-should-simply-remove-the-stumbling-block/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T15:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no easy path to a free country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Party Sucks]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192184</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-party-sucks"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T15:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday, the Wall Street Journal published an op-ed by Arkansas Senator Tom Cotton under the headline "Tom Cotton: Send In The Troops, For Real." The piece was ostensibly written in response to the protests against the Trump administration's anti-immigrant crackdowns currently taking place in Los Angeles, and it argues that the administration should use an "overwhelming show of force" to put an end to the protests.
It's an odd piece of writing. For one thing, the troops have already been sent in—President Trump has sent National Guard troops and U.S. Marines to Los Angeles to guard federal buildings and ICE agents, against the wishes of California Governor Gavin Newsom. For another, the "show of force" has already happened—protestors have spent the last five days being beaten, arrested, tear-gassed, and shot with debilitating "less lethal" munitions. Taken on its own, it's hard to imagine what the editors of the WSJ opinion page might have expected moderately informed readers to gain from Cotton's piece, other than a vague sense of confusion and the less-vague sense that a United States Senator was upset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone Will Be Abuzz About The Season 8 Finale]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192196</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/everyone-will-be-abuzz-about-the-season-8-finale"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T15:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve made my fair share of terrible relationship decisions. There was the time my college sweetheart and I decided we would break up at the end of the semester, but stay together for the ensuing four months. There was the time I decided to date an ex of my nemesis. There was the time I decided it would be appropriate second-date behavior to light candles in every room my rental—in Tucson, in July, at 2:00 p.m. And then there was the time I agreed to an open relationship for the wrong reasons. 
This feels like something of a rite of passage for those of us on the dating scene in the last few decades. In this case, however, our friend-of-a-friend makes a similar decision under much stranger conditions: she’s the tag-along girlfriend of a guy doing a six-month apprenticeship at an internet-famous bee farm, which happens to be thrumming with socialism and polyamory. We’re thrilled to bring you this tale of sex and chaos as our season finale!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BWOOP BWOOP BWOOP! Now The Red Sox Have Summoned A Mighty Lad]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192124</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bwoop-bwoop-bwoop-now-the-red-sox-have-summoned-a-mighty-lad"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By at least one measure, the Boston Red Sox of 2025 are doing just fine. They've outscored their opponents on the season, modestly, but at a better clip than that of, say, the Philadelphia Phillies, who are presently nine games over .500 and slotted into the final National League wild card spot. Their lineup has been impressive, notwithstanding the lingering hurt feelings of a thoroughly jerked-around Rafael Devers: Boston ranks in the top six among all teams in batting average, on-base percentage, and slugging, yes with certain indications of batted-ball luck but nothing that would cause a Bostonian to assert any more than their usual dispensation of God's particular favor. Devers has been excellent; Carlos Narváez, Jarren Duran, and Ceddanne Rafaela have been productive; Kristian Campbell, a rookie, has cooled off some but has still performed pretty admirably for one who appears to be a lanky child. Alex Bregman has been an absolute stud.
By other measures, the Sox are feeling some mid-summer pressure. They're presently three games below .500, and are nine games back of the New York Yankees in their division, and are eighth in the wild card race, closer to the bottom than to the promised land. If the Baltimore Orioles were not cursed dog-doo, the Red Sox would almost certainly be last in the American League East, which incidentally is where they finished in consecutive seasons before seeming to take a step forward with 81 wins in 2024. This is not really a roster constructed to contend for a World Series, but the Red Sox have now hit a point in their rebuilding project where they will need to show some definite signs of seriousness in order to prove that they are not just settled into a condition of mediocrity, or worse. A fourth-place finish and 76-odd wins will be hard to explain as anything other than a stall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rime Of The Big Dumper, Or How And In What Manner Cal Raleigh Became A Bonafide Slugger]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191932</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-rime-of-the-big-dumper-or-how-and-in-what-manner-cal-raleigh-became-a-bonafide-slugger"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cal "Big Dumper" Raleigh is an outlier in the obvious sense—he is the current MLB home run leader—but pile on the descriptive adjectives, and you wind up with an amalgam of three truths, all theoretically past their prime: Cal Raleigh is a switch-hitting catcher who plays for the Mariners. Somehow, he is still the current MLB home run leader by a not-insignificant margin of two, his 26 homers beating out names like Aaron Judge and Shohei Ohtani. Per traditional standards, he is slashing a very respectable .264/.370/.632. Throw in some adjusted metrics, and he has a 182 wRC+, which is to say 82-percent better than the average MLB hitter, which is to say, the second-best player in baseball, beating out names like Freddie Freeman and Shohei Ohtani. Raleigh has, so far, cared not for the underpinnings of modern baseball. Where to even start? Perhaps in iambic tetrameter.
PART I: THE CONCEPT OF BEING A GOOD CATCHER]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High fly]]></title>
        <id>6848a5823897ec0001cddea0</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-337/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T23:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nathan Munn trips the balls fantastic; a new HYDRANYM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HYDRANYM No. 3]]></title>
        <id>6848b0b33897ec0001cddf52</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hydranym-no-3/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T23:29:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A word game just for Flaming Hydra subscribers.
Subscribe to Flaming Hydra to play! It's bizarrely fun, plus you get to read the newsletter each weekday AND participate in the Comments Section?! A STEAL for just $3/month, or $36/year.
RULES
Please create an ENTERTAINING and APT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Bustillos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My First Acid Trip]]></title>
        <id>684892783897ec0001cdde56</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/my-first-acid-trip/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T23:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nick and I were sitting in the basement of his parents’ house, waiting for Tim. Amid the storage boxes, pairs of skis, and miscellaneous furniture, an area had been cleared for a TV, a coffee table and a couple of couches, all anchored together on a thick rug. Tonight,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Munn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Think This Is The Best Catch I’ve Ever Seen]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192126</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-think-this-is-the-best-catch-ive-ever-seen"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T22:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is the nature of a really good catch to make you feel like what you've just seen is the coolest thing ever to happen. That is how you know that what you've just seen is really good, and you can tell that you have seen something sufficiently cool if, for a moment, you find yourself reconsidering everything else you've seen. A great play should disorient you; a really great one will feel as if it was dropped on you from a great height.
There is a whole disordered way of being a sports fan that is built around following that natural instinct to reconsider everything all the way out, and into recursive madness; at every game you attend, there will be thousands of other people there whose relationship with sports amounts to constantly rearranging the faces on their own personal Mounts Rushmore and updating and itemizing a detailed personal taxonomy of Signature Moments. As a general rule, I think it is better not to be like that, and to just let the awe overtake you when and where it finds you. Not because it is smarter or more reasonable; no one cares about sports to become smarter or more reasonable. Just because it is more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Megan Greenwell On Living Under And Outside Of Private Equity, The Invasive Species Eating American Life]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192046</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/megan-greenwell-on-living-under-and-outside-of-private-equity-the-invasive-species-eating-american-life"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T19:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fact that you are never quite as safe as you should be is one of the facts of contemporary American life, although the nature of that hazard varies from one American to the next. An unreasoning horror at and fear of the unknown is at the heart of the nation's dominant political movement, and while much of that is bullshit—think of the seething, car-brained fear of The Cities And Their Crime that animates so much conservative media and agitates so many conservatives into full-spectrum derangement—there is also some truth to all that perceived hazard. That social anxiety generally tends to be directed towards big, cinematic threats, both because that sort of thing makes for better TV and because the actual forces that make American life precarious do that work much more quietly.
Few of those forces have done more damage, in relative secret, than the private equity firms that have spent the last few decades busily buying up and chewing through various American industries in relative secret are kind of abstract in comparison. What they have done, and what they do as a matter of course, is plenty brutal. It just isn't quite violent enough to rate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In This House We Believe Faith No More Is One Of The Most Important Bands In History]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192077</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/in-this-house-we-believe-faith-no-more-is-one-of-the-most-important-bands-in-history"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T18:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about the NBA, dogs, Los Angeles, and more.
Kurt:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Golden State Valkyries Are Beloved And Ahead Of Schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192058</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-golden-state-valkyries-are-beloved-and-ahead-of-schedule"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T17:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Golden State Valkyries coach Natalie Nakase sat down with ESPN for an interview shortly after her team's inaugural season began, the first question she fielded was an obvious one. What were her expectations? Her answer was honest, relatively optimistic, and riddled with coded ways to softly say the unavoidable: The Valks were probably going to lose a lot.
I was with her when she said, "It's going to take time," "Let's just get one percent better every single day," and "I just want them to play with joy," because expansion teams never win. Not in basketball, anyway, where individual star talent tends to be the one thing that matters. The last two teams to join the WNBA, Atlanta and Chicago, won four and five games, respectively, in their inaugural efforts. These Valkyries were all but explicitly constructed as a team of seat-warmers, here to give the front office an up-close look before this offseason's forthcoming free-agent apocalypse. They selected Lithuanian wing Juste Jocyte with their first-ever draft pick, yet she won't even play until next season. The roster is young, undersized, and extremely European ("I have to learn French is what I’ve learned," Nakase recently quipped to the Athletic.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brad Marchand Is Still A Royal Pain In The Ass]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192048</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/brad-marchand-is-still-a-royal-pain-in-the-ass"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T17:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the Panthers acquired Brad Marchand at the trade deadline, it kind of felt like putting a hat on a hat. Or a rat on a rat. This was a team already known and feared and hated for the way they relentlessly antagonized their opponents, and the division-leading defending champs had returned their top eight players by points from the previous campaign. It was unclear if Marchand, who'd just suffered an injury, would make all that much of a difference in his first stop outside of Boston. But even if he didn't, Florida could taunt the rest of the league with just his presence. Oh, you called us dirty before? What will you think when we join up with the Mad Licker Of The West End?
As a regular-season Panther, Marchand did indeed contribute little of note, getting two meaningless goals in the last three games before the playoffs. But in the postseason, the 37-year-old has proven a nuisance, a playmaker, and a devastating scorer. Across what might turn out to be the most important stretch of the Stanley Cup Final, from the end of Game 2 to the start of Game 3, Marchand seized the spotlight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is This An Era Of Cultural Stagnation?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191831</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/is-this-an-era-of-cultural-stagnation"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T16:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Listening Habits, a column where I share the music I’ve been fixated on recently.
There’s a profile of the Clipse in the latest issue of GQ. Timed to the imminent release of their long-awaited reunion album, Let God Sort Em Out—executive produced by Pharrell but no Chad Hugo—it’s full of little tidbits about Pusha T’s label drama and Malice’s long break from rap and all the things you might expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Will Never Be Another ‘WTF With Marc Maron’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191534</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/there-will-never-be-another-wtf-with-marc-maron"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T15:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I heard Marc Maron announce he was ending his podcast the way that I imagine he'd've wanted me to—while walking through my neighborhood in Los Angeles, through wired headphones, just a little too hopped up on caffeine. A younger version of Maron would have given an "Oh, come on!" to my caffeine source, a matcha latte, as opposed to Maron's preference, the strongest coffee possible. But longtime listeners know Maron also went through a tea phase (episode 949), so I like to think that the current version of Maron would let it slide.
I first listened to WTF with Marc Maron in October of 2010 (episode 117) because I heard This American Life host Ira Glass say that he had appeared on it. I was immediately hooked. I had simply never heard an interview like that one, with a host so engaged and a guest so honestly and openly themself. I binged as many as I could the following weekend while cleaning my apartment and told my long-distance boyfriend he had to start listening, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Panthers Are Having A Laugh]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=192004</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-panthers-are-having-a-laugh"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T12:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Well, definitely, the third period is an unraveling," Oilers coach Kris Knoblauch said, and he was underselling it in a nice little piece of dry coachspeak. Edmonton seized the opportunity of getting blown out to take out all their collected frustrations toward the Panthers, and they had plenty of those. That's sort of what the Panthers do. They make you very, very mad, and then you blow up, and then they mock you, because they're winning 6-1 and have a 2-1 lead in the Stanley Cup Final. Because Florida's means, mean as they are, have an end beyond agitation for its own sake. They want you to play their game. And they're better at it than you are.
This was the quintessential Florida Panthers playoff game. A true ass-kicking from 56 seconds on, when Brad Marchand punched home a loose puck after an offensive-zone faceoff. Panthers physicality led directly to Panthers goals, with no better illustration than Sam Bennett basically body-checking himself to a breakaway the other way, and the fourth Florida goal that gave this one official rout status.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Nourishing Hate Of Stephen Miller]]></title>
        <id>684721fcf28b5e0001e312ee</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/the-nourishing-hate-of-stephen-miller/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T11:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The devourer of hate is now in charge of creating the conditions for a military crackdown on the American public.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Outright Thomas Hatch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=854609</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/06/royals-designate-thomas-hatch-for-assignment.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T02:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TODAY: Hatch cleared waivers and was outrighted to the Royals’ Triple-A affiliate, as per the righty’s MLB.com profile page. JUNE 5: Between games of today’s doubleheader, the Royals made a roster move. Left-hander Cole Ragans, the scheduled starter for the second game, has been reinstated from the 15-day injured list. Right-hander Thomas Hatch has been…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bold explorers / Dangerous arguments]]></title>
        <id>6846ddecbb23340001442d6f</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-336/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T22:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Talia Lavin ventures into the cold! HYDRANYM victors... and Nathan Schneider on where true hope begins]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[None but Cowards]]></title>
        <id>6846d245bb23340001442d3e</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/none-but-cowards/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T22:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Agoraphobia comes in waves for me. When it’s better I can leave my house, even take car trips by myself. Sometimes I can be places alone—even, on occasion, crowded or large ones. 
When it’s bad, I can’t… do any of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Talia Lavin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antisemitism and the Unspeakable]]></title>
        <id>6846f749bb23340001442da9</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/antisemitism-and-the-unspeakable/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T22:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 12, 2001, Ward Churchill, a professor at the University of Colorado Boulder (where I now teach) published an essay about the terrorist attack that had taken place in New York the day before. With the subtitle “On the Justice of Roosting Chickens,” Churchill compared the 9/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Schneider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friends Forever]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/friends-forever-5c48</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/friends-forever-5c48"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T22:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But how do you feel on the inside?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cork Whoops Limerick, Proving Hurling Shootouts Aren’t Ass]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191990</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cork-whoops-limerick-proving-hurling-shootouts-arent-ass"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T21:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cork upset dynastic host Limerick at a sold-out Gaelic Grounds on Saturday on penalty shots to take the 2025 Munster hurling championship in the first final decided on penalty shots in the 147-year history of the annual provincial competition. With the win, Cork booked a spot in the semifinals of this year’s All-Ireland tournament. 
The match, a non-stop affair full of lead changes and roughhousing, was the latest in a string of instant classic playoff tilts the ancient Gaelic game has delivered fans in the last few years. After regulation and two overtimes, the score stood at Limerick 2-27, Cork 1-30, or 33 points apiece.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Wiggins Is The Key To Understanding OKC’s Revolutionary Depth]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191951</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/aaron-wiggins-is-the-key-to-understanding-okcs-revolutionary-depth"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T19:23:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the fun, mildly disorienting experiences inherent to watching the Oklahoma City Thunder is having to remember just how many guys they have. Were you aware that they traded five second-round picks last summer for a rookie from Weber State named Dillon Jones, and that Jones played 10 minutes a game this year? One would assume that the quality and level of OKC's depth would matter less as the playoffs progressed. While that is true in the sense that Jones and his cohort of deep bench-mates have been marginalized in the postseason, OKC is still dominating with their depth. Consider: Aaron Wiggins.
The fourth-year guard was critical for the Thunder off the bench in Game 2 of the Finals, logging 18 points in 21 minutes and finishing a team-high plus-24. Somewhat strangely for a bench player, the stuff Wiggins is good at is best-player stuff. His best and most important skill is three-point shooting, though he's far more than a shooter. He is 6-foot-6 with a plus wingspan; he's extremely athletic, if a little bit slight. Wiggins can drive, handle the rock in traffic, read scrambling defenses, and kick the ball out to open shooters. He has moves, and he uses them at the rim to make all sorts of impressive and impressively tough shots. Wiggins is a decent rebounder, never turns the ball over, and an active, pesky on-ball defender. The most important thing about Wiggins is that he doesn't have a weakness, not one that is all that damaging anyway. He dropped 41 and 14 on the Kings this year!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Queen Mia Scott Is A National Champion]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191934</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/my-queen-mia-scott-is-a-national-champion"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T18:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mia Scott is a menace to every team unlucky enough to face her. At third base, she's an immovable object and a nightmare for all right-handed batters. In the batter's box, she demonizes opposing pitching. Over the three games of the NCAA Softball World Series last week, Scott hit a whopping .529 with two home runs.
In the third game of the WCWS, Scott came up to bat with the bases loaded and no outs, her Texas Longhorns already up 6-0. The Texas Tech pitcher whipped the ball toward her without enough rise or movement. It just sat there above the plate, and Scott's hands flew at it so fast you could barely see the bat make contact in real time. She dropped the bat behind her and trotted to first base, because that gorgeous highlighter-yellow ball was soaring way out to center field, past the 220 sign, and into the stands: a grand slam, in what might have been the very last game of her career.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Hill Has June 15 Opt-Out In Royals Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=855042</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/06/rich-hill-has-june-15-opt-out-in-royals-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T18:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran left-hander Rich Hill signed a minor league deal last month. It appears the club will soon have to make a decision on whether or not to call him up. Robert Murray of FanSided reports that there’s a June 15th opt-out in that deal. Since signing that pact, Hill has made four minor league starts,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nuno Mendes Made The Nations League Worth The Hassle]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191905</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nuno-mendes-made-the-nations-league-worth-the-hassle"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T18:31:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nations League is, at its core, a money grab. Replacing international friendlies with an ostensibly meaningful tournament is a sensible idea on paper, but UEFA's (and later CONCACAF's) main motivation for it was to wring more money out of the previously low-stakes, low-interest midseason international breaks. When taken in that context, it's easy to dismiss the tournament as yet another monument to soccer's ruling powers' insatiable greed.
Since the competition itself has no historical relevance and little actual prestige, the attempts to juice these matches with Significance scan as pretty silly. An example: The Nations League semifinal between France and Spain was billed as a head-to-head showdown between Ousmane Dembélé and Lamine Yamal, two of last season's most outstanding players, for no less than the Ballon d'Or itself. This is the type of pre-match hype that the Nations League, by its very existence, demands. It's not important enough on its own, so there must be a manufactured narrative to make it matter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Terminated Analyst At The Substance Abuse And Mental Health Administration]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191538</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-terminated-analyst-at-the-substance-abuse-and-mental-health-administration"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T17:36:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joy Binion learned that she had lost her job as a social science analyst at the Substance Abuse and Mental Health Services Administration, or SAMHSA, on April 1. So she posted on Facebook that she had been affected by a reduction in force, or RIF. A month later in a conversation with a friend, Binion mentioned the fact that she had lost her job. He reacted in total shock. "I thought that was an April Fool's joke," Binion's friend said of her Facebook post.
SAMHSA (pronounced sam-sah), which is housed under the Department of Health and Human Services, might not be a familiar acronym to most people. The agency supports Americans who suffer from mental health conditions and who experience addiction. SAMHSA operates the 988 Suicide & Crisis Lifeline, which has received more than 14.5 million calls, texts, and messages since it launched in July 2022. The agency also assists communities with grants for treatment and recovery centers, especially in rural areas where long distances from treatment centers act as a barrier to recovery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Battle For Professional Volleyball Has Officially Begun]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191901</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-battle-for-professional-volleyball-has-officially-begun"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Megan Courtney-Lush was ready to retire. She played four years of college volleyball at Penn State and then went on to play professionally in Puerto Rico, Poland, Turkey, and Italy. After 10 years, she had decided that it was time to come home and move on to the next stage of her life. She bought a house in Columbus, Ohio and was several months pregnant in 2023 when she got an unexpected phone call. Someone was starting a professional women's volleyball league in the U.S., and they wanted her to play. "I said 'No thanks, I'm out,'" she told me, laughing.
But the calls kept coming. Columbus would have a team, they told her, coached by Ángel Pérez, former captain of the Puerto Rican men's national team. Pérez called Courtney-Lush himself, trying to see if he could get her on the court, and she kept looking for excuses to stay home: "I played hardball. I kept coming up with all these random things I would need and they kept saying yes." Four months after having her first child, Courtney-Lush found herself back on the volleyball court, playing in the first active professional women's volleyball league in the United States since 1989.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rose Eveleth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, June 9: Yes, Chef!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191918</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-june-9-yes-chef"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you can't handle the heat, don't try our Monday crossword. This week’s puzzle was constructed by Rebecca Goldstein and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Rebecca is a research scientist and crossword constructor in the Bay Area. She is also a co-director of Westwords, a crossword tournament taking place in Berkeley, Calif., and online on June 22.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Don’t Speak Connor McDavid]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191891</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/we-dont-speak-connor-mcdavid"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T14:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have spent all weekend replaying and marveling over Connor McDavid's assist. Between me and McDavid, that makes one of us who spent any time thinking about it.
The Oilers star was at practice yesterday, two days after his absurd first-period carve-up was relegated from pivotal play to mere highlight-reel staple by the Panthers' eventual double-overtime victory. The unwritten rules of postgame press conferences dictate that questions won't dwell on a play that ended up not affecting the game's outcome, especially for the losing team, and McDavid wouldn't have wanted to talk about it on Friday anyway—the usual blank-faced captain's deflections would'n't have made good copy. But I was hopeful, at Sunday's skate and media availability, that McDavid might've moved on from the loss and been willing to walk us through exactly what was in his mind when he did this:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Cuomo Is Garbage]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191874</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/andrew-cuomo-is-garbage"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T13:37:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter.
As a voter in the New York City mayoral race, I keep thinking about the rats and the garbage cans. The story of the election, as generally framed, is that Andrew Cuomo has come down to New York from the suburbs and back from political exile to offer his own hard-nosed, practical experience as an alternative to a field of candidates who are some combination of too idealistic, too leftist, or too unseasoned to handle the serious business of running a great and difficult metropolis. The city, he declared in Wednesday's mayoral debate, is in a "management crisis"—as well as a "fiscal crisis" and a "societal crisis"—and he is the one person who is prepared and willing to take on "dysfunctional city management."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shai Gilgeous-Alexander Can Make Anyone Look Bad]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191871</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/shai-gilgeous-alexander-can-make-anyone-look-bad"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T12:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shai Gilgeous-Alexander was, during the competitive portion of a not-very-competitive Game 2, about as good as it is possible to be at the sport of basketball. There was an insanely cool sequence in the first half where he seemed to take a horse-hair bow and go fiddle mode on the superstrings of reality. It started with a glaring mismatch. The Thunder were up a point inside the final minute of the first quarter, and the floor was out of shape, with Andrew Nembhard switched onto Isaiah Hartenstein, Aaron Nesmith sagging off of Alex Caruso in the corner, and Gilgeous-Alexander guarded up near the arc by Thomas Bryant, a backup center. An appalling 16 seconds were left on the shot clock, an eternity for a bumbling big guy like Bryant to spend isolated against the game's very best shot creator…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carlos Alcaraz Wins The Match Of A Lifetime]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191809</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/carlos-alcaraz-wins-the-match-of-a-lifetime"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T21:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A match that perfect deserves no restraint, so: Carlos Alcaraz's 4–6, 6–7 (4), 6–4, 7–6 (3), 7–6 (10–2) French Open final victory over Jannik Sinner is the best tennis match I've ever watched, and one of the greatest sporting events you or I will probably ever have the privilege of witnessing. You do not have to know or care about tennis or either of these players or even sports to find something to love about this match. All you need is a body, to appreciate the limits each player overcame out there on the red clay, and a spirit, to appreciate how deep they each had to dig to reach a place no pair has ever gone at Roland Garros.
The five-hour, 29-minute marathon saw the duo break all manner of records. Alcaraz saved three match points, the first time anyone's ever done so en route to the title. The final was nearly 45 minutes longer than the previous longest French Open final and 24 minutes short of the 2012 Australian Open decider for the longest major final in the open era. Alcaraz had never come back from two sets down, and Sinner had never lost a major final. Neither player had, for that matter. The 12th meeting between Sinner and Alcaraz was comfortably the best, clearing the lofty bar they set three years ago at the U.S. Open.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If I Were The Oklahoma City Thunder, I Would Simply Sustain A Lead All The Way To The End Of Game 2]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191816</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/if-i-were-the-oklahoma-city-thunder-i-would-simply-sustain-a-lead-all-the-way-to-the-end-of-game-2"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T20:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oklahoma City led for all but scant moments of Game 1 of the NBA Finals. For around 39 seconds of the first quarter, the score sat at 10–10, between an Andrew Nembhard three-pointer that tied it for Indiana and a floater from Shai Gilgeous-Alexander that untied it and put the Thunder ahead. Oklahoma City kept that lead until Tyrese Haliburton's game-winning jumper with 0.3 seconds left to play. For much of that time, the Thunder led by double digits, or at least by a handful of possessions' worth of baskets.
Likewise, for much of that time, particularly in the first half, Oklahoma City's half-court offense just kind of didn't matter: Between the advantages the Thunder got by running off of Indiana's copious turnovers and misses, and Gilgeous-Alexander's ability to create points and free-throw attempts off the dribble, they didn't really need to calm down and manufacture a series of baskets. Then they did need to do that, and couldn't. As Indiana scrambled to wipe away a nine-point deficit over the game's final three minutes or so, the Thunder, perhaps just tuned this way by a season of playing at a full sprint, repeatedly let themselves get baited into early shots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coco Gauff Won’t Be Rattled]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=191806</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/coco-gauff-wont-be-rattled"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T17:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The aspect from Coco Gauff's altogether impressive French Open final win that I find myself most impressed by is, oddly, something that didn't go her way. Gauff is now a two-time Grand Slam champion, and though are several parallels between her two upsets of Aryna Sabalenka, her most recent triumph was the more thorough of the two. Consider how things started for her on Saturday.
Gauff lost a heartbreaker of a first set to Sabalenka at Roland Garros, a 6–7 (5) odyssey that lasted longer than an hour and cost her a tremendous amount of effort to get back into, go ahead in, and eventually lose. Sabalenka raced out to a 4–1, 40–love lead in the set in the first 20 minutes, and the final seemed like it might go the way Gauff's first French Open final did, when she barely bothered to give Iga Swiatek anything to do in 2022. But Sabalenka faltered and allowed Gauff to break her serve and then hold, kicking off a gnarly run of five straight breaks that led into a tiebreak. Gauff finally got ahold of her serve and seized a 4–1 in that tiebreak before Sabalenka ripped it away from her.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>