<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-12-04T01:19:56.313Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Planning To Move Kris Bubic Back To Rotation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=832630</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/12/royals-planning-to-move-kris-bubic-back-to-rotation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T22:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals intend to use Kris Bubic as a starting pitcher in 2025, write Will Sammon, Katie Woo and Ken Rosenthal of the Athletic. The southpaw pitched out of the bullpen this past season after a 14-month layoff rehabbing Tommy John surgery. Kansas City presumably always intended for Bubic’s relief role to be a short-term…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KU’s Vespers Tradition plays on 30 years after the long-standing heritage nearly went up in flames]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863738</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/carrying-the-torch-kus-vespers-tradition-reigns-on-30-years-after-the-long-standing-heritage-nearly-went-up-in-flames/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T22:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of KU School of Music In the winter of 1923, Donald Swarthout—in his first year as Dean of Fine Arts at the University of Kansas—began a Vespers tradition that is ongoing today. Taking place in old Fraser Hall’s 700-seat theater—what was then known as Christmas Vespers—would gradually become an event that would draw in enough people to fill...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veni, Vidi, Snorti: I Came, I Saw, I Did A Bump]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=175066</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/veni-vidi-snorti-i-came-i-saw-i-did-a-bump"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T21:01:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There comes a time when you have been out for hours—your bones are tired from so much running around, your eyes are bleary from the smoke, and your ears are ringing from all the noise—and you just need a little pick-me-up. So you reach down to your belt, pull out a tiny silver spoon, and scoop up a tiny mound of powder, and take a snort. Suddenly, you feel extremely ready to go back out there; "out there" meaning the misted marshes of Northern Europe during the Roman Period, and rejoin your buddies, meaning the other Germanic warriors that have gathered today for battle. Sure, you might be brutally dismembered, but at least you're going out on a high?
This was the conclusion of a paper published recently in the German journal Praehistorische Zeitschrift, in which archaeologists analyzed 241 tiny spoons found buried in what is now Germany, Scandinavia, and Poland, along with items of warfare from the Roman Period, and concluded the warriors must have been bumpin' that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Reach Deal With Diamond Sports Group]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=832654</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/12/royals-reach-deal-with-diamond-sports-group.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T20:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced today that have signed a new deal with Diamond Sports Group, owner of the FanDuel Sports Network, formerly known as Bally’s. That company will continue to broadcast the club’s games in 2025. Coming into today, the Royals were one of the few clubs with their broadcast situation still up in the air.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Are No Small Servings Of The Jameis Winston Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=175147</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/there-are-no-small-servings-of-the-jameis-winston-experience"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T20:44:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the euphoria over the glorious return of Jameis Winston during his giddy and maximalist Monday Night Football performance seemed to forget the helpless victims of Jameis Being Jameis—starting with the man who could lose his job because of it, Winston’s indulgent coach Kevin Stefanski.
It is true that Jameis is a singular entity in the insurance company world of the National Football League, from the way he enters games to what he does during them and on the post-game podium afterwards. He has as much fun doing superoptimal things on a suboptimal team as any quarterback has since Bobby Layne quarterbacked the Detroit Lions and Pittsburgh Steelers while largely hung over throughout the 1950s. Plus, Layne didn't wear a facemask and still got to the Hall of Fame, and what's more fun than that?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drink This Now: The Valtrex at Incline on 9th]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859409</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/drink-this-now-the-valtrex-at-incline-on-9th/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T20:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valtrex at Incline on 9th // Photo by Tiffany Watts Kansas City’s West Bottoms has a new addition that’s making waves not just for its food but for its creative cocktails. Tucked into a historic building with an ambiance that’s equal parts industrial chic and cozy lounge, Incline on 9th has the area buzzing. I recently had the pleasure of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How A Sleepy Ancient Amphibian Became A Link To An Endangered Language]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174006</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-a-sleepy-ancient-amphibian-became-a-link-to-an-endangered-language"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T19:54:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the winter of 2015, David Lovelace, a vertebrate paleontologist at the University of Wisconsin-Madison Geology Museum, remembered a rock the size of a soccer ball that had been sitting on a shelf in his lab for months. He'd collected it the previous year, walking back to his car after a day of searching for fossils. It contained a small burrow, barely four inches long. He wanted to extract the burrow. "Being a good geologist, I hit the whole thing with my hammer," Lovelace said.
Unfortunately, the strike did not free the burrow, but it did reveal the skull of a small animal that had died inside. The tapered snout of the skull appeared crocodilian. But as Lovelace glued the bones back together and prepared the fossil, he realized it was actually an amphibian. Its skull had small pits and ridges characteristic of early amphibians, as well as grooves indicating a lateral line organ. Another strike of the rock revealed another skull and partial skeleton of the same kind of animal. Lovelace and his colleagues recently reported on this new species, a burrowing amphibian, Ninumbeehan dookoodukah, in Proceedings of the Royal Society B.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UConn And UMass Created And Abandoned College Football’s Goofiest Rivalry Trophy]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=175018</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/uconn-and-umass-created-and-abandoned-college-footballs-goofiest-rivalry-trophy"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T18:49:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UMass and UConn were all set up for the big one. The two programs played 77 times before, but this was the first time that a trophy sponsored by an NIL collective would be on the line. Sure, UConn was 7-4 coming into the game and UMass was 2-9. But with UMass moving to the MAC next season, it might be the last time these two teams played for a while. And there was a brand new trophy to fight for. This had all the makings of a classic.
Players were aware of the significance. “I did see it on social media,” UConn offensive lineman Chase Lundt, a sixth-year senior, told the Hartford Courant about the trophy. “Pretty neat. It would be cool if we could get something like that.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hell Is Being Defended By Tari Eason And Amen Thompson]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174994</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/hell-is-being-defended-by-tari-eason-and-amen-thompson"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T17:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday night's game between the Oklahoma City Thunder and Houston Rockets, one of the best of the regular season, hit maximal tension when Dillon Brooks began to tear a rebound out of Shai Gilgeous-Alexander's hands. The scrap escalated until both parties started to laugh—a wholesome incident between Team Canada pals. On most teams, Brooks's defensive intensity would be an anomaly, and yet he might not even be the second-most aggressive defender on the Rockets' roster.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wQZNHT-cZY4]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Fringe Fest’s Gulag Girls delivers international drama through feminist force]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861789</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-fringe-fests-gulag-girls-delivers-international-drama-through-feminist-force/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T17:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Taylor Zimmerman Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be publishing these...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Are Not Prepared For How Cool The 12-Team Playoff Will Be]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=175013</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/you-are-not-prepared-for-how-cool-the-12-team-playoff-will-be"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T16:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about the Bears, well-done meats, Monty Python, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crowd Work Isn’t A Substitute For Comedy]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174957</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/crowd-work-isnt-a-substitute-for-comedy"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T15:33:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hate to say it, but the biggest laugh in James Acaster’s new special, Hecklers Welcome, comes from a heckle. Obviously. The show opens with the British comic naming his house rules, which amount to allowing all forms of audience disruption (except if it’s, you know, actually offensive). Anyone who knows Acaster—I know him from his very popular food podcast, Off Menu, which he co-hosts with fellow comedian Ed Gamble—knows he hates a heckle, so to build an entire show around it is kind of a big move. Being the pro writer that he is, the start of the show is a rundown of the various formative heckles of his career, the first of which arrived very early on during what he calls the worst gig he’s ever done. “Does your mother know you’re up this late?” was the trigger, to which a young Acaster apparently responded that his mother was dead (she wasn’t)—and that she had died really recently. Which silenced the heckler, obviously. As well as the rest of the audience, for the entire show.
Fast-forward about 30 minutes into this latest special, and the punchline to another Acaster joke is a guy yelling to a bunch of bullies that their parents don’t love them. To which one audience member pipes up: “My parents are dead!” Acaster is so impressed by the callback that he says: “Lovely to have a heckler in here who appreciates structure.” But then a few moments later, another audience member adds: “...by suicide.” Acaster asks his name (it’s Richard, because this is England). Then Acaster says, completely deadpan: “Richard, what is wrong with you, mate?”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: From winter coats to shorts? (TUE-12/3)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3747499</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-from-winter-coats-to-shorts-tue-12-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T15:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a cold morning out there with temperatures in the mid-teens to start our bright and sunny Tuesday]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: From winter coats to shorts? (TUE-12/3)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3747499</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-from-winter-coats-to-shorts-tue-12-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T15:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a cold morning out there with temperatures in the mid teens to start our bright and sunny Tuesday. Today will be a transition day as we briefly return to near 50° weather tomorrow and then take another cold shot tomorrow night into Thursday with blustery conditions returning for a day or two before we [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Watches A Christmas Movie: ‘’Tis The Season To Be Irish’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174579</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-watches-a-christmas-movie-tis-the-season-to-be-irish"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T14:02:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the time of year when the best, biggest, and most ambitious movies come out. Not Oscar season, but rather that stretch when the halls of streaming services are decked with the brightly lit, thinly disguised advertisements that are the year's new Christmas movies. There are more than 100 new Christmas films to watch this holiday season, and whether that number horrifies or excites you depends upon how much of a freak you are for the festive. Sabrina is proud to say they are a real Christmas freak, and this year they asked some of their colleagues to watch some of the most, uh, available new holiday movies. The third movie in our lineup is 'Tis the Season to Be Irish, a Hallmark movie that dares to ask, "What's the Gaelic word for house-flipping?" This week, we are joined by an extra special guest: Leigh McKenna.
Leigh McKenna: This is Leigh. I'm on here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Square Peg Marketing & Branding CEO Kim Kramer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863704</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-square-peg-marketing-branding-ceo-kim-kramer/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T14:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Kim Kramer There’s plenty of girl power inside the walls of Square Peg Marketing & Branding. In fact, CEO and Owner Kim Kramer wouldn’t want it any other way at her agency. “My all-female team is a powerhouse of talent,” she says. “We deliver killer branding, digital marketing, and design solutions that actually move the needle.” Kramer says her specialty is helping...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Evaluating Trade Market For Middle-Of-The-Order Bat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=832587</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/12/royals-evaluating-trade-market-for-middle-of-the-order-bat.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T03:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals already made one move to improve the offense, acquiring Jonathan India from the Reds two weeks ago. India will hit at the top of the lineup. Kansas City is also on the hunt for a middle-of-the-order bat, write Will Sammon, Katie Woo and Ken Rosenthal of the Athletic. As with India, it seems a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hallmark’s Holiday Touchdown: A Chiefs Love Story is less rom-com, more literal love for football merch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863775</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/hallmarks-holiday-touchdown-a-chiefs-love-story-is-less-rom-com-than-literal-love-for-football-merch/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T22:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Hallmark It’s finally here! Holiday Touchdown: A Chiefs Love Story, the long-awaited Chiefs-centric, regionally-shot Hallmark Christmas movie, premiered November 30. In the interest of letting you all draw your own conclusions about this deeply silly bit of holiday entertainment, we decided to wait until after it aired to run our thoughts. So, now that we’ve seen it, what do...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from the Editor: Return the gift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863714</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/letter-from-the-editor-return-the-gift/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T22:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome, dearest reader. This is the December 2024 print issue of The Pitch, dispatched regularly from your home hub here in KC.  Due to time constraints for the turnaround on getting these issues through the printing press, today’s ‘Letter from the Editor’ has been typed up too close to the election to possibly unpack all the important, bizarre, and confounding...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt Eberflus Made Bears History In The Bad Way]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174906</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/matt-eberflus-made-bears-history-in-the-bad-way"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T21:18:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday afternoon, the day after a total clock-management disaster resulted in a three-point loss to Detroit, the team canned Eberflus. He becomes the first-ever Bears head coach fired midseason, and he deserves that distinction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Brat summer steers citywide celebrations into indie sleaze fall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861771</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-brat-summer-steers-citywide-celebrations-into-indie-sleaze-fall/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T20:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of KC Pet Project Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Kansas City Mavericks fall short to Tulsa Oilers as race for first place heats up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863822</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-kansas-city-mavericks-fall-short-to-tulsa-oilers-as-race-for-first-place-heats-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T19:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City Mavericks versus Tulsa Oilers on Nov. 30, 2024. // Photo by Eli Ralls On Saturday, Nov. 30, the Kansas Mavericks took a disappointing 4-2 home loss to the Tulsa Oilers, despite having 13 more shots on net. The Oilers got going early with a goal about ten minutes into the first period, and KC answered back with their...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Ralls</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is this bill the key to reducing gun suicides in Kansas and Missouri?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863824</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/is-this-bill-the-key-to-reducing-gun-suicides-in-kansas-and-missouri/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T19:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas and Missouri lawmakers could consider voluntary do-not-sell lists for guns. Credit: Scott Canon / The Beacon Donna Nathan loved two-stepping and The Beatles. The radio was always on at her house. That love of music easily translated to dancing in parades. Nathan and her daughter, Katrina Brees, even worked together at a studio making sculptures for Mardi Gras parades....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Blaise Mesa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Care delayed and care denied’: Doctor recalls 30 months under Missouri abortion ban]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863816</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/care-delayed-and-care-denied-doctor-recalls-30-months-under-missouri-abortion-ban/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T19:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Betsy Wickstrom, a high-risk obstetrician who works in the Kansas City metro, is a lifelong Republican who was outspoken in her support for Missouri’s Amendment 3, which lifted the state’s near-total abortion ban (Anna Spoerre/Missouri Independent) Dr. Betsy Wickstrom understands where some of the voices opposed to abortion are coming from. She used to be one of them. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Spoerre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liverpool Is Winning A Battle Of Attrition]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174898</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/liverpool-is-winning-a-battle-of-attrition"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T19:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the time of writing, on Dec. 2, 2024, Liverpool is nine points clear at the top of the Premier League table. The Pool Boys have been in torrid form domestically this season: 11 wins, one draw to second-place Arsenal, and one less-shocking-by-the-day loss to sixth-place Nottingham Forest. That run of 13 games includes wins over third-place Chelsea, fourth-place Brighton, and an always-pleasant thrashing of rival Manchester United. As of Sunday, it also includes a quite comfortable 2-0 victory over Manchester City, a club in full-blown crisis, insomuch as the Sky Blues can be in crisis; the loss to Liverpool threw City into fifth place, and the reigning champions have not won in seven matches across all competitions.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fNI7qrWFeqI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is What Getting Left Behind Looks Like]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174909</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-is-what-getting-left-behind-looks-like"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T18:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The theory of the dribble handoff is sound: The hub, typically a center brutish enough to dislodge trailing defenders with a screen but adept enough with the rock to make quick passing decisions, scrambles typical pick-and-roll coverage by simultaneously acting as both ball-handler and screener. With a live dribble, they have the latitude to punish overzealous help defense and dictate the angle of the screen. The player coming around the DHO can either pop into open space or attack a slightly shifted defense, with the hub either rolling or popping themselves. 
One NBA team, Sacramento, has made the DHO the foundation of its half-court offense. This made total sense when the Kings implemented the system two seasons ago and won 48 games; it also helps explain why the team is currently drawing dead in a conference that has passed them by.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers Suffers Further Indignity]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174901</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/aaron-rodgers-suffers-further-indignity"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T18:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You'd think it would get old by now, but it really hasn't: It's almost therapeutic to watch Aaron Rodgers eat shit week after week. The preceding months of smugness, sneers, and hack pop-culture references just enhance the results, and in a stroke of serendipity, today is Aaron Rodgers's 41st birthday. Hey—happy birthday, big guy. You don't play a day over 65.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Tucker Just Can’t Find The Range]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174923</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/justin-tucker-just-cant-find-the-range"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T17:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Tucker sat encased in a sideline cape and hidden under a hood, alone with his thoughts and the millions of other people thinking them. He had just missed a 53-yard field goal that would have put the Baltimore Ravens ahead of the Philadelphia Eagles, and Tucker looked more than just morose. He looked even more than baffled. The most productive NFL kicker of the last decade looked like the living embodiment of a yip.
People speak of the yips often, usually in relation to a golfer with putting issues; for whatever it may be worth, the Oxford English Dictionary pegs the first use of the term as having been in 1935, in American Golfer. Everyone agrees on what it is: the sudden inability to perform a task one has performed many times before because the one performing the task is thinking too hard about the task itself and becoming overwhelmed by the very idea. It’s less that the task becomes more difficult and more that it just slips further and further out of perspective.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bigots Don’t Know Ball]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174876</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bigots-dont-know-ball"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T17:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Saturday, the San Jose State women's volleyball season came to an end, as the Spartans were beaten in four sets by the Colorado State Rams in the Mountain West Conference championship. A top seed comfortably prevailing over a second seed in a small conference tournament final is not a particularly remarkable or noteworthy outcome, but SJSU's tournament run gained national attention thanks to the hard work of people who hate sports almost as much as they hate transgender people.
Last week, ESPN's Katie Barnes published a long and deeply reported story about SJSU's volleyball season, which I highly recommend you read. The short version is that earlier this year an anti-trans activist group called Independent Council on Women's Sports (ICONS) and professional bigot Riley Gaines trained their sights on SJSU's volleyball team, claiming that the team has a transgender player. (The player in question has not been named in non-reactionary media coverage.) In March, ICONS and Gaines filed a lawsuit against the NCAA seeking to overturn the policies that allow transgender athletes to play sports. In September, SJSU co-captain Brooke Slusser joined the lawsuit, claiming that the presence of a transgender player on her team posed a safety risk to her teammates and opponents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Audio experiment Sound Mandala combines tech and tremendous dreamlike adventures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861757</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-audio-experiment-sound-mandala-combines-tech-and-tremendous-dreamlike-adventures/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T17:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Mardikes // Photo by Ellen Beshuk Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Dec. 2: Hot Ones]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174899</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-dec-2-hot-ones"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T16:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s puzzle was constructed by Rebecca Goldstein and Rachel Fabi, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Rebecca is a scientist and crossword constructor in the Bay Area. Rachel is a crossword constructor and a professor of bioethics. When she's not professing bioethics or doing crossword things, Rachel enjoys biking, hiking, video games, and baking, and she is currently in third place in her family's 17-team fantasy football keeper league. 
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Beautiful Wolves Are Freaks For Nectar]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174676</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/these-beautiful-wolves-are-freaks-for-nectar"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T14:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The flame-colored blooms of the Ethiopian red hot poker grow around mountain-rimmed meadows, as high up as 13,000 feet above sea level. The dry season snuffs out the poker's flowers, leaving the plant parched and yellow. But in the rainy season, the plants first regrow their spiky leaves, then their towering stem, and finally their red-hot flowers. "They look like hundreds of fire torches covering the landscape," Sandra Lai, a senior scientist at Oxford University's Ethiopian Wolf Conservation Program, or EWCP, wrote in an email.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: So, when's our next snow chance (MON-12/2)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3745938</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-so-whens-our-next-snow-chance-mon-12-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T14:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, that was quite the snow on Saturday morning... anywhere from 1-5" of snow in the Metro with that concentrated area of 3-5" right near the I-70 corridor, and that was roughly a 5-10 mile wide band that went east to west through parts of eastern Kansas and into the areas east of KC. All [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: So when's our next snow chance (MON-12/2)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3745938</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-so-whens-our-next-snow-chance-mon-12-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T14:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well that was quite the snow on Saturday morning...anywhere from 1-5" of snow in the Metro with that concentrated area of 3-5" right near the I-70 corridor and that was roughly a 5-10 mile wide band that went east to west through parts of eastern KS and into the areas east of KC. All the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How The Art Modell Law Could Keep The Browns From Leaving Cleveland]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174515</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-the-art-modell-law-could-keep-the-browns-from-leaving-cleveland"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T14:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cleveland loves to immortalize its sports heroes. The street behind the left-field bleachers at the Guardians' ballpark was renamed for Larry Doby in 2012. The Browns' offices in Berea are on Lou Groza Boulevard. There are parks named for Luke Easter, a Negro Leagues slugger who played for the Indians, and Mel Harder, a longtime pitcher and coach. (Harder's park is also his final resting place. His ashes were scattered there following his death in 2002.)
But Cleveland immortalizes its sports villains, too. Art Modell has an Ohio law named for him.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vince Guerrieri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unicorn offers up Ebenezer Scrooge’s Big KC MO Christmas Show as holiday hooliganism on your way to the bar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863567</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/the-unicorn-offers-up-ebenezer-scrooges-big-kc-mo-christmas-show-as-holiday-hooliganism-on-your-way-to-the-bar/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T14:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Don Ipock Kansas City does not lack for annual holiday traditions. It can probably be said double so for the theater community, where each season brings with it a handful of recurring shows that are consistently excellent. The thing of it is, there’s apparently always space for more. Productions like Milking Christmas and Electric Poe have carved out their high...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Wizards Won Nothing In November]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174830</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-washington-wizards-won-nothing-in-november"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T00:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Wizards started the season at a plucky 2-2. Perhaps that was pluckier than they intended. They proceeded to lose all 14 games they played in November, settling in the muck at a league-worst 2-16. This would be bleak new territory for most teams, but incredibly, this is not even the franchise's first winless month in the current calendar year. Last season's Wizards went 0-12 in February. That was part of a larger 16-game losing streak, tied for the worst in franchise history. Should the current Wizards lose three more games—and, given that the opponents are the Cavs, Mavs, and Nuggets, they might—they would claim that franchise record instead.
Another astonishing aspect is how uncompetitive the games themselves have been. The Wizards lost all 14 games in this streak by a margin of at least nine points, which had never been accomplished in NBA history. In 10 of those games, they were blown out by at least 15 points. The team is omni-directionally bad, with both the league's worst offensive rating and the worst defensive rating and, as such, the worst net rating, a gruesome -14.1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azeez Al-Shaair Confronted And Ejected After Ugly Hit That Gave Trevor Lawrence Concussion]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174809</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/azeez-al-shaair-confronted-and-ejected-after-ugly-hit-that-gave-trevor-lawrence-concussion"/>
        <updated>2024-12-01T23:56:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jacksonville Jaguars quarterback Trevor Lawrence left Sunday's game on a medical cart after Houston Texans linebacker Azeez Al-Shaair hit the QB while he was sliding, appearing to lead with his forearm and helmet. The smack of the tackle could be heard on TV.
Lawrence lay motionless on the field in what looked like a fencing response. But it was hard to see all of Lawrence's body because, almost immediately, a fight broke out. After Al-Shaair made the tackle, Jaguars tight end Evan Engram rushed over and shoved him, and players from both teams escalated the clash. At one point, the broadcast showed a huge swath of players on one sideline as the fight wound down while, further away, a handful of personnel tended to Lawrence. ESPN's Michael DiRocco reported that "an official knelt to protect Lawrence as the skirmish moved toward the Jaguars sideline."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iga Swiatek Suspended After Testing Positive For Banned Substance]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174790</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/iga-swiatek-suspended-after-testing-positive-for-banned-substance"/>
        <updated>2024-12-01T19:09:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the second time in 2024, one of the best tennis players in the world has violated anti-doping rules. The International Tennis Integrity Agency announced Thursday that Iga Swiatek, currently the world No. 2, tested positive for the banned substance trimetazidine, a heart medication used in Europe and Asia to treat angina. It was detected in an out-of-competition test Swiatek provided just ahead of the Cincinnati Open in August, the ITIA said. Swiatek formally admitted to the anti-doping rules violation and accepted a one-month ban from the sport; her three weeks of provisional suspension earlier in the year count toward that ban and she is currently serving the remaining eight days during a meaningless stretch of the tennis calendar. She was also stripped of $158,944 in prize money and 390 ranking points for her semifinal run in Cincinnati.
Swiatek previously had a provisional suspension as she sought to explain the source of the trimetazidine to the ITIA. While doing so, she missed tournaments in Seoul, Beijing, and Wuhan in September and October. Swiatek was able to have her suite of at least 14 supplements analyzed to identify a possible source of contamination. She concluded that the culprit was her melatonin, which Swiatek has long used, she said, because with "all my traveling, jet lag and work-related stress mean that sometimes without it, I couldn’t fall asleep." She provided both an opened and unopened containers of the melatonin to the ITIA, which had them analyzed and found the contamination consistent with the trace amounts of trimetazidine detected in Swiatek's urine sample. Her provisional suspension was lifted and she was able to continue competing at the WTA's year-end finals, per the ITIA decision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Police Pepper Spray Players During Michigan-Ohio State Postgame Fight]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174796</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/police-pepper-spray-players-during-michigan-ohio-state-postgame-fight"/>
        <updated>2024-12-01T18:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michigan beat Ohio State on Saturday for the fourth season in a row. The win gave this year's senior class at Michigan a clean sweep over their longtime Buckeye rivals, and it was a stunning upset as OSU hosted the game and came into it ranked second in the country. Sure, college players are increasingly transferring between programs and extending their careers into their mid-twenties, but facts like that mean little next to the emotions of a longstanding rivalry that goes back more than a century. The most important fact of all is that Ohio State and Michigan hate each other. When the Wolverines won in Columbus, 13-10, and a player tried to plant a Michigan flag on the field, a brawl unsurprisingly followed.
Reporters were already on the field when the fight broke out, and Nicole Shearin of WBNS got video of what happened. The Michigan player, carrying a Michigan flag on a pole, walked up to an area of the field and motioned as if to plant the flag. He was slowed down, first by what looked like people in Ohio State clothing, followed by someone in Michigan clothing who put his arms around the player. The Michigan player wasn't able to plant the flag, but kept talking as Ohio State athletes filled up the area. Video from another angle by UMGoBlue showed that after the failed flag planting, an Ohio State player grabbed the cloth part of the Michigan flag and ripped it off its pole. In the videos, this is when the fight started. (A different video also showed former Wolverine turned broadcaster Jason Avant securing the loose Michigan flag, but it's hard to tell when that happened relative to everything else.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Band of snow creates a mess in KC (SAT-11/30)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3744369</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-band-of-snow-creates-a-mess-in-kc-sat-11-30/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-30T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not a wide band, but it's a mighty one. About 10-15 miles from north to south around that band there are little or no impact, and in the band, there are crashes and road closures. This is what I've been concerned about for two days and last night I hit this hard. I had [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Band of snow creates a mess in KC (SAT-11/30)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3744369</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-band-of-snow-creates-a-mess-in-kc-sat-11-30/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-30T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not a wide band, but it's a mighty one...roughly 10-15 miles from north to south...around that band there is little or no impacts and in the band there are crashes and road closures. This is what I've been concerned about for two days and last night I hit this hard. I had a bad [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enjoy The Lily Yohannes Victory Lap]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174490</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/enjoy-the-lily-yohannes-victory-lap"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T21:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States Women's National Team is currently in Europe to play a pair of friendlies that will thoroughly stretch the meaning of that designation.
First up is a date with England at Wembley, both a homecoming for USWNT coach Emma Hayes and a fascinating opportunity to consider the dynamics of the transatlantic soccer exchange on both the Olympic champions and the European champions. Hayes, of course, made her name managing Chelsea for over a decade, though she got her start coaching in New York, a bit north of where Three Lionesses manager Sarina Wiegman played college soccer. USWNT vets have enjoyed short stints in England, and so many England players have tussled in the NWSL that The Athletic ran a long story with quotes from each payer about how physical and demanding the standard of play was stateside. The game is not exactly a referendum on whose development environment is better, though it does provide an occasion to think seriously about at the state of the best women's club league and the second-best as it closes the gap. It's also a serious test for both teams with close to their full rosters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Does A Recipe Become Your Own?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174752</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/when-does-a-recipe-become-your-own"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growing up, my grandma lived in a small green house that sat under a towering cottonwood tree on the south side of Minneapolis. She had many old things, or at least things that felt old to my young brain: a cast-iron fireplace that looked like it could forge steel, a massive wooden cabinet TV that hummed and seemed almost radioactive, a whole rainbow's worth of colorful mixing bowls that were sturdy enough to survive in the oven.
The bowls are what I remember the most, because I remember the kitchen more vividly than anything else. On holidays like Thanksgiving, Christmas and Easter, work would start in the narrow galley of a kitchen very early and it would go late, until family arrived, until the very minute everyone sat at the table, through the combative games of Uno to decide who would do dishes after no one was foolish enough to eat more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Last Pitcher]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174670</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-last-pitcher"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T17:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defector has partnered with Baseball Prospectus to bring you a taste of their work. They write good shit that we think you’ll like. If you do like it, we encourage you to check out their site and subscribe.
This story was originally published at Baseball Prospectus on November 22.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Dubuque</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Fast moving snows Saturday (FRI-11/29)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3743490</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-fast-moving-snows-saturday-fri-11-29/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T16:50:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we head toward the last day of November tomorrow, Mother Nature may give us a last day of November snow, and perhaps, it may be more than just a casual amount for parts of the area]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Does Hotel Art Look Like That?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174198</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-does-hotel-art-look-like-that"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T14:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently stayed at a blandly business-oriented hotel in San Jose in order to celebrate my birthday, drink a tall boy, and watch the Sharks lose. You know this type of hotel. There were white duvet covers, white sheets, beige walls, dark wood for the closet and bathroom doors. There was a nice light under a wall bench to help you find your way to the bathroom in the middle of the night. The soundproofing was good.
There was also, of course, a picture on the wall. There is always a picture on the wall in hotel rooms. It was a photograph and it showed a cement wall and floor belonging to what seemed to be a warehouse building.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felix Kent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>