<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-05-12T03:12:30.801Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Savannah Bananas Make Baseball Boring]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189317</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-savannah-bananas-make-baseball-boring"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T16:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["What's the deal with the Savannah Bananas?"
Like five different times over the past few months, someone at this website has posed that question to the rest of the folks who work here. For the uninitiated, I will begin with the most dispassionate, factual answer in the paragraph below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Sox Now Chasing Rafael Devers Across The Country, Waving Lineup Card]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189329</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/red-sox-now-chasing-rafael-devers-across-the-country-waving-lineup-card"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T15:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rafael Devers did what his bosses wanted. The Red Sox went out and grabbed a big-time addition over the winter, but to maximize their investment they needed Devers to shift away from his preferred position—the one he's been playing his entire career, and the one the Red Sox extended him a nine-figure contract to continue playing off into the future. Devers wasn't happy about the request and resisted for a while. He eventually caved, and then he endured an embarrassing, historically awful start to the season while adjusting to this new deal. But he's recovered admirably and been a reliable and productive contributor for a fun and competitive Red Sox team.
Now the team is at it again. First baseman Triston Casas, off to a hateful, miserable start of his own, nuked his left knee while trying to beat out an infield single on May 2 and has been lost for the year. The Red Sox have since tried out Romy Gonzalez, Abraham Toro, and Nick Sogard over at first, with results that you would call broadly lousy—7-for-26 at the plate with zero extra-base hits—were it not for the fact that Casas was producing an OPS+ of [awful retching noises]. It's not that these are especially terrible baseball players—although scanning Toro's Baseball Reference page is causing an alarming intensification of the retching—but certainly none of those poor bozos is the sort of guy a team is eager to get into the lineup, least of all a team with semi-credible playoff aspirations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leon, No!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189334</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/leon-no"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T14:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It didn't matter that the Oilers jumped out to a 2–0 lead in Game 3. It didn't matter that Stuart Skinner, forced back into action after Calvin Pickard's injury, allowed fewer goals than he did in his two catastrophic starts against the Kings. And it didn't matter that, with the score 3–2 Vegas in the final few minutes, Connor McDavid unlocked the Golden Knights' defense with a little pass from the corner that went in off an enemy skate. All anyone's going to remember from Saturday night is the very last second, which is how Vegas managed to cut into Edmonton's 2–0 series lead.
Any reasonable person would have been ready for overtime as William Karlsson broke into the offensive zone and took the puck behind the net with under five seconds to play. But in retrospect, when the VGK original sent the puck flying backward into the slot for another one of his expansion-season brethren, Reilly Smith, neither man had yet given up on the third period, and there was still enough time to inflict the knockout blow. Smith, using nearly every tenth of a second allotted to him, zoomed past a diving Oilers defender and tried to round a sliding Skinner as he fired a shot in the direction of the crease. The puck bounced so quickly that in real time, the closest official didn't see a goal. But replay review revealed the buzzer-beater, and worse, the person most responsible for it crossing the line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celtics Flatten Knicks By Sticking To The Formula]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189322</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/celtics-flatten-knicks-by-sticking-to-the-formula"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T13:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Boston Celtics and New York Knicks have played 149 minutes across three games of their second-round playoff series. The Celtics—the higher seeded team and the defending NBA champions—have led outright for about 128 minutes of that time, and the teams have spent about another 11 minutes tied, meaning the Knicks have led in this series for a little over 10 total minutes. The Celtics have gained leads of at least 20 points in each game, while the Knicks have never led by double digits; they have, in fact, never once had a three-possession lead. This isn't a real metric, I may have just made it up while I sat here, but: If you total together New York's maximum lead from each of the three games, and then multiply the sum by the total minutes they've spent in the lead, you get 90. If you do the same for the Celtics—20 points in Game 1, another 20 in Game 2, 31 points in Game 3, added together and then multiplied by total time in the lead—you get 9,088.
This is very dumb, meaningless math, but for some weird reason I have always been tickled by one number being way huger than another number. The Knicks have 90 units of advantage through three games, against Boston's 9,088: Wow! And also: Ha! By my dumb metric, it would be absolutely ludicrous to guess that the team holding the overall lead in the series today is the New York Knicks. But here we are! Boston needed a win Saturday to avoid falling into a 3–0 hole in a matchup that they have otherwise absolutely dominated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kyle Wright Pulled Off Rehab Stint With Shoulder Fatigue, Continuing To Play Catch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=851551</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/kyle-wright-pulled-off-rehab-stint-with-shoulder-fatigue-continuing-to-play-catch.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-10T02:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyle Wright’s first appearance with the Royals will wait a little longer than hoped. The team announced this evening that they’ve pulled him back from his rehab assignment in Double-A after Wright reported shoulder fatigue. The club specified that they believe it to be a minor setback, saying the “tentative plan” is for him to skip…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maple leaf rage / Undead blues]]></title>
        <id>681e5f3174fb8d000119c8a2</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-317/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T21:47:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nathan Munn explains the Canadian election to Zach Rabiroff; the music of ‘Sinners’ enchants Rax King]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PODCAST Round Table! Episode 9: Canadasplainer!]]></title>
        <id>681e5e5874fb8d000119c895</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/podcast-round-table-episode-9-canadasplainer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T21:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nathan Munn, Canadian, and Zach Rabiroff, New Yorker, discuss the recent and somewhat surprising results of the big election in Canada. Joe MacLeod pressed the RECORD button.
Listen on Apple/Spotify/RSS/plus more options at pod.link

Episode 9: CANADASPLAINER
Nathan Munn, Canadian, and Zach Rabiroff, New]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Munn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pick Poor Robin Clean]]></title>
        <id>681e5a5774fb8d000119c879</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/pick-poor-robin-clean/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T21:25:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rax King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A’s Designate Noah Murdock For Assignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=851501</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/as-designate-noah-murdock-for-assignment.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T21:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The A’s designated Rule 5 pick Noah Murdock for assignment, relays Martín Gallegos of MLB.com. Righty Elvis Alvarado was recalled from Triple-A Las Vegas to take his spot in the bullpen. Alvarado is already on the 40-man roster, so the move drops their count to 39. Murdock, 26, was the fourth player selected in last winter’s Rule…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Staff Chat Begins Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189296</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-staff-chat-begins-right-now"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T18:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello. It's Friday. Let's chat. We'll be down below waiting to answer all of your burning questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lamine Yamal’s Wait Is Over]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189044</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lamine-yamals-wait-is-over"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T17:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the conclusion of Tuesday's Barcelona vs. Inter match, Lamine Yamal had taken up the traditional loser's pose: sitting on the ground, his arms encircling his knees in a loose hug, his back curved in a hunch of exhaustion and dejection, eyes vacantly staring into the distance.
Something about that image made stark the irresolvable paradox of this 17-year-old and his staggeringly advanced game. Part of it was the akimbo posture, accentuating the youthfulness of his sinewy limbs, which, unlike when the ball is at his feet, made him look every bit the callow teen he is. Part of it was the emotional tenor of the moment, the blessed, childlike state into which sports can transport anyone—child or adult, on-pitch participant or TV viewer from thousands of miles away—where the result of a silly little game can send hot tears of anguish streaming down millions of faces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Reads A Book: Defector Rides A Bike]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188904</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-reads-a-book-defector-rides-a-bike"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T17:22:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In college, I briefly and unsuccessfully raced bikes, a humbling experience that taught me that the dog in me was not of requisite size to hang with anyone who wasn't a middling amateur. Every part of racing was a drain, from being nervously sardine-packed alongside dozens of other gangly 20-year-olds to figuring out when to burn energy and when to chill in the pack so that I actually had energy to burn. I never won anything or even came close, though loving bike racing means loving the draining stuff. That's all you can count on.
This is the right way to think about professional cycling, and really any form of racing. Think about this sort of competitive framework seriously enough, and you rub up against the limits of describing or thinking about racing in cold, analytical language. Easy and forgivable as it is to roll one's eyes at a conception of bike racing rooted in romantic notions like bravery, or the virtues of suffering with dignity, those do form the competitive substrate of the sport. Like most racing sports, cycling is foremost a pain tolerance contest. Strategic thinking is centered on how to trick other people into suffering more than you. How could you not think about guts, in both usages?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Bea]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189238</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/for-bea"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T17:03:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was still reeling in the aftermath of our dog Chop's sudden and horrible heart-failure death, stunned and breathless with grief, feeling very much the way you do after taking a hard blow to the head, when all at once our Bea became a ghost of herself. She was old, and had been thinning in the way old dogs do in their final year, but still in all outward respects her loud, wiseass, insistent self, buzzing with impatience, shepherding my wife to bed at The Appointed Time, shoveling her snout under your hand and levering it onto her neck when she wanted pets: Bea.
Then, on a Saturday evening in early April, she all at once flipped out at our other dog, Grover, when he came up behind her: Snarling and snapping, fighting as though for her life. We had to pull them apart. In the immediate aftermath, she was the most alarmingly depleted dog I have ever seen. She could scarcely stand. It was as though a band had snapped in there. It was as though she had spent the absolute last of herself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Notes: Outfield, Caglianone, Harvey]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=851428</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-rumors-jac-caglianone-promotion-leody-taveras.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T16:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals enter the weekend with the American League’s fourth-best record (23-16) and in possession of the league’s second Wild Card spot. Their starting rotation, as highlighted by MLBTR’s Anthony Franco yesterday, looks exceptional. Their top four relievers, by workload, have ERAs of 2.65 or better. Pitching was never going to be the question with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Restart Your Computer!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189232</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/restart-your-computer"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T15:25:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At our bi-weekly all-hands meeting, Jasper Wang, our Business Man, will usually share his screen with the appropriate slides. But this week, his computer was bogged down and wouldn’t load said slides. Jasper offhandedly remarked that he was paying the price for not having restarted his computer for a couple weeks, and I similarly offhandedly implored everyone to restart their computers once a day, if not more. Immediately a horde of my coworkers began clowning my adherence to good computer hygiene, and even more so when I mentioned that I have been known to restart my computer four or five times a day.
Here’s the thing: I am right and they are wrong. There is no reason to not shut down your computer, at the very least, at the end of the day, and boot it up fresh the next morning. Their qualms were easily batted away. Oh no, what about my tabs?!?! Every browser now has the ability to restore your last session, so you can get your stinkin’ tabs back that way. (Side note: Excessive tabs are an argument for another day.) Who cares if it runs a little slow, I don’t need my computer’s full processing power and memory to write a post. It’s much nicer when you can flit around the internet at lightning speed without your browser slowing to a crawl. You are a slave to the machines. Fine, but my machine at least runs reliably and with great speed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Pierce Turns Grim Men’s Wager Into Pleasant Men’s March]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189176</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/paul-pierce-turns-grim-mens-wager-into-pleasant-mens-march"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T14:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been a while since we last checked in with Paul Pierce, the world's foremost practitioner of the grim men's lifestyle. He does some studio work for FS1 now—that tracks—and on Wednesday's episode of Speak, he made a bold proclamation: If the Boston Celtics lost Game 2 of the Eastern Conference semifinals to the New York Knicks, he would walk to work the next day. This was quite the promise, as Pierce stated on air that he lives some 15 miles from the studio where Speak is filmed.
We all know what happened in Game 2, and we are pleased to report that Pierce seems to have actually followed through on his promise. Before sunrise on the west coast he fired up his Instagram account and posted a video of himself—wearing sweatpants, a t-shirt, and a robe—leaving his house to begin his long walk. "Welcome to this journey, here I go," he said in the dark of the early morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every Episode Of The Danny McBride HBO Universe, Ranked]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188695</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/every-episode-of-the-danny-mcbride-hbo-universe-ranked"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T14:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Righteous Gemstones' final episode aired on Sunday, closing another chapter in what has been a 16-year project by comedian-writer-creator Danny McBride and his co-creators/friends from college, Jody Hill and David Gordon Green, to tell the stories of life in the South and the fantasies of American exceptionalism. The stories of career charlatans, egomaniacal has-beens, greedy televangelists, drug-addicted hustlers, hard-living gamblers, and human volcanoes ready to burst; the kinds of people who inspire Warren Zevon or Townes Van Zandt songs. No one has captured 21st-century America with more specificity, showing the comical obsessions—with hypermasculinity and accumulation—that always threaten to destroy us.
In 2009, McBride teamed up with his friends and collaborators from the University of North Carolina School of the Arts, namely Hill, Green, and Ben Best, to create Eastbound & Down. McBride played Kenny Powers, a John Rocker-meets-Jose Canseco type of baseball superstar at the worst point in his life. All of his money and success and chances to play had burned out, reducing him to moving in with his brother Dustin (John Hawkes) and filling in as a substitute PE teacher at the elementary school where his former love April (Katy Mixon) works. Eastbound proved that McBride and his team could take what might have been a silly sitcom and elevate it to a novelistic character study of man in a spiritual battle between his worst impulses and his desires for change and human connection. It was an instant hit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Only Takes A Second]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189204</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mcdavid-draisaitl-yes-again"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T13:28:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the start of overtime, your mid-drowse blogger took a look at the scoresheet for Oilers–Golden Knights, and then looked again, on a different site, because he thought the first one must have been glitching or something. Four Edmonton goals, and none involved Leon Draisaitl or Connor McDavid? Not even a single measly assist? That can't be right. But it was true: For 75 minutes, including that ensuing overtime, Vegas clamped down on the Oilers' superlative-scoring duo, keeping them off the board and mostly away from any serious threats. They needed to do it for 76.
There was a lot to like about the game the Knights played, which makes the 5-4 result that much more painful. They made life miserable for Calvin Pickard, scoring four goals for the first time since Game 4 of the Wild series. They capitalized on two of their five power plays, Victor Olofsson scoring both times. Their kill was flawless, especially on a five-minute man-disadvantage in overtime. Their top skaters were buzzing, Jack Eichel contributing three assists and Mark Stone two apples of his own. They even mounted a stirring comeback, clawing back from 3-1 and then 4-2 in the third to send it to an extra frame.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Accursed Chicago Baseball Fan Base Will Get To Claim Pope Leo XIV?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189200</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/which-accursed-chicago-baseball-fan-base-will-get-to-claim-pope-leo-xiv"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T12:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would seem that The Fourteenth Leo has some clarification to make regarding his CV. Not about his papal bona fides, which we are neither fit nor inclined to judge. So far, he knows how to wave to people who like him, which is both something and maybe most of the actual job. The issue, here, is whether he grew up a Cubs fan, as originally reported, or whether he is, as his brother later told WGN News, a White Sox fan. He owes the world an answer, and that clarification better not be in Latin, or read out of some leather-bound book of ancient Hebrew—if the Pope has an opinion about DeWayne Wise, we’ll need to hear it in plain, nasally Chicagoan. Preferably while Archbishop of the 35th Avenue Diocese Harold Baines holds up a copy of the Sun-Times behind him.
It would not be unlike some surreptitious member of Big Cub, perhaps the shadowy Archbishop Bartman, to jump the gun on "Pope Durocher," as they doubtless would call him. But let's say that the former Bobby Prevost’s brother John is right. Let’s say that the man who is now the pope did grow up a White Sox fan, in a household with a Cubs fan mother and a Cardinals fan father. There would, in this case, be some signs of pre-papal equanimity in making that compromise choice between two arch-rivals, and picking the White Sox would also make sense given that meek-inheriting-the-earth lie. He could put that debate to rest for good by beginning his papacy by forgiving all the Black Sox and Arnold Rothstein, too. But we can only speculate on such matters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Trevor Richards To Minor League Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=851352</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-sign-trevor-richards-to-minor-league-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T00:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have signed right-hander Trevor Richards to a minor league deal, according to an announcement from the Omaha Storm Chasers, Kansas City’s Triple-A affiliate. The righty has been assigned to Omaha and will give the Royals some non-roster bullpen depth. Richards, 32 next week, hasn’t been in good form lately. The Twins acquired him…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A wing and a prayer]]></title>
        <id>681d11c074fb8d000119b6c9</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-316/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T22:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A dream of care and convalescence from Sam Thielman]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charisma]]></title>
        <id>681cfd9074fb8d000119b685</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/charisma/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T22:48:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summer after I turned twelve my granddad shot a dove with a BB gun and called me in a panic. 
He, that is my grandfather, was a really charismatic old guy. People always think of charisma as a sort of superpower but in my experience there’s]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Thielman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State Of The Onion, With Ben Collins]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189075</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-state-of-the-onion-with-ben-collins"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T20:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's not a lot of identifiably positive progress happening out there at the moment, but this week's episode does mark a short but nonetheless real step in the right direction. We first tried to book Ben Collins as a guest back when he was at NBC News, and were given a polite but definitive "maybe come back in one calendar year" from that network's press handlers. It may well have been for the best. Ben's old beat—the political version of online psychopathy, more or less—probably would have made for a compelling bummer of an episode, but it would have been a bummer for sure. While it's hard to say the broader world is doing much better now than it was then, this week's episode—which is just Ben and me, as Drew is off—is much happier. So, it seems, is Ben, who led the group that bought The Onion a year ago, and which has since overseen both an ambitious expansion and a total vibe refurbishment. Which means that, instead of talking about the absolute worst stuff online, we were talking about one of the few truly sunny-sided stories in American media.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Well, They Made A Cubs Fan The Pope]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189157</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/well-they-made-a-cubs-fan-the-pope"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T18:46:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Pope Leo XIV is truly from Chicago, he celebrated the news of his election by firing down a Malört with an Old Style chaser and eagerly accepting an invitation from the Cubs to sing "Take Me Out To The Ball Game." Otherwise, well, what's the point of the Chicago thing at all?
The first American-born pope, the Villanova-educated artist formerly known as Cardinal Robert Francis Prevost, just picked up his new gig, and within a half-hour the Pittsburgh Pirates used his election as cover to announce the firing of manager Derek Shelton, proving that Leo’s is truly the first National League Central papacy. Or it just proves that opportunism knows no season, and only the Pirates and their mudslide public relations sense could see the use in doing it this way. "The Pope has our back," you could almost hear owner Bob Nutting saying. "Let's do it now." It probably didn't happen exactly that way, but also nothing says they had to announce it then. Whatever the case, the announcement of Don Kelly as Pittsburgh’s new manager will not lead the local news this evening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Surfer’ Mostly Sputters And Flails]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189152</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-surfer-mostly-sputters-and-flails"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T18:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Hollywood, a surfer can be one of three things: a weed-smoking, wave-chasing airhead (Jeff Spicoli); a crunchy, woo-woo hippie (some of the penguins in the startlingly charming Surf’s Up); or an edgy, degenerate type, whose passion for adrenaline is paired with a generally violent demeanor (Patrick Swayze’s Bodhi in Point Break). The truth, as ever, is somewhere in between—you can expect even the gentlest of “soul-surfers” to hiss and fight over their home break. 
What, then, can we make of the unnamed protagonist (played by Nicholas Cage) in Lorcan Finnegan’s latest feature, The Surfer, beaten and humiliated in his quest to surf the Edenic waves of Luna Bay, the Australian beach where he grew up? Having been born there doesn’t grant him status as a local: “Don’t live here, don’t surf here,” goes the tag-line spat at him by the local crew. In the days leading up to Christmas, the surfer drives to the Bay to show his son the house where he grew up, which he is on the verge of buying back, if only he can outbid a competitive buyer. The surfer has long neglected his family, and a return to the wholesomeness of the beach—the beautiful surfing, the house perched on the cliff, the memory of an idyllic childhood—might help rebuild the relationships that have been sacrificed at the altar of his career.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafaela Bassili</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired Web Content Manager At The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188269</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-web-content-manager-at-the-consumer-financial-protection-bureau"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T17:46:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before Chuck Sebian-Lander joined the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau as a web content manager, he knew about as much about the agency as "anybody who watched The Big Short and got really angry about it," he said. Previously, he'd worked as a proofreader and then project manager for a federal contractor that served federal health agencies, and Sebian-Lander saw this work as tremendously important, if slightly removed from his day-to-day life—"they're doing work studying diseases I've never heard of or they're treating children's cancer," he said.
Once at the CFPB, however, Sebian-Lander immediately understood how that agency's work intersected with his own life. He graduated with student debt, and he and his wife took out a mortgage to buy their home. In his work on the CFPB's website, he maintained pages that shared educational information about auto loans, bank loans, credit cards, credit reports, and credit scores, and debt. "It's all stuff that everybody has to deal with in a very existential way, even if you're a perfectly healthy person," he said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The DOGE Fencing Hearing Was Stupid And Pointless Even By Congressional Standards]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189068</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-doge-fencing-hearing-was-stupid-and-pointless-even-by-congressional-standards"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest in the long line of futile congressional sports hearings happened Wednesday. You probably missed it, as most people did. I was one of about 1,000 people watching it, according to YouTube at the time. Since then, about 12,000 people—out of a country of more than 341 million—have watched, though of course there's no way to know how many watched for more than the 30 seconds it takes YouTube to count a view. Like the sports-centered hearings that came before it, about steroids in baseball and sexual abuse in gymnastics, it was mostly political theater. Where it differed is in the intended audience. Previous hearings were about creating sound bites for television. This one was for the memes.
Officially, Wednesday's DOGE subcommittee was called to discuss the viral story about a fencer who refused to compete against another fencer in a minor competition because her opponent was a trans woman. In reality it was mostly yelling and grandstanding to be cut and clipped for the internet. The Republicans yelled at the Democrats. The Democrats yelled at the Republicans. The Republicans waved around Trump executive orders. The Democrats waved around charts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals’ Rotation Looks Stronger Than Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=851327</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/the-royals-rotation-looks-stronger-than-ever.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T16:40:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals had one of baseball’s best rotations in 2024. Kansas City starters posted a 3.55 earned run average that trailed only the 3.38 mark of Seattle’s star-studded staff. They logged 911 innings, again second-best in MLB behind the Mariners. Seth Lugo and Cole Ragans placed among the top four in AL Cy Young balloting. Michael Wacha and Brady…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikal Bridges Is Making A Meal Of The Celtics’ Mess]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189111</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mikal-bridges-is-making-a-meal-of-the-celtics-mess"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtics lost again, and now find themselves in an extremely precarious position: down 0-2 to the Knicks and heading to New York for the next two games of the Eastern Conference Semifinals. This is not a position that a 61-win defending champion is supposed to find itself in, so what the hell is going on here?
It can be frustrating to attempt any meaningful analysis of a Celtics loss, because the team's style of play only ever produces one answer: The three-point shot wasn't falling. The Celtics blew 20-point leads in both Game 1 and Game 2 because the shots they count on to go in simply did not. Boston set an NBA playoff record by missing 45 threes in Game 1, and lost Wednesday night's contest, 91-90, behind a 10-of-40 shooting display from behind the arc. If a few more of those shots hit at their average rate, the Celtics are up 2-0 right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allowing For Various Metaphors]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189112</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/allowing-for-various-metaphors"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T15:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the second straight game of their Eastern Conference semifinal series against the New York Knicks, the Boston Celtics blew a 20-point second-half lead, turned the ball over to Mikal Bridges at the most crucial possible moment, and lost. In his wee-hours postgame blog about this, ESPN's Brian Windhorst wrote the following sentence:
[Celtics star Jayson] Tatum didn't address the media after the game because TD Garden had to be evacuated because of a fire alarm, allowing for various metaphors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tread, Baby, Tread. Just Not On Me.]]></title>
        <id>681cbd180643d000010d33d4</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/tread-baby-tread-just-not-on-me/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T14:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bad faith of the Don't Tread On Me crowd has been fully exposed in this second Trump term]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Knicks And Maple Leafs Are Refusing To Stick To The Script]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189114</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-knicks-and-maple-leafs-are-refusing-to-stick-to-the-script"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T14:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are essentially two kinds of playoffs—the playoffs themselves, and the stranger, smaller sub-spectacle in which the New York Knicks and Toronto Maple Leafs get their fan bases excited. We have reached that second stage.
This will not be a slagging of either of those respective fan bases; first, we've already done that, and second, those fans are not responsible for the latest tandem developments. The Knicks and Leafs are now both two games to the good against the defending champions in their respective sports, and have gotten there on merit as well as through the temporary shortcomings of their alleged betters. If that isn't enough to reboot your will to live, well, you're either a Boston Celtics fan or The Dan LeBatard Show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On His Third Team Of The Season, Mikko Rantanen Is Second To None]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189086</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/on-his-third-team-of-the-season-mikko-rantanen-is-second-to-none"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T12:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right after Mikko Rantanen completed his natural hat trick en route to a 3-2 Stars win in their series-opener in Winnipeg, Stars GM Jim Nill could've been forgiven for breaking out the slip 'n' slide goal celebration. It would have been ill-advised; suite carpeting burns something fierce. But this, in Dallas's wildest dreams and the worst nightmares of the two teams who previously employed him this season, is why the Stars bet the farm and mortgaged a few drafts to lock up the 28-year-old Finn for most of the next decade. At that moment, the winger was decidedly on a heater. Six of the last seven Stars goals, dating back to Game 7 against Colorado, had come off Rantanen's stick. Six of eight scored by anybody, on either team, were his. He racked up his consecutive hat tricks in just 14:53 of ice time. It is possible no one has even been hotter.
"The chance to acquire and extend one of the best forwards in the NHL is an opportunity that we couldn’t pass up," Nill said at the time, and while it's boilerplate front-officespeak, truisms don't get to be truisms without being, you know, true. Superstars don't come available often in this league, not in their primes, not in a league that sometimes seems designed to deny us the drama of player movement. And superstars win games. And Rantanen proved the difference between Dallas going home in the first round and beating the Avs—and, for the Avs, not having him was the reason they're booking tee times. Now he's got the Stars up a game, solving home-ice Connor Hellebuyck thrice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Stephen Nogosek To Minor League Contract]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=851293</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-sign-stephen-nogosek-to-minor-league-contract.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T02:37:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals added reliever Stephen Nogosek on a minor league deal and assigned him to Triple-A Omaha. The move was announced by the affiliate. Nogosek, 30, signs out of the Mexican League. He’d made 10 appearances for the Diablos Rojos. The surface numbers aren’t all that impressive. The righty gave up 10 runs (six earned) on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A pack of villains / The comfort of the boss]]></title>
        <id>681ba76174fb8d000119a1c5</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-315/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T23:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Saward on advances in biotechnology; insights on the Latino vote from Felipe De La Hoz]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Something Dire]]></title>
        <id>681bb27c74fb8d000119a2a3</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/something-dire/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T23:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A letter to the new young wolves]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Saward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Foreman You Can Trust]]></title>
        <id>681ba7ac74fb8d000119a1d7</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/a-foreman-you-can-trust/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T23:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Texto en español
English text

Texto en español
Cada cuatro años, los comentaristas, periodistas y políticos angloparlantes perciben, como si por primera vez, que no existe tal cosa como un bloque electoral unificado de latinoamericanos en los Estados Unidos. Al igual que]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felipe De La Hoz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Still Know Babies]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188974</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-still-know-babies"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T18:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I found myself holding a baby the other day. It wasn't my baby, because I’m old and snipped. The baby in question belonged to my best friend, Howard. Howard is my age but got married late and is having his first child. Howard’s wife, Yesenia, is closer in age to him than to Jordon Hudson, so the arrival of this baby—her first child, as well—was never cleanly assured. A middle-aged pregnancy means that the mother and child are at a statistically higher risk for birth defects, miscarriage, and other terrifying complications. The mother also has to carry around a bowling ball sitting atop her bladder all day long. Tricky business.
I remember all that from when my wife I had our own kids. I remember the fear. I remember the emergency bedrest. I remember long nights in an alarmingly bustling NICU. You find out you’re expecting and your instincts force you to account for everything that can go wrong. Those instincts don’t leave you. Ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mess At Newark Airport Is Only The Beginning]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188966</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-mess-at-newark-airport-is-only-the-beginning"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T17:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is one feed—a remote line described as a "long extension cord"—that connects the radar for air traffic above Newark Airport to the air traffic controllers in Philadelphia, who make sure that planes take off and land safely. The line has gone down at least twice before, and last week, on Apr. 28, it went down again.
“We use floppy disks. We use copper wires,” Transportation Secretary Sean Duffy said on Friday. “The system that we’re using is not effective to control the traffic that we have in the airspace today.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inter Survived A War For The Ages]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188970</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/inter-survived-a-war-for-the-ages"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T17:18:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seemed impossible to top the first leg of the Champions League semifinal between Internazionale and Barcelona, a beautiful concerto of impossible goals and individual stardom. And yet, the two clubs, fighting savagely for a spot in the final, went out on Tuesday at the San Siro and not only topped it, but sent the entire tie into tournament lore. Seven goals across 120 minutes, unheralded stopgaps stepping into the spotlight, another magnificent goalkeeping display, a center back scoring the goal of his life ... the second leg had it all and more, and it was only due to a moment of nervous excellence from Inter's Davide Frattesi that the Italian side is on its seventh Champions League final, while Barcelona will rue this narrowest of missed opportunities.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qudvFiKZ6lY]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Any “Halfway Decent Person” Can Join And Own Ireland’s Oldest Gym]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188820</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/any-halfway-decent-person-can-join-and-own-irelands-oldest-gym"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T16:39:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DUBLIN — It’s raining. In Dublin this is as predictable as the phases of the moon. So predictable that I prewrote this lede. But I was right: It’s raining.
I’m in the capital chasing a fascination of mine. I turn off a modern thoroughfare and squeeze my Yaris down a narrow residential street. Older, brickwork houses and apartments stretch around a maze of similar streets ahead of me. Just before the houses, I find my quarry. The Hercules Club, founded 1935, is Ireland’s oldest gym and fully owned and operated by its members.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jasper Hutson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leon Draisaitl Makes Everything Easier]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189009</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/leon-draisaitl-makes-everything-easier"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T16:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adin Hill had a bad day at the office. As the Edmonton Oilers came back from 0-2 down to take Game 1 in Las Vegas, 4-2, every goal let in by the Golden Knights netminder seemed to leave him in a slapstick position. The first Edmonton tally had Hill spinning like a turtle on his backside. The go-ahead game-winner late in the third period saw him uselessly holding up his glove like he was waving hello to an enemy who'd already sped by him at 160 kph. And the insurance tally, soon after, completely isolated Hill when the Other Connor—Brown—conjured a counterattack breakaway and enjoyed plenty of time to pick his spot.
But that's only three out of four! The best Oiler goal, to me, came from their most productive player all year. That's right: Leon Draisaitl. Expecting someone different?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rolling The 20-Sided Dice On Love]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189002</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rolling-the-20-sided-dice-on-love"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T15:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve dabbled in D&D, but I’ve never tried live action role-playing, otherwise known as LARPing. To be completely honest with you, I bet I’d be a happier person if I tried it. I suspect that LARPing shapes your spirit and tempers your character. 
Luckily for the people in this story, they won’t share my regrets. Today we’re bringing you a tale straight from Camp Gonedoor, where many a camper (and many a counselor) have come of age. What does it mean to come of age? For some, it may mean surviving your first midnight encounter with a Ouija board. For others, it may mean figuring out how to be the dungeon master of your own life. For our friend of a friend, it means finding the courage to figure out if his crush likes him back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Abundance Of Concrete]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188808</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-abundance-of-concrete"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T14:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reliable sources tell me that you're not supposed to judge a book by its cover. Until you actually read the thing, though, it's the only data you have to go on. So here's what I first noticed about Abundance, Ezra Klein's and Derek Thompson's zeitgeisty manifesto touting a construction-oriented liberalism: the wildlife. At risk of describing a jacket that you've already seen on a thousand podcast promo posts and airport bookstore racks, Abundance's cover depicts a planet neatly divided in two, with skyscrapers and farms and solar arrays juxtaposed against a jungly hemisphere replete with swooping birds and happy deer. It all recalls Half-Earth, the idea proposed by the biologist E.O. Wilson that 50 percent of our landscape should be devoted to the conservation of nature. So far, so good. 
Look a little closer, though, and you'll notice something odd: The animals don't really make sense, at least not on the cover of a book about American politics. The deer, which has the white spots of a fawn but the majestic rack of a trophy buck, is probably an Indian chital. The most conspicuous bird appears to be a scarlet ibis, a species native to South and Central America. Wherever you can find these fantastic beasts, it generally ain't this continent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Goldfarb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tyrese Haliburton Sure Knows How To Pick His Spots]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188924</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tyrese-haliburton-sure-knows-how-to-pick-his-spots"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cleveland's home crowd was caught chanting "overrated" at Pacers star Tyrese Haliburton during the second quarter of Tuesday night's Game 2. Donovan Mitchell, performing heroically for a severely depleted Cavaliers squad that was at that moment up 10 points, made an effort to discourage the chanting, but it persisted long enough to be picked up by TNT's microphones. This was a minor miracle: The production quality Tuesday was somehow even worse than it was Sunday. Greg Anthony's diving bell was even deeper into the Mariana Trench; the berserk home crowd's teeth-rattling clamor was reduced to an occasional slithering and shuffling; a bizarrely tuned court-side microphone managed to pick up no sound except for one Cavs fan screaming "bullshit" at key whistles. But the mics sure picked up that "overrated" chant. It's not that this is bad crowd behavior—it is, in fact, good and appropriate crowd behavior when facing a divisional foe in the playoffs—but it turned out that this was an unfortunate night to be caught on the record mocking Indiana's point guard.
Haliburton was quiet for most of the night, but it was generally the good kind of quiet, a biding of time that suited the contours of the game. The Cavs, still without Darius Garland but now also without top perimeter defender De'Andre Hunter plus literal Defensive Player of the Year Evan Mobley, ramped up their defensive intensity, threw their deeply unsexy point-of-attack defenders way the hell up the floor, and helped on dribble-penetration like absolute demons. The effort and precision of it all was downright stirring to watch, and it flustered several of Indiana's ball-handlers, and before the Pacers had developed anything like an offensive rhythm the scoreboard showed them down 20 points. Presumably the crowd was losing it, though I will need someone who was there in person to confirm this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popcorn time]]></title>
        <id>681a69cd74fb8d0001198e6b</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-314/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T00:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A.J. Daulerio predicts your summer cinema hits]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Preview of the Biggest and Best Summer Movies of 2025]]></title>
        <id>681a453774fb8d0001198e1a</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/a-preview-of-the-biggest-and-best-summer-movies-of-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T00:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Due to a fortunate birthdate, I was 11 years old during the vaunted “Summer of 1985” movie season which released heavy hitters like Back to the Future, Cocoon, Fletch, and Rambo: First Blood Part II. It was also jam-packed with many of my personal old favorites—Summer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>A.J. Daulerio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oh No, It’s Another Emotional Story About My Cat!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188789</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/oh-no-its-another-emotional-story-about-my-cat"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T19:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not sure when I first noticed she was gone. Our cat had been sleeping next to me since we’d moved into the new place five years ago. Sometimes she slept at my wife’s feet instead. She was almost always in our bed at night. Then one day it stopped.
Detective John Munch, which is the name of the cat, wouldn’t come upstairs with us when we went to bed. She was going up later and sleeping on the third floor, we thought? I wasn’t sure. All I knew for sure was that she wasn’t with us at night, and so wasn’t where she’d been there pretty much ever since I met Detective (and my future wife). Eventually she began avoiding our bedroom entirely. The past year or so, she’d been spending most of her days sleeping in the little fabric cove that approximated a yurt. “She’s in her yurt!” I’d say as I took my 10,000th lifetime photo of our cat sleeping. But when I walked into our bedroom, she’d never be there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtics Will Just Keep Doing This Until We Are All Driven Insane]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188894</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-celtics-will-just-keep-doing-this-until-we-are-all-driven-insane"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T18:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The higher-seeded and hosting Boston Celtics lost Game 1 of their Eastern Conference semifinal series against the New York Knicks on Monday night, 108–105. The Celtics led by 16 at halftime, and by 20 midway through the third quarter, and then spent the rest of the night barfing into their laps. Here is the funniest number from the night: 45. That is how many three-point attempts the Celtics missed in Game 1. No NBA team has ever missed that many threes in a single playoff game before.
Even at their best, the Celtics under coach Joe Mazzulla play offense with a kind of numbing actuarial bloodlessness: 3 > 2, forever and ever, and so they just keep huckin' up those three-pointers—an appalling 54 percent of their field goal attempts were threes this season, seven points higher than any other team—and trust the math, supported by their outstanding defense, to sort itself out. Last season it did, and they won the Finals, and they might do it again this year. At their worst, though, this approach lapses into what looks like team-wide obsessive-compulsive disorder, as it did on Monday night, with the game steadily slipping away from Boston for the final 18 minutes of regulation and the overtime period and the blank-eyed Celtics just continually pumping up those threes, clang-clang-clang. They attempted 49 field goals in the second half and overtime, and 37 of them were threes, and 27 of those threes were misses. Their third-quarter shot chart looks like a cry for help:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired EPA Environmental Justice Program Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187739</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-epa-environmental-justice-program-analyst"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way Amanda Cronin sees it, her environmental education began at the farmers' market in her hometown in New York's Hudson Valley. She marveled at the sheer abundance of produce, so much so that, at age 11, she became the market's on-camera personality. Every Saturday, she would go to the market and interview a farmer about their growing process, such as how olive oil becomes "extra virgin." She tasted her first oysters and learned about the distinction between organic foods and other green-washed labels. Eventually she read Michael Pollan's The Omnivore's Dilemma, which cemented the idea that "our food system is broken and Big Ag is really corrupt," she said.
Cronin started working directly for the planet at the age of 13. She interned for an organization called iMatter Youth, which encompassed youth-led organizing for the climate crisis. "Because I was so young, I couldn't really be a full-time employee," she said. iMatter Youth's mission was to train youth activists across the country to make changes at a municipal level, exposing Cronin not just to the power of environmental policy, but the concept of environmental justice: the idea that everyone, regardless of race, class, or any other identity, deserves the same environmental protections and benefits. The idea just made sense to her. "I grew up in a very privileged place where I had access to clean water, clean air, a backyard to roam around in," she said. "I didn't have to worry about living near a power plant, or have direct environmental harms."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s The Worst CD You’ve Ever Purchased?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188800</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/whats-the-worst-cd-youve-ever-purchased"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T17:09:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about pepper, normalcy, cooking while baked, and more.
Before we get to the festivities, a quick “only in New York” story for all of youse. I drive into the city on Thursday to visit my friend. I park my car in a garage because I’m don’t have the energy to battle it out for a street spot. It’s one of those tight garages with a car elevator to accommodate all of the inventory, so you have to surrender your keys to them, visions of the joyriding parking attendants from Ferris Bueller dancing through your neuroses. This isn’t my first time in such a garage, so I give up my key fob and then go about my business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ravens Release Justin Tucker, Claim It’s A “Football Decision”]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188815</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ravens-release-justin-tucker-claim-its-a-football-decision"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T16:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFL kicker Justin Tucker is currently under investigation by the league because 16 massage therapists have accused him of sexual misconduct. On Monday, he was released by the only team he's ever played for, the Baltimore Ravens. But if those two things are related, the Ravens are pointedly refusing to admit it.
The way that Baltimore announced Tucker's exit would have made perfect sense if you saw it before January, when his claim to fame was still his lengthy run of incredible accuracy. The 35-year-old had a team-friendly out in his contract for this offseason, and he's coming off the least effective year of his career. To that end, this statement—credited to EVP and GM Eric DeCosta—has all the hallmarks of a typical farewell to a beloved veteran-in-decline. "Sometimes football decisions are incredibly difficult, and this is one of those instances," it begins, presumably to avoid giving grounds for a potential NFLPA grievance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trent Alexander-Arnold Gave Liverpool Everything It Needed]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188670</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/trent-alexander-arnold-gave-liverpool-everything-it-needed"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T15:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a long courting period and the slow march of inevitability, Trent Alexander-Arnold confirmed on Monday that he will be leaving Liverpool this summer, almost certainly to take his talents to Spain and Real Madrid. The news is hardly a shock, since reliable reports had for several months been saying this was going to happen, but it's still noteworthy that the local lad, who has spent his entire youth and senior careers as a Pool Boy, is leaving Merseyside to test himself at the biggest club in the world.
Put that way, you can't fault Alexander-Arnold, who won everything with Liverpool in his nine first-team seasons, including two Premier League trophies. The England international has appeared 330 times for Liverpool, scoring 21 goals and notching 82 often incredible assists (64 of those came in the Premier League, a record for a defender), and though he may have taken some reputational knocks for his lackluster defending, there's little to criticize about his tenure at his boyhood club, which also included an FA Cup, two League Cups, and the 2018-19 Champions League trophy. For almost the entirety of his time marauding down the right flank as a right back/playmaker/passing genius, Alexander-Arnold was one of the engines that drove Liverpool in this era of success, and his partnership especially with Mohamed Salah made opposing left backs squirm under repeated interplays and pinpoint crosses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gregg Popovich Was Too Far Ahead To Be Patient]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188627</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/gregg-popovich-was-too-far-ahead-to-be-patient"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T14:21:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The night your author got Popped came at the onset of an epic hangover nobody quite knew about yet. More specifically, it came early in the 2017 Western Conference Finals that elevated the Golden State Warriors and slowly but surely undid the San Antonio Spurs. Two days earlier, Kawhi Leonard had landed on Zaza Pachulia's foot on a shot in front of the San Antonio bench, ending his season and obliterating most of the next. That moment fundamentally changed the ensuing years of professional basketball more than any other player, team, or event. Nobody knew that then, of course, but it dawned on Gregg Popovich before it did for anyone except perhaps Leonard himself.
The Spurs, who were up 76-55 in the third quarter of the game when Leonard got hurt, went on to lose it 113-111; they dropped Game 2 by the score of 136-100, and then lost the two after that. Until that moment the Spurs had been, in the previous 20 years under Popovich, demonstrably and by a wide margin the best team in the sport; since then, they are 25th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Wouldn’t Be A Panthers Postseason Without A Cheap Shot By Sam Bennett]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188756</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/panthers-leafs-stolarz-bennett"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:43:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Maple Leafs started off about as well as a team can, with William Nylander scoring his first of two goals 33 seconds in, and building to a three-goal lead before the game's midway point, after which they held on for a 5-4 victory over the Panthers. It's a big change from the last time they faced Florida, when, two years ago, in their only taste of the second round in forever, they went down 0-3 in the series and fell in five. And yet this win tastes a little bitter, because of the I-word: implications. It's got 'em, thanks to Sam Bennett forcing goalie Anthony Stolarz from the game with an elbow to the head.
There hasn't been a formal update on Stolarz, but he was taken to the hospital for observation in an ambulance, after cameras caught him vomiting on the bench a few minutes after the Bennett hit—classic concussion stuff. He's out of the hospital this morning, at least. There was no penalty called on the play, and it's not clear if Bennett will face supplemental discipline from the league, but the Leafs were furious. "Elbow to the head," head coach Craig Berube said. "Clearly. Clear as day. I'm not sure why there wasn't a call on it, but it was clearly a penalty."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That Was All Mark’s Dang Fault]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188760</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/that-was-all-marks-dang-fault"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T13:28:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hypothetical: You are an NBA head coach and your team is leading a playoff game by three points with 11.1 seconds to go. The opposing team is getting ready to inbound the ball from under their own basket, they have no timeouts, and their best player is stuck on the bench. Do you foul and send them to the line, or trust your ferocious defenders—I forgot to mention that you have the best defense in the league—to get set and deal with what will surely be a semi-panicked attempt to fling up a potential game-tying shot? If you're Thunder head coach Mark Daigneault, you choose to lose the game.
It is always cruel and simplistic to hang a bad result on one play, decision, or even set of decisions, but Daigneault cannot be spared the hot light of scrutiny after he and the Thunder fumbled away Game 1 of their second-round series against the Denver Nuggets. The Thunder were up 11 with 4:31 left to play, and seemed ready to put away a game that they had led and dominated all night. A shocking 12-2 Nuggets run made it 115-114 with 1:07 to play, which is about when the bad decisions started being made. The teams traded misses on the next two possessions, and Shai Gilgeous-Alexander ended up at the line with 14 seconds left. He hit both free throws to put the Thunder up by three.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 'Abundance Agenda,' Torpedo Bats, And The Limits Of Reflexivity]]></title>
        <id>680934f7db769a000141c5d5</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/the-abundance-agenda-torpedo-bats-and-the-limits-of-reflexivity/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T11:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The left can't be defined by only talking about complex solutions to complex problems]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Elrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burn the flags / Split the check]]></title>
        <id>681904329d3b0600014eb266</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-313/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T21:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Julianne Escobedo Shepherd’s poetic fire; new fiction from Miles Klee]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the Blood]]></title>
        <id>6818a6789d3b0600014eb174</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/in-the-blood/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T21:07:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following is an excerpt from The Last Year, a longer work of fiction currently in progress. The previous chapter is available here. 

I am broke by most definitions.
That is, I am down to my last two weeks of severance pay, and the approximately $450 per week from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miles Klee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Borders Are Fake]]></title>
        <id>6818b57d9d3b0600014eb1b3</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/borders-are-fake/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T21:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fact that borders are divorced from reality has long vexed me. They are fictions drawn by men wielding guns and pens, men whose avarice has turned them maniacal. The fact of a fence erected across the Sonoran Desert means nothing to the rest of the natural world, at least]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julianne Escobedo Shepherd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Naoya Inoue And Ramon Cardenas Salvaged Boxing’s Meek Weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188735</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/naoya-inoue-and-ramon-cardenas-salvaged-boxings-meek-weekend"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:44:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ramon Cardenas saved boxing. Or, he at least made the biggest weekend the sport has seen in years memorable for good reasons. But, damn, he took a beating along the way.
Cardenas, obviously overmatched by Japanese opponent Naoya Inoue in everything but heart, knocked the mythically powerful champ down with a lightning-quick and savage left hook in the second round of their thrilling and brutal super bantamweight title fight Sunday in Las Vegas. And for a few moments, the 29-year-old, 122-pound Texan seemed on the verge of pulling off one of boxing’s biggest all-time upsets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Another Ferrari Radio Meltdown Classic]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188658</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-another-ferrari-radio-meltdown-classic"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T19:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We pause our typical post-race Drivers' Championship standings update to bring your attention to an all-important midfield battle that cemented itself at the Miami Grand Prix: the newly corporatized Williams vs. real midfield team Ferrari. This is not an exaggeration, or fluke of the weather, or any particular driver underperformance. As Lewis Hamilton said after the Ferraris qualified P8 and P12, "On pure pace, we've been out-qualified by a Williams." Fact check: The Ferraris were outqualified by two Williams cars.
Charles Leclerc's despondency post-qualifying was equally damning. "When I finish a lap, again today in qualifying, I feel very satisfied with my lap, but it's only bringing us, whatever it is," Leclerc said. "P8 or something."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connor Hellebuyck Earned A Reprieve]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188687</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/connor-hellebuyck-earned-a-reprieve"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T18:51:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is not a website known for holding back when an athlete gives an egregious performance on a big stage, but even I, the cynical blogger hardened by years of easy insults, couldn't help but feel my heart sink when Connor Hellebuyck let in two goals on the St. Louis Blues' first four shots. I've referred to the 10-year Winnipeg Jets vet as the league's hardest-working goalie—this regular season was his fifth topping the NHL in games played—but yet again, it looked like he took an untimely vacation when his team needed him most. It required some incredible Jets magic to bring Hellebuyck back from Fraudwatch, but that's exactly what his teammates did.
Up until three seconds remained in Game 7, Hellebuyck's last three years had all followed a frustrating pattern. In the regular season, he would be an absolute workhorse who produced staggering shot-stopping numbers—the kind that could singlehandedly lift any team into Cup contention. But as soon as the playoffs started, that skill would mysteriously desert him. In 2023, the Golden Knights dispatched the Jets in five as Hellebuyck's save percentage plummeted from .920 in the regular season to .886 for the series. In 2024, Helle won the Vezina Trophy for the second time in his career but made the ceremony a bit awkward by putting up a 5.23 goals against average in a five-game loss to the Avalanche. This series, against a streaking Blues squad, saw him hit a new career low—three yanks in three road losses where he allowed a total of 16 goals, with an overall first-round save percentage of just .830. In his lowest moments, including the first period on Sunday, Jets skaters weren't doing anything to ease his burden. But as the team's most important guy—maybe the single most important guy on any team—it was Hellebuyck's job to provide a solid foundation, and instead he was the sinkhole.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Got To Be Something Better Than In The Middle]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188668</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/got-to-be-something-better-than-in-the-middle"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T17:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following is excerpted from a chapter of The Dad Rock That Made Me a Woman, by Niko Stratis. The book is available for purchase now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niko Stratis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired Science For Development Fellow At USAID]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188225</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-science-for-development-fellow-at-usaid"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T16:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In August, Charla Burnett moved from Michigan to Washington D.C., with her 5-year-old son, for a new job. She joined the first class of USAID Science for Development fellows, working on energy subsidy reform, AI data center placements, and expanding access to renewables around the world. The post would be a stepping stone to full-time employment at USAID as a foreign service officer, which was Burnett's ultimate dream. Burnett was set to take the Foreign Service Exam in February. She took her official USAID portraits on Jan. 11, posing in front of the agency's flag, and soon received the watermarked versions. To Burnett, this felt like a milestone—one she'd been working toward for 13 years. "I felt like I finally made it," Burnett said. Weeks later, she was fired. Ten days after that, the administration canceled her exam.
Hoping, at least, to retain one artifact of her time in federal service, Burnett emailed and asked if the photographer could send her the actual headshots. But he never emailed her back. Burnett suspects he was also fired. "Complete breakdown of communication by everyone, because everyone just got let go," she said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Watch Basketball]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188551</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-to-watch-basketball"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T15:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NBA playoffs are in full swing, and as such, I find myself watching and talking about the games with people who do not watch as much basketball as I do, probably because watching basketball is not their job. A perceptual phenomenon that quickly becomes apparent is that there is so much happening on the TV screen at every moment of a basketball game that it is not easily possible to take in everything in real-time. If you simply watch the ball, you will miss most of what goes on during a possession. Hardcore fans accept this as background radiation, and I ultimately find something beautiful in the existence of such a limit.
I have a suspicion, then, that while most people who are serious about basketball-watching are perceiving the same gestalt, they are assembling that whole out of different arrangements of constituent parts. This is true in the macro sense, as two people can get equal amounts of satisfaction by focusing variably on who is doing cool moves and which offensive system is operating more harmoniously, though what I am talking about is the micro sense: Where does your focus shift? What do you look at during a basketball game?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Posts From The Glorious Future: The End Of Social Media]]></title>
        <id>6818d0a1079e46000164c064</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/blog-posts-from-the-glorious-future-the-end-of-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T15:20:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If representative democracy was going to be re-established in the US, social media had to go]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, May 5: Ice Queens]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188653</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-may-5-ice-queens"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T15:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week's puzzle was constructed by Rachel Fabi and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Rachel (she/her) is a crossword constructor and a professor of bioethics. She is the founder and co-editor of the crossword puzzle fundraiser "These Puzzles Fund Abortion," which raises money for five abortion funds across the country, so if you like crossword puzzles with a progressive bent and helping people afford necessary healthcare, you can donate here through the end of May to receive the puzzle pack!
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pacers Out-Styled The Cavaliers And Swiped Home-Court Advantage]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188634</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-pacers-out-styled-the-cavaliers-and-swiped-home-court-advantage"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T14:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They say the home crowd was extremely noisy Sunday night, in Game 1 of the Eastern Conference semifinal series between the Indiana Pacers and the Cleveland Cavaliers. Play-by-play guy Spero Dedes called it "just deafening." Pacers head coach Rick Carlisle, asked about the challenge facing his young team in the second round of the playoffs, didn't even mention the opponent. "This place is very loud, very crazy," he told TNT sideline reporter Jared Greenberg, after the first quarter. 
I'll have to take their word for it, and not only because my home sound system is pathetic: The broadcast quality sucked shit! After a big awkward crap-out in this same arena back on April 21, TNT's audio was all screwed up again Sunday. Greg Anthony sounded like he was dialing in via Zoom, or had his head submerged in water. Since no one in particular wants to hear from Anthony, this presented more an annoying distraction than a real deficit of information. Several times Dedes's voice was swallowed up at random, so that whatever it was he had to say about a particular event suddenly sounded as if it was being mumbled by someone at the other end of a hallway. Worst of all, the mix deadened crowd noise, so that it was hard to connect with Dedes when he said, during a third-quarter run by the home team, that the arena was the loudest he'd ever heard. I considered the possibility that he was gassing up the event with hyperbole, but the rim noises were distracting and Anthony's voice continued to sound as if it was being bounced off of Voyager 2, so it was easy enough to accept that TNT simply did not want home viewers to experience any of the crowd's ear-splitting enthusiasm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes It’s The Buddy Hield Game]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188631</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/sometimes-its-the-buddy-hield-game"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T13:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Game Sevens take on many forms, and far more often than not the words Game and Seven are heavier on promise than delivery. In a world of rapidly shrinking attention spans, those games are expected to validate the results of Game Six, because we only recall the last thing we saw and imagine that the coaches are out of ideas.
Rarely, though, do Game Sevens deviate from the established norms of the preceding six games the way that Golden State and Houston did on Sunday night. We can start with the obvious plot line: Buddy Hield, Postseason Hero, a phrase making its debut in the English language here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They’ll Talk About That One In Winnipeg Forever]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188635</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/theyll-talk-about-that-one-in-winnipeg-forever"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T13:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No hockey team has historically killed joy faster than the Winnipeg Jets. When they make the postseason, they appear quietly and leave moments later. In fact, Winnipeg itself is from the Cree word for, "lost in the first round." They have been so committed to the bit that it’s still not clear that they actually won Game 7 over the St. Louis Blues Sunday night, even though I have watched the game twice since the actual game ended. The Jets don't win that game because the Jets never win that game.
But here we are. The Jets, known mostly for their seemingly incurable playoff interruptus, set themselves up for yet another galling failure Sunday night and actually failed to fail in a situation where failure was all but assured. They parlayed the league’s best record and the best goalie and turned it into a humiliating 3-1 defeat … that is, until the final 116 seconds of regulation, when they turned it into the first bedtime story Jets fans will tell their grandchildren without firing down a slug of Caribou Crossing to dull the pain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Settlers’ Makes Louis Theroux Say What He Thinks]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188614</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-settlers-makes-louis-theroux-say-what-he-thinks"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T19:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In order to watch The Settlers, I first had to fraudulently assert my right to do so. The latest film by much-lauded documentarian Louis Theroux was broadcast earlier this week on BBC Two, and is available to stream via BBC iPlayer, which you can only access with an IP address in the UK (an international release date is apparently coming soon.) So I lied in order to have the thing I wanted, which seemed fitting enough. 
Theroux has made a name for itself over the years as someone uniquely skilled at getting people to reveal truths they might rather hide. He approaches his subjects—often people with reprehensible beliefs, like Afrikaner separatists or members of the Westboro Baptist Church—with a disarming affability. His slightly naive persona is matched by his physical presence: generally folding in on himself as if embarrassed about his height, bespectacled face often scrunched in a quizzical expression, looking always in danger of tripping over something. He invites people to explain themselves without passing judgment in the moment, relying instead on heavy silences or a voiceover.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Jensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Very Grisly Caterpillar]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188589</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-very-grisly-caterpillar"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T17:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the light of the moon glimmering over just six square miles of a mountain range on O‘ahu, a little egg waited to hatch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, I Attacked That Woman, And I’d Do It Again]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188582</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/yes-i-attacked-that-woman-and-id-do-it-again"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T15:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's get one thing straight: We eagles obey no courts of law. We heed no judges. We've never even heard of the concept that you call "police." So however many times you try to tell me that everything I say can and will be used against me in a court of law, your threats mean nothing to me. The carceral system is for you puny humans, not us noble eagles. I don't come into your home and tell you how to live your life! OK? OK. With that understanding, I will now share my side of the story.
I was minding my business in the tropical forests of French Guiana, which, as you may imagine, is my home. I live by the Kourou River Basin, near the coast, and aside from the occasional ecotourist, my home is undisturbed. Would I prefer a home free of uninvited guests? Yes, obviously. But do I generally put up with a few sightseers? Yes, because I am not an asshole. I watch these tourists as they take photos of smaller, less noble birds, like those annoying-as-hell great kiskadees squawking all day long or those twangy silver-beaked tanagers. All the real big players in the forest, like me and the jaguars, are too smart to be "captured" by a "content creator." But occasionally, when I'm feeling generous or having a great feather day, I'll cock my head and emerge from my perch high in the canopy to give them a little show. I watch them as they snap photos of me with their obscenely phallic camera lenses. In this, at least, we are aligned: I'm literally stunning. If I saw me perched elegantly overhead, I too would have to stop and stare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>A. Harpy Eagle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nikola Jokic’s Friends Showed Up When He Needed Them Most]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188581</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nikola-jokics-friends-showed-up-when-he-needed-them-most"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T14:09:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Considered from an appropriate distance, there is nothing all that noteworthy about the Denver Nuggets prevailing in their first-round series against the Los Angeles Clippers. An evenly matched series eventually broke in the direction of the team with home-court advantage; the team with the best player in the series won it; the Clippers looked noticeably gassed throughout Game 7 after spending a great deal of physical and mental energy to stave off elimination in Game 6. This is pretty much how all this stuff is supposed to go. The fun of watching sports, however, is not just in observing outcomes. It's in feeling the texture of each moment leading up to a result. It's in all the little stories that get told about players and teams over the course of a seven-game series.
Coming into this series, the story of the Nuggets season was one of angst. The team proved just how disappointing a 50-win season can feel, and the end-of-season firings of head coach Michael Malone and general manager Calvin Booth were the front office's way of admitting that an untenable toxicity had infected the whole organization. Through no fault of his own, the source of all this anxiety was Nikola Jokic. Booth and Malone split the franchise into warring factions due to their inability to agree on how best to build a winning roster around the best player in the world. Every loss and stretch of lifeless play stung so bad precisely because of how great of an individual season Jokic was having. Everyone was letting the big fella down, and everyone felt terrible about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Talking To The President]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188372</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/talking-to-the-president"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T21:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is only sort of true to say that you know what you're going to get when Donald Trump sits for a television interview. It is true in the sense that, after a decade spent alternately threatening and occupying the White House, everyone knows how he is going to act. There is some more uncertainty when it comes to what Trump is actually going to do, but even these variables aren't notably variable. He is going to act like Donald Trump, or some version of Donald Trump. This is something that can be prepared for, to some extent.
If he is being interviewed by someone from one of the television channels he likes, Trump will be drawling and digressive in his familiar toastmaster mode, the tone he puts on when he is Making Some Remarks before an audience that he senses is eager to applaud him. "A little secret," he told Fox News' Laura Ingraham while showing her around his increasingly cluttered and gilded oval office, "throughout the years, people have tried to come up with a gold paint that would look like gold. And they've never been able to do it." No, Ingraham agreed, in a tone of hushed awe, while the Fox camera focused on a dorky little golden cherub above a door. "That's why it's gold." He sounds like he's talking in his sleep, murmuring through a dream in which he is doing exactly this sort of thing. That's one version.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Share the glow / leave the ashes]]></title>
        <id>68150bf69d3b0600014e9b60</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-312/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T20:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diana Moskovitz of the BTS ARMY reporting for duty; new fiction from Luke O’Neil]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Almost Beautiful]]></title>
        <id>681396c39d3b0600014e84fa</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/almost-beautiful/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T20:32:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fullest extent of the law
The morning after the wildfires had spread widely enough that they begged addressing the mayor stood up outside of the charred strip mall where we used to get takeout Korean and assured the public that any looters would be dealt with in the harshest]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke O'Neil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lightsticks]]></title>
        <id>6814f6fa9d3b0600014e9abc</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/lightsticks/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T20:28:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I fell into BTS fandom during the height of the COVID-19 pandemic, when all the news was bad and I had plenty of time on my hands to learn what exactly was going on with this Korean boy band that people kept talking about. So I really did want to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Select Luke Maile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=850671</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-select-luke-maile.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T20:13:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that they have selected the contract of catcher Luke Maile. Infielder Tyler Tolbert was optioned to Triple-A Omaha to open an active roster spot. To get Maile onto the 40-man, right-hander Alec Marsh was transferred to the 60-day injured list. More to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wild Fans, This Is Just Your Life Now]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188560</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/wild-fans-this-is-just-your-life-now"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T18:07:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Long-suffering" in a sporting context is largely nonsense, for the very simple reason that the people who complain about it are doing no suffering whatsoever. They're choosing to watch an unaccomplished team, and that's all. We don't need to run down the list of people who are actually suffering, given that the list is growing hourly, but it surely isn't sports fans. In other words, please take time out of your busy and productive days to shut the hell up. 
Besides, suffering even in this milieu is entirely an eye-of-the-beholder deal. New York Knicks fans suffer far less than, say, Charlotte Hornets/ Bobcats/Hornets Again fans, who since losing their original team in 2002, have gotten a new one, missed the playoffs 18 of 21 years, and lost the only three series they have ever played in. Next to this, the prototypical Knicks fan suffers only because of their own idiotic expectations. The notion that because they haven't won a title in 52 years means they're due is exactly the way gamblers go broke.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Lampley Knows Friday Night’s Alright For Fighting]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188399</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jim-lampley-knows-friday-nights-alright-for-fighting"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you enjoy old-timey American pastimes, have I got a weekend for you! Three consecutive nights of televised title fights! Who invited the mid-1950s? 
The fistic windfall kicks off tonight with a poorly planned and bizarrely promoted but intriguing-as-all-getout three-fight, Saudi-sponsored pay-per-view outdoor card at Times Square in New York, with a feature match pitting Ryan Garcia coming back from a PED suspension and intoxicant-addled haze to face Rolly Romero for a welterweight world championship belt. Then on Saturday, boxing's top international draw, Mexico's Canelo Alvarez, celebrates another Cinco de Mayo season in the ring in Riyadh, boxing's new Las Vegas, where he'll fight perhaps the most anonymous champion extant, William Scull, for a super middleweight title. And the capper, maybe best bout of 'em all, comes Sunday in the old Las Vegas, as Japanese KO king Naoya Inoue brings his powers to the west to face Ramon Cardenas for the undisputed junior featherweight championship.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Release Nick Gordon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=850622</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-release-nick-gordon.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:41:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have released infielder/outfielder Nick Gordon, who’d been with their Triple-A affiliate in Omaha, per the transaction log at MiLB.com. He’s free to explore opportunities with other teams. Gordon, 29, has spent time with the Triple-A affiliates for both the Orioles and Royals already in 2025. Kansas City acquired him from Baltimore in exchange…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Vikings Belong To J.J. McCarthy Now, As Does My Cold Black Heart]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188494</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-vikings-belong-to-j-j-mccarthy-now-as-does-my-cold-black-heart"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things are happening in Minnesota. While Rudy Gobert is still busy collecting his 96th rebound against a Lakers team that tried to advance in the NBA playoffs without a frontcourt, the Vikings have used this week as an occasion to unofficially cap off a rebuilding project that they started three years ago:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BNjTAESsqAg]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Went To Japan To See One Building]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188270</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-went-to-japan-to-see-one-building"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T15:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOKYO — Last year, when I visited Major League ballparks in Philadelphia and Minnesota for the first time, I made the same obvious-but-still-true observation: "It looks like it does on TV." Well, Korakuen Hall feels like it does on TV, or at least, on the Japanese wrestling streams I watch on my laptop: unadorned, practical, dignified. Arriving at Tokyo's wrestling epicenter last month, my brain still reeling from an international flight that had landed only the night earlier, I had a hard time distinguishing between my actual presence and the idea that I might be dreaming the whole thing. It was as if the setting had sprung out of two dimensions. The simple bleachers; the "East" and "West" signs, in kanji and English, on either end; the small balconies with banners hanging from them—I had seen it all before, kind of. I had never been within 5,000 miles of it, yet this was a room I knew intimately.
I went to Tokyo, basically, to see Korakuen Hall. I'm about to turn 30, and I have the normal feelings about that. Plus, I'd never traveled internationally except to Canada. I wanted to mark the big 3-0, and also see what it was like out there. So I did some big-time flying around the Pacific, the majority of it by myself, with a few specific destinations in mind. It was an amazing trip, one that affirmed my confidence in my resourcefulness and independence while also reminding me of my incredible luck. But I really think the crown jewel of it all—four cities in four different countries on three continents—was the pro wrestling. I went to three shows at Korakuen—plus one mini-adventure to the outlying wrestling shed Shin-Kiba 1st Ring to see an intimate show from the deathmatch promotion Freedoms—and this building that I had admired from so far away, miraculously, gave me exactly what I was hoping to find.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>