<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-01-14T01:10:15.164Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSGeoLive – Linux distribution focusing on geospatial software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140818</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/osgeolive-linux-distribution-geospatial-software/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T23:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OSGeoLive is a Linux distribution that lets you to try a wide variety of open source geospatial software without installing anything. 
The post OSGeoLive – Linux distribution focusing on geospatial software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kickers Live Their Lives For All To See]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178397</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/kickers-live-their-lives-for-all-to-see"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T21:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before he became the Washington Commanders’ sixth kicker of the season, in mid-November, Zane Gonzalez hadn’t kicked in an NFL game since 2021. He weathered injuries and training-camp battles at one of the more volatile, confounding positions in football. So his mere appearance in Sunday night’s Wild Card game and his doinked-in game-winning field goal made him an appropriate hero for the Cardiac Commanders, who have now won five straight games on the final play from scrimmage.
As a euphoric London Fletcher put it on the Commanders radio call, Gonzalez “kick[ed] in the door and kick[ed] us into the second round of the playoffs” in the team's 23-20 win over the Tampa Bay Buccaneers. After the game, Gonzalez said he’d been dealing with some hip discomfort during his previous kick, but that he felt good about the attempt as it left his foot. “I’m just a small part of a big plan,” he told reporters, adding that he was excited to get home to his wife and newborn son.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Christie Gives The Surprising Kings The Freedom To Be Good]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178407</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/doug-christie-gives-the-surprising-kings-the-freedom-to-be-good"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T19:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since replacing two-time Coach of the Year Mike Brown with Doug Christie, who was in the broadcast booth three seasons ago, the Sacramento Kings have become the hottest team in the NBA. They fired Brown on Dec. 27, after five straight losses, and lost Christie's first game in charge the following night; since then they've won seven in a row and have looked like a totally revitalized team in the process. 
The operative question is: What are the Kings doing differently? I'd like to nominate a stretch of time at the start of the fourth quarter of the game in Boston against the Celtics this past Friday as the most explanatory chunk of play in the short Doug Christie era.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike McCarthy, Who Couldn’t Escape The Cowboys, Escapes The Cowboys]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178410</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mike-mccarthy-who-couldnt-escape-the-cowboys-escapes-the-cowboys"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T19:29:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, when not-yet-former-coach Mike McCarthy was denied permission by the Dallas Cowboys to speak to the Chicago Bears about their own perpetually vacant coaching position, it was obvious that the Cowboys wanted to keep him in his current role as the frontman and designated crap-catcher for their carousel of nonsense. And yet it makes perfect sense, and is somehow exactly as obvious, that the Cowboys fired McCarthy on Monday, the next-to-last day of their exclusive negotiating window with him. I mean, that's how you figured it would go, right—one way or another, the team would find the dumbest thing to do, for the dumbest reason, and do it at the dumbest time. That is the Cowboy Way. And when we say "Cowboys," we mean of course Jerry Jones.
Now you may find that firing McCarthy has its merits; this would especially be true if you somehow saw him as the only thing keeping the Cowboys from their true place at the center of the football universe, which is a denial of both logic and Jones's position as owner/general manager/godhead/glowering presence. This past season alone, McCarthy was up for a new deal after going 3-2 in the first five weeks, fired a million times when they lost the next five in succession, guaranteed a new deal a million and one times because the team then won four of their next five games to get to the edge of playoff contention, and then just left to sear evenly on the hot seat because nobody could figure out how to decipher the two losses at the end of their season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Isaiah Collier Screws Up, Enrages Teammate, Forces Utah Jazz To Win A Basketball Game]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178376</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/isaiah-collier-screws-up-enrages-teammate-forces-utah-jazz-to-win-a-basketball-game"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T17:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Isaiah Collier is having a rough rookie season for the Utah Jazz. That team stinks real bad: After a cute 2022–23 season of pretending not to tank under then-new team CEO Danny Ainge, the Jazz have decided to suck shit for a while, and entered Sunday's home tilt against the Brooklyn Nets with the second-worst record in the Western Conference. They'll get down to the bottom soon enough, provided Zion Williamson of the New Orleans Pelicans can stay ambulatory for a few weeks. Collier, who was taken by the Jazz with the 29th pick in the 2024 draft, is certainly doing his part.
Collier came to the Jazz from USC, where as a hot-shot one-and-done freshman he shared the spotlight with Bronny James on a distressingly Fortnite-coded operation, earning with his chaotic and eyeball-searingly unethical style of play a reputation as someone you dearly hope will never wear the jersey of your favorite professional hoops team. Collier entered Sunday's home game against the Brooklyn Nets shooting 32 percent from the floor and 16 percent on three-pointers, and turning the ball over on more than a third of his possessions. Attention to detail is not yet a strength of his game. This all suits the purposes of a team that wants to lose, even if it sometimes drives his coach and veteran teammates to hysterics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JAWS and the 2025 Hall of Fame Ballot: Ben Zobrist]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=454487</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/jaws-and-the-2025-hall-of-fame-ballot-ben-zobrist/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T17:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The switch-hitting multiposition star helped three teams to the World Series in a nine-year span.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Jaffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[cations – habit tracker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140901</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/cations-habit-tracker/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T16:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[cations is a lightweight application that helps you build and maintain good habits through incremental progress.
The post cations – habit tracker appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“I Dare Not Talk About Nico Collins”: Incarcerated Fantasy Football Managers Reflect On The Season]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178299</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/incarcerated-fantasy-football-managers-reflect-on-the-season"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T16:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was produced in partnership with Empowerment Avenue, a program that supports incarcerated writers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antoine E. Davis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Jan. 13: You Don’t Mean That]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178384</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-jan-13-you-dont-mean-that"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T16:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A great Monday crossword lies ahead. This week's puzzle was constructed by Patrick Maher, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Patrick is a software engineer and occasional crossword constructor. Unfortunately he is a Jets fan. He lives in Times Square with his wife and daughter.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russell Westbrook Is Enjoying The Nikola Jokic School For Wayward Careers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178375</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/russell-westbrook-is-enjoying-the-nikola-jokic-school-for-wayward-careers"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T15:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In some ways, my worst nightmares about Russell Westbrook joining the Denver Nuggets have come true: He has wormed his way into the starting lineup; he has usurped the point guard position from Jamal Murray; he is shooting the ball quite often; he is shooting threes; Michael Malone loves him. And yet as all of this has happened, as Westbrook's role with the team has grown larger and more important, the Nuggets have gotten ... better? Just what the hell is going on here?
Things didn't start off so well. At the beginning of the season, Westbrook was ensconced in the second unit, and entrusted to keep the offense humming while Nikola Jokic sat on the bench. The non-Jokic minutes have always been a disaster for the Nuggets, but Westbrook was just making things worse. His early-season stints were full of the smoked layups, ill-advised jumpers, and reckless playmaking that came to define his seasons in Los Angeles and marked him as a candidate for ignominious retirement this past offseason. But then injuries started to bite the team, which shuffled Westbrook into the starting lineup, and from there the Nuggets just kind of stopped losing. The 23-15 Nuggets are 13-4 in games that Westbrook has started, and it's not by coincidence. As a starter Westbrook is averaging 15 points, seven rebounds, and eight assists per game. He's also getting two steals per game as a starter, and shooting 53 percent from the field.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U++ – rapid application development framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140872</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/uplusplus-rapid-application-development-framework/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T15:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U++ is a C++ cross-platform rapid application development framework focused on programmers productivity.
The post U++ – rapid application development framework appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Cisco Modeling Labs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140878</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-cisco-modeling-labs/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T14:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Modeling Labs is an on-premises network simulation tool. We recommend the best free and open source Linux alternatives.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Cisco Modeling Labs appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Doink Heard ‘Round The Beltway]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178357</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-doink-heard-round-the-beltway"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T14:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Call it a doink-off win. Zane Gonzalez’s 37-yard field goal attempt bounced off the right upright and through the goalposts as time expired as his Washington Commanders beat the Tampa Bay Buccaneers in their wild card matchup, 23-20. 
The kick, which climaxed a four-minutes-plus Commanders drive that featured several clutch plays from rookie/franchise quarterback/savior Jayden Daniels, gave the team its first playoff win since 2006 (also against Tampa). And so Washington’s feel-goodest season of this century continues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F3OS – Debian-based Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140854</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/f3os-debian-based-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T09:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[F3OS (The Free Family-Friendly Operating System) is a Linux distribution based on Debian Stable that includes DNS-based web filtering
The post F3OS – Debian-based Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fingerterm – terminal emulator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140858</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/fingerterm-terminal-emulator/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T09:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[fingerterm is a terminal emulator with a custom virtual keyboard. It is designed for the Nokia N9 and Jolla's Jolla devices.
The post fingerterm – terminal emulator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KMRU (Interview)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/kmru-interview</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/kmru-interview"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T08:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to KMRU, a Kenyan electronic musician from Nairobi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radon]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3037/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3037/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Play Timer – native-feeling timers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140785</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/play-timer-native-feeling-timers/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-12T21:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Play Timer is a timer app with seamless integration accomplished by pretending to be a media player.
The post Play Timer – native-feeling timers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Texans Told Justin Herbert To Take A Seat]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178328</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-texans-told-justin-herbert-to-take-a-seat"/>
        <updated>2025-01-12T20:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quarterbacks are football’s main character; other players don’t have their faces spliced together in increasingly gruesome playoff preview graphics. But in the Chargers–Texans AFC Wild Card game, a fever dream befitting the Saturday afternoon TV window, both teams seemed determined to show the quarterbacks just how little they mattered. 
By the start of the fourth quarter, things were getting downright goofy. Down 23-6 to the Texans and fresh off back-to-back interceptions, Justin Herbert took two quick sacks to set up third-and-forget-about-it inside his own 15. On the next play, rookie receiver Ladd McConkey made a grab in traffic and shook a sticky defensive back loose for an 86-yard house call. Leave it to the Chargers to score a four-point touchdown. Texans special teams blocked the extra point, evidently spooked kicker Cameron Dicker into forgetting the rules of football (he tried batting the ball down as if that might get the play whistled dead), and returned the blocked kick for the first defensive two-point conversion in playoff history. Even when the Chargers offense found the end zone, the Texans defense said it would have to be on their terms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Vrabel Finds His Landing Spot]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178333</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mike-vrabel-finds-his-landing-spot"/>
        <updated>2025-01-12T18:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Patriots went 4-13 this season under the stewardship of first-year head coach and former New England linebacker Jerod Mayo. After firing Mayo shortly after the team's final game of the season, the Patriots have landed on a method for improving the team: Replacing Mayo with a different former Patriots linebacker.
Mike Vrabel is your new Patriots head coach. He returns to the organization where he spent eight years as a player and became one of the more annoying avatars of the Patriot Way. That wasn't really his fault—the Patriots fanbase was always going to latch onto a square-jawed white linebacker who occasionally caught touchdown passes from Tom Brady.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plop Linux – distribution designed for advanced Linux users]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140813</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/plop-linux-distribution-advanced-users/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-12T18:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plop Linux is a distribution built from scratch. It's designed for advanced Linux users.
The post Plop Linux – distribution designed for advanced Linux users appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CHADTree – file explorer for Neovim]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140773</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/chadtree-file-explorer-neovim/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-12T16:13:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CHADTree is a file manager / file explorer for Neovim.
The post CHADTree – file explorer for Neovim appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ravens Ran ‘Em Over]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178322</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-ravens-ran-em-over"/>
        <updated>2025-01-12T15:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The final score of Saturday night's wild card matchup between the Steelers and Ravens indicates a closer game than was had. The Steelers managed to outscore the Ravens 14-7 in the second half, securing a respectable-if-you-squint 28-14 final score. But everything that happened in the second half of this game—all those nice passes Russell Wilson threw to his receivers—was perfunctory, because by halftime the Steelers had already been run over and left for dead.
"Run over" is not a metaphor in this instance. There is simply no other way to describe what happened to the Steelers through the game's first two quarters, in which the Ravens built a 21-0 lead. After the Steelers ended the first drive of the game with a punt, the Ravens went on a 13-play, 95-yard drive that ended in a touchdown and ate just over seven minutes off the clock. The Ravens ran the ball on nine of those 13 plays, and it became immediately clear that the Steelers' defense was incapable of stopping the Ravens' ground attack. Derrick Henry's first big run of the game went for 34 yards and came as the result of a direct snap. It was a play that augured what was to come: The Ravens' offensive line creating huge gaps for Henry to run through, and Henry dishing out physical punishment to any defender brave enough to try and tackle him. I guess you could say Henry used a stiff arm on Minkah Fitzpatrick to gain a few more yards at the end of that run, but it was really more of a punch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Best Free and Open Source GUI Image Compression Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=75380</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-gui-image-compression-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-12T13:44:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data compression is the process of storing data in a format that uses less space than the original representation would use.
The post 9 Best Free and Open Source GUI Image Compression Tools appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BUTT – broadcast using this tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140782</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/butt-broadcast-using-this-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-12T08:34:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BUTT (Broadcast Using This Tool) is an easy to use, streaming tool supporting Icecast, Shoutcast and WebRTC.
The post BUTT – broadcast using this tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitFourchette – the comfortable Git UI for Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140844</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gitfourchette-comfortable-git-ui-linux/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-11T21:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitFourchette offers powerful tools to stage code, create commits, and manage branches.
The post GitFourchette – the comfortable Git UI for Linux appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NuTyX – flexible Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140805</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/nutyx-flexible-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-11T14:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NuTyX bills itself as a complete Linux distribution with high flexibility, thanks to the collections and the groups concepts.
The post NuTyX – flexible Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NERDTree – tree explorer plugin for Vim]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140769</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/nerdtree-tree-explorer-plugin-vim/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-11T14:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NERDTree is a file system explorer for the Vim editor. It's free and open source software written in VimL.
The post NERDTree – tree explorer plugin for Vim appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fruit Credits – keep plain text accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140838</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/fruit-credits-keep-plain-text-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-11T11:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fruit Credits is a double-entry accounting GUI app based on the command-line tool hledger.
The post Fruit Credits – keep plain text accounts appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fast Reader – read text quickly and effectively]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140777</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/fast-reader-read-text-quickly-effectively/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-11T08:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fast Reader is a versatile application designed to assist users in reading text swiftly and effectively.
The post Fast Reader – read text quickly and effectively appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Free and Open Source Graphical Download Managers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=124412</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-graphical-download-managers/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-11T06:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A download manager is a type of software that manages the downloading of files from the Internet.
The post 11 Best Free and Open Source Graphical Download Managers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File Shredder – file deletion software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140796</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/file-shredder-file-deletion-software/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T20:33:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File Shredder is a file deletion program designed to permanently remove sensitive files from your computer.
The post File Shredder – file deletion software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Injury Luck Is All About Timing]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178270</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/injury-luck-is-all-about-timing"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T18:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watching the Orlando Magic lose to the Minnesota Timberwolves on Thursday, in the Magic's final game without their best player, I was reminded of the spring of 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AnduinOS – Debian-based Linux operating system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140751</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/anduinos-debian-based-linux-operating-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T18:40:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AnduinOS is a custom Debian-based Linux distribution that aims to facilitate developers transitioning from Windows to Ubuntu.
The post AnduinOS – Debian-based Linux operating system appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Puzzling Time]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178254</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-puzzling-time"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T18:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A part of being home for the holidays is trying to find something to do in the New Jersey suburbs, especially as someone who despises driving but, to be very clear, has developed much more confidence in driving alone. After a couple of weeks of on-the-town reporting and extensive testing of all available entertainment options, I can officially confirm: The best form of entertainment is solving jigsaw puzzles at the municipal library.
I have visited two local libraries, and this is enough of a sample size to conclude that all suburban libraries must have a communal puzzling–type situation. One (my town's library) had a communal puzzle table with the pieces laid down flat, and another (the neighboring town's library) had a sort of inclined board covered in felt that wooden puzzle pieces stuck to—kinder on the neck but more difficult to slide large chunks of puzzle about. Anyone can work on the puzzle. Once the puzzle is completed, it is swapped out with a new one, which means a theoretically infinite supply of free puzzles. Sounds like a bargain to me!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week In Maligned Little Fish]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178218</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-week-in-maligned-little-fish"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T17:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two species of tiny, drab, and otherwise forgettable fish—the blotchy brown snail darter and the pale, silvery delta smelt—will never meet in real life. The snail darter swims in rivers and streams in America's South and the delta smelt can only be found in a single estuary in California. But the fish have more in common than you might think. Both snail darters and delta smelt are freshwater fish that are native to the U.S. Both species have been listed as endangered at some point and subsequently become the lodestar of a controversial conservation battle. And both fish are in the news this week.
These two species collided in the news for seemingly different reasons—the darter starred in a new paper arguing it is actually not a distinct species, and the smelt was unlucky enough to become the subject of a tenuously coherent response from Donald Trump to a question about the L.A. wildfires. Two odd little fish making national headlines in one week might seem like a coincidence, but these fish are more entangled than they'll ever know. (How could they know? They're fish.) They tell a story about the process of science and conservation, and how blameless species become scapegoats for quagmires of our own making.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Does The NFL Hate London So Much?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178257</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-does-the-nfl-hate-london-so-much"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T16:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no news in England that does not have some microscopic yet tangential link to Prince Harry and Meghan Markle, and while America has helped fuel that machine by taking the poor semi-orphaned waifs in to see how much Netflix money they could steal, it had not yet occurred to anyone that we might be just as sick of their story as the Brits are.
Well, shots fired back, kids. Roger Goodell, in his ancillary role as international agent-provocateur, has delivered unto London its 2025 football ambassadors, and he could not have chosen them with a more malicious eye. They are the Jacksonville Jaguars, the perennial colonial finger in the eye, the New York Jets, who may be trying to set up Brick Johnson for a future peerage but otherwise have no business being exported anywhere beyond Moonachie, and the Cleveland Browns, the most unpleasant team the league can offer. Jags, Jets, and Brownies are the buzzkill of this century, and they will all be ordered to infect Tottenham and Wembley Stadiums this coming fall in what under normal circumstances would be considered an act of war.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Of MLB Is Chasing Roki Sasaki]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178188</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/all-of-mlb-is-chasing-roki-sasaki"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T15:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DALLAS — I’m a punk who’s been in many mosh pits in my lifetime. Never have I experienced a media scrum that felt more like a mosh pit than the one surrounding Roki Sasaki’s agent Joel Wolfe at MLB’s Winter Meetings. The presser moved quickly, not just in terms of the brisk cadence of questions and answers but physically moved—from a corner in the Hilton Anatole’s Grand Ballroom, which acted as the media workroom, onto the stage with the podium and the MLB logo backdrop. Journalists followed Wolfe until they were crowding around the stage like they were at a basement show.
Wolfe addressed the scrum with a microphone that didn’t always work—adding to the DIY show feel, come to think of it—while fielding but not quite answering questions about where the most interesting international free agent in years would be likely to sign. That, honestly, is where the comparison to a punk show ends. Everything else is pure transactional offseason baseball, with a generous side order of rules—all of it just about the least punk thing imaginable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jen Ramos Eisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: One more system over the weekend (FRI-1/10)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3786114</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-one-more-system-over-the-weekend-fri-1-10/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T15:23:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is another snow system coming Kansas City's way Saturday night. It's a cold front that will create a line of snow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[wxDownload Fast – download manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140764</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/wxdownload-fast-download-manager/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T15:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[wxDownload Fast is a multithreaded download manager written using wxWidgets and Aria2. This is written in C++.
The post wxDownload Fast – download manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raise your glass: Kansas City’s ultimate zero-proof celebration is happening this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866881</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/raise-your-glass-kansas-citys-ultimate-zero-proof-celebration-is-happening-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T15:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pitch archive photo of Dry Vibes 2023 // photo by Samantha Levi Sip Steady, a zero-proof creative agency, aims to redefine the way we celebrate. Dry Vibes: A Zero Proof Experience will be held on January 12 at The Station by 28 Event Space. For the third year, this event will showcase the art socializing without a single drop of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notre Dame Derangement Syndrome Is Real]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178245</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/notre-dame-derangement-syndrome-is-real"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T14:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are now assured of 10 more days of Notre Dame in our faces, and ridiculously, that means another 10 days of hearing how the Irish not being tied to a conference like all the poor schools is an unfair advantage. I mean, what other program has a kicker with a chiropractor on call to come in every week and keep his bones aligned?
The kicker in question, Mitch Jeter, hit a 41-yard field goal with 12 seconds left to give the Irish a 27-24 victory in a highly disjointed game that for three quarters looked like it should have been played in a rainstorm. The chiropractor in question, Andrew Jeter, is his dad, who flew in each week to work on his son's directionally challenged leg after a hip injury. The conferences that Notre Dame are not in, the story goes, mean they don't have to share their playoff payoff with anyone else, giving them a leg up to keep Jeter's leg up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Tracker – simple time-tracker program for GNOME]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140757</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/time-tracker-simple-time-tracker-program-gnome/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T12:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time Tracker is a simple time-tracker program for GNOME. This software is written in JavaScript.
The post Time Tracker – simple time-tracker program for GNOME appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to popular CLI tools: Wget]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=113934</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alternatives-popular-cli-tools-wget/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T10:09:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We spotlight alternatives tools to Wget, a non-interactive network downloader.
The post Alternatives to popular CLI tools: Wget appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new and exciting for KC Restaurant Week 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2025-01-10/kc-restaurant-week-2025-deals-where-to-eat-kansas-city</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2025-01-10/kc-restaurant-week-2025-deals-where-to-eat-kansas-city"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City Restaurant Week, which runs this year from Jan. 10-19, will give local diners a chance to get out of the house after the blizzard and explore the city's diverse eateries — with special menus and deals. A portion of Restaurant Week proceeds will also support local charity House of Hope.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kraske, Josh Marvine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bosnian bakery hidden in Kansas City's Northland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/podcast/kansas-city-today/2025-01-10/a-bosnian-bakery-hidden-in-kansas-citys-northland</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/podcast/kansas-city-today/2025-01-10/a-bosnian-bakery-hidden-in-kansas-citys-northland"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Step inside the tiny A-frame cottage where local bakery Burek and Cake makes fresh Bosnian baked goods on the daily — and always with love. Owner Fatina Hodzic opened it two years ago and already has a slate of regulars, whom she greets by name.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nomin Ujiyediin, Olivia Hewitt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shy One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/shy-one</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/shy-one"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T08:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Friday so we’re listening to something more upbeat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Free and Open Source Web Hosting Control Panels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=5309</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/webhostingcontrolpanels/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T07:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web hosting control panels offer an attractive solution to developers and designers that host multiple web sites on virtual private servers and dedicated servers.
The post 11 Best Free and Open Source Web Hosting Control Panels appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TUXEDO OS – Ubuntu-based Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140740</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tuxedo-os-ubuntu-based-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T07:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TUXEDO OS is a Linux distribution that's based on Ubuntu / Kubuntu.
The post TUXEDO OS – Ubuntu-based Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Free and Open Source Replacements for ls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=70404</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-replacements-ls/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T06:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When invoked without any arguments, ls lists the files in the current working directory. We recommend some great replacements.
The post 11 Best Free and Open Source Replacements for ls appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chess Zoo]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3036/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3036/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elive – Debian-based desktop Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140674</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/elive-debian-based-desktop-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T23:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elive is a Debian-based distribution featuring the Enlightenment window manager.
The post Elive – Debian-based desktop Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nolan Arenado Reportedly Less Likely To Be Traded]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=837434</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/01/nolan-arenado-trade-rumors-red-sox-royals-cardinals.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T22:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nolan Arenado saga has been perhaps the main storyline of the Cardinals’ offseason. As the club looks to scale back payroll and open up playing time for younger players (Nolan Gorman, in particular), Arenado has become one of the most prominent trade candidates in the sport. His full no-trade clause, downturn at the plate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Los Angeles Is A Football Town, With Diana Moskovitz]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178039</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/los-angeles-is-a-football-town-with-diana-moskovitz"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T20:12:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While The Distraction is allowed to get as heavy as we want, the idea is mostly to do something goofy or stupid. I reminded myself of that while listening to this week's episode, in which our own Diana Moskovitz breaks down the first weekend of the NFL playoff slate from her home in Los Angeles. We recorded it Tuesday morning, in what turned out to be the last remotely normal-seeming moments of the week in that region. It's a fun episode, but because things have gotten very bad in Los Angeles in the days since we recorded, and because of the extent to which that reality is absent from the episode ... well, this was a good opportunity for me to remind myself that the name of the podcast is The Distraction, and then to say it until I believed it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: Restaurant closures and openings, local Dry January options, and more food news]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866865</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-restaurant-closures-and-openings-local-dry-january-options-and-more-food-news/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T20:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Life in KC is pretty delicious. In fact, there is often so much going on that it can be hard to decide where to go and what to try. That’s where I come in.  I’ve curated this weekly list of events, openings, deals, and celebrations to keep you in-the-know. Cheers! Something New Kansas City Restaurant Week:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ECT – fast and effective C++ file optimizer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140642</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ect-fast-effective-file-optimizer/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T19:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient Compression Tool (or ECT) is a C++ file optimizer. It supports PNG, JPEG, GZIP and ZIP files.
The post ECT – fast and effective C++ file optimizer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evan Mobley Is The Real Thing]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178172</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/evan-mobley-is-the-real-thing"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T18:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any time you get Cleveland and Oklahoma City into the first sentence of your blog, you can be reasonably sure that no one from either coast of North America will read it all the way to the end. The pressure's off! I can fill this blog with anything I like! Therefore I am choosing to spend the next several paragraphs sermonizing about the divine skills of Cleveland big man Evan Mobley. Mobley and the Cavaliers prevailed Wednesday night over the visiting Thunder, in a matchup of teams carrying combined 25-game active win streaks. This was a great game, from beginning to end, and if you ignored it because you consider these to be flyover teams, you deserve to feel bad this morning.
Mobley was incredible. Cavaliers head coach Kenny Atkinson is putting him everywhere on the floor and using him in as many ways as possible. The Cavaliers run normal-ish stuff to get the ball moving toward the basket, but Mobley's particular gifts make all the actions a tick or two more dangerous than they'd be if you replaced him with a normal-ish NBA big man. Consider the dribble handoff, or DHO. It's a staple of the modern game, but NBA defenses are getting better at defending it, so that it often feels less like a powerful go-to and more like some shit your team does by lazy habit, or from lack of any better ideas. In a DHO, the ball is passed to a big man up the floor, near the free-throw line. Guards and shooters whir around the arc; the big man takes a hard dribble or two parallel to the free-throw line and hands the ball off to one of his buds, who pulls a sprinting defender into a collision with the big man, and is thus freed to slice down the middle of the floor. All the quick-moving action around the perimeter creates secondary opportunities, but this is the basic action: a big guy lumbering sideways and punching the ball into the tummy of a teammate while absorbing into his own tummy his teammate's defender.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dahliaOS – intuitive Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140717</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/dahliaos-intuitive-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T17:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dahliaOS is a Linux distribution with a modern user interface, multitasking, advanced networking, security features and respectful privacy.
The post dahliaOS – intuitive Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Must Free Joe Burrow]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178155</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/we-must-free-joe-burrow"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T17:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
The advent of a 14-team playoff field in the NFL has forever neutered the possibility that a deserving team might not make it into the bracket. Not that you could make such arguments convincingly before; it’s not like I’m shedding tears for Matt Cassel and the 2008 Patriots. But a smaller field made the idea of bubble teams just plausible enough for Stephen A. Smith to make his best “Excuse me?!” face whenever a boring-ass 10-win team somehow got excluded. Any team that misses the playoffs now is one that indisputably deserves to, regardless of its preseason expectations or standout individual performances. You thought you could get in with style points, but you can’t. You are scum. Garbage. Dogshit. The Raiders by another name.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to popular CLI tools: curl]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=106327</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alternatives-popular-cli-tools-curl/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T16:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We spotlight alternatives tools to curl, a utility for transferring data from or to a server, supporting many protocols.
The post Alternatives to popular CLI tools: curl appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CuerdOS Linux – distribution of Spanish origin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140706</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/cuerdos-linux-distribution-spanish-origin/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T16:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CuerdOS is a Debian-based Linux distribution of Spanish origin focused on stability and constant performance.
The post CuerdOS Linux – distribution of Spanish origin appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Accumulating snows likely (THU-1/9)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3784679</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-accumulating-snows-likely-thu-1-9/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T15:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City weather will change later Thursday afternoon as clouds increase, some light snow moves up the I-35 corridor from the southwest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Topgrade – system specific update tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140698</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/topgrade-system-specific-update-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T15:32:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Topgrade detects which tools you use and runs the appropriate commands to update them.
The post Topgrade – system specific update tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NHL Has Given Up On New Year’s Day]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178149</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-nhl-has-given-up-on-new-years-day"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T14:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I didn't watch the Winter Classic. I can't even blame that fact on the teams involved, shit-ass as they may have been, because the draw of an outdoor game is almost entirely the venue: the visuals, the pageantry, the novelty of a hockey game in a non-hockey building under the open sky. The reason I didn't watch was that I hadn't realized until the morning of the game that it was being held on Dec. 31 instead of the usual New Year's Day, and by that point I already had plans, and canceling plans to watch Blues–Blackhawks is a great way to lose friends and gain regrets.
I liked it when it was New Year's Day. It's a perfect day for sports: I'm almost certainly not leaving the house, and I'd like something pretty and low-stakes to watch. I also liked that the NHL had its day. Every other league has its day. The NBA has Christmas. The NFL, which greedily wants Christmas for itself but will never truly own it, has the Super Bowl, which is basically a holiday already. MLB has its summer holidays, days off work being ideal for afternoon first pitches. And New Year's Day was for hockey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has The Tennis Ball Gotten Worse?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173112</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/has-the-tennis-ball-gotten-worse"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T14:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best way to snap an athlete out of platitude autopilot in a press conference is to get them to vent about some technical complaint. Like everyone else, they have esoteric gripes about their workplace, and are happy to explain them in full when given the chance. During my time at the ATP Finals, a year-end tournament in Italy for the top of the men’s tour, I asked several players to reflect on the object they clobber all day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>