<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-02-18T02:44:05.471Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ClipQR – scan QR codes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142397</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/clipqr-scan-qr-codes/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T23:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ClipQR is a simple app to scan QR codes on screen and from camera, the result is in your clipboard.
The post ClipQR – scan QR codes appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sceptres Have All The Help They Need]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181610</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-sceptres-have-all-the-help-they-need"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T21:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Toronto Sceptres learned the hard way last year that it’s risky to lean too hard on one star, even when the star's up to the task. When Natalie Spooner tore her ACL in the third game of the semifinal round of the PWHL playoffs in May, the Sceptres lost a league-leading goalscorer and pretty much their entire offense, too. Toronto scored just one goal in the final three games of that series. The injury cut short their inaugural season, and complicated their next one: The Sceptres would have to replace an MVP’s production for as long as it took Spooner to get back. Could they make it work?
No, the first few games suggested. Behind a shaky defense, Kristen Campbell, the league’s top goalie last year, struggled to start the season. The team clearly missed Spooner’s net-front presence and the high-percentage shots she generated with her size and quick hands. But things took an encouraging turn in late January, when the last-place Sceptres began to lose in shootouts instead of in regulation. Suddenly, they were putting together a point streak. Soon, the point streak became a win streak. With a 3-2 overtime win against Ottawa on Sunday, Toronto’s fourth straight, the Sceptres moved into second place in the PWHL standings, only behind juggernaut Montreal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No One Can Save Manchester United From Itself]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181612</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/no-one-can-save-manchester-united-from-itself"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T20:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester United is not any good. There's no reason to think they will or even theoretically could turn things around before the season is out. It will probably take yet another major offseason overhaul for United to even start to address its problems. None of this is breaking news, but what is legitimately stunning is how the Red Devils keep contriving to make a bad situation—one entirely of the club's own making—even worse.
On Sunday, Manchester United traveled to North London to face Tottenham, another so-called Big Six team that is in moderate-to-severe crisis. Aside from their positions on the table—much lower than either expected—there are not many similarities between Tottenham and United. The former is an injury-ridden mess that beats itself more often than not, while the latter is by almost every metric a middling team that plays even worse than that due to something unquantifiable: a rancid air of stagnation that has seeped into every pore of the once-vaunted club.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to popular CLI tools: tree]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=105876</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alternatives-popular-cli-tools-tree/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T18:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article spotlights alternative tools to tree, a utility that lists the contents of directories in a tree-like format.
The post Alternatives to popular CLI tools: tree appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nico Harrison’s Reasons Are Not Getting Any Better]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181636</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nico-harrisons-reasons-are-not-getting-any-better"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T18:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Athletic's profile of Dallas Mavericks general manager Nico Harrison will change no minds re: his role in the exile of Luka Doncic, but at least we saw this side of him: He seems like the kind of person you would do anything to avoid talking to at a party. Or maybe you find this paragraph a sign of a good friend:
Harrison is a notorious nutrition devotee and will occasionally begin conversations by quizzing friends on their health habits. "What did you eat today?" is one of his go-to greetings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Has To Save The Film And TV That Studios Won’t]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181599</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/someone-has-to-save-the-film-and-tv-that-studios-wont"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T17:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HBO had a series of legendary stand-up specials in the 1990s, and one of the best of those came from a performer who was not a comedian. Ricky Jay and His 52 Assistants was incredibly funny, but Jay was a magician, although that seems not quite right. The press material for the special, which first aired on December 17, 1996, called him an “illusionist.” That feels closer, but still not quite sufficient. The special, which was directed by Jay’s regular collaborator David Mamet, combined a number of astonishing card tricks with a breezily thorough recounting of the history of magic. That was more or less Ricky Jay's act; no one else has ever really done anything like it.
Ricky Jay, who died in 2018 at the age of 72, combined mastery of his craft with a thorough knowledge of its culture and lore. His 52 Assistants special was notable for his ability to throw playing cards into a watermelon and also his skill at explaining the long history of the cups and balls trick. You probably don’t need to be told not to get tricked into playing that by a hustler on the subway; Jay walks his audience through the long history of that hustle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Extend GM J.J. Picollo, Exercise 2026 Option On Manager Matt Quatraro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=841972</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/royals-extend-gm-j-j-picollo-exercise-2026-option-manager-matt-quatraro.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T17:29:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have signed general manager J.J. Picollo to an extension that runs through the 2030 season and contains a 2031 club option, per a team announcement. They’ve also exercised their 2026 club option on manager Matt Quatraro, reports Anne Rogers of MLB.com. Picollo, 54, has been with the Royals for nearly two decades, originally…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abysmal Kevin Hart Special Interrupted By Sporadic Basketball]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181609</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/abysmal-kevin-hart-special-interrupted-by-sporadic-basketball"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T17:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I thought I was being smart when I turned the NBA All-Star Game on 30 minutes late. NBA tip-off times are notoriously far afield of what is promised by TV listings, and I wasn't eager to spend any more time than was absolutely necessary watching pregame ceremonies, or listening to Kevin Hart talk. 8:30 ET seemed like a good time to tune in, even if it meant I might end up missing the first few minutes of the first game. When the TV flicked on, that game hadn't started yet, and Kevin Hart was screaming at me.
This was supposed to be the All-Star Game that got things back on track, whatever that means. Commissioner Adam Silver, who never misses an opportunity to bemoan the lack of effort and attention given to the All-Star Game by the players, unveiled a new format that was meant to force a little competitive spirit into the game. Instead of one normal game—between East and West, or Americans and internationals, or Team LeBron and Team Ghost Of Kobe Bryant—we were treated to three mini-games that would make up a tournament. Three separate teams of all-stars, selected by Shaquille O'Neal, Candace Parker, and Kenny Smith, were thrown into a bracket with the Rising Stars team. The winners of the two semifinal games, played to 40 points, advanced to the final, also played to 40 points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s The Point Of Bill Gates?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181569</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/whats-the-point-of-bill-gates"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T16:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I started reading Bill Gates’s new memoir Source Code the day after David Lynch died. In between learning about his pioneering BASIC coding language, I struggled to grasp what Laura Dern was saying in Inland Empire. In many respects, the two couldn’t be more different, but in some ways they act as mirrors—two lives that could have reversed with just a few small tweaks. Both were strongly identified with the West Coast: Gates in Seattle, Lynch in foresty Washington and then Los Angeles. Both held singular visions in their respective fields. One man pursued his passion with antisocial intensity, the other became the subject of clip compilations like “David Lynch melting my heart for three minutes straight.” One has spread software we use day in and day out, the other masterminded some of the most beguiling cinema ever produced. And now, Gates, one of the world’s richest men, has delivered one of its most pointless memoirs.
Bill Gates, the co-founder of Microsoft, served as the company’s CEO and largest shareholder until 2014. He founded the philanthropic Bill & Melinda Gates Foundation with his now ex-wife, and his net worth hovers in the hundreds of billions. Along the way, he’s been accused of bullying, anti-competitive business tactics, and even spending too much time with noted pedophile Jeffrey Epstein. When the tech tycoon came out swinging for vaccine patents in 2021, The New Republic called him a “monster.” But as he continues to fight climate change and Covid misinformation, a memoir offers a perfect opportunity to try to boost his spiraling reputation by reflecting on his earlier, more innocent childhood idylls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grace Byron</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIM – universal image viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142467</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/fim-universal-image-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T16:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FIM (Fbi IMproved) is a highly customizable and scriptable image viewer. It aims to be a "Swiss Army knife" for viewing images. 
The post FIM – universal image viewer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Feb. 17: In The Ballpark]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181598</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-feb-17-in-the-ballpark"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T16:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have some time to spare, why not try our Monday crossword? This week's puzzle was constructed by Frédérick Lavoie, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Frédérick is an avid board gamer from Canada, who learned lawn bowling in no small part to fit in with his then-girlfriend's family. They just got married, so it looks like that bet paid off!
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: One nasty snowy cold week in KC (MON-2/17)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3827205</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-one-nasty-snowy-cold-week-in-kc-mon-2-17/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T15:41:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A winter storm warning has been placed into effect for the metro. These are issued when the risk of at least 5" of snow is there and that's what we have for at least parts of the metro tonight into Wednesday morning]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Connect – wireless communications and data transfer between devices over local networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142488</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/kde-connect-wireless-communications-data-transfer/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T14:56:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Connect is a multi-platform app that allows your devices to communicate.
The post KDE Connect – wireless communications and data transfer between devices over local networks appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Country That Was Here Is Gone]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181586</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-country-that-was-here-is-gone"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T14:31:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I lived in Beijing, our apartment had two front doors on it. There was a regular, sturdy wooden apartment door, and outside that was a thick steel door, with heavy deadbolts mounted not only on the side but at the bottom. Up and down our entryway were various other steel apartment doors, apparently add-ons by the owners, in different styles and finishes. 
This apartment was a sublet in middle-class worker housing, in a compound with a guardhouse at the entrance, in a neighborhood that included embassies, a fancy patisserie, an upscale Japanese mall, and a Pizza Hut. Now and then there might be a drunken scuffle in the alley outside, but the interior courtyard was never troubled by anything worse than grimy stray cats. Daily life was peaceful and secure. Yet there were those steel doors, subtle monuments to the proposition that things could—someday, quickly—be very different.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decibels – simple audio player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142504</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/decibels-simple-audio-player/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T14:15:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decibels is designed to be a simple program that lets you play audio files.
The post Decibels – simple audio player appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven More Massage Therapists Have Accused Justin Tucker Of Sexual Misconduct]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181585</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/seven-more-massage-therapists-have-accused-justin-tucker-of-sexual-misconduct"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T14:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month the Baltimore Banner reported on allegations against Ravens kicker Justin Tucker, made by six women who had worked as massage therapists in the Baltimore area between 2012 and 2016. They each described having similar experiences while massaging Tucker, which included Tucker moving the sheet during the session to expose his erect penis, brushing his penis against their bodies, and leaving what appeared to be ejaculate on the massage table. The Banner has since published two follow-up reports in which more massage therapists say they experienced similar misconduct while massaging Tucker, bringing the total number of women to have come forward to 16.
The latest report, published Sunday, concerns allegations made by seven massage therapists. These women say they also had sessions with Tucker between 2012 and 2016 at various spas around the Baltimore area. Each of them described versions of the same experience: Tucker's erect penis was visible under the sheet when the session started, and he repeatedly attempted to remove the sheet. One woman said Tucker brushed her thighs with his fingers during the session, and another said he left what appeared to be ejaculate on the massage table when he left, which is something that several women in the Banner's first story reported seeing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[18 Top Free and Open Source Rust Web Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=85055</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/free-open-source-rust-web-frameworks/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T13:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the types of software that’s important for a web developer is the web framework. We pick the best Rust web backend frameworks.
The post 18 Top Free and Open Source Rust Web Frameworks appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decoder – scan and generate QR codes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142378</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/decoder-scan-generate-qr-codes/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T12:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decoder is billed as a fancy yet simple QR Codes scanner and generator. It's written in Rust.
The post Decoder – scan and generate QR codes appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LinuxConsole – lightweight distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142415</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/linuxconsole-lightweight-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T11:04:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LinuxConsole is billed as a lightweight Linux distribution for children and kids. 
The post LinuxConsole – lightweight distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[mothur – analyze microbial communities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142451</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/mothur-analyze-microbial-communities/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T08:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[mothur fills the bioinformatics needs of the microbial ecology community. It's software for describing and comparing microbial communities.
The post mothur – analyze microbial communities appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hollie Kenniff (Interview)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/hollie-kenniff-interview</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/hollie-kenniff-interview"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T08:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Hollie Kenniff, a Canadian-American multi-instrumentalist and composer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magnifiqus – Qt based screen magnifier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142530</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/magnifiqus-qt-based-screen-magnifier/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T07:45:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magnifiqus is a screen magnifier system tray tool; once started, a floating window appears after clicking on the tray icon.
The post Magnifiqus – Qt based screen magnifier appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archive Request]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3052/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3052/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hypnotix – IPTV streaming application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142479</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/hypnotix-iptv-streaming-application/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-16T23:19:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hypnotix is an IPTV streaming application with support for live TV, movies and series.
The post Hypnotix – IPTV streaming application appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Luke Maile To Minor League Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=841882</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/royals-sign-luke-maile-to-minor-league-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-16T22:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that catcher Luke Maile was signed to a minor league contract.  Maile will receive an invitation to Kansas City’s big league Spring Training camp. Salvador Perez and Freddy Fermin are locked in as the catching tandem on the Royals’ active roster, so Maile projects as a depth piece for their minor league…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QEMU – machine emulator and virtualizer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142403</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/qemu-machine-emulator-virtualizer/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-16T20:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[QEMU is a generic and open source machine emulator and virtualizer. QEMU can be used in several different ways.
The post QEMU – machine emulator and virtualizer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hell Yeah: This Maggot Has A Face On Its Butt]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181555</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/hell-yeah-this-maggot-has-a-face-on-its-butt"/>
        <updated>2025-02-16T18:49:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Mission Impossible franchise is famous for its mask reveals. A dubiously explained technology allows an innocuous silver briefcase to print out a gummy-like mask that, once plastered to a face, transforms Tom Cruise into the spitting image of Philip Seymour Hoffman or various others, enabling him to infiltrate various lairs and turrets. The masks in Mission Impossible make for a fun game as a viewer: Is the bad guy you're watching really a bad guy, or is he actually Ethan Hunt?
If Mission Impossible ever took place in a colony of harvester termites in the mountains of Morocco, Ethan Hunt might be, for once, out of a job. A new paper in Current Biology describes how the larvae of a blow fly has evolved to live, apparently unnoticed, inside the nests of harvester termites. Its main strategy, it seems, is the "termite mask" that protrudes from its rump. This mask features two antennae, a pair of sensory palps, and two large red "eyes" that are actually breathing holes. (Yes, the termite breathes from its butt; so what!)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KMagnifier – screen magnifier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142518</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/kmagnifier-screen-magnifier/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-16T18:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KMagnifier is a  screen magnifier created by KDE.
The post KMagnifier – screen magnifier appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hell Yeah: Shohei Ohtani Throws Baseball 14 Times]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181548</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/hell-yeah-shohei-ohtani-throws-baseball-14-times"/>
        <updated>2025-02-16T17:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the the 2024 National League Most Valuable Player award, Shohei Ohtani was the most valuable player in the National League in 2024. He achieved this status on a new team, his World Series-winning Dodgers, as a mere designated hitter who nevertheless put up a 9.2 bWAR through 54 home runs, 59 stolen bases, a .390 OBP and a 1.036 OPS. He's one of the most amazing position players any of us have ever seen, but get this: He pitches, too!
That's right. It was easy to ignore with all that he gave the Dodgers last season, but LA was only receiving half of the Ohtani package in 2024. Due to an elbow injury, Ohtani hasn't taken the mound for an MLB game in nearly 18 months, but from 2021 to 2023 he was an ace-caliber hurler for the Angels, peaking in that middle campaign with a 1.012 WHIP and a 172 ERA+ off an AL-leading 11.9 strikeouts per nine. Here are a few highlights to jog your memory:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You Entranced By The Turtle Dance?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181414</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/are-you-entranced-by-the-turtle-dance"/>
        <updated>2025-02-16T17:35:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Across much of the animal kingdom, the meanings behind some creatures' gestures are reserved only for other members of their species. A person watching a honeybee's waggle dance would not understand the information about a pollen-rich flower patch or nearby watering hole that the bee is communicating through its dance. Anyone lucky enough to witness the busty dance of the sage grouse will certainly be impressed—but of what, exactly, they may not be so sure. And yet I recently learned of a behavior in turtles called "turtle dance" whose meaning was immediately obvious to me, a non-turtle.
Without further ado, I present to you the turtle dance:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada Still Alive In 4 Nations Despite Pugnacious Defeat In Montreal]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181545</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/canada-still-alive-in-4-nations-despite-pugnacious-defeat-in-montreal"/>
        <updated>2025-02-16T16:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Connor McDavid scored the opening goal of Team Canada's hotly anticipated 4 Nations game in Montreal on Saturday night, but it wasn't enough for a home-team victory. The Canadians would go on to surrender two in response on frustrating mistakes, then find themselves locked up by conservative defense as an empty netter made the final score 3-1. Nevertheless, a date with Finland to end the round-robin stage on Monday afternoon still gives them hope, as a win would likely propel them into a Thursday night final weighted with the possibility of revenge.
Not a lot of hockey games start like this one did, as the rowdy Tkachuk boys and the rowdy canuck boys announced the intensity of their competitiveness from the moment the puck dropped. Brandon Hagel had a ferocious fight with Matthew Tkachuk just two seconds in, and after the officials pulled the two off the ice and put them in the penalty box, Brady Tkachuk and Canada's Sam Bennett sabotaged the attempt to restore order. Officially three seconds into the game, the refs cleared out so the two could consensually hit each other until Brady executed a tackle on Bennett. A tiny bit of hockey happened after those penalty minutes appeared on the box score. But when Canada goalie Jordan Binnington froze the puck with 19:51 on the clock, it was JT Miller and St. Albert's own Colton Parayko whose tempers boiled over, with Parayko using his size to hold off Miller's assault until the two were exhausted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Top Free and Open Source PHP Web Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=81585</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/free-open-source-php-web-frameworks/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-16T16:06:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recommend the best free and open source PHP web frameworks.
The post 15 Top Free and Open Source PHP Web Frameworks appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bevy – data-driven game engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142435</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/bevy-data-driven-game-engine/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-16T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bevy is a refreshingly simple data-driven game engine built in Rust
The post Bevy – data-driven game engine appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exherbo – Linux distribution for developers, tinkerers, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142420</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/exherbo-linux-distribution-developers-tinkerers/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-16T06:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exherbo aims to be a stable and flexible distribution for developers, tinkerers and people who need their distribution to help them be productive.
The post Exherbo – Linux distribution for developers, tinkerers, and more appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[trrc – ToRRential Card processor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142353</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/trrc-torrential-card-processor/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-15T23:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ToRRential Card processor (trrc) is a command-line unix-like program to create anki cards using AnkiConnect plugin
The post trrc – ToRRential Card processor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Best Free and Open Source GUI Tools for System Resources Monitoring in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139904</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-gui-tools-system-resources-monitoring/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-15T19:07:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tools featured in this roundup are targeted at a desktop user who wants to monitor resources being used on their machine.
The post 8 Best Free and Open Source GUI Tools for System Resources Monitoring in Linux appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qrca – QR code scanner for Plasma Mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142376</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/qrca-qr-code-scanner-plasma-mobile/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-15T17:52:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qrca is a simple application for Plasma Desktop and Plasma Mobile that lets you scan many barcode formats and create your own QR code images.
The post Qrca – QR code scanner for Plasma Mobile appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[stree – visualize the directory tree structure of an S3 bucket]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142283</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/stree-visualize-directory-tree-structure/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-15T15:27:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[stree is a CLI tool designed to visualize the directory tree structure of an S3 bucket.
The post stree – visualize the directory tree structure of an S3 bucket appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[39 Best Free and Open Source Linux Terminal Emulators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=3437</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/terminalemulators/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-15T13:39:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A terminal emulator is computer software which emulates a dumb video terminal. We make our recommendations.
The post 39 Best Free and Open Source Linux Terminal Emulators appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revise – TUI Anki client]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142350</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/revise-tui-anki-client/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-15T10:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Revise is a command-line program used to schedule the review of items using spaced repetition. 
The post Revise – TUI Anki client appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KolibriOS – tiny Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142426</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/kolibrios-tiny-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-15T09:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KolibriOS is a tiny yet incredibly powerful and fast operating system. The distro needs  only a few megabyte disk space and 8MB of RAM to run.
The post KolibriOS – tiny Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Free and Open Source Linux HDR Imaging Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=3196</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/hdrimaging/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-15T07:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High dynamic range imaging (HDR) is an important technology for photographers. We pick the best HDR software for Linux.
The post 11 Best Free and Open Source Linux HDR Imaging Software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals, Cole Ragans Agree To Three-Year Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=841728</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/royals-cole-ragans-agree-to-three-year-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-15T01:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals are in agreement with ace Cole Ragans on a three-year, $13.25MM deal that covers this season and his first two years of arbitration, reports Jeff Passan of ESPN. The signing does not change Kansas City’s window of team control. Ragans, who has two-plus years of service time, remains controllable through the 2028 season. He’ll…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mako – lightweight and easy to use PHP framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142070</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/mako-lightweight-easy-to-use-php-framework/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T23:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This PHP framework allows you to serve high traffic websites on modest hardware.
The post Mako – lightweight and easy to use PHP framework appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Counters – keep track of anything]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142337</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/counters-keep-track-anything/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T21:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Counters is a simple counting application that lets you create counters to keep track of anything you want.
The post Counters – keep track of anything appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JuJu Watkins Is The Whole Story]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181479</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/juju-watkins-is-the-whole-story"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T20:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JuJu Watkins was everything and the only thing. On Thursday night against No. 1 UCLA, she was the beginning, hitting three threes in the first quarter to send that awful she’s got it tonight feeling through the Bruins’ stomachs. She was the middle, literally all of it. When the sophomore guard found teammate Kennedy Smith alone at the rim in transition to start the fourth quarter, Smith’s layup was USC’s first non-Watkins field goal since the end of the first. And then she was the end. In the fourth quarter, the No. 6 Trojans trailing and gasping for breath, she blocked three shots in the span of a minute and scored two quick baskets to regain the lead her team had lost early in the third.
Not until the two-minute mark of the fourth quarter did any of her teammates finally break double digits. But by that point, there was no mystery left. JuJu Watkins had spoiled the plot: No matter how many times UCLA took control, no matter how many layups her teammates fumbled, no matter how sludgy the offense got, she would not be losing tonight. End of story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[mdfc – learn with flashcards and spaced repetition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142347</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/mdfc-learn-flashcards-spaced-repetition/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T19:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown Flashcards (mdfc) is software which lets you create and study flashcards using a markdown file.
The post mdfc – learn with flashcards and spaced repetition appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eagles Win Loan Of Manet Painting In Super Bowl Bet, Which Is What This Thing Was About All Along]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181423</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/eagles-win-loan-of-manet-painting-in-super-bowl-bet-which-is-what-this-thing-was-about-all-along"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T18:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Philadelphia Eagles’ Super Bowl parade ends at the steps of the Philadelphia Museum of Art. In a few months, that museum will receive its own prize from the Eagles’ win—an Édouard Manet painting, won on loan from Kansas City’s Nelson-Atkins Museum in a Super Bowl bet.
This is the second time the museums have wagered on the Super Bowl; two years ago in April KC’s museum got Thomas Eakins’s 1875 oil painting Sailing from the Philadelphia Museum of Art. It was on display for about two months. While it would be Very Philadelphian to have settled this bet using a Philadelphia artist, the Nelson-Atkins curators were the ones to pick that painting from the PMA’s collection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JD Vance Would Throw His Own Kids Under A Bus If Donald Trump Were Driving It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181428</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jd-vance-would-throw-his-own-kids-under-a-bus-if-donald-trump-were-driving-it"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T17:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although an American politician will have plenty of occasions to denounce racism, it's rare that said politician would be put in a position to denounce racism toward Indians, specifically. Rarer still is the scenario in which such a politician has an Indian wife and kids himself.
Vice President JD Vance found himself in those narrow circumstances earlier this month. Marko Elez, a 25-year-old enlistee at Elon Musk's center for bussin' constitutional violations, had been linked to a Twitter account that posted things like "Just for the record, I was racist before it was cool," and "Normalize Indian hate." Straightforwardly vile stuff, although I must note that if Elez really did attend Rutgers and major in computer science, he wasn't trying all that hard to avoid us.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Remember Some Comments From 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181484</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lets-remember-some-comments-from-2024"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T16:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Halley's Comment: I have to admit that I had a hard time finding the motivation to do this year’s comment roundup (and likely wouldn’t have without Drewbert’s encouragement). This may have something to do with why a post about comments we liked from 2024 is being published in February 2025.
Things generally feel real bad right now, and that has a way of permeating just about everything. It can make posting a comment on the internet seem even more pointless than normal (which should be impossible), and it can make compiling a list of comments from one website (even our favorite website) seem like a gigantic waste of time.  But you know what, we got into looking through comments, and I found myself forgetting these feelings and laughing instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Halley's Comment</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to popular CLI tools: man]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=104903</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alternatives-popular-cli-tools-man/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T16:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Linux system comes with a whole collection of system reference manuals (known as man pages). There's a man page for each command or program.
The post Alternatives to popular CLI tools: man appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Cold and more snow coming (FRI-2/14)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3825088</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-cold-and-more-snow-coming-fri-2-14/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T16:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been out for the last four days, in what is the longest stretch of sick time I've taken in my 30 years here at FOX 4. I could work, and am putting together blogs for you daily, but one thing about being on TV is you need to have a voice...and that has been [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Cold and more snow coming (FRI-2/14)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3825088</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-cold-and-more-snow-coming-fri-2-14/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T16:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been out for the last 4 days, in what is the longest stretch of sick time I've taken in my 30 years here at FOX 4. I could work, and am putting together blogs for you daily, but one thing about being on TV is you need to have a voice...and that has been [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Pistachio Wars’ Tells The Story Of California’s Terraforming]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181412</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/pistachio-wars-tells-the-story-of-californias-terraforming"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T15:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s last-minute decision to release water into Tulare County reservoirs as a belated solution to the fires in Southern California didn’t make much sense to anyone. The water wouldn’t actually make it to Los Angeles, and the places in the San Joaquin Valley where it was going are more at risk of flooding right now than of drying out. Even the supposed beneficiaries of the water windfall knew that gorging now meant potentially being dry during the long hot summers when they actually needed the water. 
“A decision to take summer water from local farmers and dump it out of these reservoirs shows a complete lack of understanding of how the system works and sets a very dangerous precedent,” Dan Vink, a longtime Tulare County water manager told SJV Water.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vince Mancini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volta –  JavaScript Tool Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142340</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/volta-javascript-tool-manager/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T15:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volta is billed as a hassle-free JavaScript tool manager.
The post Volta –  JavaScript Tool Manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rowdy Tkachuk Boys Wreak General Havoc On Finland]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181453</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rowdy-tkachuk-boys-wreak-general-havoc-on-finland"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T14:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States in 2025 may not be among the world leaders in human rights. Or democracy. Or education. Or healthcare, press freedom, income equality, environmental protection, political transparency, child and maternal mortality, or life expectancy. But no one can say we don't have one hell of a hockey team. USA! USA! USA!
Just how good this Team USA is, heralded as perhaps the best roster the country has ever iced, is still to be determined, even after a 6-1 shellacking of Finland in Montreal on Thursday night that served as both a barometer and a warm-up for Saturday's throwdown with Team Canada. Business was taken care of against the overmatched Finns, even if it took a little while to transact. "We either win or we learn," said Finland captain Aleksander Barkov. "We learned a lot."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HardV – terminal-based flashcard tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142345</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/hardv-terminal-based-flashcard-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T09:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HardV is billed as a powerful cross-platform flashcard program.
The post HardV – terminal-based flashcard tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[19 Best Free and Open Source Linux Time Tracking Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=4640</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/timetracking/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T08:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time tracking software is a type of computer software that records time spent on tasks. This category of software can enable users to run billing reports, and prepare invoices for clients.
The post 19 Best Free and Open Source Linux Time Tracking Software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yagya]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/yagya</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/yagya"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T08:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Yagya, an electronic music project from Icelander Aðalsteinn Guðmundsson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refine – tweak various aspects of GNOME]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142278</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/refine-tweak-aspects-gnome/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T06:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Refine is a simple tool that lets you tweak various aspects of GNOME.
The post Refine – tweak various aspects of GNOME appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hardwood]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3051/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3051/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-14T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paste69 – pastebin tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142269</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/paste69-pastebin-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-13T23:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paste69 is a modern, Go-based pastebin service. 
The post Paste69 – pastebin tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fileobj – ncurses based hex editor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142253</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/fileobj-ncurses-based-hex-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-13T22:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[fileobj is an ncurses based hex editor. It sports a vi interface. 
The post fileobj – ncurses based hex editor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Describe An Ass-Kicking]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181339</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-to-describe-an-ass-kicking"/>
        <updated>2025-02-13T21:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Super Bowls fade pretty quickly from memory, but it takes a special sort of dud to basically tape over itself in real time. Super Bowl 59, for all the highlights it generated and the broader satisfaction of its thoroughness, was more or less erasing itself as it happened; by the time it finally lapsed into the Rob Lowe-hosted game show that followed it on FOX, it was pretty much gone and the long sports winter already felt deep and endless. For Defector, this is both a challenge, because there just aren't a lot of sports happening right now, and something of an opportunity to stretch out a little bit, write some anglerfish fiction and jarringly vivid descriptions of bad smells and the like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flight – fast, simple, extensible framework for PHP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142121</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/flight-fast-simple-extensible-framework/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-13T21:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flight is a fast, simple, extensible framework for PHP.
The post Flight – fast, simple, extensible framework for PHP appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[greentext – create green-text memes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142285</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/greentext-create-green-text-memes/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-13T19:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GreenText Generator CLI is a command-line tool built with Go that lets you create classic greentext with ease.
The post greentext – create green-text memes appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art Of Chilling]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181239</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-art-of-chilling"/>
        <updated>2025-02-13T18:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
There’s a story about me from my days at Gawker Media that still gets told, which is strange because my old employer set an impossibly high bar for internal war stories. To be indoctrinated into Gawker lore, you usually had to either do a shitload of cocaine or get yourself sued.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Best Free and Open Source GUI Electronic Circuit Simulators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=102521</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-gui-electronic-circuit-simulators/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-13T18:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electronic circuit simulation uses mathematical models to replicate the behavior of an actual electronic device or circuit. We feature the best GUI tools.
The post 7 Best Free and Open Source GUI Electronic Circuit Simulators appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slim – PHP micro framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142116</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/slim-php-micro-framework/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-13T18:15:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slim is a PHP micro framework that helps you quickly write simple yet powerful web applications and APIs.
The post Slim – PHP micro framework appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cautious Whales Sing In A Whisper Orcas Cannot Hear]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181116</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cautious-whales-sing-in-a-whisper-orcas-cannot-hear"/>
        <updated>2025-02-13T17:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blue whales are not just the largest animals alive today, but the largest animals to ever live on Earth. They can stretch past 100 feet long and weigh up to 330,000 pounds. Being this big, it seems, should render blue whales impervious to predators. But just as no bank is too big to fail, no whale is too big to totally evade being eaten by the ocean's top predator. Killer whales prey on nearly every large animal species found in the ocean, and blue whales are no exception.
In 2022, scientists confirmed that a pod of orcas can take down an adult blue whale, not to mention the smaller calves they frequently hunt. "Killer whale attacks on large whales is the biggest predation event that occurs on the planet," Robert Pitman, a researcher with the Marine Mammal Institute at Oregon State University, wrote in an email. "There probably hasn’t been anything on that scale since dinosaurs roamed the earth."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everton And Liverpool Drove Everyone The Good Kind Of Crazy]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181354</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/everton-and-liverpool-drove-everyone-the-good-kind-of-crazy"/>
        <updated>2025-02-13T17:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being a sports fan is never more embarrassing than in those moments when it's made clear that your personal obsessions and hangups are your own. All it takes are a few accurately derisive tweets from Kevin Durant, or a photo of two players you thought were sworn enemies chumming it up at one of Michael Rubin's awful parties, to be reminded that the people who actually play these games experience the sport in ways that are entirely alien to you, and vice versa.
There are moments, however, when the membrane between athletes and fans is at its thinnest, and the game in question resolves into a universal experience in which everyone is a fanatic. On Wednesday, Everton and Liverpool created one of these moments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Stinky Pilgrimage To The Corpse Flower, With Notes Of Rat, Sweat, And Cheese]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180435</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/corpse-flower-journey-brooklyn"/>
        <updated>2025-02-13T17:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standing five feet away, I could smell it in the air. Acrid, damp, toe-curling—a memory from my past. The nose is a powerful historian, so it took only a few seconds to place it: the stench of the rat that died in the walls of my second apartment in New York City.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Arctic air ALERT next week (THU-2/13)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3823842</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-arctic-air-alert-next-week-thu-2-13/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-13T15:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're all wondering when my voice will come back, because it's not today. Good morning. Two to four inches of snow fell Wednesday (mostly in the morning) as a fast moving wave came through the region. It was so fast that the accumulating snows ended towards 9 a.m. (or earlier) and as a result the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Arctic air ALERT next week (THU-2/13)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3823842</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/joes-blog-arctic-air-alert-next-week-thu-2-13/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-13T15:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While wondering when my voice will come back, because it's not today. Good morning. 2-4" of snow fell yesterday (mostly in the morning) as a fast moving wave came through the region. So fast that the accumulating snows ended towards 9AM (or earlier) and as a result the snow totals fell just a bit short [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Got Comfortable With Cooking, And Eating]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181108</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-i-got-comfortable-with-cooking-and-eating"/>
        <updated>2025-02-13T15:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a document on my computer called "food.txt." According to the metadata, I created it in October 2023, and I'm sure I've opened it at least every couple days since. It would be incoherent to anyone who sneaked a peek, but it's a very useful piece of infrastructure in my life. It's a list of entrees, basically, with sections separated by planned grocery store trips. There are no specific dates attached, but the list is reverse chronological: Whatever I'm going to eat next is at the top, and my future meals proceed from there. At the very bottom are meals I want to make but don't have an assigned spot in the batting order yet.
The document is adjusted and revised often, which is why I don't lock in any meal to a particular day. When I make social plans that involve eating, or would cause me to miss a meal, I do some shuffling. As I write this, though, "food.txt" stretches out eight weeks in advance—pastas, chicken recipes, tacos, even a tentative visit to a bagel shop. It sounds very intense, I know. It's a symptom of an anxious mind that leans heavily on structures and plans. But I'm still kind of proud of how I got here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>