<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-03-21T10:17:39.370Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Night-Dwellers]]></title>
        <id>67dca0042cc2220001e16ab8</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-night-dwellers/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-21T01:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the perks of life as a freelance journalist is being able to set your own schedule. Or perhaps another way of putting it is that I’ve only ever considered career options that allowed me to avoid getting up in the morning. Whatever would keep me out]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Hioe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Face turn / Night shift]]></title>
        <id>67dca0312cc2220001e16ac2</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-281/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-21T01:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maria Bustillos read that exposé, and Brian Hioe stays up late]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s in the Book Mark Zuckerberg Doesn't Want You to Read]]></title>
        <id>67dcadc42cc2220001e16ad5</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/whats-in-the-book-mark-zuckerberg-doesnt-want-you-to-read-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-21T01:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo: Anthony Quintano [CC BY 2.0] via Wikipedia
People are all in a snizz about this Facebook memoir by former executive Sarah Wynn-Williams, and rightly so. Careless People: A Story of Where I Used to Work provides a rare and detailed look into the disastrous early years of Facebook&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Bustillos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Through The Transfer Portal, With Ken Pomeroy]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184635</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/through-the-transfer-portal-with-ken-pomeroy"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T21:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A big part of the fun of watching March Madness comes from being wrong. This may not be true for the loyalists and degenerates who have an emotional or financial stake in the outcomes, but I treat the college basketball season and its giddy final act more or less the same way that I treated my classes in college: I do enough research to feel OK with myself and pass for informed, otherwise consume whatever feels right whenever it occurs to me, and try to bear in mind that it doesn't really matter that much. I am roughly as good at filling out a bracket as I was at being a history major, and while I'm not a historian, I do have a diploma.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired USDA Specialist]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184356</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-usda-specialist"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T19:46:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consider the sugar beet, a sweet and tapered tuber. Unlike tropical sugarcane, sugar beets grow in temperate zones, enabling colder regions of the United States to farm their own sugar instead of relying on imports. From the late 19th century through the late 1970s, Utah abounded with sugar beet farms, and the crop's presence influenced the state's food culture. To Kate Wheeler, who until recently worked for the U.S. Department of Agriculture's Food and Nutrition Service, the sugar beet is a perfect portal into the Farm to School movement. Students can learn about Utah's history with the beet in social studies class. They can plant the beets in school gardens. And they can sample beets from nearby farms in the school cafeteria. Ideally, they're doing all three.
This is the spirit of Farm to School, which is not a government program but a tool that makes those programs more effective, Wheeler explained. Farm to School can involve local procurement of food, nutritional education, and school gardens. But Wheeler believes the tool becomes stronger when all three of these wings are combined in classrooms, cafeterias, and the community. Students are learning about food and nutrition, they are being nourished during the school day, and local farmers are building connections to schools. "This is a movement to change the way all of these other programs are interacting with the food system," she said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Group Led By Private Equity Ghoul Buys Boston Celtics For $6.1 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184690</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/group-led-by-private-equity-ghoul-buys-boston-celtics-for-6-1-billion"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T19:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weeks after the Boston Celtics won the 2023–24 NBA championship, owner Wyc Grousbeck announced that the team was up for sale. Grousbeck was clearly selling as high as he possibly could, on the heels of a new owner-friendly CBA and a title and ahead of whatever massive economic turmoil the second Donald Trump administration is about to throw the country into. While the Celtics were going to fetch more than the then-record $4 billion Mat Ishbia paid for the Phoenix Suns in 2022, I was still surprised to see the eventual purchase price, announced Thursday morning: A group led by Bill Chisholm agreed to pay Grousbeck $6.1 billion, and will take over after the 2027–28 season.
That sum represents a seventeenfold increase on the price that Grousbeck and his co-owners paid in 2002, an exospheric leap that makes one wonder who exactly can afford to pay roughly the GDP of Sierra Leone for ownership of a sports team. Chisholm runs Symphony Technology Group, which is a private equity firm dedicated to hoovering up and degrading tech companies. In this sense, he's the perfect owner for a sports team based in Boston, a hub for private equity firms both competent and incompetent, and he epitomizes the new ownership class that will gradually take over from an extant crop of owners who may soon look to sell into such a frothy market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[36 Veteran Players With Looming Opt-Out Dates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=845099</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/03/36-veteran-players-with-looming-opt-out-dates.html"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T19:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022-26 collective bargaining agreement implemented a new series of uniform opt-out dates for players who qualified as free agents under Article XX(b) of said agreement and sign a minor league deal in free agency. More specifically, that designation falls on players with six-plus years of MLB service time who finished the preceding season on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cade Cunningham Is In Dude Mode]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184687</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cade-cunningham-is-in-dude-mode"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T17:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Detroit basketball fans have a new chant. In addition to the "DE-TROIT BASKETBALL" thing—more of a shout, really, but you take my meaning—they now chant "M-V-P" for young Cade Cunningham, who in his fourth NBA season has made The Leap. Cunningham is posting career highs in points, assists, defensive rebounds, blocks, usage, and scoring efficiency, and is the best player for a bonafide playoff team otherwise made up of well-meaning guys, plus Ausar Thompson (hell yeah) and Tobias Harris (gulp). Cunningham isn't really a serious MVP contender—basically no one is in a league that contains both Shai Gilgeous-Alexander and Nikola Jokic—but he's earned this adoration. Anyway, he's got about as good a case as anyone else in his shit-ass conference. Let them chant, I say.
The Pistons beat the Miami Heat Wednesday night, in a contest that was maybe a little bit closer than it should've been. The Heat stink. Shipping off Jimmy Butler may have removed a distraction but it left the roster with just one player, in Bam Adebayo, who is capable of making regular contributions at both ends in a rotation gig. The Pistons maybe aren't exactly a powerhouse, but they're supposed to handle this lousy Heat outfit. "We just couldn't find that momentum to put us ahead," said head coach J.B Bickerstaff, after the game. "Every time it seemed like we were making a run, you'd look up and we were down by three." Cunningham mostly had an off night, shooting-wise, the Pistons struggled to produce clean three-pointers, and Erik Spoelstra's lean 7.5-man rotation made headway against Detroit's otherwise respectable bench units. It's just like that sometimes, especially for teams that have only recently arrived at conditions of general competence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cybertruck And Our Muskian Infection]]></title>
        <id>67dc3d17b3068f0001ef2105</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/the-cybertruck-and-our-muskian-infection-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T16:54:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybertruck owners are desperately seeking the inescapable hellscape Elon Musk has promised]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s The Damn Sandro Mamukelashvili Game]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184662</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-the-damn-sandro-mamukelashvili-game"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T15:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So much of this portion of the NBA season feels sloggy and labored, even after you allow for the drama of multiple seedings battles—West places two through eight and also ten and eleven; East places four through six; the sewage gumbo of the Southeast Division—and the lopsided Vengeance Pageants being staged by Jimmy Butler against Miami and Luka Doncic against Dallas. The NBA season is very long, and never feels longer than it does right around now.
But then there are the moments of crystalline beauty at the edges of the league that catch even the most jaded fans unaware. When those happen, they should if possible include Flavor Flav.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I’m Having Trouble Thinking Of A Funnier Goal]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184668</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/im-having-trouble-thinking-of-a-funnier-goal"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T14:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wednesday night, the Maple Leafs scored on a piece of improbably timed slapstick; Buster Keaton couldn't have done better. Simply trying to clear the zone on a penalty kill, Simon Benoit—he of do-a-cool-punch-then-get-punched fame—put the puck around the boards. Referee Kelly Sutherland, preparing to get out of the way, tripped over his own skates, fell down, and stopped the puck with his prone body in perfect position for Steven Lorentz to skate in and score the shorty. It would prove the winner in a 2-1 Toronto win over Colorado.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XAgxLlNUR74&ab_channel=SPORTSNET]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off Goes Rogue For Tarte Soleil]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184564</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-not-so-great-defector-bake-off-goes-rogue-for-tarte-soleil"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T14:40:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to a special, unsanctioned edition of the The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off. Usually, Kelsey and Chris attempt to complete the technical challenges from the newest season of The Great British Bake Off in their own home kitchens, with the same time parameters as the professional-grade bakers competing on the show. Today, they are just baking, as a treat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Izzo And Rick Pitino Are Up Against One Of March’s Weirdest Curses]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184451</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tom-izzo-and-rick-pitino-are-up-against-one-of-marchs-weirdest-curses"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T13:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did not want to be writing about Tom Izzo and Rick Pitino this week. You can find glowing features on each of those septuagenarian coaching legends from the past few days at various media outlets. They don’t need me to carry water for them; the two have won a combined 1400 games, three national titles, and 15 Final Fours. There is no denying they are great basketball coaches. This week, though, they have a chance to make a different kind of history. They can do it by overcoming a curse that has haunted the tournament since it expanded to 64 teams back in 1985.
My favorite fun fact related to the tournament is that no team with a one- or two-seed that was unranked in the preseason AP poll has made a Final Four during the 64-team era. Those teams are not the rare occurrence you might expect, either. There have been 39 cases of this over the past 39 tournaments. For 39 teams seeded among the field’s top eight teams to collectively whiff on a Final Four appearance is pretty staggering, and enough to make this fact not just fun, but actually meaningful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Pomeroy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Department Of Defense Backtracks After Deleting Jackie Robinson Article For “Woke DEI”]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184599</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/department-of-defense-backtracks-after-deleting-jackie-robinson-article-for-woke-dei"/>
        <updated>2025-03-19T22:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday night, ESPN MLB writer Jeff Passan shared that an innocuous article on the Department of Defense website honoring MLB legend Jackie Robinson's sporting and military career had been removed. Trying to access the old page redirected to a new, inoperative page with a URL that had "DEI" jammed into it. The Robinson article was part of a series called "Sports Heroes Who Served." Other such articles, like the one for fellow MLB Hall of Famer Bob Feller, remained live and un-DEI-ified. Now what could possibly explain the difference between Robinson and Feller?
The removal of the Robinson article followed an internal memo from Feb. 27, calling for a "digital content refresh" to "remove and archive DOD news articles, photos, and videos promoting Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion." When asked about the removal of the page, DoD press secretary John Ullyot sent ESPN a statement, which is worth quoting in full for its self-satisfied derangement:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Houston, we have a roach problem]]></title>
        <id>67db0d092cc2220001e15925</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-280/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-19T21:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A far-out trip with Sam Thielman]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Small Step]]></title>
        <id>67db0ded2cc2220001e15938</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/one-small-step/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-19T21:21:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fiction by Sam Thielman
Illustration by Joe MacLeod
In the surprising study chosen by our editors for the cover of this issue, researchers examined CENTIPAWN, a civilization of superintelligent cockroaches based in disused New York subway tunnels. We believe that these cockroaches discovered interplanetary space flight last year.
We realize]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Thielman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Am Asking Aaron Rodgers, Once And For All, To Leave My Team The Fuck Alone]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184449</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-am-asking-aaron-rodgers-once-and-for-all-to-leave-my-team-the-fuck-alone"/>
        <updated>2025-03-19T21:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This morning I received what appeared to be blessed confirmation from NFL insider Tom Pelissero that the Minnesota Vikings were officially out of the Aaron Rodgers (snickering) sweepstakes. I had waited far, FAR too long for this news to drop. The Rodgers-Vikings connection only made sense to media members carrying water for a desperate, jobless Rodgers, and to casual observers who remembered Brett Favre joining the team in 2009. To everyone else, nearly all Vikings fans included, any suggestions that the team might be interested in Rodgers was as nonsensical as it was enraging. So I was grateful to Pelissero for putting the kibosh on all of that speculation and allowing me, at last, to bask in what has been a remarkable offseason for my team.
But Rodgers, like herpes, is a virus that refuses to die once inside your system. So here came Dianna Russini of The Athletic, vehemently attempting to keep the story alive by reporting that Minnesota was “simply not making a decision at this time.” That report, I could write off with ease, but then Vikings beat reporter Kevin Seifert of ESPN filed this report, buttressed by sources in Eagan, that officially kept the door 0.00000000000001 inches ajar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case For And Against Every Contender In The Women’s Tournament]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184234</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-case-for-and-against-every-contender-in-the-womens-tournament"/>
        <updated>2025-03-19T19:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The transitive property is always a faulty tool in March, but this year, it feels especially useless. Anyone using it to predict their women’s tournament champion must first untangle this regular-season mess: No. 1 overall seed UCLA beat South Carolina, who went 2-1 against Texas this season but lost at home to UConn, who lost to Notre Dame and USC, who beat UCLA twice but lost to Notre Dame, who just lost three of their last five games. To choose our champion and build our own perfect bracket, we’ll have to study the six serious contenders more closely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What The Beads Can Tell You]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184548</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-the-beads-can-tell-you"/>
        <updated>2025-03-19T19:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A week after Doug Ford (our provincial version of Trump, in every sense of the word) handily won the premiership of Ontario for a third time in a row, and within days of the announcement that some fucking banker was taking over as the new Prime Minister of Canada, I was in The National Gallery of Canada looking confused. I looked like this because I thought they had put a J-cloth, smeared in oil, behind a glass case and called it art. But then I looked closer—it took me a minute, but I noticed the material before the stiffness. I noticed that what I thought were those trademark zig-zaggy blue and white cellulose fibers were actually countless little blue and white glass beads, so expertly sewn together that this sculpture looked like any number of scrunched-up kitchen rags I had seen in my…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fans Everywhere Are Slobbering At The Chance To Try Devin The Dugong’s Algorithmically Generated Sandwich]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184492</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/fans-everywhere-are-slobbering-at-the-chance-to-try-devin-the-dugongs-algorithmically-generated-sandwich"/>
        <updated>2025-03-19T17:36:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Opening Day is just around the corner, and if you follow the local news, there's a decent chance you've been treated to a sneak peek of your home team's bold innovations in the ballpark concession space. There's the Sluggerrr Dog in Kansas City—"chorizo topped with Manchego, tempura batter, Doritos Cool Ranch crust, and avocado aioli." There's Kyle's Cutlets in Philly—"topped with creamy burrata, crispy fried pepperoni, and arugula, drizzled with a sweet and spicy hot honey sauce on a Liscio’s Bakery roll." There's the H-Town Hot Chicken Loaded Fries in Houston—"crispy fresh cut French fries, fried chicken bites tossed in H-Town Hot Sauce, ranch, hot honey aioli, and green onions." There's the Fried Almond Torte in Pittsburgh—"funnel cake batter dipped, fried and topped with raspberry sauce, icing, and burnt almonds." I could go on and on, but why would I, when Defector has something better than all of them?
To really hit "a home run" on Defector's signature premium concession for the 2025 season, we turned to the one true genius on our staff: Chief AI/Metaverse Officer Devin The Mixed-Reality Dugong. Thanks to Devin's work with our cutting-edge AI technology, our proprietary algorithm was able to generate the ideal sandwich for everyone to enjoy while watching a baseball game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novak Djokovic’s Loose Players Union Files Huge Lawsuit Against Tennis Power Structure]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184415</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/novak-djokovics-loose-players-union-files-huge-lawsuit-against-tennis-power-structure"/>
        <updated>2025-03-19T17:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Novak Djokovic's players union has mounted its most significant challenge to the governing superstructure of tennis. On Tuesday, the Professional Tennis Players Association, along with one dozen named professional tennis players, filed a sweeping lawsuit in U.S., U.K., and E.U. courts against the four most powerful agencies in global tennis: the International Tennis Federation, which oversees the administration of the Grand Slams and is the closest thing tennis has to an international governing body; the International Tennis Integrity Agency, which runs anti-doping; and the ATP and WTA tours. 
You can deduce a good deal about the strange, diffuse ways tennis is run through both the identity and quantity of both plaintiffs and defendants. This legal battle is, at heart, a conflict between labor and management over the latter's control of the former's production, though the PTPA is not technically a union of salaried employees and management is less a cohesive unit than an assemblage of interconnected bodies. The ATP, for its part, is partially constituted of the players themselves. Djokovic is not one of the named players in the suit, though the 585th-best WTA player and 1,099th-best ATP player in the world are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Walz: Bad Faith Times Subscriber?]]></title>
        <id>67daf0edb3068f0001ef20a8</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/tim-walz-bad-faith-times-subscriber/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-19T16:34:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hours after I published Friday's piece about Tim Walz being too damn nice to emerge as a leading anti-authoritarian voice, the Minnesota governor delivered a goddamn zinger at a town hall targeting Elon Musk and immediately proved me wrong. 
Walz might just be mean enough. Or maybe he&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hmm, What About The Clippers?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184437</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/hmm-what-about-the-clippers"/>
        <updated>2025-03-19T15:57:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe you forgot about the Los Angeles Clippers. It's cool. It happens to me all the time. I think I did not remember them even once between Christmas and, uh, Sunday. If you'd asked me Tuesday afternoon to place the Clippers in the Western Conference standings without looking, I would've said, "Anywhere between third and ninth," and you would've asked me to be more specific, and I would've said, "Hmm, probably somewhere between fourth and eighth, but also maybe tenth." The West is like this, yes, but my brain has been conditioned over decades to mark all active knowledge of the Clippers as a waste product and to scrub it from short-term memory. It's not even that I expect them to be bad. I expect them just not to matter very much.
With Tuesday's performance, the Clippers made a compelling case for closer attention. They fell behind early at home to the buzzsaw Cleveland Cavaliers, scrambled back, and then spent the second half beating the hell out of one of the NBA's very best teams. The extremely convincing win puts the Clippers a season-best nine games over .500, and keeps them within a game of the rising Golden State Warriors, who currently occupy the conference's sixth seed, clear of the play-in. Lots can happen between now and the end of the regular season. The top eight teams in the West are really good. The seven teams below Oklahoma City in the standings are separated by just five games; a proud homestand here, a swoon there, and anyone in there might conceivably snatch the second seed. Ask the Rockets, who held the second seed for 29 straight days then plummeted to fifth, and now find themselves back in second. Or the Grizzlies, who rose to second in February and were there as recently as last week, and woke up this morning in fifth, with the Warriors, Clippers, and seventh-place Minnesota Timberwolves all fogging up their sideview mirrors. It'll be a desperate sprint from here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gun Assembly Required]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184412</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/gun-assembly-required"/>
        <updated>2025-03-19T14:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m watching The Gorge, a made-for-Apple movie that isn’t very good but will do the job on a lazy weekend morning. The story here is that there’s a gorge. It’s a very deep gorge, and its contents are so potentially dangerous that all of the world’s superpowers have deemed it necessary to entrust 24-hour surveillance of the gorge to … two people. Who are stationed on opposite sides of the gorge. One of those guards is professional idiot Miles Teller. The other is living Vermeer painting Anya Taylor-Joy. These two highly trained super soldiers aren’t allowed contact with one another from their respective watch tower positions. That would compromise the security of the gorge, and we can’t have that. We must protect this gorge.
However, thanks to tactical binoculars and a truly fantastical ability to write legible signs, our gorge-crossed lovers meet-cute at a distance and, in keeping with the spirit of tired romantic comedy, even manage to dance to the Ramones together before they both fall into the gorge. Once stuck down there, they must spend the rest of the movie killing knockoff Last of Us zombies while trapped in a knockoff Upside Down from Stranger Things. As I’ve told you, this isn’t a very good movie. And yet I have to stick with it from the opening scene, and do you know why? Because of the gun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Read Mahmoud Khalil’s Letter From An ICE Detention Facility]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184434</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/read-mahmoud-khalils-letter-from-an-ice-detention-facility"/>
        <updated>2025-03-19T12:58:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On March 8, pro-Palestinian activist and Columbia University graduate Mahmoud Khalil was arrested in his apartment building in New York by agents from the Department of Homeland Security. Khalil, a green card holder who is married to a U.S. citizen, has been held in a detention facility in Jena, La. since his arrest despite not being charged with a crime. The White House has been brazenly honest about the fact that Khalil is not accused of breaking any laws, instead arguing that the administration has a right to deport Khalil because he "led activities aligned to Hamas."
Tuesday night, Khalil's attorney released a letter from Khalil that had been dictated from inside the Louisiana detention facility. Here is that letter:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The past echoes]]></title>
        <id>67d9c0712cc2220001e14762</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-279/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T22:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zach Rabiroff in the aftermath]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scorched Earths]]></title>
        <id>67d9bd0d2cc2220001e1474d</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/scorched-earths/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T22:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illustration: Joe MacLeod
I have a cassette tape recording of an old man’s voice, thickly-accented in the type of lilting Yiddish twang that has since vanished from contemporary life. This is the voice of my great-grandfather, Sam Freed, being interviewed by his school-age grandson sometime around 1980. Sam]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Rabiroff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michigan Baseball Player Sorry For Doing The Cocaine Thing]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184414</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/michigan-baseball-player-sorry-for-doing-the-cocaine-thing"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T21:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps there is someone out there who follows Michigan baseball player Mitch Voit on Twitter without keeping close tabs on the junior's on-field exploits. It's fun to imagine this hypothetical person opening the app this morning and seeing the following message from Voit:
I would like to apologize for my actions on third base yesterday. I made an immature decision in the heat of the moment. The gesture I made does not reflect my character, the household I was raised in, or the block M that I represent in any kind of way. I take full responsibility for what I did, and I am truly sorry to all those who I have negatively impacted by doing this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re All We’ve Got Left]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184327</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/were-all-weve-got-left"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T18:12:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Saturday, U.S. District Judge James E. Boasberg tried and failed to block an agreement between the Trump administration and El Salvador that would pay the Central American country $6 million to imprison hundreds of people who were living in America. To make the deal happen, the Trump administration invoked the Alien Enemies Act of 1798, used most notoriously to justify the mass internment of Japanese-Americans during World War II. The act, in theory, can only be deployed in the context of war, but the Trump administration is using it as a weapon for a peacetime immigration clampdown. By claiming that Venezuelan "gang members" are invading the U.S., the Trump administration is attempting to bypass standard legal protections to quickly deport any immigrant whom they decide to say is associated with a gang.
Boasberg's ruling came after the ACLU sued on behalf of five people facing imminent threat of deportation. Already, however, the administration was sending hundreds of people on a pair of flights to Central America. While Boasberg verbally ordered the planes to be turned around so those on them could have a chance to be heard in court, the Trump administration refused, and instead took the opportunity to gloat about defying the order.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enjoy A Defector Subscription For The Cost Of Two Large Eggs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184239</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/enjoy-a-defector-subscription-for-the-cost-of-two-large-eggs"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T17:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, everyone is always talking about the price of eggs. Well it’s time to stop that. Now is the time to talk about the price of blogs: For a limited time, new subscribers can try a month of Defector for just $0.98. That’s roughly the going rate for two Large, Grade A eggs! Is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quentin Grimes Is The Tragicomic Protagonist Of The Terminal NBA Season]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184340</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/quentin-grimes-is-the-tragicomic-protagonist-of-the-terminal-nba-season"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T17:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've always liked Quentin Grimes. He's athletic and smart, and when he broke out as the fifth starter for the cool-as-hell 2022–23 Knicks, he did so by defending the point of attack with ragged intensity and taking advantage of the opportunities created for him by Jalen Brunson and Julius Randle. Like a plant thriving in low-light conditions, he was a master of fitting into the Knicks' scheme without ever disrupting things.
The bummer of Grimes's career is that his modularity and scant caloric demands, the very traits that made him fit in so well with New York, also made him fit in everywhere else. He has played for four teams in his four professional seasons: The Clippers traded him for Keon Johnson on draft night, the Knicks traded him to for Bojan Bogdanovic at the deadline last year, the Pistons traded him for Tim Hardaway Jr. last offseason, and the Mavericks just traded him to Philadelphia for Caleb Martin a few weeks ago. Grimes is a restricted free agent after this season, so it's easy to imagine him wearing his fifth NBA uniform next fall. Every step of the way, Grimes has played the same role, starting about one third of the time and playing about 25 minutes per game, because every previous team he's been on had either a Luka Doncic knockoff or the man himself to run things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired NOAA Director]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184115</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-noaa-director"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T17:07:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2006, by the time the scientist Sarah Cooley finished graduate school in marine science, oyster larvae in the Pacific Northwest had already begun dying mysteriously and dramatically—unable to form shells. By 2008, the largest oyster hatchery on the West Coast suffered losses of 80 percent. Hatcheries spent thousands of dollars stamping out any possible pathogens. But scientists eventually realized the killer was not bacterial, but chemical. The seawater had become acidic, the result of the ocean absorbing some of the surplus of carbon dioxide in the air. In 2010, researchers from the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, or NOAA, determined this corrosive water was killing the baby oysters.
The pH of the ocean is generally stable. But when carbon dioxide dissolves in water, a series of chemical reactions occur to create carbonic acid, lowering the pH of seawater and altering the chemistry of the ocean. In the past two centuries, the ocean has become 30 percent more acidic, a shift that has happened faster than any known change in ocean chemistry in the last 50 million years. This process, called ocean acidification, has profound effects for the many lives, human and non-human, that depend upon the ocean—dissolving the homes of shelled animals like oysters and the skeletons of coral, as well as destabilizing food webs and ecosystems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Artist’s Way’ Week 10: Reflecting Near The End]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184326</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-artists-way-week-10-reflecting-near-the-end"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T16:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're close to the end of our 12-week journey with The Artist's Way and it's prompting reflection among the more sentimental of us. What have we gained from this wacky, woo-woo experiment in nurturing our inner artist? Maybe it was a journaling habit. Maybe it's a greater sensitivity to the coincidences that pop up in our everyday lives. Maybe it's a deep resentment toward Julia Cameron and a confirmation of our disdain for the self-help genre. As we round out the last two weeks of this project, a few of us are re-committing to the process in the hopes of ending strong, and others are counting down the days. If you've been following along with us, congratulations on making it this far. Which camp have you landed in? 
How many days this week did you do your morning pages? How was the experience for you?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons From A B-Minus Dog Owner]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184307</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lessons-from-a-b-minus-dog-owner"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T16:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about America the brand, blocking wideouts, peanut butter jelly time, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baseball’s Sort Of Back]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184313</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/baseballs-sort-of-back"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T16:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having the regular season start before Opening Day is a prospect as indulgent as it is unreal—once you're up early to watch the Los Angeles Dodgers play the Chicago Cubs at 6 a.m. ET, you may as well buy in, even if the game had a nasty spring training hangover. No pitcher was fully stretched out. The Hanshin Tigers shut out the Dodgers and Cubs in back-to-back exhibition games just two days ago; Mookie Betts and Freddie Freeman were out with ailment and injury for this morning's lower bracket match-up. There wasn't much, as far as glimpses into how each team would look throughout the rest of the regular season go.
This is not a complaint. The only thing better than one Opening Day is two, and the soft power exchange of MLB with Pokémon meant that no fewer than six Pikachus dressed in baseball jerseys were placidly bobbling about the diamond for the teams' on-field introductions. Novelty value aside, Joe Davis gave a brief history of Japanese baseball as cultural exchange; Japanese baseball legend Sadaharu Oh was present for the game. If it didn't quite feel like regular season baseball, well—that was hardly the most important part. Last year's Seoul Series, for all its splendor, was overshadowed by the news of Ippei Mizuhara's gambling scandal. This year, there was just baseball and Cool Japan, and the fans in the stadium got a little bit of everything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NWSL Soccer Is Back, But The Scandals Haven’t Gone Away]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184283</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nwsl-soccer-is-back-but-the-scandals-havent-gone-away"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T15:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NWSL kicked off its 13th season this weekend. Kansas City crushed the Portland Thorns. Washington started its quest to return to the title game with a victory. And the Orlando Pride raised its championship banners, followed by a decisive 6-0 win over the Chicago Stars. After the match, Pride midfielder Haley McCutcheon talked about the club’s plans for defending its title: "We don’t like to talk about outside noise, but there’s been a lot of talk about 'Who's gonna win the shield? Who's gonna win the championship?' and we’ve not really been in the conversation, which is hilarious to us." 
The season openers also followed an offseason that saw the league bouncing from one report of abuse to another. The latest is this: the San Francisco Chronicle reported earlier this month that two formal complaints have been filed against Bay FC head coach Albertin Montoya, who's been with the club for about a year and a half. Players called his coaching methods "toxic" and said team management knew about their concerns. One complaint was cleared by a third-party investigation initiated by the team. The second complaint was made through the league’s anonymous tip line but, per the Chronicle, its status remains unknown. From that same report:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lesley Ryder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Music Club Is Getting The Led Out]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184218</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-music-club-is-getting-the-led-out"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T13:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Defector Music Club, where a number of our writers get together to dish about an album. Today, Israel Daramola, Dave McKenna, Ray Ratto, David Roth, and Lauren Theisen discuss Led Zeppelin's penultimate studio album Presence on what is very nearly its 49th birthday.
Israel Daramola: OK, I want to start this off by clearing out for Dave and Ray here a little bit. So guys, please tell us why we’re talking Led Zeppelin today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Act naturally]]></title>
        <id>67d888292cc2220001e135d2</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-278/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T23:06:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Pendarvis and Ace Atkins hit the road]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ace Goes to Hollywood: A Podcast for Your Eyes]]></title>
        <id>67d47fd5e3b9960001dcc081</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/ace-goes-to-hollywood-a-podcast-for-your-eyes/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T23:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Jack Pendarvis
Maggie the neighborhood pit bull
Episode 1: The Good News and the Bad News
JACK PENDARVIS: All right, let’s record. Hello! This is Jack Pendarvis. I’m in my driveway in Oxford, Mississippi. Uh, Ace is sitting there in his truck—my friend]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Pendarvis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mirra Andreeva Grabs Center Stage]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184228</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mirra-andreeva-grabs-center-stage"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T20:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After defeating Clara Tauson in February to win the first Masters 1000 title of the season, 17-year-old phenom Mirra Andreeva became a top-10 player for the first time in her young career. She joked in her on-court interview that doing so meant she'd already accomplished her primary goal for the season. In the moment, that felt like a sensible benchmark, impressively achieved. Three weeks later, having completed a stunning run through the best players in the world to win in Indian Wells, Andreeva looks to have been selling herself short.
Andreeva's run to her second title of the year was phenomenal. She dropped six total games against Tauson and Elena Rybakina over the third and fourth rounds, and dispatched the red-hot Elina Svitolina to set up a foreboding summit push: a semifinal against Iga Swiatek and a potential final against Aryna Sabalenka. Neither had dropped a set until facing Andreeva. Ripping through the rest of the WTA elite is one thing, but the world's best two players stand head and shoulders above the field, especially with Coco Gauff still struggling with her serve. Swiatek and Sabalenka each present distinct problems for opponents to solve, and each is capable of bullying opponents off the court with relative ease. Last year's U.S. Open final made clear how wide the gap between one and four is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playboi Carti Goes Big Game Hunting]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184231</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/playboi-carti-goes-big-game-hunting"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T19:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wouldn't be a Playboi Carti album rollout if you didn't have to sweat for it. Music, which comes five years after Whole Lotta Red, and which we thought we would get sometime last year, finally arrived Friday morning, though even that included a multiple-hour delay from its original 12 a.m. Pacific time slot. With its daunting 30-song track list, you can see that Carti tried to make up for the wait.
Music (or I Am Music, if you prefer) is a hard album to review because of how little it resembles an album in any classic sense, and I'm not just referring to the DJ Swamp Izzo tags throughout the project. It's more reminiscent of mixtapes by Gucci Mane, Waka Flocka Flame, or, more specifically, Lil Wayne's Drought and Dedication series. It's a collection of 30 songs that don't always jell together, and (sorry, old man here) aren't exactly sequenced well. But no one would ever argue that Gucci's Chicken Talk or Wilt Chamberlain tapes were cohesive, perfect projects, as mixtapes of that ilk tended to be a mixed bag. What made the classic ones classic was a combination of time and place, the good songs being especially good, and the creative freedom that comes from not being pressured to make some big artistic statement. Music maintains this spirit, flooding you with music and letting you make of it what you want. The highs are high enough to forgive the lows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France Deposes Ireland As Six Nations Champs While Disappointing Failed Imperialist Country Where Rugby Was Invented]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184189</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/france-deposes-ireland-as-six-nations-champs-while-disappointing-failed-imperialist-country-where-rugby-was-invented"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T18:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dammit. At least England didn’t win.
Heading into the final round of this year’s Six Nations, Ireland needed a win over Italy and lots of help from above to get back to the top of the table and take an unprecedented third consecutive continental championship. The Irish did their part, creaking past Italy, 22-17, for a bonus-point win in Rome. The gods? Not so much. So there will be no three-peat. Tres bien, France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joey Gallo Is Going To Give It A Shot]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184237</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/joey-gallo-is-going-to-give-it-a-shot"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T17:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the beginning of the 2017 season, Joey Gallo's first full-time season in the major leagues, he and Juan Soto have hit exactly the same number of home runs. I think we all know where the story goes from here.
Well, mostly we know. Gallo is in some ways the prototypical no-average/high-power lug of his era, and for a while was a player who could convince teams to take the 40-homer seasons and defensive benefits (he’s a two-time Gold Glover) alongside the 200 strikeouts and sub-.200 averages that came with them. It might be that the more apt tense on that verb in fact is now "was." Gallo put up a .161/.277/.336 slash line in 76 games with the Nationals last year, and was released by the talent-destitute Chicago White Sox last Friday after going 2-for-21 with 11 strikeouts in spring training.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popularism: The Loser's Crown Jewel]]></title>
        <id>67d82ad6669e16000109e522</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/popularism-the-losers-crown-jewel/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T17:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want the right wing to craft reality? Then you're going to love popularism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, March 17: Penalty Boxes]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184205</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-march-17-penalty-boxes"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Monday crossword is major fun. This week's puzzle was constructed by Matthew Stock and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Matthew is a crossword constructor in Gainesville, Fla., where he is pursuing a master’s degree in counseling. His puzzles have been published in the New York Times, USA Today, and the New Yorker, among other venues. When he’s not making puzzles, Matthew enjoys cooking, birdwatching and playing ultimate frisbee.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All My Favorite Lines From ‘With Love, Meghan’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184107</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/all-my-favorite-lines-from-with-love-meghan"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T14:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Somewhere among the crudités, preserves, and edible flowers in With Love, Meghan, you may notice a tragedy: The Duchess of Sussex would have made an excellent working royal. Is this not their whole thing? Using the soft power of images to hide how little they have to say? Perfecting party tricks because they need no other skills? The eight-episode Netflix cooking show claims our lives can be “elevated” with just a tiny bit of plotting. (Serving a basket of croissants with strawberry preserves and a couple fresh strawberries, for example, can tell “a strawberry story.”) Meghan wraps gifts, works peonies into wild floral arrangements, speaks enough Argentinian Spanish to get by, and prints menus for brunch parties in her own chic calligraphy.
The whole thing is soothing and perfectly forgettable—except for these lines, which I plan to incorporate into my own story, to the confusion and alarm of my friends. (All are spoken by the Duchess herself, unless otherwise noted in parentheses.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chuck Schumer Is Responsible]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184207</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/chuck-schumer-is-responsible"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T14:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chuck Schumer was always going to come out of the budget showdown a loser. The only question was which of the two available forms of losing he would end up with: an organized legislative surrender to Donald Trump and Elon Musk, which was the outcome he was trying to lead the Democrats toward, or a personal public rejection by his own party. 
In the end, the Senate minority leader got both. He scraped up eight more Senate Democrats to join him and John Fetterman in breaking his own party's filibuster, allowing the continuing resolution written by the House Republicans to advance and sparing Donald Trump from presiding over a government shutdown. He pulled the deal together—allowing Democrats to offer amendments that would fail to pass, to show they'd tried—over the enraged objections of the united House minority, from Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez ("To see Senate Democrats even consider acquiescing to Elon Musk, I think is a huge slap in the face") to Nancy Pelosi ("This false choice that some are buying instead of fighting is unacceptable").]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[And Now It Is March]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184193</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/and-now-it-is-march"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T13:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Up until Saturday night, the athletic legacy of the University of California San Diego centered on its national championship-level surfing team. Yeah, surfing—it’s a sport, and you SEC-centric troglodytes will have to deal with it. You don't like it? Go take it up with your fussy Airbnb host/god, Nick Saban.
And surfing is very much the sort of sport that a school like UCSD would be good at. UCSD is mostly known as a Public Ivy—long on brain, mostly indifferent to brawn. It tried football for one year a long time ago, went 0-7, and determined that high-speed human collisions weren't for them, as smart folks might. The athletic department has done good work in other areas, but surfing is the calling card. If only there were raftloads of NIL money that came with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newcastle Exposed The Cracks In Liverpool’s Armor]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184173</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/newcastle-exposed-the-cracks-in-liverpools-armor"/>
        <updated>2025-03-16T19:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a week for Liverpool, and I mean that in the most derogatory way possible. In retrospect, going down 1-0 to bottom-dwelling Southampton last Saturday should have been a warning sign, even if the Reds came back to win 3-1. The two matches since that mildly annoying Premier League showdown have cost Liverpool chances at two trophies—and even more concerningly, they've raised real doubts about the club's ability to hang on to first place and earn the one that's most important.
It started with the Champions League, a competition that Liverpool had romped through in the league stage. Its only loss was a 3-2 defeat to PSV Eindhoven in a match that didn't seem to matter at the time. However, that loss made it so Liverpool would face the winner of Brest against Paris Saint-Germain, which was (unsurprisingly) PSG. The reward for its dominant first stage was to meet the second-hardest possible opponent in the round of 16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Should Only Get One Timeout In Basketball]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184169</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/you-should-only-get-one-timeout-in-basketball"/>
        <updated>2025-03-16T19:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two kinds of sports: movement sports and anticipation sports. In movement sports, the pleasure of watching comes from lengthy stretches of action that absorb your attention with a smooth rhythm and beautiful motion. In anticipation sports, the excitement is build-and-release—you have a good sense of when, exactly, you need to focus closely on what's happening, and the rest of the time you spend gaming out scenarios for what might go down. Soccer, hockey, and cycling are among the movement sports. Baseball, football, and tennis are among the anticipation sports. I'm not saying one type is better than the other, just that each has its own particular style.
But what happens when you try to force a movement sport to go against its DNA and become an anticipation sport? You get something flawed and unnatural, annoying and unpleasant. You get the final minute of a basketball game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Blanches]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184159</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/four-blanches"/>
        <updated>2025-03-16T18:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first time I saw Blanche DuBois, she was just words on a page. I was a teenager with somewhat sophisticated reading tastes, and so I'd bought a skinny paperback copy of the Tennessee Williams play A Streetcar Named Desire. I moved through it quickly and at least partially recognized its greatness, but I was almost entirely focused on the character of Stanley Kowalski. Someone just reading the script of a play has to create a "performance" almost entirely with their mind, but Stanley helps you out plenty. He's blunt, harsh, dominant. In contrast with Blanche, whose inefficient dialogue hovers around the edges of what she means, Stanley creates a forceful impression.
STANLEY:
What does it cost for a string of fur-pieces like that?
BLANCHE:
Why, those were a tribute from an admirer of mine!
STANLEY:
He must have had a lot of—admiration!
BLANCHE:
Oh, in my youth I excited some admiration. But look at me now!
[She smiles at him radiantly]
Would you think it possible that I was once considered to be—attractive?
STANLEY:
Your looks are okay.
BLANCHE:
I was fishing for a compliment, Stanley.
STANLEY:
I don't go in for that stuff.
BLANCHE:
What—stuff?
STANLEY:
Compliments to women about their looks. I never met a woman that didn't know if she was good-looking or not without being told, and some of them give themselves credit for more than they've got. I once went out with a doll who said to me, "I am the glamorous type, I am the glamorous type!" I said, "So what?"
BLANCHE:
And what did she say then?
STANLEY:
She didn't say nothing. That shut her up like a clam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The F1 Season Got Off To A Very Wet And Very Wild Start]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184149</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-f1-season-got-off-to-a-very-wet-and-very-wild-start"/>
        <updated>2025-03-16T14:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I wrote about the 2023 Australian Grand Prix, I figured it would be the most chaotic Melbourne race I'd ever recap. In fairness to the me of two years ago, it's hard to top three red flag stoppages—something that hadn't happened before and hasn't happened since. However, the 2025 edition of the Melbourne race, this time the season opener, might have had it beat. It's all thanks to one of the few elements of Formula 1 racing that the meticulous teams can't control: rain.
After a dry weekend of practice sessions and qualifying—where McLaren continued their dominance from last season by putting both Lando Norris and Oscar Piastri on the front row—the forecast for Sunday's race called for rain, and the rain obliged. The Formula 2 race scheduled for the hours before the main event was cancelled, and even though the precipitation had mostly quieted down by the time the F1 cars got to the grid, the track was still sopping wet. It didn't take long for things to get messy. On the formation lap before the start of the race, rookie VCARB driver Isack Hadjar lost control of his car and banged into the wall. It was a devastating debut for the 20-year-old (one so painful that it even got Anthony Hamilton, father of Lewis Hamilton, to walk over and console the rook) and a sign of things to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laboratory demonstration]]></title>
        <id>67d48f43e3b9960001dcc0b5</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-277/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-15T00:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Misha Angrist on science and authoritarianism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Science]]></title>
        <id>67d4b214e3b9960001dcc108</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/its-science/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-15T00:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a collective of 60 writers, on fire and hard to kill]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Misha Angrist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The RC Car Racing Nationals Is Where Racing Gets Small]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184043</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-rc-car-racing-nationals-is-where-racing-gets-small"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T16:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This piece was originally published in The Autopian, a member-supported blog for car enthusiasts formed by ex-Jalopnik writers/editors. If you think starting a website in the middle of the pandemic was a terrible idea, you should see the cars we buy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hardigree</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Chop]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184089</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/for-chop"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T16:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2017 a lady selling puppies texted me a photo, of a wrinkly, tiny, brand-new little sad-eyed Boxer puppy sitting on a beat-up dog bed, looking right into the camera. What I thought, sitting alone on my porch, and probably muttered out loud, was, "Aw, look at that little porkchop." And that became his name: Chop. Later I learned that I had inadvertently and embarrassingly given him the same name as the protagonist's pet Rottweiler in the video game Grand Theft Auto V, but by then it was too late. He'd fully inhabited the name, and that's who he was: Chop, Chopper, Choppeez. And at any rate what I mostly called him was "little buddy." As in, "C'mon little buddy," and "Hi little buddy!" and, when he would put his paws on my shoulders and lay down on my chest, face to face, "Oh, little buddy."
When we met him (as well as the puppy we named Grover and also took home), he tried to scramble up into my lap where I sat on the lady's couch, but he was too small. I scooped him up—it took one hand; he was so little—and he immediately and with intense purpose began licking my face. You would have thought he was performing CPR. It was like he was making up for all 37 of the years I had spent not having my face cleaned by him. He was so happy to be doing it, ears laid back, nose snuffling loudly, his entire back half fully a-wag, like this was a music recital he'd been rehearsing for all (10 weeks of) his life. To stop him would have been unkind, so I didn't, and so he kept at it, with brief interruptions, for seven years. He and I were, if not literally inseparable, then only grudgingly separable and for as briefly as possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heartwarming: Hockey Executive Trades Son For Future Considerations]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184111</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/heartwarming-hockey-executive-trades-son-for-future-considerations"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T15:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all wish this story could be taken at face value as a victory for merit and against nepotism, a triumph of the lack of human spirit and a blow against familial gladhanding. We want it to be a message of total bastardy in action, because we are small people in a small era. We're probably wrong, but damn it, we can dream.
Dan MacKinnon, the assistant general manager of the New Jersey Devils and therefore the de facto general manager of the Devils' top minor league team, the American Hockey League's Utica Comets, did in fact trade his son Will to the Cleveland Monsters for future considerations. Future considerations including nothing whatsoever. We dare your heart to resist that strange warming sensation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real Madrid Is A Monster, And Every Derby Is Halloween]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183988</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/real-madrid-is-a-monster-and-every-derby-is-halloween"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T14:57:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you win as relentlessly as Real Madrid, you're destined to be perceived as the bad guy. Every club in Europe knows that when they face Madrid in the Champions League, they will confront an opponent endowed with the attributes of a comic-book villain. The Blancos have a vast array of superpowers, which only grow in number and potency in times of crisis. They are unaffected by the vicissitudes of battle, always supremely confident that the time will eventually come for them to turn the tables and win. Most of all, the moment you think you've finished them off is when they always, always, always land their biggest blow.
This dynamic takes on an even scarier tint when the team on the other side is Atlético Madrid. Real has haunted Atleti's dreams for generations now, and over the past decade has induced especially painful nightmares. When a Madrid Derby is on the horizon, the Colchoneros can't close their eyes at night without sleep sending them back to Lisbon or Milan, the sites of the most soul-crushing losses in the club's history. Surrounding the two losses to Real in those Champions League finals are a couple more UCL knockouts at the same hands, each one close and hard-fought and all the more excruciating for being so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How The Dunk Was Banned]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183960</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-the-dunk-was-banned"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T14:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following is excerpted from Mike Sielski's Magic in the Air, a narrative romp through the history of basketball, culture, and race in America. In this exclusive excerpt, Sielski details some of what led to one of the most infamous decisions in sports history: the banning of the dunk in high school and college basketball from 1967 to 1976.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Sielski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Walz Is Too Damn Nice]]></title>
        <id>67d43b9b669e16000109df8b</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/tim-walz-is-too-damn-nice/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T14:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can't forget about Walz's disastrous vice presidential debate performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Feinstein Never Stopped Doing Everything]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=184075</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/john-feinstein-never-stopped-doing-everything"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T13:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Post database shows that John Feinstein wrote his first story for the newspaper in 1977. It was about college basketball. Feinstein also wrote a story about college basketball that ran in the Post on Thursday, the day he died.
Between his first and last Post pieces, Feinstein went from a local D.C. reporter to a national powerhouse and back. He’d recently moved to Farmville, Va., but was back in town to cover the A-10 Conference basketball tournament being held in the nation’s capital when he died, and had already filed a preview piece for the event that ran earlier this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Timely And Frankly Too Thorough 2025 Formula 1 Season Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183839</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-timely-and-frankly-too-thorough-2025-formula-1-season-preview"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T13:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dare we say that it is possible to get excited about the upcoming Formula 1 season? While history means that Red Bull and Max Verstappen should still be the favorites, McLaren and Ferrari are looking like contenders for both championships. Even in the event that there isn’t a multi-driver race for the title, back-of-the-napkin math offers at least a 50-50 chance at a new Drivers’ Championship winner. And yet it's arguably one of the least important changes in the 75th anniversary of F1's existence.
Rosters have been drastically overhauled. Carlos Sainz Jr. moved to Williams. Lewis Hamilton is at Ferrari. There’s a new second driver at Red Bull. There are five new drivers on the grid and not one pay driver among them, which makes this the biggest rookie class since the 2019 lineup of Lando Norris, Alexander Albon, and George Russell. With any luck, this year will produce a driver on their caliber. In an era of increasing engine reliability, rookie mistakes may infuse the kind of randomness and safety-car strategic shakeups that have been missing from recent seasons. It comes at the minor tradeoff of preexisting narratives, but who needs those? Lewis Hamilton is at Ferrari!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exquisite corpus]]></title>
        <id>67d33a84e3b9960001dcadf6</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-276/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T23:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kọ́lá Túbọ̀sún won’t let words fail]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebuilding Babel]]></title>
        <id>67d339cee3b9960001dcade6</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/rebuilding-babel/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T23:34:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a collective of 60 writers, on fire and hard to kill]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kọ́lá Túbọ̀sún</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hummingbirds Brought Me Around]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183941</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-hummingbirds-brought-me-around"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T20:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LAS VEGAS — For as long as I can remember, I have felt drawn to creatures often described as uncharismatic: deep-sea fish; an ugly bunch of bugs; maggots with faces on their butts; any creature with "blob" in its name. As I've grown older, this interest has felt increasingly moral, as these creatures are less likely to bask in the glow of a spotlight in conservation with the power to lift a species out of the trenches of endangerment, or even extinction. But sometimes I'll see a, let's say, conventionally adorable animal that makes me forget all these weirdos, at least for a moment, and think: Whoa. Now there's a cutie patootie. 
Last week, I experienced one of these rare moments of awe while appreciating in the biodiversity of Las Vegas, a city that, for all its illuminated turrets and spheres, borders some of the most beautiful nature I've seen. I was walking with a few friends in their neighborhood park, which snaked through a miniature valley of desert scrub. At first, it seemed like we were the only ones here. But the longer we walked, the more creatures emerged. We were mooned by sandy-colored desert cottontails foraging right before dusk. We were menaced by a small, striped rodent I would later identify as a male white-tailed antelope squirrel who sported two impressively pendulous balls below his wee little tail. We watched Gambel's quails scuttling from the shadows of one bush to another, their black plumes bobbing with every step. I recently got a pair of binoculars, and I watched each of these creatures go about their afternoon with much delight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yearning For The Mike White Era, With Jasper Wang]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183954</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/yearning-for-the-mike-white-era-with-jasper-wang"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T20:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We talk about a wide range of topics on The Distraction, and one of our goals is to eventually broaden it to include areas of interest beyond sports, aging, and lunch sometime in the next few years. Of the many possible options that we've discussed, a pivot to "true crime" had ranked pretty low. It's not the energy we seek to cultivate, and hearing Drew honking through the details of a high-profile unsolved kidnapping would be pretty upsetting regardless of what those details were. So it's likely that this week's episode, which begins with Jasper Wang's perplexing Montana real estate mystery, is as close to true crime as we're likely to get.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tabs Hiatus 2: Hike Harder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/tabs-hiatus-2-hike-harder</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/tabs-hiatus-2-hike-harder"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T18:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ok this time I’ll finish the Appalachian Trail for sure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Belichick: Please Email My Girlfriend]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183982</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bill-belichick-please-email-my-girlfriend"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T16:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Belichick has a lot of work to do to turn the University of North Carolina football program into a perennial success. That's why the 72-year-old has assembled a team of top football minds around him. All the heavy hitters are here: Michael Lombardi, Freddie Kitchens, Steve Belichick, Matt Lombardi, Mike Priefer, and Jordon Hudson. 
Hudson is Belichick's 24-year-old girlfriend. Their relationship was a queasy one from the moment it launched, and it has become only more grimace-inducing as time goes on. Last month, for example, Pablo Torre reported that Hudson has essentially been acting as Belichick's agent. That reporting is now seemingly backed up by an email uncovered by The Assembly reporter Matt Hartman while he was reporting on UNC's rapidly increasing athletics budget.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[United States Dollar Bills, Ranked]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183967</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/united-states-dollar-bills-ranked"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T15:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we were discussing gifts for young children, and Jasper surprised us all by telling us that kids "go wild for $2 bills." Kids, and Barry. Here are the best bills.
1. $2. So rare! So delightfully wrong; receiving one feels like briefly being transported to a parallel dimension where everything is just slightly off, like you'd break your $2 to purchase a Poca-Cola. Did you know, the front ("obverse") of the two-dollar bill is the oldest of any current U.S. banknote, going unchanged since 1929? Did you know the number of two-dollar bills being produced is actually increasing?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Aaron Rodgers “Open” To Possessing God-Like Dominion Over Earth, Sea]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183964</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/report-aaron-rodgers-open-to-possessing-god-like-dominion-over-earth-sea"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T14:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that the NFL’s free agency market is open, everyone is dying to know: Where will Aaron Rodgers end up? This is the ONLY free agency move any of us care about, and yet a resolution has proven frighteningly elusive. The reason? EVERYBODY wants to hire this man.
Don’t believe me? Dianna Russini of The Athletic is saying that Rodgers is “intrigued” by the idea of playing in Minnesota. And Peter Schrager of NFL Network told his audience that Rodgers might sign with the Steelers, but needs “up to four weeks” to make his decision, and that the Steelers are “giving him some space” to think it through. An uncharacteristically terse Adam Schefter says that the Giants “want” him. That’s a lot of suitors! But which of them will go all in to secure the services of this four-time MVP? Or will a surprise contender—Kansas City?—emerge from out of nowhere? WE NEED AN ANSWER, DAMMIT!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Had Diana?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183091</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/diana-taurasi-retirement-uconn-phoenix-mercury"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T13:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We have Diana, and they don’t,” the quote went. But who ever had Diana? It is the magic thing about her, the way she gave herself over to no one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offseason In Review: Kansas City Royals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=843708</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/03/offseason-in-review-kansas-city-royals-16.html"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T01:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals began the offseason with a three-year signing to keep their excellent rotation intact. They traded from that starting staff a month later to acquire a new leadoff hitter. Kansas City hoped to follow up with an impact offensive acquisition that never materialized. They instead turned to the relief market late in the winter…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pals on the screen / Enemies on the road]]></title>
        <id>67d1ecd8e010aa0001436405</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-275/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T01:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emily Flake’s imaginary friends, and Julianne Escobedo Shepherd on a modern Tantalus]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to My Parasocial Relationships]]></title>
        <id>67d1e7e6e010aa00014363a5</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/a-guide-to-my-parasocial-relationships-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T01:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Emily Flake]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Flake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vehicle for Resentment]]></title>
        <id>67d1eddae010aa000143641d</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/vehicle-for-resentment/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T01:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Julianne Escobedo Shepherd

Photo illustration by Joe MacLeod. Photo of Tesla car by Vauxford - CC BY-SA 4.0 via Wikipedia
In the armpit days of the 2010s, the Tesla was marketed as an advance in luxury electric vehicles, a savvy choice for moneyed people moderately concerned about climate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julianne Escobedo Shepherd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bobby Witt Jr. Suffers Forearm Contusion, Avoids Any Fractures After HBP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=844387</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/03/bobby-witt-jr-suffers-forearm-contusion-avoids-any-fractures-after-hbp.html"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T00:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals appear to have avoided the worst on Bobby Witt Jr. ESPN’s Jeff Passan reports that the superstar shortstop avoided any fractures after being hit by a pitch in the left forearm/wrist area this afternoon. Kansas City subsequently announced that Witt sustained a forearm contusion and said he’d be reevaluated tomorrow. Manager Matt Quatraro said…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AL Notes: Meadows, Pérez, Mateo, Estévez]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=844359</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/03/al-notes-meadows-perez-mateo-estevez.html"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T21:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tigers are facing a few injuries in their outfield mix, with each of Matt Vierling, Parker Meadows and Wenceel Pérez battling health issues. Vierling has already been ruled out for Opening Day due to a rotator cuff strain and Meadows might not make it for the opener either. Meadows has been experiencing a nerve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lamine Yamal Wows On Accident And On Purpose]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183863</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lamine-yamal-wows-on-accident-and-on-purpose"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T19:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lamine Yamal's first stardust play of the game began with an apology. Carrying the ball up the field 10 minutes into Tuesday's deciding leg of the Barcelona-Benfica Champions League tie, Lamine picked up his head, saw Raphinha opening up his stride, and lifted his hand in contrition.
The gesture communicated that he appreciated the Brazilian forward's run, which presented the duo a great chance for another one of the thunderbolts they've spent all season tossing back and forth to each other, but as he hadn't read the play quickly enough and wasn't prepared to hit the pass before its window of opportunity closed, the Spaniard couldn't reward his teammate's effort with the pass the moment called for. Coming from the talent it came from, implicit in this apology was another sentiment: "Don't worry, I'll make up for it."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Should Cooper Flagg End Up?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183870</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/where-should-cooper-flagg-end-up"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T17:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooper Flagg has been conceived of as the surefire top overall pick in this June's NBA Draft since he reclassified two years ago, and despite taking on the enormous pressure of getting into the draft sooner, Flagg has only strengthened his case this year. Around him in the lottery, Rutgers' Dylan Harper has been doing a convincing Ethical James Harden bit; Baylor's VJ Edgecombe has been making all the Draft hardcores I read flush in awe; and Harper's teammate Ace Bailey has finally learned to pass the basketball, showing both an awareness of other people lacking through the first three months of the season and the capacity to grow and change. Nothing that cohort, nor anyone else in college or international basketball, has done has been as impressive as what Flagg's been doing at Duke. Not only has he produced at a staggering level, he's playing tomorrow's basketball, today.
With hopefully just a few more games left in his college career, and with the stinky end of the NBA content to befoul the court now that the trade deadline has passed and its members can lose in peace, it is time to consider where Flagg could end up. Also, more to the point, where he should end up. Not every team in the lottery is as worthy, by my arbitrary standards, of capturing the Flagg. The NBA Draft's structure not only limits how much money Flagg can make for many years, the draft lottery means he has zero control over where he will work for the majority of the next decade. Such is life in the NBA, under the current Collective Bargaining Agreement. Some players walk the blessed path and end up in a great city and on a great roster, and others are drafted by the Sacramento Kings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The San Francisco 49ers Are Closing The Window]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183897</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-san-francisco-49ers-are-closing-the-window"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T17:17:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last time the San Francisco 49ers had the kind of crisis of faith they’re currently enduring, they wrote it off as a weird emanation from COVID. Back then, they went from ending a season with a Super Bowl loss to Patrick Mahomes to enduring one of double-digit losses, mostly because the bulk of their offensive playmakers were gone for some portion of the season and  their defense slipped from elite to meh, bordering on feh. That relative patience was rewarded with a bounce-back season in 2021 and a trip to the conference final, a double-down season in 2022 and another trip to the conference final, and finally another run of excellence in 2023 that ended with...losing another Super Bowl to Patrick Mahomes.
History has a way of repeating itself, especially where losing to Patrick Mahomes is concerned, but the 49ers do not seem to believe that this cycle is going to make another revolution. Last year was another injury-plagued season that saw the Niners go from double-digit wins to double-digit losses. This time, Kyle Shanahan, who runs the building with full acquiescence from the fully satisfied York family, has seemingly decided that the windows are not only closed but need full replacement and double-paning. At least we think that's what he decided. For the first time in his eight-plus years in charge, he might not actually be in charge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Should Be Consequences For Filming A Tesla Ad At The White House]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183849</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/there-should-be-consequences-for-filming-a-tesla-ad-at-the-white-house"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T16:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, the President of the United States filmed an advertisement for Tesla on the driveway of the White House. They might as well have erected a ginormous flag and one of those balloon men that flop around, because the South Lawn is a car dealership now. Maybe they could have unfurled a sign that read "Deals Deals Deals!"
Except there were no deals. Instead, there was a line of five Teslas looking like shiny garbage. The reason behind this is simple: Elon Musk is now the president's big boy best friend, and Elon Musk has four jobs (Twitter, SpaceX, destroying the government illegally, and Tesla). His fourth job, Tesla, is the one he seems the most sensitive about, probably because it's the only one that had even a slight chance of success. Instead, Tesla stock has been dropping since mid-December, because many Americans have realized that Elon Musk is a goon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They Should Call It The Free Piss]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183816</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/they-should-call-it-the-free-piss"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T16:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who likes The Free Press? This is a question I have found myself asking, more often than is good for me, about Bari Weiss's suddenly large and well-monied media company, which according to the New York Times Magazine has more than three dozen full-time employees and at least 100,000 paying subscribers. I recently went to the homepage, scanned the day's meager offering of bone-dry headlines—highlights: "How I Became A Wife" and "Things Worth Remembering: Money Can Ruin Your Life"—and there was the question again: Who is getting fired up to read this crap?
It's a question that has become easier to answer in recent days and weeks. Over the weekend, pro-Palestine activist and Columbia University graduate Mahmoud Khalil was detained by the Department of Homeland Security and disappeared to a detention facility in Louisiana without being charged with a crime. As a set of facts—a campus activist was arrested by the federal government over speech acts—this is a story that should have been red meat for Weiss and The Free Press. Weiss essentially built her career by positioning herself as one of the few people brave enough to ring the alarm bell about the rise of anti-speech illiberalism on college campuses and in broader society. It's something she and her cohort never really shut up about, in fact. And yet, so far, The Free Press has published one article about Khalil's arrest, which reads as a wholly dispassionate rundown of the facts of the case and cedes its point of view to the Some people say this is good, while others say it is bad framing that was long ago perfected by The New York Times:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pacers Drew Up A Beauty And Were Rewarded With A Miracle]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183825</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-pacers-drew-up-a-beauty-and-were-rewarded-with-a-miracle"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T16:03:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The play that won the game for the Indiana Pacers Tuesday night deserved a bucket. The ethical fan of the Milwaukee Bucks, otherwise mired in frustration and disillusionment this fine spring morning, cannot deny this much: Rick Carlisle sketched up a beaut. 
Down three points with just under four seconds to play, the Pacers used a timeout to move the ball into the front court, but then positioned the inbounder's four teammates in the backcourt, in a spread formation not unlike what you'd see before a Hail Mary pass in football. The possibility flashed through my mind; it must've occurred to the Bucks, who were gesturing and repositioning and glancing around in uncertainty until the moment the play was triggered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today's Politics Are Not Trapped In Amber]]></title>
        <id>67d177c55b79a900011bd6e3</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/todays-politics-are-not-trapped-in-amber-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T14:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Americans did not speak for the final time in 2024. Some high-profile Democrats don't seem to understand this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saturn Has 274 Moons Now; Jupiter Is Crying Itself To Sleep; It Literally Cannot Believe It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183828</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/saturn-has-247-moons-now-jupiter-is-crying-itself-to-sleep-it-literally-cannot-believe-it"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T13:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For centuries, Jupiter reigned as king of the moons. Initially, the Big Four, discovered by Galileo, and then as optics and astronomy advanced, more and more, smaller and smaller bodies, until Big J could proudly boast of 95 moons in its orbital thrall. But Jupiter got cocky. Jupiter rested on its laurels. Jupiter, it turns out, was playing against plumbers and mailmen when it put up its record numbers. 
Saturn, meanwhile, was hungry. Saturn ate the tape and put in the hours in the gym. In 2020, astronomers discovered 20 new Saturnian moons. In 2023, they racked up 62 more. This week, the International Astronomical Union formally recognized a whopping 128 further new satellites, giving Saturn a total of 274 moons, a record that will surely never be broken (in this solar system, which as we all know is the galaxy's top-tier league). Saturn has more moons than it knows what to do with! It has more moons than the rest of the planets combined! Jupiter can attempt to dry its tears with its pathetic 95 Jovian moons, which compared to mighty Saturn might as well be no moons at all. Jupiter? More like Venus!! When it comes to moon-having.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Payton Pritchard Brings The Hush]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=183767</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/payton-pritchard-brings-the-hush"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T12:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 29, 1970, Dave DeBusschere of the New York Knicks hit a jump shot from the circle with three seconds left to give his team a 102-100 lead over the Los Angeles Lakers in the third game of the NBA Finals. LA’s Wilt Chamberlain inbounded the ball immediately to guard Jerry West. His first dribble was a feint to the left. West then cut back toward the middle of the court and let fly from 60 feet, over, I think, Dick Barnett . (The video looks like it was shot underwater on Mars.) On the video of the shot, the sound in the arena almost cuts out entirely until the ball goes through the net to force overtime—at the end of which, I would point out, the Lakers lost anyway.
It is probably as iconic a basket as was ever scored in the NBA, not only because it was scored by a certifiable NBA legend, but also because the shot was … a shot. It was not a heave. It was not a “desperation toss,” as Gene Hackman warned his Hickory Huskers against in the Sectional Finals against Linton. It was not some kind of baseball pass aimed roughly at the area code in which the basket is located. There was nothing freaky about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charles P. Pierce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confidence is real]]></title>
        <id>67d0b6c9e010aa0001435096</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-274/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-11T23:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Saward believes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detroit Pistons, Momentum, Belief]]></title>
        <id>67d0995be010aa0001435056</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/detroit-pistons-momentum-belief/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-11T23:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by John Saward

In late February, the Detroit Pistons beat the Boston Celtics 117-97. The Celtics, a kind of perverse, analytics-defiled basketball project joylessly hunting 3-pointers with the cold determination of a hedge fund manager, have scored under 100 points in just six games this year. It was Detroit’]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Saward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>