<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-02-24T12:32:41.034Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning in Linux: Jan – alternative to ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142725</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/machine-learning-linux-jan-chatgpt/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-24T11:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan is a ChatGPT-alternative that runs 100% offline on your desktop. This is free and open source software.
The post Machine Learning in Linux: Jan – alternative to ChatGPT appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12 Best Free and Open Source Vulnerability Detection Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=84796</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-vulnerability-detection-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-24T11:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerability scanning is an essential activity for enterprise security. We recommend the best free and open source vulnerability detection tools.
The post 12 Best Free and Open Source Vulnerability Detection Tools appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redox – Unix-like general-purpose microkernel-based operating system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142792</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/redox-unix-like-general-purpose-microkernel-based-operating-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-24T10:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redox is a Unix-like general-purpose microkernel-based operating system written in Rust.
The post Redox – Unix-like general-purpose microkernel-based operating system appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volaris –  encryption tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142993</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/volaris-encryption-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-24T08:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volaris is an encryption tool designed to prioritize privacy and security.
The post Volaris –  encryption tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mathias Grassow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/mathias-grassow</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/mathias-grassow"/>
        <updated>2025-02-24T08:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Mathias Grassow, a German electronic musician based in Bad Soden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Free and Open Source CSS Front-End Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=5926</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/frameworks/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-24T06:49:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article recommends the finest free and open source software that lets you dive into responsive design using CSS. 
The post 11 Best Free and Open Source CSS Front-End Frameworks appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magnus – very simple screen magnifier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142586</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/magnus-very-simple-screen-magnifier/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-23T23:49:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magnus is billed as a very simple screen magnifier. It's designed for Ubuntu but runs on other Linux distributions.
The post Magnus – very simple screen magnifier appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is Something Like Baseball On]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182249</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/there-is-something-like-baseball-on"/>
        <updated>2025-02-23T23:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You shouldn't really watch spring training baseball. Look at it from time to time, sure; let a game lay down a baseline level of low-intensity audio noise in the background by all means. It takes time to remember this, or just the length of one regulation winter to forget it. But as the days got longer and crueler and worse and the start of the baseball season began to feel less abstract if only minimally less distant, I tried to remind myself of this. There was going to be something that looked and sounded acceptably like baseball, and soon, and it was worth looking forward to that. But once it actually got here, I would need to remember not to overindulge. Let it back in, please and thank you, but do it like an IV drip—a little bit at a time, invisibly, to put a little bit of color in your cheeks.
Spring training is longer than it needs to be. It takes time for ballplayers to get back into playing shape, but nothing like the sort of time it took back when ballplayers spent their winters working second jobs or eating big greasy joints of mutton. Players do not arrive at spring training quite so wheezing and gouty anymore, or at least the percentage that arrive slicked in mutton sweat is lower than it was. MLB players stay in shape, they improve over the winter by refining their craft near the homes they own in states that don't have income taxes, or by throwing in front of high-speed cameras and coaches in converted warehouse spaces. But if it does not take a month and a half for contemporary ballplayers to look like ballplayers, it does take a while for the ballgames to look or feel like ballgames.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Notes: Rotation, Cameron, Bowlan, Mitchell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=842692</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/royals-notes-rotation-cameron-bowlan-mitchell.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-23T22:48:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cole Ragans, Seth Lugo, and the re-signed Michael Wacha and Michael Lorenzen project as the Royals’ top four starters, setting up a competition for the fifth spot between such pitchers as Kris Bubic, Alec Marsh, Kyle Wright, and Daniel Lynch IV.  However, MLB.com’s Anne Rogers writes that left-handed prospect Noah Cameron might also be on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous Lint Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142759</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/asynchronous-lint-engine/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-23T20:51:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALE (Asynchronous Lint Engine) is a plugin providing linting (syntax checking and semantic errors) in NeoVim 0.6.0+ and Vim 8.0+.
The post Asynchronous Lint Engine appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is The Last Thing You See Before You Die (If You Are A Crab)]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182226</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-is-the-last-thing-you-see-before-you-die-if-you-are-a-crab"/>
        <updated>2025-02-23T20:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You, a purple mangrove crab, have had a good run. You began your life as a larva drifting around the tropical blue waters of the Indo-Pacific. When you had molted enough to settle on the seafloor, you spent your days scuttling around the chandelier-like roots of mangroves and nibbling on leaf litter. Then, one day, you found yourself scooped up into a plastic container, tied to a string, and anchored to coral rubble off the Raja Ampat islands of eastern Indonesia. There you must wait until your worst nightmare appears. It might look like a gray spaceship, one dark stripe moving across its body in the gloaming sea. It might look like a leaf, olive green and drifting slowly toward you. It might resemble an innocuous branching coral, arms kinked outward. Or, most mysteriously, it might appear as a whitish specter containing one dark, pulsing inkblot that appears and vanishes as it comes your way. But it does not much matter which of these four (sea)horsemen of your apocalypse heaves onto your horizon, because by the time they have come, it is already too late. You, precious crab, are about to become dinner.
A group of scientists have described the four distinct hunting displays of the broadclub cuttlefish in a paper recently published in the journal Ecology. They also captured video footage of each display—passing-stripe, leaf, branching coral, and pulse—from the perspective of the final moments of a crab (RIP).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dallas Mavericks Oafishly Edit Hype Video, Then Delete Hype Video]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182170</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dallas-mavericks-oafishly-edit-hype-video-then-delete-hype-video"/>
        <updated>2025-02-23T20:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most compelling reasons not to trade Luka Doncic are not the administrative kind, but those reasons exist, too. Weaker-minded decision-makers would have been stopped by more urgent basketball and business considerations having to do with Doncic being a historically good player beloved by the team's fans, and dismissed the urge to deal Doncic as a fleeting call-of-the-void-type impulse. But the Dallas Mavericks' new ownership and GM Nico Harrison were able to see, beneath the jarringly ruddy exterior of the 25-year-old superstar who carried an otherwise unremarkable team to the NBA Finals just last season, a toxic and fast-depreciating asset that needed to be jettisoned 1) immediately and 2) in secret. That trade happened three weeks ago, which turned out to be much more time than was necessary for it to blow up on the Mavericks. Basically no one understands any of it.
And, again, that is just the top-line stuff. The deal itself might not have been anything more than the faulty whim of the team's bummy new ownership, represented in this case by a man who looks like the result of entering "business doll boy (real)" into an AI image generator, and facilitated by a GM with a dangerously advanced case of Contemporary Success Guy brain. It might just be one of those classic deals that instantly immolates a generation or so of fan goodwill and makes a team worse in both the near-term and long-term, made out of spite or boredom or just as the result of a decision-making process that is the result of having contracted some sort of debilitating brain spore from a Mar-a-Lago steam-table entree. This does not make it any easier to parse, to be clear, and also doesn't really explain anything. Also in retrospect that sort of trade is not really one of the classic kind of deals that exist, at least beyond the extent to which the Hindenburg could be said to represent one of the classic kinds of dirigible excursions one could have.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Gets To Determine A Hate Crime?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182222</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/who-gets-to-determine-a-hate-crime"/>
        <updated>2025-02-23T18:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Feb. 13, Sam Nordquist, a Black trans man from Minnesota, was found murdered in a field in upstate New York. He was 24 years old. The ongoing investigation suggests that Nordquist was subjected to prolonged physical and psychological torture for over a month before he was murdered. "No human being should have to endure what Sam endured," Major Kevin Sucher, commander of the state police troop in the region, said during a news conference. The New York State Police has charged seven people with murder.
The majority of the media appears to value Nordquist as a lurid true crime story rather than as a person. Nordquist's death has been widely reported on, with outlets tending to focus on the grisly details of his torture and death that have since emerged in court documents, all of which misgender Nordquist. Only a few queer outlets, such as Autostraddle, have attempted to paint a fuller picture of who Nordquist was as a person—how he spent his days (working at a group home for disabled adults), what he loved (nature, video games, TikTok, Puma sweatshirts, and cooking), and who loved him (his coworkers, his family, his friends, and his two adopted cats, Pumpkin and Storm).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warpinator – share files across the LAN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142764</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/warpinator-share-files-across-lan/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-23T16:42:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Warpinator is software which lets you send and receive files across a local network.
The post Warpinator – share files across the LAN appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harper – English grammar checker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142756</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/harper-english-grammar-checker/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-23T15:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harper is an English grammar checker designed to be just right. Harper takes advantage of decades of natural language research.
The post Harper – English grammar checker appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Best Free and Open Source Terminal-Based Diff Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=54955</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-console-based-diff-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-23T14:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File comparison compares the contents of computer files, finding their common contents and their differences. The result is known as a diff.
The post 16 Best Free and Open Source Terminal-Based Diff Tools appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Haml – markup language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142800</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/haml-markup-language/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-23T14:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Haml is a markup language that's used to cleanly and simply describe the HTML of any web document without the use of inline code. 
The post Haml – markup language appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UbuntuDDE –  remix flavor of Ubuntu with DDE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142927</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ubuntudde-remix-flavor-ubuntu-dde/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-23T12:39:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UbuntuDDE is a Linux distribution based on Ubuntu with the Deepin Desktop Environment (DDE).
The post UbuntuDDE –  remix flavor of Ubuntu with DDE appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Best Free and Open Source Linux CLI File Encryption Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142851</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-linux-cli-file-encryption-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-23T10:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This roundup explores the finest CLI-based file encryption tools.
The post 7 Best Free and Open Source Linux CLI File Encryption Tools appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[yuki-iptv – IPTV player with EPG support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142767</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/yuki-iptv-iptv-player-epg-support/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-23T07:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[yuki-iptv is an IPTV player with many features. yuki-iptv doesn't provide content or TV channels.
The post yuki-iptv – IPTV player with EPG support appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wordle CLI – play Wordle in your command line]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142631</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/wordle-cli/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T23:11:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wordle CLI is a command-line program that lets you play the famous Wordle puzzle game.
The post Wordle CLI – play Wordle in your command line appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fibbo – web-based game engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142701</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/fibbo-web-based-game-engine/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T21:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fibbo is a web-based game engine that allows you to create interactive experiences using JavaScript, right in your browser.
The post Fibbo – web-based game engine appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shinken – flexible and scalable monitoring framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142896</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/shinken-flexible-scalable-monitoring-framework/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T19:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shinken is a modern, Nagios compatible monitoring framework, written in Python.
The post Shinken – flexible and scalable monitoring framework appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kickpad – experimental kick drum audio sample generator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142666</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/kickpad-kick-drum-audio-sample-generator/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T17:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kickpad is an experimental kick drum audio sample generator written in Go.
The post Kickpad – experimental kick drum audio sample generator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Google Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142534</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-google-files/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T16:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Files is a file management app developed by Google for file browsing, media consumption, storage clean-up and offline file transfer.  We recommend the best free and open source alternatives for Linux.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Google Files appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teable – manage your data and connect your team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142878</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/teable-manage-data-connect-team/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T15:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teable uses a simple, spreadsheet-like interface to create powerful database applications without any coding skills.
The post Teable – manage your data and connect your team appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Equibop – snappy Discord app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142709</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/equibop-snappy-discord-app/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T14:35:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Equibop is a cross-platform Vesktop Fork desktop app aiming to give you extra plugins but still give you a snappier Discord experience
The post Equibop – snappy Discord app appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ccrypt –  tool for encrypting and decrypting files and streams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142836</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ccrypt-tool-encrypting-decrypting-files-streams/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T10:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ccrypt is a tool for encrypting and decrypting files and streams. It is based on the Rijndael block cipher.
The post ccrypt –  tool for encrypting and decrypting files and streams appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some of Kansas City's best barbecue is found at these Korean and Japanese restaurants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-02-22/kansas-city-barbecue-kbbq-korean-japanese-food</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-02-22/kansas-city-barbecue-kbbq-korean-japanese-food"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond burnt ends, Kansas City also has a scene for Korean barbecue (K-BBQ) and Japanese barbecue (J-BBQ) full of flavorful sauces, marinated meats and enormous portions. Here's a guide to local restaurants and how to cook at home.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Xiao daCunha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Best Free and Open Source Web Project Management Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=13845</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/excellent-web-project-management-software/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T09:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Project management is the application of processes, methods, knowledge, skills and experience to achieve the project objectives. We pick the finest free and open source web project management software.
The post 15 Best Free and Open Source Web Project Management Software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sxcs – minimal X11 color picker and magnifier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142594</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/sxcs-minimal-x11-color-picker-magnifier/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T07:23:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sxcs is a minimal X11 color picker and magnifier with mouse and keyboard support.
The post sxcs – minimal X11 color picker and magnifier appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YTSubConverter – create styled YouTube subtitles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142658</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ytsubconverter-create-styled-youtube-subtitles/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T23:50:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YTSubConverter is primarily an .ass to .ytt converter.
The post YTSubConverter – create styled YouTube subtitles appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Details On Nolan Arenado Trade Talks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=842553</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/details-on-nolan-arenado-trade-talks.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T22:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For much of the offseason, a Nolan Arenado trade seemed inevitable. But spring training is now rolling along and he’s still a Cardinal. Today, Katie Woo of The Athletic takes an extensive look at the twists and turns of the winter. Many of the details came out over the past few months but the piece…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[microStudio – game engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142786</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/microstudio-game-engine/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T21:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[microStudio is a free, open source game engine online. It is also a platform to learn and practise programming.
The post microStudio – game engine appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Kluwe Arrested At City Council Meeting For Calling Out Garish MAGA Plaque]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182150</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/chris-kluwe-arrested-at-city-council-meeting-for-calling-out-garish-maga-plaque"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T20:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former NFL punter Chris Kluwe was arrested Tuesday night after speaking out in protest at a Huntington Beach City Council meeting. The California resident had voiced his disgust against a proposal to mark the 50th anniversary of the Huntington Beach Central Library with a plaque adorned with Trumpist kitsch. He spent the rest of his allotted time detailing what the MAGA movement actually represents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gephi – Open Graph Viz Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142810</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gephi-open-graph-viz-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T18:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gephi is visualization and exploration software for all kinds of graphs and networks. Like Photoshop but for graph data.
The post Gephi – Open Graph Viz Platform appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glossy, Gunky And Ready In Minutes: AI Meal Recipes Are Overrunning The Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181831</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/glossy-gunky-and-ready-in-minutes-ai-meal-recipes-are-overrunning-the-internet"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T18:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It all started with a Messenger notification. In my inbox was a blurry image of a Tiramisu Cupcake sent by my grandpa, featuring a too-perfect frosting swirl with a thick coating of cocoa powder and a mysterious missing chunk from the cupcake liner that made me think: What kind of monster eats through the cupcake liner? 
Like so many times before, the picture that he sent accompanied a short note: "Can we make this next time you're home?" Usually, I jump at the chance to plan a menu with my grandpa (my grandparents owned a restaurant for over 30 years and in lieu of going to culinary school, I learned how to cook from them). This time though, there was a problem: The post was very obviously AI-generated. When I called to tell him that the cupcake was AI—or "made by a robot," as he said—he had no idea. He has since sent me dozens more AI recipes, despite our conversation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Domrongchai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Snowing Sea Cucumbers At The Bottom Of The Sea]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181797</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-snowing-sea-cucumbers-at-the-bottom-of-the-sea"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T17:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At first, the footage could pass for a swath of sky that has suddenly become host to a flock of birds. Doves, perhaps. But soon the camera adjusts to reveal two white stellate shapes. They are too big, too lumpy and organic to be stars in the sky. As the camera drifts closer, they reveal themselves as sea stars, one with arms that taper elegantly, and one with arms that end in rounder stubs: the Bert and Ernie of the seafloor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prospect Limbo: The Best of the 2025 Post-Prospects]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=456462</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/prospect-limbo-the-best-of-the-2025-post-prospects/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T17:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s run through the long-term scouting prognoses for some of the players who no longer fit the parameters of my prospect lists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Longenhagen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Yankees No Longer Have To Look Like That, Will Still Be Acting Like That]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182116</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-new-york-yankees-no-longer-have-to-look-like-that-will-still-be-acting-like-that"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T16:22:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Yankees have finally addressed the reason they lost last year's World Series and haven't won one since 2009. Or possibly they are tired of looking like enormous 12-year-olds. Either way, the team is taking action.

https://bsky.app/profile/riveraveblues.bsky.social/post/3lioyqsgjg22v]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do You Make Sex And Party Music For An Era Uninterested In Both?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181815</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-do-you-make-sex-and-party-music-for-an-era-uninterested-in-both"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T15:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Listening Habits, a new column where I share the music I’ve been fixated on recently.

https://youtu.be/cH_QusSap2I?feature=shared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: The turnaround begins! (FRI-2/21)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3831577</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-the-turnaround-begins-fri-2-21/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T14:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another day another record low temperature for KCI...many areas, especially from the Metro northwards tanked sub-zero again, but that's it for that. There won't be sub-zero lows tomorrow, nor the next day, nor next week. Conceivably not for the rest of the season either. The worst of the cold appears to be over and while [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe's Weather Blog | In-depth Kansas City forecasts | FOX4KC</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Game Always Speaks For Itself]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182103</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-game-always-tells-canada-4-nations"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T14:36:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The only thing wrong about Canada's 3-2 overtime triumph over the United States in Thursday's 4 Nations title game is that there was only one extra period, and that lasted under 500 seconds. By rights, it could have, nay, should have lasted past midnight in the east, with every subsequent overtime as high-octane as the first.
Other than that, it could not have been much better as entertainment, as long as you accept the fact that there was an annoying level of contrivance to it. The country that cares most about hockey won, the game's most recognizable player, Connor McDavid, scored the winning goal, the game's disputably best player, Nathan MacKinnon, was named the most valuable player, and the goaltender who stole the show, Jordan Binnington, fully resuscitated the reputation as a big-game player he last enjoyed six years ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Secure-K OS – Debian-based live operating system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142788</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/open-secure-k-os-debian-based-live-operating-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T14:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Secure-K OS is an operating system booting from a USB key in which you can safely create and store your personal and private data. 
The post Open Secure-K OS – Debian-based live operating system appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pitch’s Sandwich Week 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?post_type=gtx_link&amp;p=872597</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/gtx_link/the-pitchs-sandwich-week-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T14:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From March 24-30th, you get 1/2 off some of our favorite sandwiches in the city!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>THE PITCH STAFF</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pitch’s Sandwich Week 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?page_id=872498</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/the-pitchs-sandwich-week-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T14:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From March 24-30th, you get 1/2 off some of our favorite sandwiches in the city! 1930 Classic Kitchen BBQ Honey Sriracha Boneless Chicken Breast This sandwich is piled high on a brioche bun with kosher pickles, lettuce, and a side of homemade coleslaw. 1930 N 77th St, Kansas City, KS 66112 (913) 258-5556 Website Bar Central The Club Sandwich Jalapeño...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Advisory Position</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hockey Remains Canada’s]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182080</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/hockey-remains-canadas-4-nations"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T14:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a long enough time scale and if the sport is widely popular, a country tends to lose its dominance in a sport it creates. England ceded soccer long ago. The U.S. is, perhaps, in the process of losing its unquestioned position as the supreme basketballing nation. Canada, not for the first time and certainly not the last, faces a reckoning with its place in the hockey world. Since the fall of the U.S.S.R., the top of the sport has become more European, increasingly global, and, above all else, creepingly American. A smaller percentage of NHL players are from Canada than ever before, and more of the best players are from the U.S., as the league has expanded below the border and contracted above it. It's a numbers game, and if it isn't reflected in relative culture cachet, it'll become apparent by who raises the trophies in international competition. Canada may well lose its iron grip on hockey—but not yet.
Team Canada re-expressed its dominion with a 3-2 overtime win over the U.S. in the final of the 4 Nations Face-Off, a totally made-up all-star replacement that almost accidentally stumbled its way into becoming a geopolitical referendum, and served as emphatic notice that the sport is still Canada's to lose. I won't drag out this blog before giving you the climactic goal, the one that'll be replayed for years and years. And because the champions wear red maple leaves, you get the Chris Cuthbert call:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genome Analysis Toolkit (GATK)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142634</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/genome-analysis-toolkit-gatk/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T12:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GATK is a genomic analysis toolkit focused on variant discovery.
The post Genome Analysis Toolkit (GATK) appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Best Free and Open Source Linux File Encryption Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142719</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-linux-file-encryption-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T11:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This roundup looks at the finest GUI-based file encryption tools. Only free and open source software is included.
The post 6 Best Free and Open Source Linux File Encryption Tools appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tangent – clean and powerful notes app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142642</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tangent-clean-powerful-notes-app/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T08:10:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tangent is designed to let you write the way you think. Your thoughts are connected; Tangent lets you link to existing notes and make new ones with ease.
The post Tangent – clean and powerful notes app appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raven]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/raven</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/raven"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T08:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Friday so we’re listening to something more upbeat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Words! – word puzzle game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142624</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/words-word-puzzle-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T06:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words! is a word puzzle game where you have 6 tries to guess a hidden word.  A simple and addictive game.
The post Words! – word puzzle game appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scream Cipher]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3054/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3054/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[abPOA – adaptive banded Partial Order Alignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142456</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/abpoa-adaptive-banded-partial-order-alignment/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T23:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[abPOA is an extended version of Partial Order Alignment (POA) that performs adaptive banded dynamic programming (DP) with an SIMD implementation. 
The post abPOA – adaptive banded Partial Order Alignment appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Bayern Munich, What Michael Olise Says Goes]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181838</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/at-bayern-munich-what-michael-olise-says-goes"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T21:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's hard to know whether or not Bayern Munich is particularly good this season. On one hand, they have the best stats in Europe. Die Roten score more domestic goals than anyone in the Old Continent's top-five leagues, and allow among the fewest. Even in the Champions League, where their underwhelming results consigned them to the funky but fun new format's purgatory round, the Germans could point to their competition-best expected goal difference as evidence that their performances have been better than the scoreboards might indicate. And just in terms of pure talent, Bayern doesn't have to look at any other team's roster with envy. By all accounts, this should be one of the best teams in the world.
On the other hand, Bayern's cumulative showings across the season give off a strong whiff of a flat-track bully. Though they consistently hammer their lessers, Bayern's record against more or less equals isn't very good: four draws and no wins against Bayer Leverkusen (twice), Eintracht Frankfurt, and Borussia Dortmund in league play, a loss to Leverkusen that bounced them from the German Cup, and three Champions League defeats to Aston Villa, Barcelona, and Feyenoord by a combined score of 8-1. A 1-0 win over almost-didn't-even-make-it-to-purgatory Paris Saint-Germain and a 5-1 Bundesliga win over FC Lawn Ball Sports are the closest Bayern has come to statement victories this season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oboete – simple flashcard application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142554</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/oboete-simple-flashcard-application/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T20:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oboete is a simple flashcards application for the COSMIC desktop.
The post Oboete – simple flashcard application appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marina Mabrey Does Not See Her Future In Connecticut]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181844</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/marina-mabrey-does-not-see-her-future-in-connecticut"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T20:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An athlete who makes two separate trade requests in six months will probably not have public opinion on her side. But it’s also true that to this point in Marina Mabrey's WNBA career, luck has not been on her side either.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Basketball, Some Sandwich, with Rohan Nadkarni]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181858</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/some-basketball-some-sandwich-with-rohan-nadkarni"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T20:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About halfway through this week's episode, returning champion guest Rohan Nadkarni asked a question I didn't really know how to answer. We'd spent the first half talking about the NBA, which I enjoyed, and per the pre-show rundown the idea was to get back to it for a while in the second half before things kind of inexorably move in the direction of "talking about fried appetizers" in the way they always do on Rohan episodes. But before we could do that, Rohan asked why it is that we still feel compelled to do the sports talk at all when we could very easily justify doing an entire hour on foods we have enjoyed, with a couple Funbag questions stuck on at the end. It wasn't a gag, or anyway it wasn't just a gag. It's a good question.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: New sandwich passport, free coffee Friday, and Ruby Jean’s expands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=872486</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-new-sandwich-passport-free-coffee-friday-and-ruby-jeans-expands/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T20:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Life in KC is pretty delicious. In fact, there is often so much going on that it can be hard to decide where to go and what to try. That’s where I come in.  I’ve curated this weekly list of events, openings, deals, and celebrations to keep you in-the-know. Cheers! *Author’s note: I’m relieved to be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bobby Portis’s Big Suspension Is Ruinous Bullshit]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181984</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bobby-portiss-big-suspension-is-ruinous-bullshit"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T19:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday morning, the NBA announced that Milwaukee Bucks forward Bobby Portis would be suspended for 25 games after testing positive for the pain medication tramadol. The Bucks have 29 games left in the regular season, so they will be without a critical player for an extremely important stretch run in which they will have to fight desperately to stay in front of, somehow, the Detroit Pistons. Portis, in turn, will lose $2.8 million in game checks, so everyone involved is screwed—all over what Portis's representatives are calling an accident involving a substance of questionable performance benefit.
As Portis's agent Mark Bartlestein detailed to ESPN's Shams Charania, Portis takes the very similarly named Toradol to manage pain and inflammation from an elbow contusion he picked up at the start of the season, which explains the mixup. "The tramadol pill he took came from an assistant of his, with a valid prescription for the painkiller, which he mistakenly told Bobby was Toradol," said Bartlestein. Portis does not plan to appeal the suspension.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Victor Wembanyama Is Done For The Season Due To A Blood Clot In His Shoulder]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181993</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/wemby-blood-clot-shoulder"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T19:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Victor Wembanyama will not play for the rest of the regular season due to a deep vein thrombosis in his left shoulder, the Spurs announced Thursday. The team believes that the blood clot is an "isolated condition," per Shams Charania of ESPN.
Wembanyama was on court as recently as Sunday's All-Star Game, where he tried pretty hard, at least within the context of that game. The team said that the condition was discovered upon his return to San Antonio. Wembanyama had been feeling "low energy," and that feeling persisted throughout the All-Star break, which prompted the tests that uncovered the blood clot, according to Sam Amick of The Athletic. The Spurs are optimistic he'll return for the 2025-26 season, Tim MacMahon of ESPN reported, citing a team source.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please Stop Liking My Sport]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181990</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/4-nations-please-stop-liking-my-sport"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T18:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm just trying to watch a hockey game, man. Just trying to do some (friendly!) trash-talking with my Canadian relatives and pals. Leaning in to a (friendly!!!) rivalry with our closest neighbor, and hopefully beating them at their own sport, and, maybe if we're lucky, making Brad Marchand cry. I didn't sign on for Team USA becoming the icebound avatar of Trumpism.
Blame Bill Guerin. On Monday the former NHLer and Team USA GM went on Fox News to plead with the president to attend Thursday's 4 Nations Face-Off final in Boston, a rematch of Saturday's game that saw the U.S. defeat Canada 3-1 in Montreal, before which the American anthem received moderate but notable boos. After that, a whole bunch of people who have never watched a hockey game in their life all of a sudden became huge, or at least loud, Team USA fans because their politics consist solely of supporting things that will upset the people they're told they should hate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Checkmk – IT monitoring platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142687</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/checkmk-it-monitoring-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T17:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Checkmk provides comprehensive and specialized solutions for dealing with the very diverse environments within IT infrastructures.
The post Checkmk – IT monitoring platform appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Gordon On Grief, Connection, And His Novel ‘See Friendship’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181840</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jeremy-gordon-on-grief-connection-and-his-novel-see-friendship"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T17:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, I was going through the thousand-odd people I follow on one social media site in an effort to ease my transition onto another, when I noticed that I was still following the accounts of several people who were dead. I tabbed over to their pages, knowing I would not see anything profound or overwhelming, merely the mundane thoughts they'd had in 2013, 2017, or 2024, preserved in amber as long as the platform clings to life. The contrast between ephemerality and permanence was jarring. I didn't know whether it felt more respectful to continue following them or let them go.
This precise, hypermodern dissonance is one of the subjects of Jeremy Gordon's forthcoming novel, See Friendship. Gordon's book tells the story of Jacob, a somewhat adrift digital-media drone who needs to create something substantial to keep his career going. Once he learns that a close high school friend named Seth did not die in his sleep as he was told, but under stranger and more tragic circumstances, he decides to create a narrative podcast investigating the death.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Rubiales Found Guilty Of Sexually Assaulting Jenni Hermoso]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181971</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/luis-rubiales-found-guilty-of-sexually-assaulting-jenni-hermoso"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T16:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The National Court of Spain delivered its verdict today in the trial of former national soccer federation (RFEF) president Luis Rubiales, charged with sexual assault over the unbidden, nonconsensual kiss he planted on the mouth of women's national team star Jenni Hermoso during the medal ceremony after Spain's victory in the 2023 World Cup. Judge José Manuel Fernández-Prieto found Rubiales guilty of the assault charge, but acquitted him of an accompanying charge of coercion concerning his subsequent efforts at pressuring Hermoso into supporting him and downplaying the incident.
Although the prosecution had asked for a prison sentence of one year for the sexual assault charge (and a further 18 months for the coercion), the court opted to impose a fine instead: €20 per day over 18 months, €10,800 in total. Rubiales is also forbidden from contacting Hermoso or coming within 200 meters of her for one year. Also acquitted of coercion were Rubiales's fellow defendants on that charge, former women's national team coach Jorge Vilda and former federation executives Albert Luque and Rubén Rivera.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Black Box Diaries’ Splits A Journalist In Two]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181970</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/black-box-diaries-splits-a-journalist-in-two"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T16:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “black box” in the title of Shiori Itō’s documentary Black Box Diaries, in which the journalist investigates her own sexual assault, essentially refers to the excuse Japan gives for not properly investigating rape cases. “Because it’s in a black box, we’ll never really know what happened,” is what Itō was told, and as she says in the film, “I think that tells everything about our justice system.” But the black box works as a loose metaphor for another kind of unknowability that permeates the documentary, which was recently nominated for an Academy Award and is made up largely of personal video diaries, sound recordings, and a fly-on-the wall footage of the filmmaker as she investigates her case and ultimately writes a memoir about it (Black Box, 2017). Itō explains a few times that her way of surviving is to wrap herself up in work, to treat her case as a journalist would. But in the midst of this singular focus, the filmmaker in a sense puts herself—that is, Itō the survivor—in a black box. In the midst of this grand investigation, she herself remains unexamined. “I realized I haven’t faced myself,” she says at one point. The tension between the two sides of her—Itō the journalist and Itō the survivor—makes Black Box Diaries a kind of stealth dual narrative, one in which it becomes clear that a guilty verdict is not the end, not even close.
The film starts with a trigger warning, and I will defer to it here. Itō’s documentary opens with cherry blossom petals floating along the water beneath a script warning of the content and offering up how she has dealt with triggers in the past: by closing her eyes, by taking a deep breath. The flowers seem like just a pretty aesthetic choice at first, but by the end of the film you learn that these petals themselves became a trigger for Itō, and only later did she realize it was because the crime took place during cherry blossom season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[14 Best Free and Open Source Terminal-Based Image Viewers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=91820</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-terminal-based-image-viewers/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T15:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to view 24-bit high definition images in your terminal? We recommend our favourite terminal-based image viewers.
The post 14 Best Free and Open Source Terminal-Based Image Viewers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Hojicha at Goat Hill and biriyani at Moti Mahal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=872106</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-hojicha-at-goat-hill-and-biriyani-at-moti-mahal/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T15:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goat Hill Coffee Soda // Photo By Tiffany Watts Some coffee shop visits are meticulously planned—checking menus, mapping the best seat in the house, and prepping for the perfect Instagram shot. This was not one of those visits. After a satisfying brunch in the Westside neighborhood, we found ourselves wandering with no particular destination in mind. Then, like a casual...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Bitter cold will leave soon (THU-2/20)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3830320</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-bitter-cold-will-leave-soon-thu-2-20/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T14:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last night we managed to set two records within 5 minutes of each other. We tanked in the late evening to -4° to set a record low for yesterday's date. Then 5 minutes later, we set a record low for today's date. We kept on dropping to at least -9°, if not -10°, to bottom [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Bitter cold will leave soon (THU-2/20)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3830320</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-bitter-cold-will-leave-soon-thu-2-20/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T14:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in Kansas City it will be bitterly cold and tonight we'll be sub-zero again, and tomorrow we should moderate back into the 20° range.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Picket – screen color picker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142589</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/picket-screen-color-picker/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T14:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Picket is a screen color picker for Linux with magnifier and custom/user defined formats.
The post Picket – screen color picker appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is Why You Spend So Much Money On Kylian Mbappé]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181934</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-is-why-you-spend-so-much-money-on-kylian-mbappe"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T14:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What do you get the club that has everything? Trophies provide a buzz, as does dominance over another of the so-called titans of European soccer, but nothing gets the juices flowing more than a brand-new superstar. Soccer is a team sport, but few things can tilt the favor in the direction of one team more than a world-beating attacker. Real Madrid already had one such superstar in Vinícius Junior, but Wednesday's second leg against Manchester City demonstrated why one is never enough for this club and its limitless ambition. These must-win games, in the competition Real Madrid has won more than anyone else, are why the club spent multiple summers courting and, eventually, landing Kylian Mbappé.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s1aQb1bgPdQ]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[multiClock – track the time around the world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142578</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/multiclock-track-time-world/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T11:47:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[multiClock is software that lets you track the current time in major financial centres around the globe.
The post multiClock – track the time around the world appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SME Server – Linux Server distribution for small to medium sized enterprises]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142650</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/sme-server-linux-server-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T08:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SME Server is billed as a complete, secure, stable and versatile Linux Server distribution.
The post SME Server – Linux Server distribution for small to medium sized enterprises appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Muriel Grossmann]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/muriel-grossmann</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/muriel-grossmann"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T08:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Muriel Grossmann, an Austrian saxophonist and composer born in Paris and raised in Vienna.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eloquent – proofreading software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142693</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/eloquent-proofreading-software/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T07:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eloquent is a proofreading tool for English, Spanish, French, German, Portuguese, Polish, Dutch, and more than 20 other languages.
The post Eloquent – proofreading software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redot Engine – multi-platform 2D and 3D game engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142621</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/redot-engine-multi-platform-2d-3d/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T07:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redot Engine lets you create your 2D and 3D games, cross-platform projects, or explore innovative ideas in XR technology.
The post Redot Engine – multi-platform 2D and 3D game engine appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>