<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-01-27T08:20:56.762Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Staying: Leaving Records Aid to Artists Impacted by the Los Angeles Wildfires]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/staying-leaving-records-aid-to-artists</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/staying-leaving-records-aid-to-artists"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T08:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Staying: Leaving Records Aid to Artists Impacted by the Los Angeles Wildfires. The collection consists of 98 tracks by artists such as André 3000, Emily Sprague, Laraaji, Arushi Jain, Celia Hollander, Photay, Total Blue, Sam Wilkes, Luke Schneider, marine eyes, Reggie Watts, and KMRU. To quote the liner notes, “Leaving has pulled out all the proverbial stops to release a benefit compilation consisting of affiliated artists and supporters far and wide (many of whom have indeed lost everything). Seeking to supplement the numerous GoFundMes and the profound, often harrowing acts of mutual aid that are currently buoying recovery efforts, and in lieu of donating to a third party organization, all proceeds will be donated directly to impacted individuals.” Just a Bandcamp link today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[matrix-commander – simple CLI-based Matrix client]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141382</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/matrix-commander-simple-cli-based-matrix-client/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T07:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[matrix-commander is a simple but convenient CLI-based Matrix client app for sending and receiving.
The post matrix-commander – simple CLI-based Matrix client appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Super Bowl 59: Same Shit, Different Day, Brought To You By Fumble-A-Rooskie-Doo]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179538</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/super-bowl-59-same-shit-different-day-brought-to-you-by-fumble-a-rooskie-doo"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T04:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So it's the Super Bowl everyone hated because it's the Super Bowl everyone feared—the one you saw two years ago. You know, the one with all the points and yards and lead changes and quarterback stuff. Yeah, that one. The one that sucked even though everyone liked it at the time.
Yes, you spoiled piglets, you're getting the much-dreaded reprise of Chiefs-Eagles, the third-highest scoring Superb Owl of them all. It's all because Josh Allen couldn't reach Dalton Kincaid with a drive-saving pass because George Karlaftis was the one pass rusher the Buffalo Bills couldn't account for with the AFC championship on the line, and because Patrick Mahomes could find Samaje Perine in the flat with the game's security on the line. Because Kansas City is on a roll of winning games by a cheese-slice-thick margin almost unprecedented in NFL history and is, for the moment, the most unbeatable beatable team there has ever been. Because the Chiefs, for all their socially recidivist trappings, just knows how to do this shit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So! Many! Quads!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179543</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/so-many-quads"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T03:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we last checked in with Quad God, aka figure skater Ilia Malinin, he was busy winning the 2024 figure skating world championships while landing six quad jumps. Now Malinin is back, and this weekend he competed a free skate that has him attempting seven quads, plus a now-legal backflip. Look, there's no need to get too technical here. It's. Seven. Freaking. Quads. (No one has ever landed seven clean in competition.) Sometimes, the facts explain themselves.
Malinin didn't land all seven quads on Sunday at the U.S. figure skating championships, but his entire free skate is still impressive as hell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Florida Hoops Coaches Are The Subject Of University Investigations; Both Are Still Coaching]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179521</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/two-florida-hoops-coaches-are-the-subject-of-university-investigations-both-are-still-coaching"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T01:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At first glance, a casual men's basketball fan might think all is well in the Swamp. The Gators' most recent game was a thorough, 30-point stomping of rival Georgia. The squad is 18-2, third in the SEC, and ranked in the top 10 in both the coaches and AP polls. After years without a deep run in March Madness, the Stephen C. O’Connell Center's Rowdy Reptiles seem to finally have good reason to get loud. 
Except on Nov. 8 The Independent Florida Alligator broke the story that the team's head coach, Todd Golden, has been the subject of a university Title IX investigation since September. Per The Alligator, the complaint said that Golden was under investigation for allegations of sexual exploitation, sexual harassment, and stalking aimed at Florida students. From The Alligator:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chaos Is Fun But It’s Not The Way To Bet]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179536</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/chaos-is-fun-but-its-not-the-way-to-bet"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T00:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Commanders are new to this big game thing, which is why they acted on their first drive like their only way to beat the Philadelphia Eagles in the NFC championship game was to never relinquish the ball. They must have known that they would spend the rest of Sunday relinquishing everything.
Such is the price of being a newbie—errors happen and then compound themselves. The plucky underdog with the pretty new quarterback (Jayden Daniels) started out treating fourth down like it was second down with a bad attitude. They drove for 18 plays, converted two fourth-and-punt-the-ball downs, and ground out seven minutes of clock to give the game the chaotic feel that they needed it to have.  It worked out for the opening score, though weirdly they kicked a field goal rather than press their luck. It was the omen that nobody saw coming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MCalc – calculator for performing simple mathematical operations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141385</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/mcalc-calculator-performing-simple-mathematical-operations/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-26T23:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MCalc is a calculator for performing simple mathematical operations in all existing number systems.
The post MCalc – calculator for performing simple mathematical operations appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Framed – Files and Directories Reusability, Architecture, and Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141404</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/framed-files-directories-reusability-architecture-management/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-26T21:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Framed is a CLI tool that simplifies the organization and management of files and directories in a reusable and architectural manner. 
The post Framed – Files and Directories Reusability, Architecture, and Management appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[backdown – a deduplicator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141401</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/backdown-deduplicator/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-26T20:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Backdown helps you safely and ergonomically remove duplicate files. This is a command-line tool written in Rust.
The post backdown – a deduplicator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Best Free and Open Source Graphical Git Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=4651</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gitclients/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-26T19:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is one of a number of open source revision control systems available for Linux. We recommend the finest GUI-based tools.
The post 16 Best Free and Open Source Graphical Git Clients appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sysz – fzf terminal UI for systemctl]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141325</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/sysz-fzf-terminal-ui-systemctl/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-26T17:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sysz is an fzf terminal UI for systemctl. This is public domain software.
The post sysz – fzf terminal UI for systemctl appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loco – Web or API framework for Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141375</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/loco-web-api-framework-rust/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-26T15:07:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Loco is a Web or API framework for Rust. It's also a productivity suite for developers.
The post Loco – Web or API framework for Rust appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[shallow-backup – Git-integrated backup tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141395</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/shallow-backup-git-integrated-backup-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-26T13:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[shallow-backup lets you easily create lightweight backups of installed packages, applications, fonts and dotfiles.
The post shallow-backup – Git-integrated backup tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PelicanHPC – Linux distribution for high performance computing cluster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141362</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pelicanhpc-linux-distribution-high-performance-computing-cluster/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-26T11:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PelicanHPC is a Debian-Based "iso-hybrid (CD or USB) image that let's you set up a high performance computing cluster in a few minutes.
The post PelicanHPC – Linux distribution for high performance computing cluster appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new pizza shop in Kansas City's Historic Northeast wants to serve up a 'unifying food']]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-01-26/pizza-kansas-city-historic-northeast-noah-quillec</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-01-26/pizza-kansas-city-historic-northeast-noah-quillec"/>
        <updated>2025-01-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Northeast Pizza, which is set to open across the street from PH Coffee, will offer New York-style slices and whole pies. Noah Quillec grew up inside his family's restaurants around Kansas City, but wanted to design a spot for his own neighborhood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joyce Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USBKVM – keyboard, video, and mouse over USB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141332</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/usbkvm-keyboard-video-mouse-usb/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-26T09:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USBKVM is a client app for the USBKVM hardware. 
The post USBKVM – keyboard, video, and mouse over USB appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[systemctl-tui – interact with systemd services]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141321</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/systemctl-tui-interact-systemd-services/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-26T06:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[systemctl-tui is a fast, simple TUI for interacting with systemd services and their logs.
The post systemctl-tui – interact with systemd services appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lan Mouse – mouse and keyboard sharing via LAN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141283</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/lan-mouse-mouse-keyboard-sharing-lan/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-25T23:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lan Mouse is a cross-platform mouse and keyboard sharing software similar to universal-control on Apple devices.
The post Lan Mouse – mouse and keyboard sharing via LAN appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[kosmorro – calculate your ephemerides]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141273</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/kosmorro-calculate-ephemerides/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-25T21:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kosmorro is a program that calculates your astronomical ephemerides.
The post kosmorro – calculate your ephemerides appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynebolic – Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141357</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/dynebolic-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-25T15:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynebolic is a 100% Free Software Operating System for multimedia production, recommended by the Free Software Foundation.
The post Dynebolic – Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GGH – recall your SSH sessions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141318</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ggh-recall-ssh-sessions/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-25T12:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GGH is software which recalls your SSH sessions. It also searches your SSH configuration file.
The post GGH – recall your SSH sessions appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rage – simple video and audio player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141270</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/rage-simple-video-audio-player/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-25T11:49:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rage is a video and audio player written using the Enlightenment Foundation Libraries (EFL).
The post Rage – simple video and audio player appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[19 Best Free and Open Source Linux Graphical Calculators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=2932</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/calculators/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-25T11:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the basic utilities supplied with any operating system is a desktop calculator. We cover the best graphical tools.
The post 19 Best Free and Open Source Linux Graphical Calculators appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ephoto – image viewer based on the EFL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141266</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ephoto-image-viewer-efl/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-25T07:27:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ephoto is billed as a comprehensive image viewed based on the Enlightenment Foundation Libraries (EFL).
The post Ephoto – image viewer based on the EFL appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freespire – Ubuntu-based Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141249</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/freespire-ubuntu-based-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-25T00:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freespire is a community-driven Linux distribution that features the GNOME desktop environment (previousloy Xfce was used).
The post Freespire – Ubuntu-based Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Job Posting: Kansas City Royals – Multiple Openings]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?post_type=instagraphs&amp;p=455522</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/instagraphs/job-posting-kansas-city-royals-multiple-openings/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T22:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kansas City Royals are hiring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Appelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Benefits From Formula 1’s New Rules?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179458</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/who-benefits-from-formula-1s-new-rules"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FIA's priority for much of the 2024 Formula 1 season was cracking down on drivers' foul language over the radio and in press conferences. The word fuck, it made clear, was no longer acceptable, though for Federation Internationale de l'Automobile President Mohammed Ben Sulayem's clear, dog whistle–laden stance on the matter—"We have to differentiate between our sport, motorsport, and rap music"—it was not formally codified until yesterday, Jan. 23. The new International Sporting Code recommends specific punishments for misconduct, defined as language or actions that reasonably be construed as either "offensive, insulting, coarse, rude, or abrasive," or threatening. Within any two-year period, a first offense would incur a €40,000 fine (around $41,000), a second offense would incur a €80,000 fine and a suspended one-month ban, and a third offense would incur a €120,000 fine, a one-month ban and deduction of championship points. It remains unclear what a fourth offense would entail.
A professional sports league having a codified swear jar is ludicrous at face value. Though governing bodies frequently do ludicrous things and operate on ludicrous assumptions, it remains a mystery how three swear words over the course of two years would be more damaging to the sport than suspending a driver—like, say, the notoriously potty-mouthed but four-time World Champion Max Verstappen—for a month.  Verstappen's formal punishment for swearing in Singapore last year was mandatory community service. Charles Leclerc's punishment for swearing in Mexico was a €10,000 fine, half of which was suspended for a year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Input Leap – KVM software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141279</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/input-leap-kvm-software/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T20:44:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Input Leap is software that mimics the functionality of a KVM switch.
The post Input Leap – KVM software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oratorical Uncles Bond Over Increasingly Reactionary Views]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179493</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/oratorical-uncles-bond-over-increasingly-reactionary-views"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T20:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I suppose I expected something more eclectic and thrilling out of this collision between two of the most innovative sentence-level orators in New York City. And when Eric Adams said, "I'm a bald-headed, earring-wearing mayor that's saying that you don't have to have this one stereotypical look to be successful" early in his hour-long interview with Stephen A. Smith, my appetite for stupid utterances was whetted. But I was soon disappointed, and in time, disgusted. When Adams began a story "I will stop in the middle of the night when barber shops close down—I will go inside, sit down, smoke a cigar, drink a little Hennessy," I thought were were going to end in a destination more interesting than complaints about "the people who are putting out the messages of what is important to the Democratic party." That's really all this conversation was: a heavily indicted man arguing that he was ideologically abandoned, and then targeted, by a political party that he keeps threatening to quit.
Sure, it's a little funny to hear Adams complain that his biggest challenge as mayor is the fact that the media doesn't acknowledge his successes. It's a little funny to see him play the hits, like the "haters and waiters" spiel. He is sometimes sort of accidentally correct, like when he argues that the Democratic party has largely abandoned working-class concerns. And he did have one refreshingly Adamsian turn of phrase: "When a bullet carve a highway of death in your community and it hits someone it's not a Democrat or Republican." There was room for improvement in the delivery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 Best Free and Open Source Linux Terminal-Based Port Scanners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=4211</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/portscanners/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T20:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux has a good range of port scanners that help administrators identify and rectify weaknesses in a system.
The post 9 Best Free and Open Source Linux Terminal-Based Port Scanners appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big Stage Calls For Naoya Inoue]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179460</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-big-stage-calls-for-naoya-inoue"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T18:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, yeah, boxing ain’t what it was. Families ain’t gonna gather ‘round their radios to listen to prize fights ever again. And, sure, the most-watched and talked-about bout of the last couple years, Mike Tyson vs. Jake Paul, was far more a circus than a legitimate matchup. But the sport really isn’t in a horrible place right now. There are plenty of stars deserving of a bigger audience.
Case in point: Naoya Inoue, the reigning world junior featherweight champion and an absolute superstar in his native Japan. But only in his native Japan. You likely don’t know this, but Inoue already fought today. He retained his title with another artful, violent, and very expected knockout, this one of South Korean challenger Ye Joon Kim in Tokyo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RCalc – RPN calculator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141254</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/rcalc-rpn-calculator/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T18:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RCalc is an RPN (Reverse Polish Notation) calculator. It aims to be quick to open and use, and easy to extend
The post RCalc – RPN calculator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Frog Is In Its Belly Flop Era]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179318</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-frog-is-in-its-belly-flop-era"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T18:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are light enough, the water's surface is just another place to stretch your legs. The animal kingdom abounds with water-walkers: water striders perch atop ponds with thin legs held aloft with the help of water-repelling hair; basilisk lizards can run as far as five feet across water with long toes creating buoyant pockets of air; birds called western grebes have a mating ritual that involves running for up to seven seconds across water as their wide, flat feet slap the surface. And cricket frogs were long observed to cross ponds by way of "skittering," meaning jumping across the water without sinking.
Intrigued by the frogs' water-walking prowess, a group of scientists decided to study how the amphibians managed to stay at the top of the water's surface as they skittered, findings they recently reported in a paper in the Journal of Experimental Biology. When they filmed the cricket frogs on high-speed video, the researchers learned the hard truth behind skittering. Instead of bounding across the surface like a real water-walker, the cricket frogs completely submerged themselves in water between each hop. "This study is a testament to how even processes that seem so obvious can have a lot going on underneath the surface," Jasmine Nirody, a biophysicist at the University of Chicago who was not involved with the new paper, wrote in an email.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Coen Couldn’t Have Set The Bar Any Higher]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179454</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/liam-coen-couldnt-have-set-the-bar-any-higher"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T18:22:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Coen has been a head coach in the National Football League for, what, several hours now, and already he has set impossibly lofty expectations for himself. As we all know, in sports your reputation isn't found in provable success as much as it in convincing people that you were better than you should have been. And for that, Coen can thank the Tampa Bay Buccaneers and Jacksonville Jaguars, proving yet again that when you're looking for weird, you're looking at Florida.
Nobody outside The Other Bay Area much knew Coen before last week, but he is credited in that coachly way for the revivification of Baker Mayfield. And sure, why not? Mayfield was authentically great under Coen’s direction this season after nearly washing out of the league in the years prior; the Bucs didn't matter, then they did. Credit spreads like paint when a bad offensive team becomes a good one, and that will tend to benefit the guy who is otherwise only known as a forehead with a hat talking into a Denny's placemat. That’s Coen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2025 ZiPS Projections: Kansas City Royals]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=455313</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/2025-zips-projections-kansas-city-royals/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T18:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Their starting pitching and one particular batter should help the Royals keep pace with the Guardians and Twins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Szymborski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How The Hell Is Nikola Jokic Doing This?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179457</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-the-hell-is-nikola-jokic-doing-this"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T17:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know. I know. We write about Nikola Jokic all the time on Defector. We're just as aware of this as you are. I am telling you this at the start of this particular blog about Nikola Jokic because I want to make it clear that we do try to exercise some self-restraint here. OK, yes, fine, we did recently publish a whole blog about the fact that Jokic slapped a basketball a great distance, but that really was crazy. We try to keep the bar high, but the problem is that Jokic just keeps doing incredible things. 
Take last night's game against the Kings, which Jokic finished with 35 points, 22 rebounds, 17 assists, and two blocks. Wilt Chamberlain is the only other player in NBA history to have put up more than 35 points, 20 rebounds, and 15 assists in a single game, and Jokic's particular stat line had never been achieved before. Nuggets fans like to track these performances, which they call Jokigamis. It feels like Jokic has been producing one every week this season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City's Buffalo Bills bar embraces the Allen-Mahomes rivalry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2025-01-24/kansas-citys-buffalo-bills-bar-embraces-the-allen-mahomes-rivalry</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2025-01-24/kansas-citys-buffalo-bills-bar-embraces-the-allen-mahomes-rivalry"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T17:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taps on Main is a Bills Mafia hotspot located in the heart of Chiefs Kingdom. The bar embraces the friendly rivalry between Buffalo and Kansas City as Chiefs and Bills meet in the AFC Championship on Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kraske, Josh Marvine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[turbo-scanner – port scanner and service detection tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141260</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/turbo-scanner-port-scanner-service-detection-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T16:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[turbo-scanner is a port scanner and service detection tool that uses 1000 goroutines at once to scan any hosts IP or FQDN.
The post turbo-scanner – port scanner and service detection tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pix – image viewer and browser]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141244</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pix-image-viewer-browser/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T15:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pix is an image viewer and browser utility which is based on gThumb.
The post Pix – image viewer and browser appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Something stirs late next week (FRI-1/24)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3801315</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-something-stirs-late-next-week-fri-1-24/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T15:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This cold month of January continues this morning as readings dropped down to 5° earlier today, but thankfully started to recover towards daybreak, and by the end of the day we should see highs somewhere in the mid to upper 30s... so perhaps we can melt part of the glacier of ice and snow that [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Something stirs late next week (FRI-1/24)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3801315</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-something-stirs-late-next-week-fri-1-24/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T15:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This cold month of January continues this morning as readings dropped down to 5° earlier today but thankfully started to recover towards daybreak and by the end of the day we should see highs somewhere in the mid to upper 30s...so perhaps we can melt part of the glacier of ice and snow that remains [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Naval Scientist Who Wanted To Know How Football Players Would Survive Nuclear War]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179381</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-naval-scientist-who-wanted-to-know-how-football-players-would-survive-nuclear-war"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T14:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wouldn’t take much, the fan explained, just some radioactive material inside the players, who would then undergo a physical examination.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chats – messaging application for mobile and desktop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141241</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/chats-simple-messaging-app/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T13:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chats is a simple to use messaging app for 1:1 communication and small groups supporting SMS/MMS, Matrix, and XMPP.
The post Chats – messaging application for mobile and desktop appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grml – bootable live system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141233</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/grml-bootable-live-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T12:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grml is a bootable live system (Live-CD) based on Debian. It includes a collection of Linux software especially for system administrators.
The post Grml – bootable live system appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deskflow – keyboard and mouse sharing app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141231</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/deskflow-keyboard-mouse/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T11:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deskflow is a keyboard and mouse sharing app that supports Wayland, clipboard sharing, and TLS encryption.
The post Deskflow – keyboard and mouse sharing app appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TEAMGROUP MP44L 2TB M.2 NVMe SSD Review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141176</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/teamgroup-mp44l-2tb-m2-nvme-ssd-review/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T09:54:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The TEAMGROUP MP44L SSD is available in 250GB, 500GB, 1TB, and 2TB sizes. In this review, we explore the 2TB SSD.
The post TEAMGROUP MP44L 2TB M.2 NVMe SSD Review appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Tejada]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/john-tejada-3bf</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/john-tejada-3bf"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T08:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Friday so we’re listening to something more upbeat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu Cinnamon – community-driven Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141219</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ubuntu-cinnamon-community-driven-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T07:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu Cinnamon is a community-driven flavor of Ubuntu, combining Linux Mint’s flagship Cinnamon Desktop with Ubuntu.
The post Ubuntu Cinnamon – community-driven Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[astroterm – terminal-based star map]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141212</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/astroterm-terminal-based-star-map/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T06:38:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[astroterm is a planetarium for your terminal. Explore stars, planets, constellations, and more, all rendered right in the command line.
The post astroterm – terminal-based star map appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[T. Rex Evolution]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3042/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3042/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC’s food scene rakes in eight James Beard Awards nominations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=867818</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-food-scene-rakes-in-eight-local-james-beard-awards-nominations/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T02:04:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Beard Awards medal. // Photo Courtesy of James Beard Foundation After the Kansas City metro saw seven nominations for James Beard Awards in 2024, it seemed like a hard number to beat in the new year. But our city has a competitive spirit, as shown in our sports fandom, and holding true to that nature, we have outdone ourselves...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kat Alfieri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[18 Best Free and Open Source Linux Time Tracking Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=4640</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/timetracking/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T20:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time tracking software is a type of computer software that records time spent on tasks. This category of software can enable users to run billing reports, and prepare invoices for clients.
The post 18 Best Free and Open Source Linux Time Tracking Software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ec – RPN calculator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141067</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ec-rpn-calculator/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T20:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ec is a useful RPN calculator with array operations and quotations.
The post ec – RPN calculator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bop It In The Go Bag, With Justin Halpern]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179363</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bop-it-in-the-go-bag-with-justin-halpern"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T20:11:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know how it is. Someone asks how you're doing—in a casual setting, or at the top of the podcast you do every week—and in that moment you must decide just how honest an answer is appropriate, or kind, or just reasonably in keeping with the intention behind the question. If it seemed like I was stuck for an answer this week, it's because I truly was. There's a lot of bad stuff happening, enough that the usual "I'm good" kind of stuck in my throat. This is not the only reason why we have guests, but it is a good one. I was determined not to get up there and filibuster and fret in front of Justin Halpern, returning champion Distraction guest, on-call Padres magus, and executive producer of Abbott Elementary and Harley Quinn. Not right away, anyway.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best Free and Open Source Accountancy Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=83788</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-accountancy-software/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T19:53:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accountancy is the measurement, processing, and communication of financial and non financial information about economic entities.
The post 10 Best Free and Open Source Accountancy Software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe The Dodgers’ Competitors Could Show Some Self-Respect]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179380</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/maybe-the-dodgers-competitors-could-show-some-self-respect"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T18:53:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his October 2024 introductory press conference as the new president of baseball operations of the San Francisco Giants, Buster Posey declared, "We're in the memory-making business." No matter any outsized belief in RBI, it was the strongest repudiation of the old Farhan Zaidi regime, an optimized, min-maxed platoon machine with a veritable lack of new dudes, which spent each year scuttling about trying to sneak into the Wild Card, caught lightning in a bottle in 2021, and—after showing prediction models who's boss—never broke .500 since. It doesn't matter if Matt Chapman never puts up another 7 rWAR season, or if Willy Adames is the ideal guy to drop a $182 million contract on—so long as the Giants' roster winds up with people to root for, year over year, Posey's team-building philosophy will readily outperform Zaidi's as a maker of memories.
Combine commitment to the memory-making business with an optimized, min-maxed machine, and you wind up with the Los Angeles Dodgers, who are, if you missed it, ruining baseball. Admittedly, signing a guy so fans and future fans alike will have someone to root for is a bit different from signing every guy on the market; the latter is, to simplify a bit, the Dodgers' approach to this past offseason. So far, Los Angeles has signed or extended, in a semi-rapid succession of long-term contracts: Blake Snell, Tommy Edman, Hye-seong Kim (a 25-year-old free agent with 37 career home runs in the KBO, who is not to be confused with cool Padres guy Ha-seong Kim), and then, in the span of one week, Roki Sasaki, Tanner Scott, and Kirby Yates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Draymond Green Is Still Only Sorta Sorry About Punching Jordan Poole]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179389</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/draymond-green-is-still-only-sorta-sorry-about-punching-jordan-poole"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T18:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Draymond Green has been to therapy. He's worked through some things, addressed some pent-up feelings of anger and insecurity. Now he has made it through to the other side, and you know what? He still kinda feels like he was justified in punching Jordan Poole back in 2022.
This is the only logical takeaway from Green's latest podcast episode, where he once again got into the infamous altercation. After the Golden State Warriors beat the Washington Wizards in an otherwise unmemorable game—save for the fact that Poole got a warm reception from the San Francisco crowd—Poole commented on his relationship with the Warriors locker room by saying "I love those guys over there," before immediately correcting himself: "I love most of those guys over there." Green, who truly cannot help himself, took the bait, tweeting in reply "I really am sorry." Green reiterated this sentiment on the podcast saying, "I'm sorry. I shouldn't have punched him. But it happened. Let's move on."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paris Saint-Germain Revived Manchester City’s Woes]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179372</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/paris-saint-germain-revived-manchester-citys-woes"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T17:25:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the Champions League schedule came out, the Matchday Seven showdown between Paris Saint-Germain and Manchester City looked to be a veritable clash of the titans, but I have to admit I was a bit underwhelmed by its timing. Thanks to the new league-stage format, I figured that two of Europe's most expensively assembled sides would be safely through to the knockouts by this point, and that the match wouldn't have all that much riding on it.
I was wrong on two counts. First, I have to admit I did not foresee that El Gásico would be not a matchup at the top of the table, but rather a true battle of survival. Entering Wednesday's match in Paris, both clubs were in a klaxon-worthy panic, marooned in the bottom third of the 36-team table and in real jeopardy of missing the knockout round all together. My second mistake was in assuming that a PSG-City match would be anything but a banger, an intuition that seemed to bear out during the scoreless first half, only to explode into a delirious 4-2 PSG comeback win that might have been the most entertaining match of the campaign.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eat This Now: The Cookie-licious Milkshake at Sweet Thang and Café]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866971</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/eat-this-now-the-cookie-licious-milkshake-at-sweet-thang-and-cafe/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T17:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cookie-licious Milkshake at Sweet Thang and Café. // Photo by Kat Alfieri Even with a glacial wind chill, a quick run for a classic ice cream scoop is a recipe for turning a loss into a win. Sweet Thang and Café in Olathe has playful ice cream flavors, soft baked cookies and brownies, and a few sandwiches to pair with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kat Alfieri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Am Witness To The Rebirth Of Football In Washington]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179369</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-am-witness-to-the-rebirth-of-football-in-washington"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T16:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
It’s the mid-2000s. I’ve just moved to the D.C. area. My wife is from here. I am not. My wife has friends here. I do not. My wife has a job. I do not. Every day, I have to boot up a PC we borrowed from my brother-in-law and scroll through listings on Monster that are either fake jobs, or jobs I’ve already seen listed 500 times before. In the meantime, my wife is the breadwinner, working a cubicle job she hates in a suburban office building she may hate even more. We only have one car—a champagne Honda Accord her parents let us have—so I’m her ride to and from work. I have to pick her up every day just after five, but sometimes her work runs a little bit long and I stay in the car to wait. I don’t mind this wait, because while I don’t know anyone in this town, I do know that everyone here (at least, for now) loves football, and their football team in particular.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is My Most Loathed Enemy A Song From The Score Of ‘Challengers’? Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah-Yeah-Yeah Yeah Yeah-Yeah-Yeah]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179378</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/is-my-most-loathed-enemy-a-song-from-the-score-of-challengers-yeah"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T15:43:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Oscar nominees for 2025 were announced Thursday morning. The list for Best Original Score caused a minor stir in Defector's Slack when it was observed that the score of Challengers, by Trent Reznor and Atticus Ross, didn't make the cut. Reznor and Ross have been nominated before, lots of times, for lots of different awards. They've won a couple Oscars already, a BAFTA, an Emmy, three Golden Globes, and probably some Grammys. The score for Challengers was well-received and memorable, and was an important part of a well-reviewed film. And like most Reznor and Ross joints, it's something a normal person might choose to bump on their car's sound system, in those moments where they feel like driving very fast. Certainly I will not be jamming out to the score of The Wild Robot, a movie I had never heard of before this morning.
Unfortunately, I am forced to rush to the defense of the Academy in this case. However jaunty and fun the rest of the Challengers score may be, the Academy was right to penalize Reznor and Ross for having created the song "Yeah x10," which is the most irritating piece of music imaginable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Much Ado About Shrew]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179056</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/much-ado-about-shrew"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T14:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vishal Subramanyan and Prakrit Jain had never even heard of the rare shrew they would soon spend months chasing. The students were both in the same mammalogy class at the University of California, Berkeley, which included trips teaching students how to catch, handle, and process small mammals. On one such trip, Jain brought his camera and snapped some shots of voles and deer mice. Curious if there were any other small and obscure mammals nearby to photograph, Jain perused a list of the mammals of California and noticed that one species, the Mount Lyell shrew, had never been photographed before. "I was immediately fascinated," Jain said.
Jain told Subramanyan about the shrew in September, and the two hatched a scheme. Subramanyan, who has since graduated from Berkeley, is a wildlife conservation photographer and a creator in the California Academy of Science's California Creators for Nature program. Neither Jain nor Subramanyan had worked with a species like a shrew before; Subramanyan ordinarily photographs wildlife giants such as mountain lions and wolves, and Jain ordinarily photographs itty-bitty invertebrates, such as scorpions and arachnids. The small shrew offered them a chance to meet in the middle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Old Rules Are For Losers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179278</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-old-rules-are-for-losers"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T14:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The further we get away from the 2016 Democratic National Convention the more I become convinced that Michelle Obama standing on that stage saying, “When they go low, we go high,” was a death knell. By now, she’s realized it. In the brief period of this past election cycle where the Democrats were trying to win, calling Donald Trump and J.D. Vance “weird”, she backed away from the statement on the convention stage. But then, just as suddenly, Democrats backed off their line of attack. Why try something new, to seeming success, when you could run the same old playbook to failure?
The reason that phrase sticks in my head is because it was a failed strategy from the get-go. If your opponent is “going low,” following the rules will not help you. You will not be given a gold star by the teacher. In fact, it will only give your opponent more space and opportunity to play dirty. The Republicans (who are winning politics, currently) know that they are in a competition, and that the Democrats are their opponents and enemies. They behave like it. Democrats, over and over again, seem to be trying to prove that they are not actually in a feud with Republicans. In their efforts at peace-keeping, they allow violence to reign. They are unable or unwilling to fight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tmux Pomodoro Plus – incorporate the Pomodoro technique]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140963</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tmux-pomodoro-plus-incorporate-pomodoro-technique/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T09:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tmux Pomodoro Plus is software which incorporates the Pomodoro technique into your tmux setup.
The post Tmux Pomodoro Plus – incorporate the Pomodoro technique appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spyro Gyra]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/spyro-gyra</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/spyro-gyra"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T08:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Spyro Gyra, an American jazz fusion band from Buffalo, New York.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Btrbk – backup tool for btrfs subvolumes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141088</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/btrbk-backup-tool-btrfs-subvolumes/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T07:17:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Btrbk is a backup tool for btrfs subvolumes, taking advantage of btrfs specific capabilities to create atomic snapshots.
The post Btrbk – backup tool for btrfs subvolumes appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Commet – chat client powered by Matrix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141084</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/commet-chat-client-matrix/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-22T23:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Commet is a client for Matrix focused on providing a feature rich experience while maintaining a simple interface.
The post Commet – chat client powered by Matrix appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novak Djokovic Teaches Carlos Alcaraz One More Crucial Lesson]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179339</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/novak-djokovic-teaches-carlos-alcaraz-one-more-crucial-lesson"/>
        <updated>2025-01-22T21:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even prodigies must learn hard lessons in public sometimes. Carlos Alcaraz has won four major titles and extracts tennis wisdom at a disturbing rate, but there are plenty of situations on court that the 21-year-old has yet to confront. In Tuesday’s Australian Open quarterfinal against the 37-year-old Novak Djokovic, Alcaraz lost, 4-6, 6-4, 6-3, 6-4, and learned how to grapple with an opponent whose injury did not prevent him from playing at a world-historical level. 
At 4-4 in the first set, Djokovic slid hard while running to his right and seemed to tweak something in his left groin, causing him to grimace and stretch it out. On his next serve, he struggled to push off the ground with that leg. He lost the ensuing rally then shook his head at his player’s box, suggesting that he wasn’t right. Injury suddenly imperiled the most anticipated match of the men’s draw in Melbourne. After having his serve broken, Djokovic was evaluated by a physiotherapist, who took him off court to wrap up his left thigh. A doctor administered a dose of painkillers. Djokovic returned to the court and lost the first set to Alcaraz, who looked unfazed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>