<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-11-20T02:54:17.655Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Select Three Players To 40-Man Roster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=831291</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/royals-select-three-players-to-40-man-roster.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T22:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have selected left-hander Noah Cameron, right-hander Luinder Avila, and right-hander Eric Cerantola to their 40-man roster ahead of this evening Rule 5 Draft protection deadline, per a team announcement. No corresponding moves were necessary, and the club’s 40-man roster now stands at 37 players. Cameron, 25, was a seventh-round pick by the Royals…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Hallmark films a fictional Taylor/Travis Christmas rom-com during Missouri summer heat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861612</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-hallmark-films-a-fictional-taylor-travis-christmas-rom-com-during-missouri-summer-heat/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T22:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo courtesy of Hallmark Media Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be publishing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xaboo Mephaa brings traditional flavors of Guerrero, Mexico, to Lee's Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2024-11-19/xaboo-mephaa-brings-traditional-flavors-of-guerrero-mexico-to-lees-summit</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2024-11-19/xaboo-mephaa-brings-traditional-flavors-of-guerrero-mexico-to-lees-summit"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The family-run establishment began as a food truck in 2021 and just celebrated its one year anniversary at its brick-and-mortar location at 1196 Douglas Street. The restaurant specializes in traditional homestyle dishes from the state of Guerrero, Mexico.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Ellison, Claudia Brancart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockbuster adaptation of Broadway musical Wicked hits most of the right notes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862430</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/blockbuster-adaptation-of-broadway-musical-wicked-hits-most-of-the-right-notes/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T20:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wicked. // Courtesy Universal There are some movies so big they don’t need reviews. The Harry Potter movies still play on repeat in some people’s homes every holiday, despite the fact that the third film is the only one that really holds up (I said what I said). The Lord of the Rings trilogy is a Christmas staple in many...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dyson Daniels Is On The Prowl]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173822</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dyson-daniels-is-on-the-prowl"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T20:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not much for nicknames, though occasionally a moniker so good emerges that it becomes the only way I can think about a player. Atlanta's Australian ballhawk Dyson Daniels has earned such a nickname: the Great Barrier Thief. In his first season with the Hawks, the 21-year-old Daniels is starting for the first time and, as such, is having a breakout season. It's always fun when a young, promising player is given their first chance at a big role, because all that newfound responsibility is a much stronger test of their abilities; there's so much talent in the league right now that surely each team has several players who could do more if given more opportunity. Daniels has shown, through 13 games with the Hawks, that he is one of the best defensive playmakers in the NBA.
Daniels is currently leading the league with 3.4 steals per game; his 91 deflections are a whopping 34 more than second-placed De'Aaron Fox. Daniels is averaging 4.7 steals every 100 possessions, the highest such figure since Nate McMillan, the guy who coached the Hawks for some of last season, did it in 1993–94 for the Seattle Supersonics, who don't exist anymore. Daniels recently put together an unholy four-game streak of six or more steals per game, and he has recorded a steal in every single game except for Monday night's win against the Fox's Sacramento Kings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sagging 76ers Need Joel Embiid, But Not This Joel Embiid]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173838</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-sagging-76ers-need-joel-embiid-but-not-this-joel-embiid"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T19:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's no reason why a sudden, unplanned team meeting has to be a bad thing. Maybe it's a good thing! Maybe your veteran teammate is calling the team meeting, immediately after the conclusion of a road game, because he wants to shower someone in much-deserved attention, or to announce that he just got a great deal on car insurance. You can't know until you have attended the meeting. Best not to burden yourself with anxiety. Best to go into the meeting expecting it to be happy and celebratory.
Kyle Lowry, veteran guard for the Philadelphia 76ers, did not recently get a great deal on car insurance, or if he did, that was not why he called Monday's meeting. The 76ers had just played listlessly and disjointedly and had their butts pretty thoroughly hacked off by the Miami Heat, their fourth consecutive loss, dropping their record to a league-worst 2–11. It was Lowry's impression that the team—which if healthy and united should very reasonably expect to make another playoff run—needed to clear the air and share "a call to action and urgency," as sources described it to ESPN's Shams Charania.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Have Shown Interest In Alec Bohm, Taylor Ward]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=831207</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/royals-trade-rumors-alec-bohm-phillies-taylor-ward-angels.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T19:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have reportedly spoken to the Reds about a trade involving Kansas City right-hander Brady Singer and Cincinnati infielder Jonathan India, but that’s just one of multiple pursuits for Royals general manager J.J. Picollo, it seems. Anne Rogers of MLB.com reports that while no deals are necessarily close as of this moment, the Royals…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help! My Dog Gets Mad At Me When I Fart!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173746</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/help-my-dog-gets-mad-at-me-when-i-fart"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T18:12:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about Bluesky, farts, Sean Payton, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New cafe, Cortadito, brings Cuban flavors and hospitality to KCK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861427</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/new-cafe-cortadito-brings-cuban-flavors-and-hospitality-to-kck/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T18:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cortadito owners Karell Martinez and Nubia Gomez // Photo by Tiffany Watts This Saturday, Kansas City’s newest Cuban cafe, Cortadito, opened its doors, inviting the community to experience the warmth, flavor, and spirit of Cuba right in the heart of the city. Owners Karell Martinez and Nubia Gomez, both deeply connected to their Cuban heritage, aim to make Cortadito more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Tanfastic Mobile’s Andrea Irish]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862147</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-tanfastic-mobiles-andrea-irish/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T17:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Andrea Irish We don’t want to point out the obvious, but we think Tanfastic Mobile Owner Andrea Irish is missing an amazing marketing opportunity by not calling herself Tandrea. (Legit, eh?)  The spray tan artist extraordinaire recently won The Pitch’s Best Mobile Spray Tan category.  Irish ventured into the land of spray tanning more than twenty years ago....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Arctic air to enter the pattern (TUE-11/19)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3732842</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-arctic-air-to-enter-the-pattern-tue-11-19/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T16:07:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a right and not to bad of a start to our day in KC after a crazy weather day yesterday that featured more soaking rains, record rains for the date, windy conditions, stunning rainbows at sunset, very windy conditions, power outages and probably a few other things as well. That was all in response [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How An Imported State Champion Blew Up Virginia High School Football]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172497</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-an-imported-state-champion-blew-up-virginia-high-school-football"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T16:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Administrators at Hayfield Secondary School in Alexandria, Va., set out late last year to create a football powerhouse. The principal and athletic director, both new to the school, recruited the coach from Freedom High School, a school located in a neighboring county that had claimed the state title the previous two seasons and was in the Top 40 nationally. One high school poaching a football coach from another isn't all that noteworthy, unless, as in this case, all his top players and coaching staff come with him.
Basically, the best team in the state was invited to just change its address and uniforms and get back to whipping everybody's ass. And they accepted. It's been all ugliness ever since. Hayfield put together the most talked-about schoolboy football juggernaut to hit Alexandria since the 1971 team at T.C. Williams, the squad that inspired the Remember the Titans. This ain't the feel-good drama that one was, however. The administration's pre-fab superteam scheme fell into place so fast and was so successful—the Hawks went 9-0 with a scoring differential of 563-13 against other public schools—that it produced multiple investigations for rule-breaking, a postseason ban, lawsuits, and an 11th-hour court injunction. In between all of that was a whole bunch of uncompetitive football.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Forces Of Nature Are Arrayed Against Jerry Jones]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173755</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-forces-of-nature-are-arrayed-against-jerry-jones"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T15:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three hours before kickoff, the Cowboys opened their retractable roof so that God Himself could look down on his creation and recoil in horror. It was a majestic display; that whirring may as well have been the hum of the clockwork of the universe itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Macklin Celebrini Stripped The Red Wings Of Any Remaining Dignity]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173753</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/macklin-celebrini-stripped-the-red-wings-of-any-remaining-dignity"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T15:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The California road trip ain't what it used to be. About a decade ago, a team traveling from the East into the Golden State would have to duel three Cup contenders in quick succession: Los Angeles, Anaheim, and San Jose. But now, as both the Ducks and Sharks slog through a stretched-out rebuild and the Kings haven't won a playoff series since 2014, the trip's most intimidating foe is jetlag. Nevertheless, the Detroit Red Wings still spent a long weekend finding a way to lose all three meetings, dropping themselves into a precarious early-season position that already threatens to extend their postseason drought to nine years.
The Ducks game to open the trip was the most frustrating, as a 3-1 Detroit lead near the end of the second evaporated into a 6-4 defeat. In the back-to-back against the Kings, head coach Derek Lalonde's boys sleepwalked to a 4-1 loss. In San Jose on Monday, the team salvaged one point thanks to an effective power play that helped get the game to overtime, but still left the building as losers on account of No. 1 overall pick Macklin Celebrini's knockout blow at three-on-three.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 49ers Might Just Be Like This]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173668</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-49ers-might-just-be-like-this"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T13:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You never actually hear a metaphorical window close. For starters, the window in question is metaphorical; for another, that kind of window doesn't open up and down as you might imagine it, but in and out. That way, it can open and close with a gust of ill wind or a burst of good fortune. The transparency of it might make you think the window is not just wide open but a glass door that leads out to the backyard pool and allows the largest of mesomorphs easy passage. Approach with too much confidence and you might walk right into it that way, and your insurance won't cover the cost of the dentist having to pull glass out of your gums.
We don't know if the San Francisco 49ers' six-year window of Super Bowl contendership is finally closed, but it certainly has a totally unjustified sense of closing soon. They just feel too ordinary for one to care about in that way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renters and Tenant Union present lease violations to landlord amid eviction threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862280</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/renters-and-tenant-union-present-lease-violations-to-landlord-amid-eviction-threats/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T02:36:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy KC Tenants On day 46 of their rent strike, the Quality Hill Towers Tenant Union, in coordination with the Independence Towers Tenant Union, held an emergency strike picket. This action follows a Zoom meeting with the Federal Housing Finance Agency in which staff informed residents that despite their authority over Fannie Mae, the mortgage financier for the property, there...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paige Eichkorn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teri Rogers Film Grant awarded to three local filmmakers, paving the way for KC filming expansion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861958</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/teri-rogers-film-grant-awarded-to-three-local-filmmakers-paving-the-way-for-kc-filming-expansion/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T00:48:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both 2023 and 2024 Teri Rogers Film Grant recipients Eva Louise Hall, Jean-Jacques Corbier, Jerry Rapp, Mel Sangyi Zhao, Khitam Jabr, and Vy Nguyen stand together for a group photo. // Photo by Lane Rozin On Nov. 14, the third annual Teri Rogers Film Fund Reception awarded three grant recipients: Eva Louise Hall, Mel Sangyi Zhao, and Jean-Jacques Corbier. Hosted...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Global Entrepreneur Week’s Callie England]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862132</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-global-entrepreneur-weeks-callie-england/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T22:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Callie England If you’re an entrepreneur, solo-preneur, or any other preneur for that matter, listen up! Callie England has your back. Not only is she helping spearhead Global Entrepreneurship Week over the next few days, she’s sure to become your newest fan. With her 15 years of expertise in creative and brand management, she’s successfully scaled multiple consumer-facing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Willie Watson takes a deep look in the mirror on his first-ever album of original songs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862187</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/willie-watson-takes-a-deep-look-in-the-mirror-on-his-first-ever-album-of-original-songs/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T21:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Willie Watson. // photo credit Hayden Shiebler Back in February, we got a chance to catch a few sets from musician Willie Watson as part of the Folk Alliance International Conference at The Westin Kansas City at Crown Center, and we were just gobsmacked at how good his songs were. The founding member of Old Crow Medicine Show’s self-titled album—his...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bears Continue To Innovate In The Space Of Crushing Last-Second Defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173617</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bears-continue-to-innovate-in-space-of-crushing-last-second-defeat"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T20:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of course, no epidemic of kicking disasters would ever spare the Chicago Bears.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bengals-Chargers Was A Thrilling Mess Of A Sunday Nighter]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173605</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bengals-chargers-was-a-thrilling-mess-of-a-sunday-nighter"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T18:22:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's nothing quite like an exciting Sunday Night Football game. After a day of sitting on the couch mainlining RedZone, it's a nice, healthy step-down to sit back and enjoy just one game in the moment. If that game delivers, then all the better. There have been some fun ones this season, even as recently as last weekend with the Jared Goff interceptionpalooza. But for my money, Sunday's match-up between the Chargers and Bengals was the best Sunday night game of the season. Both teams, at separate times and sometimes at the same time, looked like they were trying to gift the game away; this somehow only made the game itself more compelling. A battle of weaponized incompetence might not sound like riveting viewing, but both teams traded periods of dominance across 60 minutes, and the only reason really that the Chargers came out ahead 34-27 is that they choked just a bit less in the final quarter.
If you want to be more generous than that, the Chargers won because they executed one more time than the Bengals did in the fourth, but that would ignore how Los Angeles built up a comfortable 27-6 lead on the arm of Justin Herbert, only to abruptly and completely forget how to play defense. Let's start with Herbert, though, because he was absolutely dealing in the first half. Herbert completed his first six passes on the night for 123 yards and two TDs, the first of which was a beautiful laser down the seam to tight end Will Dissly. The second was even better, as Herbert took a wide bootleg right before swerving left and leaving his feet for a bullet to a wide open Quentin Johnson in the end zone:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Jets Are In Hell, Where They Belong]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173613</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-jets-are-in-hell-where-they-belong"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the first time this season, the New York Jets finally scored at least 25 points in a game. The bad news for them was that the Indianapolis Colts scored more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Gangstagrass surprises with a pop-up show at Lucia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862065</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-gangstagrass-surprises-with-a-pop-up-show-at-lucia/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T17:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gangstagrass. // photo by Nick Spacek Gangstagrass Lucia Saturday, November 16 Friday night, hip-hop/bluegrass innovators Gangstagrass performed at what several folks delicately referred to as a “lightly-attended” show at the Folly in Kansas City. Their surprise pop-up show Saturday night at Lucia in Lawrence was a packed house. Granted, yes, Lucia holds maybe 150 people, while the Folly can seat...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: A full-time food editor favors these highlights from an overstuffed year of flavor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861547</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-a-full-time-food-editor-favors-these-highlights-from-an-overstuffed-year-of-flavor/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T17:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orange By: Devoured. // Photo by Tiffany Watts Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josh Allen Ran Through Kansas City’s Perfect Record]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173592</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/josh-allen-ran-through-kansas-citys-perfect-record"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T16:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's no surprise that the Bills and the Chiefs played a high-stakes thriller that was decided when one of their quarterbacks made a spectacular play. But there was still no way, really, to be prepared for Buffalo QB Josh Allen's improv in the most nerve-wracking of spots—up two with just over two minutes to play, facing fourth-and-two on the KC 26. Fail to the gain the yards (or opt to kick a field goal), and the Bills would be handing the ball over to Patrick Mahomes with the opportunity for a game-winning two-minute drill. Instead, Allen seized the victory for himself by beating every Chiefs defender to the end zone.
Kansas City rushed four against Buffalo's five blockers, but Allen was still able to spot a crease in the defense as he stepped up in the pocket. With two wideouts going to the sticks on the right, and another target at the same distance on his left, there was just enough of an opening in the middle for Allen to acquire the yardage he needed. But he didn't stop there. Accelerating toward the goal line, he made one diving tackler fall helplessly at his heels, shrugged off another who tried to fly at his arm, and powered through safety Bryan Cook as he fell triumphantly into the blue paint. The Bills had their two-score lead, and the defense did their part to make the final line 30-21.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Nov. 18: Turnaround Jumpers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173553</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-nov-18-turnaround-jumpers"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T15:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why not give our Monday crossword a shot? This week's puzzle was constructed by Hanh Huynh and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Hanh is a bankruptcy attorney who lives in Brooklyn, N.Y. with his wife and two kids. This puzzle was inspired by his favorite sport to watch and play: basketball. His favorite team is the UConn women.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody Is Doing It Like De’Aaron Fox]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173529</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nobody-is-doing-it-like-deaaron-fox"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T15:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to understand what makes De'Aaron Fox's game so effective and cool, the most important thing to understand is something of a signature Fox play: the surprise fast break. Several times per game, while the opposing team is in the process of setting up its halfcourt defense with obvious spatial and manpower advantages, Fox will see an opening and sprint with the ball directly into the heart of that defense, creating either a layup for himself or a wide open shot for a teammate. The sorts of gaps he pries open are not available to any other ball-handler on any other team, because nobody else in the NBA is as demon-quick as Fox, or as insistent on applying pressure in seemingly disadvantageous situations. 
You can apply the logic of the surprise fast break forward to explain the rest of his game, and as he showed over a historic weekend, the highest level of that game is startling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Strong storm changes our weather this week (MON-11/18)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3731723</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-strong-storm-changes-our-weather-this-week-mon-11-18/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T15:19:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not a terrible weekend really, I was out working in the yard for a few hours yesterday in shorts, and that's not bad by mid November standards around these parts, then on Saturday evening I was helping to light up the Legends Outlets in KCK. Comfortable compared to what it could be like in November. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pride Feasted On Kansas City’s Fear]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173552</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-pride-feasted-on-kansas-citys-fear"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T15:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Orlando Pride did not become the first team in NWSL history to collect 60 points for any one reason. On any given day, you could assign credit to Barbra Banda's attacking ferocity, Marta's ageless orchestration, or the league's stingiest defense. But in order to make it through an entire season with only two losses, you need the reliable presence of all three of those things, and more. Truly great teams are great as a matter of course. This is something that the Kansas City Current learned on Sunday, as they fell to the Pride, 3-2, in the league semifinal.
The final score conceals the convincing nature of Orlando's victory, which was claimed in the 82nd minute through an act of eye-watering beauty crafted by the best player in history. Everything that happened after Marta scored to give the Pride a 3-1 lead—16 minutes of stoppage time, the Current getting a goal back thanks to a fluky handball in the box, Banda leaving the game with an injury—may as well not have happened, because the game had already been defined for good by Marta's feat:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Ovechkin Refuses To Slow Down]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173570</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/alex-ovechkin-refuses-to-slow-down"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T14:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you'd asked me 20 years ago, I would have said confidently that Wayne Gretzky's NHL record of 894 career goals was unbreakable. It was a curio to be admired, not a number to be chased; like Cy Young's 511 wins, it came from a different era, almost a different sport entirely. If you'd asked me one year ago, when Alex Ovechkin was scuffling with five goals, which is all he'd still have even a month later, I'd have considered the chase a tragicomedy—an ancient Ovi, looking so washed up he should be talking to a volleyball, puttering his way through sad season after sad season, long after he should have retired, making his team worse. It would have been awful; it would have lessened both the record and Ovechkin's career. 
I'll extend myself some forgiveness for thinking it was over, that guys pushing 40 don't tend to have slumps, or at least not slumps that end. I would have done well to recall Ovechkin's quote from more than a decade ago, a sign that he probably stresses the least of anyone over his goalscoring droughts. "Right now I’m scoring goals and I’m the king of the world," he said. "And a couple weeks ago I was almost in the toilet. So maybe you just forget to flush me."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Celebrating weed without worry another year into recreational legality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861540</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-2024-celebrating-weed-without-worry-another-year-into-recreational-legality/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T14:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Show-Me Organics // Photo by Zach Bauman Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Godspeed You! Black Emperor glides through Liberty Hall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862061</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/godspeed-you-black-emperor-glides-through-liberty-hall/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T12:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Godspeed You! Black Emperor with Alan Sparhawk Liberty Hall Monday, November 11 What are the inner thoughts one experiences when one hears live music? I often reflect on the turmoil that has surmounted me during recent times, maybe even years past – especially for a band like Godspeed You! Black Emperor, whose music “continues to say so much without saying...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Dodderidge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Tenants host ‘Yeehaw!’ benefit featuring Caleb Hearon, Waxahatchee, Beth Stelling, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862181</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-tenants-host-yeehaw-benefit-featuring-caleb-hearon-waxahatchee-beth-stelling-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T12:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Saturday, November 23, the Kansas City Tenants Union will host the 3rd annual Yeehaw!: A Benefit for Kansas City at The Midland. Hosted by Missouri’s own Caleb Hearon and Katie Crutchfield of Waxahatchee, with performances by Beth Stelling, Briston Maroney, The Salvation Choir, and Samia, as well as some secret surprise guests, this benefit show is not one to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zoe Strohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’90s basic cable late-night thrillers get raunchy resurrection in Dream Team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861851</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/90s-basic-cable-late-night-thrillers-get-raunchy-resurrection-in-dream-team/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T23:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Whitney Horn, courtesy of Yellow Veil Pictures It’s a bit of inside baseball, but one of the easiest parts of being a film critic in the era of omnipresent streaming is the ability to recommend a film that doesn’t require a trip to an expensive theater. The subject of today’s writing is a film that absolutely was built for you...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tyson/Paul Was A Boxing Match That Felt Like Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173508</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tyson-paul-was-a-boxing-match-that-felt-like-netflix"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T21:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is only moderately useful context for one of the drearier sporting events in recent memory that, by his own telling, Mike Tyson nearly died six weeks before his fight with Jake Paul, which finally glitched and lurched and went the whole bleak distance late Friday night, was first scheduled to happen. This was in late May, when what was reported as an ulcer flare-up left Tyson vomiting blood in an airplane bathroom and then in a hospital. "I lost 25 pounds in 11 days," Tyson told New York Magazine. "Every time I went to the bathroom it smelled like tar. Didn't even smell like shit anymore." Tyson told New York that he had "like, eight blood transfusions. The doctor said I lost half my blood." The fight was delayed from late July to mid-November.
It is rude but not really inaccurate to say that Tyson looked like someone who'd had a recent near-death experience, or like someone who had turned 58 back in June, on Friday night. He did and he did, and none of that qualified as a surprise or even really a disappointment. Tyson had retired in 2005 and endured all manner of bad physical and financial health and personal tragedy since; with the exception of two exhibitions, in 2006 and 2020, he hadn't shown any indication that he wanted to fight at all. He was pretty definitive about it after that last loss, to Kevin McBride; "I don't have it anymore," Tyson said then. "I've got the ability to stay in shape, but I don't have the fight and guts...I don't have this in my heart anymore." In the last two decades, Tyson remade his public image and seemingly himself; he has a cannabis brand and a podcast and a meditation practice. He is jarringly earnest, sometimes to kid reporters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jon Jones Doesn’t Have To Change His Evil Ways]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173522</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jon-jones-doesnt-have-to-change-his-evil-ways"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T19:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jon Jones appears to be a perfect combat sports combo of skill, strength, and evil. That one-two-three punch hasn’t always benefited Jones or those around him outside the fight game, what with all the accusations of assault and various other malfeasance made against him since the late naughties, when he first came into the public eye. 
But inside the cage, well, good god. To clarify: Good fucking god.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ifs, Ands, And Headbutts: Irish Superhero Katie Taylor Takes Another Disputed Decision From Amanda Serrano]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173510</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ifs-ands-and-headbutts-irish-superhero-katie-taylor-takes-another-disputed-decision-from-amanda-serrano"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T16:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friday night’s rematch win over Amanda Serrano left Katie Taylor with all the titles in the women’s light welterweight division. But it’s hard to call Taylor the undisputed champ, at least for now, what with the disputes over the scorecards in her favor, and all those headbutts.
By the end of another brawl for the ages, Serrano had what looked like a war wound over her right eye, a gash so big it seemed to be smiling for the camera. Serrano seemed to shudder while getting ready for her post-fight ring interview when she looked at a nearby TV monitor and first saw how her face looked. How that injury came about gave this bout its main controversy, and should make for a proper selling point for why these women are gonna have to go at it yet again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reds, Royals Reportedly Discussing Jonathan India Trade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=830957</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/reds-royals-reportedly-discussing-jonathan-india-trade.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-16T21:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Reds and Royals are discussing a trade that would send second baseman Jonathan India to Kansas City in exchange for right-hander Brady Singer, according to a report from C. Trent Rosencrans and Ken Rosenthal of The Athletic. Rosenthal adds that a deal between the sides is not considered close and that India is one…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Watches A Christmas Movie: ‘Hot Frosty’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173480</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-watches-a-christmas-movie-hot-frosty"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T19:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the time of year when the the best, biggest, and most ambitious movies come out. Not Oscar season, but rather that stretch when the halls of streaming services are decked with the brightly lit, thinly disguised advertisements that are the year's new Christmas movies. There are more than 100 new Christmas films to watch this holiday season, and whether that number horrifies or excites you depends upon how much of a freak you are for the festive. Sabrina is proud to say they are a real Christmas freak, and this year they asked some of their colleagues to watch some of the most, uh, available new holiday movies. The first movie in our lineup is Hot Frosty, Netflix's romance between a human woman and a magical snowman with abs.
Sabrina Imbler: I am very grateful to both of you for taking a chance on this idea and watching perhaps the film of the 2024 Christmas movie season: Hot Frosty. Before we get into it, I wanted to ask if each of you could share more about your relationship to Christmas movies, good and bad. Had either of you heard of Hot Frosty before this?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Cold War Kids celebrates 20 years at the Truman]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861859</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-cold-war-kids-celebrates-20-years-at-the-truman/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T19:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cold War Kids. // photo by Isabella Ralls Cold War Kids with Husbands The Truman Tuesday, November 12 Celebrating 20 years as a band, indie rockers Cold War Kids took to the stage of the Truman Tuesday night for a set drawing from their extensive catalog. Oklahoma power-pop band Husbands opened, and our photographer Eli Ralls was there to capture...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Ralls</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In ‘Here,’ Robert Zemeckis Is Back On His Computer-Generated Bullshit]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173477</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/in-here-robert-zemeckis-is-back-on-his-computer-generated-bullshit"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T18:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been some time since I’ve taken Robert Zemeckis seriously. His last film to make a lasting impression was 2007’s Beowulf, an unwieldy but compelling action adaptation of the ancient epic poem that, three years after The Polar Express’s ambitious venture into the uncanny valley, proved that Zemeckis was a filmmaker willing to keep pushing past the bounds of good taste. 3D animation was no longer nascent, but his goal was to blend semi-realistic human characters via motion-capture with the elasticity and graphic creativity of 2D cartoons, somewhere beyond the territory of Looney Tunes and The Incredibles but a few stops short of Gollum in Lord of the Rings. If one were to term this a bet, Zemeckis won. Performance capture animation, from the new Planet of the Apes franchise to Into the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas K. Miller’s book Washita Love Child shines a light on Indigenous guitar legend Jesse Ed Davis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861624</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/douglas-k-millers-book-washita-love-child-shines-a-light-on-indigenous-guitar-legend-jesse-ed-davis/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T18:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Douglas K. Miller. // photo by Stephanie Link Despite an astonishing discography–multiple albums with Taj Mahal, the guitar solo on Jackson Browne’s “Doctor My Eyes,” touring with the Faces, his own solo albums, and so much more–the work of Kiowa-Comanche guitarist Jesse Ed Davis is mostly only known to musicians and the sort of music fan who digs deep into...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Small And Beautiful Seahorse Reveals An Even Smaller And Reclusive Worm]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173298</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-small-and-beautiful-seahorse-reveals-an-even-smaller-and-reclusive-worm"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T16:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Years ago, as a student at the University of the Ryukyus in in Okinawa, Japan, Ai Takahata was researching the color patterns of a seahorse about the size of a shelled peanut. The pygmy seahorse Hippocampus bargibanti lives only on knobbly, branched corals called gorgonian sea-fans, where its own, equally lumpish body is perfectly camouflaged. When Takahata cut off a branch of the seahorse's coral, a handful of worms spilled out.
She brought the worms to Chloé Julie Loïs Fourreau, a graduate student in the same lab at the university, who studies worms. "At that time I didn’t even know about this species and wasn’t looking for them," Fourreau wrote in an email. But when Fourreau looked into the literature, she identified them as Haplosyllis anthogorgicola, a species of polychaete worm that was first described in 1956 and then never recorded again. The researchers had unwittingly rediscovered a long-lost species of a tiny, nearly transparent worm about as long as a green lentil. Their paper on this rediscovery, "The Trojan seahorse," was published recently in Proceedings of the Royal Society B.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What The Fuck Is A “Vaccine Skeptic”?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173422</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-the-fuck-is-a-vaccine-skeptic"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T15:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At darker moments, contesting this kind of stuff in the wake of the 2024 election—and all the shameless, shameful, unforgivable work the American media did to produce that election's outcome—feels as absurd as demanding the cannibal presently eating your legs use a knife and fork. In less dark moments, that contestation feels like just about the only form hope can take. The language still exists. Maybe someone will need it, someday, to accomplish some good in the world, while the world still exists. If that's ever to be possible, then our language has to retain some usefulness, too. It has to be tended.
"Trump Picks R.F.K. Jr. to be Head of Health and Human Services Dept.," reads the New York Times headline from Thursday, atop a story by health policy reporter Sheryl Gay Stolberg about, well, pretty much what the headline says. We're fine up to that point. Then there's the subhed (emphasis mine): "Whether the Senate would confirm Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a vaccine skeptic who has unorthodox views about medicine, is an open question." That formulation repeats in the lead paragraph (emphasis again mine):]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saquon Barkley Is Saving Jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173417</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/saquon-barkley-is-saving-jobs"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T15:33:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because Philadelphia sports fans are the irradiated mutants they are, a win by the local team is not necessarily the central point of the exercise. If you’re wondering why the Eagles fan in your life seems grumpy and sour this morning even in victory—that is to say, slightly more hungover but otherwise normal—know that it is mostly because they are an Eagles fan, and also because they are fuming that Saquon Barkley did such yeoman's work in saving Jake Elliott's job.
Oh, they'll open any conversation, whether you asked or not, with their pleasure at the Eagles beating Washington, 26-18, grabbing the NFC East race by its saggy eyelids, and covering the 4.5 en route. But if they bet the over, they will be fuming in their own charmingly unintelligible way about the seven gettable points that Elliott, the team's veteran placekicker, could not deliver. And in a division race that now almost surely belongs to the Iggles, those little things count—not some knobhead’s bet, but the worry that your kicker might screw you in real time in December, or worse, January.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big-Brained Buffalo Boys Beat Blues By Brilliant Blueprint]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173423</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/big-brained-buffalo-boys-beat-blues-by-brilliant-blueprint"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T15:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It can be easy, as a sports fan and a blogger, to focus on the times players and teams screw up. Easy, and satisfying too. And hilarious. Oh man, when a guy really biffs it? Has a total brain-fart and all you can do is laugh and say What the fuck were you thinking? I live for that shit. If they could bottle LeBron yelling at J.R. Smith I would develop a drinking problem. 
I have lost my train of thought. Let me start over. It can be easy to focus on the poor choices made in sports, because they're aberrations. But it's worth noting the good decisions too—the unsexy choices that won't generally make highlight reels but do increase a team's chances. We had one such example in Thursday's Blues-Sabres game, tied in the final minute of regulation when St. Louis interfered with Buffalo goalie Devon Levi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>