<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-09-27T06:23:01.373Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Adams Lawyered Up BIG — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075592</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/eric-adams-lawyered-up-big-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T23:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quinn Emanuel Partner Alex Spiro Will Be Representing Eric Adams: What? Did he not want Olayemi Olurin?
The Judicial Conference Committee on Financial Disclosure Looks Out For Judges: Take that all expense covered vacation to your rich friend's resort and #BacktheBlack!
Who’s Litigating Who?: These firms are the ones you want on your side.
Not Sure You Can Blame That On Costco: Diddy's lawyer has an... interesting explanation for all of the baby oil.
The post Eric Adams Lawyered Up BIG — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks So Much To Our Advertisers]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075575</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/thanks-so-much-to-our-advertisers-17/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T23:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We really enjoy working with you.
The post Thanks So Much To Our Advertisers appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Federal Judges Need To Take Their Own Security More Seriously?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075584</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/do-federal-judges-need-to-take-their-own-security-more-seriously/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T22:18:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threats against federal judges are on the rise.
The post Do Federal Judges Need To Take Their Own Security More Seriously? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embattled Deputy Mayor Does Not Know Ball]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168500</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/embattled-deputy-mayor-does-not-know-ball"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things are not going well for New York City Mayor Eric Adams, and they haven't been for a while. The criminal charges filed against Adams on Thursday account for only a strand in the web of corruption allegations that has covered his administration. There are many other characters in this saga, including Deputy Mayor for Public Safety Phil Banks, who is no stranger to scandals himself and had his home raided by the FBI this month.
He also doesn't know shit about the Knicks! Following today's unsealing of the indictment against Adams, Banks was approached on the street and asked for comment by NY1 reporter Kelly Mena. As a graduate of the Fetterman School Of Political Oafs, Banks attempted to defuse the situation by talking about the upcoming Knicks season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Notable E-Discovery News, ALSP Elevate Acquires Consulting Company Redgrave Data]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075578</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/09/in-notable-e-discovery-news-alsp-elevate-acquires-consulting-company-redgrave-data.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T21:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redgrave’s founders Mollie Nichols, Scott Culbertson, Dave Lewis, Mark Noel, and Lindsey Worth will all join Elevate’s management team.
The post In Notable E-Discovery News, ALSP Elevate Acquires Consulting Company Redgrave Data appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Law Firms Can Leverage Video Content To Drive Business]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075506</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/how-law-firms-can-leverage-video-content-to-drive-business/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T20:46:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How one lawyer built a video marketing campaign that really rocks.
The post How Law Firms Can Leverage Video Content To Drive Business appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JARED CORREIA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Napheesa Collier Keeps The Lynx Cool]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168366</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/napheesa-collier-keeps-the-lynx-cool"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T20:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the highest honors an athlete can achieve, at least in my piddling personal head canon, is the descriptor "relaxing." It's not the only virtue for an athlete to pursue—its total opposite, jarring unpredictability, is also pretty cool—but watching a relaxing athlete can lower your own heart rate. Maybe you don't even think they'll win the game, but you do know that every gesture is backed by some intent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethics For In-House Counsel: Navigating The Ethical Responsibilities Of In-House Counsel To The Organization And The C-Suite]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075492</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/ethics-for-in-house-counsel-navigating-the-ethical-responsibilities-of-in-house-counsel-to-the-organization-and-the-c-suite/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T20:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Enron and WorldCom cases were emblematic of a broader crisis of corporate governance, where in-house lawyers failed in their role as ethical stewards.
The post Ethics For In-House Counsel: Navigating The Ethical Responsibilities Of In-House Counsel To The Organization And The C-Suite appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lisa Lang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Plaxico Continuum]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168204</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-plaxico-continuum"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T19:36:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Broadly speaking, episodes of The Distraction that are just Drew and me talking tend to break down into two different styles. They can be kind of digressive in ways that are personal or just extra loopy, and then there are ones that are ... well, it's still a podcast, and it's still this particular podcast, but I was going to say "focused." The idea behind this one was to field a bunch of listener voicemails and do a quick whip-around the sports landscape first, and what it wound up being instead was a decently detailed talk about the NFL, the state of TV color commentary, and the trouble with processing something as unprecedented as Shohei Ohtani's most recent unprecedented season. And then eventually we get to the voicemails about cat poop. But it was a pretty thoughtful podcast for a while there!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mo’ Baby Oil, Mo’ Problems: Diddy’s Lawyer Says His Client Was Just Trying To Get The Most Out Of His Costco Membership]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075586</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/mo-baby-oil-mo-problems-diddys-lawyer-says-his-client-was-just-trying-to-get-the-most-out-of-his-costco-membership/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T19:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's all about the Benjamins, baby, and Diddy allegedly uses his money to buy baby oil in bulk.
The post Mo’ Baby Oil, Mo’ Problems: Diddy’s Lawyer Says His Client Was Just Trying To Get The Most Out Of His Costco Membership appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: Free coffee, a new McLain’s location, and more restaurant news]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851216</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-free-coffee-a-new-mclains-location-and-more-restaurant-news/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T19:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Looking for delicious plans? Whether you want to impress a date, show your fam the best of KC, or just get out of the house, we’ve got you covered… all while supporting (mostly) local.  Here is your weekly roundup of the best food and drink offerings around Kansas City. Cheers! Something New Vintage ‘78 Wine Bar:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Survivor’ Should Bring Back Jon Lovett Just So He Can Bomb Again]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168438</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/survivor-should-bring-back-jon-lovett-just-so-he-can-bomb-again"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T18:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wednesday night marked the second episode of the 47th season of Survivor—and with it, the end of an all-too-brief era. For a certain member of the chattering class, this season held the sort of promise not seen since Mike White nearly conquered that Fijian beach: a chance to watch a famous writer make a fool of themselves on national television. This year's media surrogate was none other than Pod Save America co-host Jon Lovett, a man whose list of former employers includes Barack Obama, Hillary Clinton and Aaron Sorkin. None of this impressed his tribe, who voted him out at the end of last week's premiere episode.
This week's elimination was arguably even more of an upset, but still, I found myself largely unmoved, if not bored. Some important context might be needed here: I'm not a Survivor superfan. I hesitate to even call myself a fan. Until last Wednesday, I'd watched exactly half of one season while high in an AirBnb in Burlington. If reality television is a spectrum, my tastes trend more towards docusoap (think Real Housewives, Wife Swap, Selling Sunset) than competition-based programming. It most likely comes down to the fact that I fundamentally do not understand the kind of person who would voluntarily spend weeks without running water. But what I do understand is podcasters—specifically the kind of podcaster that Lovett is. He's the sort that will say on national television, with an ain't-I-a-stinker face, "And now when people ask me what I do, I have to say that I'm a fucking podcast host."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disclosure Rule Revision Displays Judiciary’s Commitment To Backing The Black]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075585</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/disclosure-rule-revision-displays-judiciarys-commitment-to-backing-the-black/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T18:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the unfortunate pun, there's no better way to describe it. 
The post Disclosure Rule Revision Displays Judiciary’s Commitment To Backing The Black appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AEW Can Be Too Much]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168399</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/aew-can-be-too-much"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T18:12:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[QUEENS, N.Y. — The final stretch of All Elite Wrestling's annual September blowout at Arthur Ashe Stadium, Grand Slam, feels remarkably similar to the back half of the nighttime tennis doubleheaders that run at these grounds for the U.S. Open a few weeks earlier. Like the Open, there is a primetime segment that captures the audience at peak capacity—for AEW, that's the live airing of their show Dynamite from 8 to 10 p.m. But also like the U.S. Open, there is a lot left for those who stick around late into the night—a whole other tennis match, or, in AEW's case, a taping for one of their other TV obligations that stretches past midnight.
As such, when I leave Arthur Ashe, the atmosphere is different than the feeling leaving any other sports arena I've ever entered. The crowd is no longer a cohesive throng high on a win, crushed by a loss, or simply juiced from the action. It's more a collection of individuals thinking, We were the ones who cared enough to stick it out, and Oh god, when am I going to get to sleep?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will & Harper is a charming, honest look at transitioning and allyship]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851326</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/will-harper-is-a-charming-honest-look-at-transitioning-and-allyship/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T17:49:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During Will Ferrell’s tenure at Saturday Night Live, he met a writer named Andrew Steele, who he hit it off with immediately. The pair proved an effective combination, both on the show and after Ferrell’s departure (Steele remained on SNL’s writing staff and was one of the head writers between 2004-2008). Steele was the writer behind the Ferrell vehicles Casa...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dirty Legal Secrets: When Startup Drama Takes Center Stage In Law]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075406</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/dirty-legal-secrets-when-startup-drama-takes-center-stage-in-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T17:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tech startup world is rife with drama, secrecy, and scandal.
The post Dirty Legal Secrets: When Startup Drama Takes Center Stage In Law appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga V. Mack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Have Given My Sons The Gift Of Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168403</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-have-given-my-sons-the-gift-of-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T17:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
I am the dad around this house, which means that I am the grillmeister. If my family needs anything grilled to imperfection—chicken, steaks, vegetables, shitty Mission tortillas—I am ready with my grill tongs and a generous amount of Pam. My grill counts as old now and, in grand American tradition, works in ways that only I understand. Only I know where the dead spots on the grate are. Only I know if the Blue Rhino tank is running on empty. And only I know that the two left burners will only ignite if you close the lid and hold down the ignition button until your knuckle cramps. This grill and I are simpatico. Whenever meat is required, we stand ready, together. I love grilling. Every middle aged guy does. It lets you play with fire, it gives you a chance to eat food before serving it, and it gives you an excuse to start drinking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Unbelievable Bits From NYC Mayor Eric Adams’s Indictment]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168416</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-most-unbelievable-bits-from-nyc-mayor-eric-adamss-indictment"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T17:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Adams, the very weird, very incompetent, and very shady mayor of New York City, is also now formally accused of being very corrupt. Adams was indicted by a grand jury and is being charged by federal prosecutors with five counts of bribery, wire fraud, and soliciting illegal foreign campaign donations. The news broke Wednesday night and the indictment was unsealed Thursday morning; the full 57-page indictment can be read at the bottom of this blog.
This follows a series of FBI raids, subpoenas and resignations among the mayor's confidants and cabinet members for a growing web of investigations that, incredibly, may be about assorted corruptions entirely unrelated to today's indictment. Today's indictment is mostly about how much Eric Adams allegedly loves Turkey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top Biglaw & Boutique Firms Headed Upmarket In Litigation (2025)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075573</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/the-top-biglaw-boutique-firms-headed-upmarket-in-litigation-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T17:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Which firms made the cut according to clients?
The post The Top Biglaw & Boutique Firms Headed Upmarket In Litigation (2025) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cannabis union drive stalls as company attempts to set national legal precedent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851278</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/cannabis-union-drive-stalls-as-company-attempts-to-set-national-legal-precedent/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T16:36:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Post-harvest employees at BeLeaf Medical’s Sinse facility await union election results on Feb. 6 at the St. Louis Public Library Barr branch (Rebecca Rivas/Missouri Independent) It’s been more than seven months since employees of St. Louis-based Beleaf Medical cannabis company held an election to unionize. The majority of the ballots — 11 of the 16 — have remained closed. “It’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Rivas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passage of Missouri sports betting amendment will squeeze Kansas gaming revenue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851266</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/passage-of-missouri-sports-betting-amendment-will-squeeze-kansas-gaming-revenue/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T16:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Proffitt, the budget director under Gov. Laura Kelly, said during an economic outlook conference at Washburn University that passage of a Missouri constitutional amendment legalizing sports wagering would reduce Kansas’ gambling revenue once Missouri residents in the Kansas City area had an alternative to driving across the state line to place online bets. (Sherman Smith/Kansas Reflector) TOPEKA — The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Carpenter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law Firm Benchmarking: Key Marketing And Financial Metrics In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075535</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/law-firm-benchmarking-key-marketing-and-financial-metrics-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T16:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your firm is seeking ways to enhance growth and profitability, these reports offer a valuable roadmap for improving financial performance and strategic decision-making.
The post Law Firm Benchmarking: Key Marketing And Financial Metrics In 2024 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicole Black</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comedian Jordan Cerminara swings through LFK/KC on wave of breakthrough album release]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851224</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/comedian-jordan-cerminara-swings-through-lfk-kc-on-wave-of-breakthrough-album-release/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T16:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy of Jordan Cerminara Stand-up comic Jordan Cerminara first picked up the microphone to perform a stand-up comedy routine in 2012 at the former venue Jackpot Music Hall in Lawrence, Kansas. At the time, Cerminara studied at the University of Kansas, where he developed his love for stand-up. A year into his comedy journey, Cerminara moved west to San Francisco,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our October 2024 events calendar features Cornocupia, Nosferatu, and plenty of scares]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=848970</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/our-october-2024-events-calendar-has-scares-david-spade-dj-shadow-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T16:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Chris Ortiz. // Art by Cassondra Jones ONGOING Oct 4 & 5 Sal Vulcano, Funny Bone Comedy Club Oct 4-6 Matthias Pintscher welcomes Gil Shaham, Kauffman Center for the Performing Arts Oct 5 & 6 Weston Applefest, Main St Weston, MO Oct 11 & 12 Michael Blackson, Funny Bone Comedy Club Oct 11-20 Kansas City Ballet Presents ALICE...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indicted NYC Mayor Eric Adams Taps High-Profile Biglaw Partner For Criminal Defense]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075580</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/indicted-nyc-mayor-eric-adams-taps-high-profile-biglaw-partner-for-criminal-defense/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T15:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pick is utterly unsurprising.
The post Indicted NYC Mayor Eric Adams Taps High-Profile Biglaw Partner For Criminal Defense appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Fish Has A Leg Up On The Competition]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168127</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-fish-has-a-leg-up-on-the-competition"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sea robin begins its life looking like any other fish: a finned, larval speck drifting in the open ocean. As the sea robin grows, the pectoral fins on either side of its body widen like two unfurling fans—still fins, if a bit extravagant. But eventually the first three rays of each fin separate. They lose their webbing, tapering into slender structures that look remarkably like legs. When adult sea robins settle on the seafloor, where they will spend the rest of their lives, they use these "legs" to walk, stilt-like, the rest of their body hovering a few inches above the sand.
Corey Allard, a cell biologist and electrophysiologist at Harvard University, knew sea robins as the fish his dad and brothers frequently reeled in from the Atlantic. But he did not realize they had legs until he saw them at the Marine Biological Laboratory in Woods Hole, Mass. "Never looked that closely, I guess, nor expected a fish to have legs like that," Allard said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discrimination Lawsuit Against Jones Day Is Heading To Trial!]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075560</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/discrimination-lawsuit-against-jones-day-is-heading-to-trial/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T14:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm's parental leave policy is under a microscope.
The post Discrimination Lawsuit Against Jones Day Is Heading To Trial! appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: A long dry stretch again for Metro (THU-9/26)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3675999</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-a-long-dry-stretch-again-for-metro-thu-9-26/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T14:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the weird things about the weather is often when one region is going crazy with weather, other regions are very quiet and it appears that the Metro will be on latter while many areas east of the region are more active. This is somewhat problematic because of the lack of rain for KC [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe's Weather Blog | In-depth Kansas City forecasts | FOX4KC</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bipartisan Duo Of Lawmakers To Introduce ‘Ships For America Act’ Following Election]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075562</id>
        <link href="https://breakingdefense.com/2024/09/bipartisan-duo-of-lawmakers-to-introduce-ships-for-america-act-following-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T14:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both Sen. Mark Kelly and Rep. Mike Waltz have spent the past year publicly floating some of the ideas that will be included in the legislation.
The post Bipartisan Duo Of Lawmakers To Introduce ‘Ships For America Act’ Following Election appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JUSTIN KATZ - BREAKING DEFENSE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Matthew Sluka Debacle Exposes The NIL System For What It Is]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168315</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-matthew-sluka-debacle-exposes-the-nil-system-for-what-it-is"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T13:48:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the arrival of NIL and the decision that college athletes deserve to be compensated for their work on the field, the NCAA, along with universities, have done everything they can to avoid responsibility for ensuring that compensation is distributed in a fair and orderly fashion. The last few years have constituted a desperate bid to maintain the illusion of amateurism, and in that desperation the NCAA and the schools have turned to boosters, NIL collectives, and corporate sponsors to keep the money flowing. As a result, NIL, while nice in theory, is deeply flawed and about as lawful and orderly as the old wild west.
Many of the problems with the current NIL system are now fully on display thanks to Matthew Sluka, the UNLV transfer who has been the starting quarterback for the Rebels during their hot 3-0 start. The team is expected to compete for the Mountain West title and now, thanks to the 12-team playoff, have a real chance at competing for the group of five slot in the bracket. Sluka, who had spent the four years prior as a dual-threat QB at FCS Holy Cross, claims that he was verbally promised $100,000 by a UNLV assistant coach to transfer over, but has only received a $3,000 relocation stipend. As a result, Sluka announced on Wednesday that he intends to redshirt and will not play for the remainder of the season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 09.26.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075570</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/morning-docket-09-26-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T13:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* If you live in a city where the mayor isn't indicted step forward... not so fast New York. [CNN]
* Texas still got nothing on Delaware. [Law.com]
* Report concludes that S&C didn't know of FTX fraud. [Law360]
* SEC takes position that crypto "boxes" are securities. More like insecurities but sure. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Smartmatic's defamation trial begins. [Reuters]
* Suspect caught in courthouse explosion. [ABA Journal]
The post Morning Docket: 09.26.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Never Forget What Killed The Oakland A’s]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168334</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ode-on-an-ass-hat-oakland-athletics-last-game"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T13:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has already been removed from the Fanatics website, and the inner doings of that particular sludge factory are hard to know, so while we can assume the worst, we should prepare to be surprised downward. Could Fanatics have known, during the time it was still available for sale, that they had created a dead-on metaphor for the Athletics franchise in perpetuity? The hat’s conception is a mystery that John Fisher's next letter to the public is unlikely to reveal, but fair is fair, and the hat is what it is, or was what it was. Folks, we give you—the Ass Hat:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creature Feature: Meet the resilient Rudy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851009</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/creature-feature-meet-the-resilient-rudy/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T13:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Scott Poore Rudy is a four-year-old pitbull/mastiff mix who weighs 90 lbs but is such a gentle boy. He loves all other animals—cats, dogs, people. Rudy doesn’t know a stranger. He is housebroken and loves toys and the kiddie pool at the shelter. Rudy is the longest-term dog at Pleasant Hill Animal Control. He was abandoned along...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Poore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Permanent wax set to celebrate 25 years of the Creature Comforts’ Teaching Little Fingers to Play]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851006</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/permanent-wax-set-to-celebrate-25-years-of-the-creature-comforts-teaching-little-fingers-to-play/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T13:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Creature Comforts // Photo Courtesy of Billy Brimblecom Jr. This Friday, Sept. 27, power pop act The Creature Comforts reunite at recordBar for their first show since 2007. Along with their contemporaries Ultimate Fakebook, the band was stalwarts of the late ’90s and early ’00s. The Creature Comforts played innumerable shows in Lawrence and around Kansas, and “Sentimental Bliss,”...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orlando Magic To Honor Late Co-Founder Pat Williams With Commemorative Jersey Band]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82312</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/09/25/orlando-magic-to-honor-late-co-founder-pat-williams-with-commemorative-jersey-band/basketball/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T01:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Orlando Magic will honor late co-founder Pat Williams by wearing a commemorative band featuring his initials on the left shoulder of the jerseys during the 2024-25 season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Get An Office, And You Get An Office, And… — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075559</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/you-get-an-office-and-you-get-an-office-and-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T23:32:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Firms Would Be Happy Amassing 100 Locations: This Biglaw firm sees that as two years’ worth of work.
They Aren't The Only Sprawling Firm In The Game: These are the 200 largest law firms in the world.
Now That's An Expensive .6!: These Biglaw partners are worth ~$3K an hour. Are you?
Trump Could Win Either Way: Who needs the presidency when you have this many Truth Social shares?
Mark Robinson Found Someone To Represent Him: Scandal isn't enough to deter a MAGA lawyer.
The post You Get An Office, And You Get An Office, And… — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General Counsel Compensation Has Taken A Dramatic Turn Over The Last 5 Years]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075552</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/general-counsel-compensation-has-taken-a-dramatic-turn-over-the-last-5-years/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T23:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty payday for those at the top of the in-house pecking order.
The post General Counsel Compensation Has Taken A Dramatic Turn Over The Last 5 Years appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Wants To Do Away With Senate Filibuster To Restore Reproductive Freedom In America]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075521</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/kamala-harris-wants-to-do-away-with-senate-filibuster-to-restore-reproductive-freedom-in-america/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T22:18:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[End the filibuster, save women's reproductive rights.
The post Kamala Harris Wants To Do Away With Senate Filibuster To Restore Reproductive Freedom In America appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chatbot Law Site DoNotPay Settles With FTC]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075533</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/chatbot-law-site-donotpay-settles-with-ftc/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T21:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guess they do pay after all.
The post Chatbot Law Site DoNotPay Settles With FTC appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 Missouri Senate Debate snaps a bleak image for the state’s future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851133</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/2024-missouri-senate-debate-portrays-a-bleak-image-for-the-states-future/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T21:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2024 Missouri Senate Debate. // Photo Courtesy of Rudi Keller, Missouri Independent Missouri U.S. Senate candidates met for a forum Friday afternoon in Springfield—sponsored by the Missouri Press Association. Present onstage were Republican U.S. Sen. Josh Hawley, Democratic candidate Lucas Kunce, Better Party candidate Jared Young, and Green Party candidate Nathan Kline. Here are the takeaways from the debate—which was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Truth Is An Inconvenience For Jake Tapper And Dana Bash]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168193</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-truth-is-an-inconvenience-for-jake-tapper-and-dana-bash"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T21:16:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, some of the most prominent figures in American broadcast news tried to get away with a staggering lie. The story is a particularly instructive case study on the dynamics of the American media's failure to accurately cover the ongoing Israeli genocide of Palestinians in Gaza.
On Sept. 12, Michigan Attorney General Dana Nessel announced that her office would pursue criminal charges against students and alumni who protested the genocide by setting up an encampment on the University of Michigan's main quad. That protest launched on April 22, one day after Palestinian civil defense crews unearthed a mass grave containing 180 bodies at Nasser Medical Complex in Khan Yunis. On May 21, university police moved against the protest in the early morning and cleared the encampment, pepper-spraying protestors in the process. Nessel's office filed misdemeanor trespassing charges against two of the protesters; the other seven face felony charges for "an additional count of Resisting or Obstructing a Police Officer," per the DA's office, for "making direct contact with the officers' bodies" while they were being arrested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rev. Jennifer Wells’ unorthodox plan to turn guns into gardens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=847766</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/a-right-to-bare-farms/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T21:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Jenny Wells Kansas City saw its deadliest year in 2023 due to a rise in gun violence. The city saw 185 homicides with 160 of those involving firearms. Over 30% of the victims were under the age of 25. Recent Pew Research Center gun statistics showed about four-in-ten U.S adults live in a household with firearms and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyrionna Clardy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Plain White T’s at the Midland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851023</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-plain-white-ts-at-the-midland/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T20:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plain White T’s // Photo by Tommy Vean Plain White T’s The Midland Monday, September 23 Emo rockers Plain White T’s played The Midland on Monday, as part of a tour opening for their contemporaries in The Used. While we weren’t able to get photos of the Used’s headlining set, our photographer Tommy Vean was there to capture Plain White...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tommy Vean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Descendents and Buzzcocks brought classic punk rock back to Liberty Hall Tuesday night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850857</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/descendents-and-buzzcocks-brought-classic-punk-rock-back-to-liberty-hall-tuesday-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T20:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Descendents // Photo by Nick Spacek Descendents w/ Buzzcocks and Grumpster Liberty Hall Tuesday, Sept. 24 Over the past 25+ years, California pop punk legends Descendents have played Liberty Hall so often that frontman Milo Aukerman joked that they’re basically “the house band” as the long-running group took the stage on Tuesday night. Despite the fact that the band comes...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Want An Elite Senior Partner On Your Case? Be Ready To Pay $3000 An Hour.]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075538</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/want-an-elite-senior-partner-on-your-case-be-ready-to-pay-3000-an-hour/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T20:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And you should hear what they're charging for junior associates.
The post Want An Elite Senior Partner On Your Case? Be Ready To Pay $3000 An Hour. appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Bridgerton’ Fans Paid Hundreds To Attend Sham Ball Organized By Uncle-Niece Duo]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168242</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bridgerton-fans-paid-hundreds-to-attend-sham-ball-organized-by-uncle-niece-duo"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T20:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Surely it gets harder and harder to pull off these scams on progressively savvier audiences. Surely the consumer begins to pick up on the obvious tells, like the gibberish AI posters promising "encherining entertainment" and "exarserdray lollipops," in the case of "Willy's Chocolate Experience." But it happened again!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyer Facing Disbarment Has DEEP THOUGHTS About Kamala Harris’s Legal Chops]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075540</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/lawyer-facing-disbarment-has-deep-thoughts-about-kamala-harriss-legal-chops/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T19:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeff Clark has cracked the case! Kamala Harris never argued an appeal and that means... something something.
The post Lawyer Facing Disbarment Has DEEP THOUGHTS About Kamala Harris’s Legal Chops appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Liberty Need This Do-It-All Version Of Sabrina Ionescu]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168213</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-liberty-need-this-do-it-all-version-of-sabrina-ionescu"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T19:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sabrina Ionescu wouldn’t be the first person who graduated college and moved to New York with quickly thwarted dreams of instant stardom. Nor would she be the first person who had to then spend her early 20s cycling through a few versions of herself before finding one she liked. What a treat that she’s arrived at this version this season, faster and stronger—a little bit new and a lot improved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fan Who Caught Shohei Ohtani’s 50-50 Home Run Ball May Be Unable To Dodge A Significant Income-Tax Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075524</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/the-fan-who-caught-shohei-ohtanis-50-50-home-run-ball-may-be-unable-to-dodge-a-significant-income-tax-bill/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T19:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IRS is likely to treat the ball as a 'collectible,' meaning that it will be taxed at a flat 28% rate.
The post The Fan Who Caught Shohei Ohtani’s 50-50 Home Run Ball May Be Unable To Dodge A Significant Income-Tax Bill appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Chung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emmy-winning comedian Dom Irrera, KC comic Mike Saccone gab ahead of Comedy Club of KC show]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850439</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/emmy-winning-comedian-dom-irrera-kc-comic-mike-saccone-gab-ahead-of-comedy-club-of-kc-show/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T18:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dom Irrera// Courtesy of Dom Irrera Emmy award-winning comedian and entertainer Dom Irrera is joining his friend and local comedian Mike Saccone Sept. 27 and 28 at the Comedy Club of Kansas City. The jokester pair will be joined by other fellow comedians as Irrera answers questions about his long-spanning career, while Saccone and comedians Kate Quigley and Billiam Cornell...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soffia Hernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So It’s Come To This: The Normal Gossip Updates Episode]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168269</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/so-its-come-to-this-the-normal-gossip-updates-episode"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T18:50:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There comes a point in any long running series when the writers and producers and actors are clearly just tired—or perhaps in treatment for, ahem, “fatigue,” or they’ve absconded to a foreign country—but contractual obligations demand that something, anything, is made for the fans to consume. Behold, the Clip Show!
Surprise! Normal Gossip is out with a brand new Bonus Episode today to revisit some of your favorite stories! But do not worry, this is not an exercise in recycling. We’re bringing you fresh updates on some of our past episodes. We’re cracking open the cold case files! Finally, the mystery of the hot dog in the toilet will be revealed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAGA Lawyer Representing Scandal-Ridden GOP Candidate Mark Robinson]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075531</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/maga-lawyer-representing-scandal-ridden-gop-candidate-mark-robinson/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T18:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not surprising which lawyer he's picked.
The post MAGA Lawyer Representing Scandal-Ridden GOP Candidate Mark Robinson appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Wild Robot is programmed to deliver a beautiful world with sweet story to boot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851162</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/the-wild-robot-is-programmed-to-deliver-a-beautiful-world-with-sweet-story-to-boot/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T18:26:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Wild Robot. // Courtesy Fantastic Fest 2024 The Wild Robot starts screening at Kansas City area theaters tomorrow. Fans of DreamWorks’ How to Train Your Dragon are in for a treat with The Wild Robot, directed by Dragon co-director and co-writer, Chris Sanders. Like the studio’s emotionally impactful fantasy series, the new film offers heartstring-tugging and inspiration in equal measures....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Torres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Padres Found The Coolest Way To Clinch]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168224</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-padres-found-the-coolest-way-to-clinch"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T18:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With two men on and no one out in the bottom of the ninth inning, Dodgers shortstop Miguel Rojas initially put his bat down for a bunt. This was the correct decision, from his team's perspective: Shohei Ohtani was on deck, and Rojas would make an acceptable sacrifice to enable a possible Ohtani walk-off against the Padres. But swing the bat Rojas did, and for that, there were consequences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 200 Largest Law Firms On Earth (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075530</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/the-200-largest-law-firms-on-earth-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T17:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because size matters in the legal profession. Which are the planet's largest law firms?
The post The 200 Largest Law Firms On Earth (2024) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debbie Does The Dormant Commerce Clause]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075528</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/debbie-does-the-dormant-commerce-clause/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T17:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why do professors think everyone has to personally experience the facts to understand the law?
The post Debbie Does The Dormant Commerce Clause appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marcellus Williams executed after U.S. Supreme Court rejects final appeal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851195</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/marcellus-williams-executed-after-u-s-supreme-court-rejects-final-appeal/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T16:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marcellus Williams, photographed in prison (photo submitted) Just a few hours after the U.S. Supreme Court rejected his final appeal, Missouri officials executed Marcellus Williams Tuesday at the Eastern Reception, Diagnostic and Correctional Center in Bonne Terre. Williams, who was backed in his appeals for clemency by St. Louis County Prosecuting Attorney Wesley Bell, left only a single sentence —...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rudi Keller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Uses The Same Pretense For New Bloodshed]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168050</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/israel-uses-the-same-pretense-for-new-bloodshed"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T16:34:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Biden's administration has insisted for months that a ceasefire in Gaza was within reach, despite no sign of progress toward that goal. This inaction has consequences: If Israel faces no repercussions for waging genocide against Palestinians, and feels no pressure to stop, there is nothing to prevent it from increasing the scope of the violence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go Ahead And Assume The Worst About The Pittsburgh Pirates]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168219</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/go-ahead-and-assume-the-worst-about-the-pittsburgh-pirates"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T16:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pittsburgh Pirates completed a painful bit of business Tuesday afternoon, designating journeyman first baseman and refrigerator-shaped fan favorite Rowdy Tellez for assignment, effectively ending his 2024 season. Tellez was in Pittsburgh on a one-year contract; in all probability, Tuesday's release brings to a close his days with the Pirates. The timing of this otherwise minor transaction is pretty icky: As first noted by Pirates fans on Twitter and then confirmed by the Pittsburgh Post-Gazette, Tellez was cut loose at the threshold of a performance bonus written into his incentive-laden contract. Tellez would've earned a $200,000 payout for hitting 425 plate appearances on the season; instead, after this last-minute maneuver, Tellez ends his campaign stuck on 421.
Ben Cherington, Pittsburgh's general manager, insists this is an unfortunate but otherwise pure coincidence. "Zero factor in the decision," Cherington said Tuesday, ahead of a game against the Brewers. "Aware of it, certainly. I’m aware of the contracts that all players have. No factor at all, zero." According to Cherington and Pirates manager Derek Shelton, the team wants to prioritize giving roster spots to the players who are most likely to factor beyond the end of this shitty, disheartening, last-place season. In related moves, the Pirates released veteran outfielder Michael A. Taylor, also wrapping up a one-year contract, and promoted a pair of minor leaguers into the big club's two fresh vacancies. One of these call-ups, 23-year-old Liover Peguero, is a gifted infielder with a somewhat faded prospect profile, the type of youngster that non-contenders traditionally do like to promote in September. The other, 29-year-old outfielder Joshua Palacios, is just a guy. Maybe one or both of them make the Pirates next season; for what it's worth, both of them have already seen time with the big club and played their way back to the minors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NetDocuments Adds To Areas Where Legal Professionals Do Their Best Work [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075317</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/netdocuments-adds-to-areas-where-legal-professionals-do-their-best-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T16:19:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NetDocuments provides a cloud-native, matter-centric DMS that delivers a single system of record for securing, organizing, automating, and collaborating on documents related to matters in workspaces.
The post NetDocuments Adds To Areas Where Legal Professionals Do Their Best Work appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Legal Tech Publishing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Largest Law Firm On Earth Plans To Open 100 More Offices By 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075522</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/largest-law-firm-on-earth-plans-to-open-100-more-offices-by-2026/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T15:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm is already HUGE, but plans are in the works to make its army of attorneys even larger.
The post Largest Law Firm On Earth Plans To Open 100 More Offices By 2026 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GloWild Legends & Lore Festival transforms the Kansas City Zoo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850825</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/glowild-lantern-festival-kansas-city-zoo-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T15:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Tyrionna Clardy The third annual GloWild Lantern Festival at The Kansas City Zoo brings an entirely new theme this year: “Legends & Lore.” The event, in collaboration with LEKTRIK Art, brings a variety of illuminated designs by 151 artisans. Each display is made with over 34 tons of steel and nearly 90,000 feet of fabric.  Walking through this...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyrionna Clardy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the Royals Were Cursed]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=447134</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/why-the-royals-were-cursed/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T15:20:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What exactly did the Royals do to earn the wrath of the baseball gods? Let's go to the tape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davy Andrews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Selling Truth Social Shares Would Be A Legendary Hedge Against Losing The Election]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075281</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/donald-trump-selling-truth-social-shares-would-be-a-legendary-hedge-against-losing-the-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T14:43:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All he has to do is hack his supporters off at the knees.
The post Donald Trump Selling Truth Social Shares Would Be A Legendary Hedge Against Losing The Election appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Wolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Watching a new hurricane (WED-9/25)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3674527</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-watching-a-new-hurricane-wed-9-25/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T14:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our day has started perfectly in the region with a touch of fog, heavy dew and cool temperatures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Has A New Roomie]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075520</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/09/sam-bankman-fried-has-a-new-roomie"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T14:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We hope the dethroned crypto king really liked ‘90s rap.
The post Sam Bankman-Fried Has A New Roomie appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: A hidden farmers’ market gem and an urban coffee hike]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850676</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-a-hidden-farmers-market-gem-and-an-urban-coffee-hike/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T13:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rozanna’s Flowers // Photo By Tiffany Watts Rozanna’s Flowers Kansas City is home to plenty of farmers’ markets, but if you haven’t visited Rozanna’s Flowers, you’re missing out on one of the city’s best-kept secrets. While known for its stunning mums and breathtaking garden display, Rozanna’s is more than just a flower shop—it’s essentially the farmer’s market you didn’t know...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Rumaan Alam’s ‘Entitlement,’ Money Comes At The Expense Of Everything Else]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167845</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/in-rumaan-alams-entitlement-money-comes-at-the-expense-of-everything-else"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rumaan Alam's new novel Entitlement begins, as so many New York stories do, on the subway. It’s summer—"strange, sultry"—and the city is being terrorized by a "lunatic at large who was jabbing unsuspecting commuters with a hypodermic needle." Creatively dubbed the "Subway Pricker," the anonymous piquerist has already claimed three victims and the imaginations of the city’s denizens. None of this concerns Brooke Orr, who considers "the pricker like Santa Claus or the tooth fairy, real only if you believed him to be." In fact, other than her new job as a program coordinator at a Manhattan foundation established by a white octogenarian billionaire named Asher Jaffee, very little seems to concern Brooke.
The headlines she reads on the train to work are "anodyne ... the good luck of a boring moment in the world's long history, Obama’s placid America." Entitlement is set in 2014, a year that that might register as anodyne in the nostalgic gaze of its post-pandemic audience, but probably wouldn't to a 33-year-old black woman like Brooke. The summer of 2014 was the summer of Ta-Nehisi Coates's landmark essay "A Case for Reparations." It was the summer of the Flint water crisis, the summer of Elliot Rodger, the summer of the Ebola outbreak, the summer of #BringBackOurGirls. It was the same summer where Michael Brown's body was left to bake on the hot Missouri pavement for four hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 09.25.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075525</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/morning-docket-09-25-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T13:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Sam Bankman-Fried and Diddy apparently share a common space. It's like an old episode of Real World except with more crime. [People]
* Meanwhile, Caroline Ellison gets two real years for fake money scam. [Reuters]
* SEC lawyer informs defense bar that the regulator is just going to drag them into expensive and time-consuming real court post-Jarkesy. Another crackerjack pro-business decision by this Supreme Court! [Law360]
* Biglaw firms duped in legally themed Nigerian Prince scam. [ABA Journal]
* Freshfields dropping the rest of its name in rebrand. [LegalCheek]
* Alex Jones IP getting auctioned off for anyone looking to own a piece of crackpot history. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Partners flirting with $3000/hour. [American Lawyer]
The post Morning Docket: 09.25.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Notes: Lorenzen, Marsh, Harvey, McArthur]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=825592</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/09/royals-notes-lorenzen-marsh-harvey-mcarthur.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T03:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Lorenzen will return from the 15-day injured list tomorrow. The Royals list him as the probable starter for the second game of their series in Washington. Kansas City will need to make a corresponding active roster move. It’s a crucial start as K.C. fights for a playoff spot. The Royals squeaked out a 1-0…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So Much For A Free Ride! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075518</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/so-much-for-a-free-ride-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T23:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Insurrection Has Its Costs: Stomping the Capitol may have cost a student a free degree from a top law school.
Law Students Aren't The Only One Acing Exams!: Wonder what the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit has to say about Pauline Newman's test results.
You Know We Were All There For The Pandemic, Right?: Law school’s excuse to not accommodate for a student doesn't really hold up.
Amy Wax Finally Has To Face The Music. Next Year: Something is better than nothing, right?
No Restraint Needed: Judge tells Biglaw firm what for. Had it coming.
The post So Much For A Free Ride! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sure, Being A Summer Associate Is Fun… A Regular Old Associate? Less So.]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075512</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/sure-being-a-summer-associate-is-fun-a-regular-old-associate-less-so/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T22:18:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firms roll out the red carpet for summer associates.
The post Sure, Being A Summer Associate Is Fun… A Regular Old Associate? Less So. appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Biglaw Firm Hopes To Magically Make Part Of Its Name Disappear In Rebranding Effort]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075481</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/top-biglaw-firm-hopes-to-magically-make-part-of-its-name-disappear-in-rebranding-effort/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T21:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abracadabra! Magic Circle firm wants to keep its name 'fresh' in these changing times.
The post Top Biglaw Firm Hopes To Magically Make Part Of Its Name Disappear In Rebranding Effort appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huge Development In Pauline Newman’s Case: The Test Results Are In!]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075513</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/huge-development-in-pauline-newmans-case-the-test-results-are-in/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T20:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gonna have to side with the doctor on this one. 
The post Huge Development In Pauline Newman’s Case: The Test Results Are In! appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Judge Slams Biglaw Firm, Says Firm ‘Defiled The Very Temple Of Justice’]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075454</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/federal-judge-slams-biglaw-firm-says-firm-defiled-the-very-temple-of-justice/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T20:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The judge holds nothing back.
The post Federal Judge Slams Biglaw Firm, Says Firm ‘Defiled The Very Temple Of Justice’ appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Judge Chutkan Dropkicks Trump’s Performative Tantrum Motion]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075515</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/update-judge-chutkan-dropkicks-trumps-performative-tantrum-motion/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T19:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOH
The post UPDATE: Judge Chutkan Dropkicks Trump’s Performative Tantrum Motion appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law School’s Refusal To Accommodate Student With Disabilities Doesn’t Really Hold Up After The Pandemic]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075494</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/law-schools-refusal-to-accommodate-student-with-disabilities-doesnt-really-hold-up-after-the-pandemic/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T19:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it really that hard to give a student a room for them to take an exam in? 
The post Law School’s Refusal To Accommodate Student With Disabilities Doesn’t Really Hold Up After The Pandemic appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Francis Ford Coppola’s navel gaze-y epic Megalopolis exists only for the guy who made it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850696</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/francis-ford-coppolas-navel-gaze-y-epic-megalopolis-exists-only-for-the-guy-who-made-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T19:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Lionsgate On a recent episode of the movie podcast Random Number Generator Horror Podcast Number 9, hosts Joseph Fink and Cecil Baldwin discussed determining “good” vs. “bad” art in relation to the movie Phantasm, a cult classic that notably eschews that kind of pigeonholing. Baldwin brought up the form of evaluation he learned in drama school, defining specific choices...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[American Royal pays homage to co-founder Tom Bass in Horse Power with The Coterie Theatre]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850270</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/horse-power-american-royal-125-anniversary-tom-bass/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T19:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of The Coterie’s Instagram In collaboration with The Coterie Theatre, the American Royal is celebrating its 125th year anniversary with a one-of-a-kind production, Horse Power, about the life of Tom Bass, one of their co-founders. The organization, formerly known as The National Hereford Show, was founded in 1899 in Kansas City. The non-profit organization fosters a diverse community...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyrionna Clardy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Lawyers Flip Shit Over Page Limits In Election Interference Case]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075496</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/trump-lawyers-flip-shit-over-page-limits-in-election-interference-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T18:35:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motion to exceed page limit? THE DEVIL, YOU SAY!
The post Trump Lawyers Flip Shit Over Page Limits In Election Interference Case appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lamine Yamal Is Already On Top]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168048</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lamine-yamal-is-already-on-top"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T17:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's hard to pin down Lamine Yamal's place amongst the top players in the world today. I guess it should be no surprise that a teenager resists fixity, being in that stage of life defined by constant growth and flux.
The difficulty is twofold. On the one hand, you don't want the allure of the new to rob you of perspective. How can you call Lamine the best player in the world for what he has done over the past six months, when, for instance, Kylian Mbappé has been doing what he does for the past six years? On the other, you can't let your attachment to the past prevent you from accurately assessing the present state of things. Yes, he's only 17, and he's only been playing like this for the better part of this calendar year. But in that brief time Lamine has already achieved feats within the reach only of the game's generational talents. How could you deny that what you routinely see from him, both in Barcelona's colors and in Spain's, earns him a place in the highest tier of the player hierarchy?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Student Accepted To Top Law School With Full Ride Sentenced In January 6th Case]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075482</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/student-accepted-to-top-law-school-with-full-ride-sentenced-in-january-6th-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T17:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From dreams of passing the bar to time spent behind bars: How this pre-law student wound up on the wrong side of the law.
The post Student Accepted To Top Law School With Full Ride Sentenced In January 6th Case appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When The Toilet Rings, You Must Answer The Call]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168148</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/when-the-toilet-rings-you-must-answer-the-call"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T17:31:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I could not help but recall J.K. Trotter's charmingly deranged old Gawker blog, "How to Find a Beeping Smoke Detector If You Don't Know Where It Is." His revelatory technique: Once you have not found the smoke detector where you expected to find it, continue looking in other places until you find it. I thought of this as my wife and I hunted a mysterious high-pitched ringing sound around the main floor of our house. Trotter had eventually found the smoke detector beneath the bathroom sink (!), in the back of a cabinet (!!), covered by a bag of sand (???), nowhere near the sound's seeming point of origin, a phenomenon he discovered was due to the auditory qualities of the alarm's sound and the acoustic properties of his bathroom. (It's a good blog!)
It was a sustained, maddening, high-pitched ringing sound, not all that unlike that made by a smoke or carbon monoxide detector when it's actually set off. We couldn't figure out what was making it; though it sounded vaguely alarm-like, it also clearly was not the sound any of our various alarms make. It seemed to be originating from the bathroom, but like Trotter's sound, not from any discernible point in the bathroom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Chaos Option Is Alive In MLB’s Wild Card Races]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168156</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-chaos-option-is-alive-in-mlbs-wild-card-races"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T17:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is baseball's version of Holy Week, and because it is a much less regular occurrence than the tawdry religious hoopdeblah of the same name, its emergence should be celebrated by more than just those directly involved.
It is that rarest of rare white elks, a true multiple-team playoff race, and no it does not matter that the race involved is for the much less climactic extra wild card spots, nor that there are four right answers and roughly twice as many quizzers. It is the beauteous chaos of simultaneous events all emanating import into other corners of the world. Or in English, it's the Royals, Tigers, Twins, and Mariners all fighting for the two American League wild card spots not already claimed by the Orioles, and the Diamondbacks, Mets, and Braves for the final two National League vacancies. All those teams have their evident flaws and alluring charms and fan bases that simultaneously warm the hearts and irritate the spleens; the winners will all both be considerable underdogs against their first-round opponents and teams with not entirely specious hopes for an improbable run deeper into the fall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Shrinking Ownership Of Law Practice Management Technology: Wrapping It All Up]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075487</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/09/the-shrinking-ownership-of-law-practice-management-technology-part-4-of-4-wrapping-it-all-up.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T17:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A wrap-up some of the key market trends in this area.
The post The Shrinking Ownership Of Law Practice Management Technology: Wrapping It All Up appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Must Address The Tom Brady Crisis (The Crisis Being That He Stinks)]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168091</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/we-must-address-the-tom-brady-crisis-the-crisis-being-that-he-stinks"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T16:52:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about Dungeons & Dragons, dating people with cancer, Katherine Heigl, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Reads A Book Is Figuring Out What Sally Rooney’s Deal Is This Fall]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168136</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-reads-a-book-is-figuring-out-what-sally-rooneys-deal-is-this-fall"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T16:32:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to those of you who joined us for our discussion of In the Freud Archives back in August. Not long after we finished DRAB-ing, I found myself with a free afternoon in Berkeley, and took myself out to the upstairs cafe at Chez Panisse. I left the meal with a 60 percent water, 40 percent roasted fig body composition. I can see why Jeff Masson wanted to dine there. If any of my future interview subjects would like to make plans there, you have my permission. Let’s expense some figs to the company.
This fall, we're doing something we never do at Defector Reads A Book. You know us by now: We're the sort of book club that skews Beowulf and Moby Dick. In a twist, we're reading a book that is not hundreds of years old—one that, in fact, just came out today. A group of Sally Rooney newbies and completists on staff is gathering to chat Intermezzo, the buzzy Irish novelist's fourth novel. Could this be the great Marxist chess novel of our time? We'll have to ask Patrick.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Time Tracking To Invoicing: How TimeSolv Transforms Legal Practice [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075313</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/from-time-tracking-to-invoicing-how-timesolv-transforms-legal-practice/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T16:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Increasing billable time and more.
The post From Time Tracking To Invoicing: How TimeSolv Transforms Legal Practice appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Legal Tech Publishing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pattie Mansur leans on her educational background as District 25 race heats up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=848011</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/pattie-mansur-leans-on-her-educational-background-as-district-25-race-heats-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T16:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Pattie Mansur’s Instagram The Missouri House of Representatives District 25 stretches along the Missouri-Kansas state border from the south end of the Country Club Plaza to Interstate 435. Since 2021, the state representative office of District 25 has been held by registered nurse and Democrat Patty Lewis. Lewis is currently running for state Senate in District 7,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Like About The Tigers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168102</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-i-like-about-the-tigers"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T15:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like their outfield defense, the team’s truest weapon. I like how they turn doubles into outs, and triples into outs, and homers into outs, and pretty soon, that’s 27 outs. They do lots of things I don’t like, but I like them so much, I forgot what those things are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sending Horny Texts To RFK Jr. Is Not A Public Service]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168001</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/sending-horny-texts-to-rfk-jr-is-not-a-public-service"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T15:34:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the half-week since news that New York suspended star reporter Olivia Nuzzi upon learning that she had, and hid, a months-long inappropriate relationship with failed presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr., many of the most powerful people in journalism are asking, rhetorically, Why are people making such a big deal about this? That's not a question to be dismissed out of hand simply because other people also happen to be mad at Nuzzi for stupid reasons.
Dead-eyed hacks like Caitlin Flanagan and Chris Cillizza have made their predictable cases, as has former Buzzfeed editor-in-chief and New York Times media columnist Ben Smith. Smith, of Smith & Smith Media, addressed the scandal in a confused edition of his newsletter over the weekend. Against the "full fury of American media prurience and self-righteousness," Smith's defense of Nuzzi is that to draw the ethical line at engaging in a sexual relationship with a reporting subject is arbitrary, and that the work of reporting is inherently compromising:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amy Wax Sanctioned But Keeps Her Job, Tenure, Confidence That School Can’t Do Anything More]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075485</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/amy-wax-sanctioned-but-keeps-her-job-tenure-confidence-that-school-cant-do-anything-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T15:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[She persistently denigrated women and minorities and all she got was this lousy half-pay sanction.
The post Amy Wax Sanctioned But Keeps Her Job, Tenure, Confidence That School Can’t Do Anything More appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard Law Grad Shares What You Really Need To Know Before Applying To Law School]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075488</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/harvard-law-grad-shares-what-you-really-need-to-know-before-applying-to-law-school/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T14:46:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone's law school journey is unique, but there are a lot of lessons you can learn.
The post Harvard Law Grad Shares What You Really Need To Know Before Applying To Law School appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formula 1 Gasps, Drops Monocle Over Max Verstappen’s F-Word]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167976</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-fia-goes-overboard-on-a-max-verstappen-no-no-word"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T14:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Formula 1 season has gotten so topsy-turvy that it fell on Max Verstappen of all drivers to make a boring Singapore Grand Prix suddenly exciting. Thanks to Red Bull's shabby performance, mysteriously cratered over the past few months, the excitement came not from the Dutchman's driving, but from his mouth. At a press conference on Thursday, Verstappen was asked about qualifying at the previous week's grand prix circuit in Baku. His reply was characteristically blunt: "As soon as I headed into qualifying, I knew the car was fucked."
For a racing entity that also has Yuki Tsunoda and Yuki Tsunoda's famously inappropriate mouth on its roster, this comment should not have rated beyond mild amusement. However, the Federation Internationale de l'Automobile (or FIA, the F1 governing body) issued a warning for drivers to watch their language following the Azerbaijan Grand Prix. That warning was received poorly going into the Singapore GP weekend, with Lando Norris noting that it's hard to control the language in the heat of the moment. Norris told The Athletic, "They can just not play the radios, so it’s quite simple from their side."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[18th & Vine Arts Festival to host a weekend celebration of Black art]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850254</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/18th-vine-art-festival-to-host-a-weekend-celebration-of-black-art/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T14:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of 18th & Vine Art Festival The second 18th & Vine Arts Festival is set to arrive in Kansas City from Sept. 27 to Sept. 29 to provide a weekend of art, music, food, and fun.  Located in the historic 18th & Vine District, the festival is a three-day celebration of black culture, history, and community. The festival...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Cohen Thought He Could Fix Wells Fargo]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075480</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/09/ryan-cohen-thought-he-could-fix-wells-fargo"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T14:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Truly, the man’s self-confidence is a wonder of the world.
The post Ryan Cohen Thought He Could Fix Wells Fargo appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: A rare "Fujiwhara effect" may affect KC! (TUE-9/24)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3673157</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-a-rare-fujiwhara-effect-may-affect-kc-tue-9-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T14:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's nice to be back in Kansas City where fall has sprung and nights are much cooler. I was in Phoenix checking to see how my mom was doing, and it was in the 90s and 100s each day. So to get off the plane last night when it was in the 60s was pleasant [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: A rare "Fujiwhara effect" may affect KC! (TUE-9/24)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3673157</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-a-rare-fujiwhara-effect-may-affect-kc-tue-9-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T14:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's nice to be back in KC where fall has sprung and nights are much cooler. I was in Phoenix checking to see how my mom was doing and it was in the 90s and 100s each day. So to get off the plane last night when it was in the 60s was pleasant for [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Driving The Rise Of The Far Right Among Young Germans?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168021</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/whats-driving-the-rise-of-the-far-right-among-young-germans"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T13:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 6, a baby-faced TikTok user named Louis, who adorns his username with two Reichskreuze—the Imperial Cross that’s often used as a neo-Nazi symbol—commented “Saxony Anhalt votes blue,” followed by a blue heart emoji, under politician Alice Weidel’s video urging people to vote AfD, the far-right Alternative for Germany party, for the 2024 EU parliamentary elections. A quick scroll down Louis’s page immediately shows two racist memes, one about Muslims and another about Black people. AfD in Saxony-Anhalt has been officially classified as an extremist group. 
Weidel’s video features an anime-style cartoon of a young man excitedly voting for the AfD. A German flag flashes before the boy’s eyes, making him quiver with joy. The entire comments section is filled with blue hearts, the color of the AfD. The video ends with the hashtag “blue instead of colorful,” referring to a rejection of the “woke madness” that embraces diversity. The youthfulness and playful animation of the video may stand in stark contrast with its deeply hateful message, but its makers know exactly who they’re targeting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luisa Rollenhagen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRGR’s Oktoberfest serves up specialty German cuisine, beer, and… milkshakes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=847763</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/brgrs-oktoberfest-serves-up-specialty-german-cuisine-beer-burgers-and-a-perfect-milkshake/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T13:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRGR // Photo by Tyrionna Clardy BRGR Kitchen + Bar has kicked off its Oktoberfest event, offering a diverse menu of traditional German food. The casual restaurant is tucked away in the quiet suburbs of Prairie Village, a stark contrast to its bustling counterpart in the Power & Light District.  I recently visited to sample some of their popular menu...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyrionna Clardy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 09.24.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075483</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/morning-docket-09-24-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T12:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Rate cut has Biglaw gearing up for big deal cavalcade. [American Lawyer]
* "The Lawyer Who Wants To Paint You." Hopefully not like one of the French girls from Titanic. [The New Yorker]
* Disrupted sleep is a big problem for attorneys. The solution, of course, is to never go to sleep in the first place. Nighttime hours are just as billable as daytime! [ABA Journal]
* One-stop-forum-shop Reed O'Connor publicly complains about Judicial Conference efforts to take away his power to write unhinged blog posts with the force of federal law. [Reuters]
* Tenth Circuit will hear challenge moving us one step closer to putting a Wal-Mart on top of the Mt Rushmore heads. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Reggie Bush sues over exploitation of his name, image, and likeness. [Law360]
* John Roberts taught at the New England Law|Boston over the summer. If that seems like a weird law school option for a Chief Justice to do some teaching, bear in mind that it's not the actual campus but a paid vacation in Ireland. [WIVB]
The post Morning Docket: 09.24.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: The Get Up Kids come home for Something to Write Home About anniversary tour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850343</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-the-get-up-kids-come-home-for-something-to-write-home-about-anniversary-tour/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T12:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Get Up Kids. // photo by Kylee Gregg The Get Up Kids with Smoking Popes recordBar Friday, September 13 Celebrating of 25 years of their iconic Something to Write Home About, KC natives the Get Up Kids kicked off three nights of sold out local shows Friday, September 13, at recordBar. In additioon to performing said album in its...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kylee Gregg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Library activist Amanda Jones speaks in KC on dismantling motivations behind national wave of book bans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850326</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/library-activist-amanda-jones-speaks-in-kc-on-dismantling-motivations-behind-national-wave-of-book-bans/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T23:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy of Kathryn & Traveis Photography Louisiana librarian Amanda Jones, recipient of the 2020 School Librarian of the Year and the 2021 School Library Journal Librarian of the Year, is headed to the Kansas City Public Library Sept. 25 to discuss her memoir That Librarian: The Fight Against Book Banning in America.  The public event comes as Jones is preparing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soffia Hernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merging Up The Ranks — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075471</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/merging-up-the-ranks-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T23:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Midsize Firm Merges Its Way Up: The new firm will have over 1000 lawyers, climbing higher in the Am Law 100!
New YSL RICO Witness Turns Heads: What did he just say?!
Dentons Is Getting Some Bad Publicity:They've being investigated on corruption charges.
Play If You Want To: Return to office policies are growing teeth.
Mess With Musicians, Face The Music: Recording artist goes to court over his music rights.
The post Merging Up The Ranks — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good News For Biglaw Associates — If You’re In The Right Practice Areas]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075458</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/good-news-for-biglaw-associates-if-youre-in-the-right-practice-areas/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T22:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lateral opportunities for some.
The post Good News For Biglaw Associates — If You’re In The Right Practice Areas appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantastic Fest 2024: Art the Clown comes home for the hellidays in Damien Leone’s Christmas bloodbath Terrifier 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850299</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/fantastic-fest-2024-art-the-clown-comes-home-for-the-hellidays-in-damien-leones-christmas-bloodbath-terrifier-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T22:12:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Fantastic Fest 2024 This is part of our coverage from Fantastic Fest 2024 in Austin, TX where genre films are debuting before they get wider release. Check out all of our coverage here.  Clowns. Some people love them. Some people hate them. Some people love to hate them. Other people, like Terrifier filmmaker Damien Leone, want to build the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Torres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantastic Fest 2024: Yugo Sakamoto’s Baby Assassins: Nice Days continues to bring trademark charm and ass-kicking in equal measure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850275</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/fantastic-fest-2024-yugo-sakamotos-baby-assassins-nice-days-continues-to-bring-trademark-charm-and-ass-kicking-in-equal-measure/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T22:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Fantastic Fest This is part of our coverage from Fantastic Fest 2024 in Austin, TX where genre films are debuting before they get wider release. Check out all of our coverage here.  For the last several years, Japanese film fans have been delighted by the delirious writer/director Yugo Sakamoto’s entertaining and enthralling Baby Assassins films. Following the antics of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Torres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marketing Roundup: Leadership Styles, Competitive Intelligence, Leveraging Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075368</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/marketing-roundup-leadership-styles-competitive-intelligence-leveraging-tech/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T21:32:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LMA shares insights on handling AI with outside vendors and leveraging firm culture for business development.
The post Marketing Roundup: Leadership Styles, Competitive Intelligence, Leveraging Tech appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KATHERINE HOLLAR BARNARD</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rep. Michael Johnson of District 23 unpacks views on abortion, education, and gun laws ahead of election]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=848019</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/rep-michael-johnson-of-district-23-on-his-views-on-abortion-education-gun-laws-and-more-ahead-of-election-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T21:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Michael Johnson’s Instagram Representative Michael Johnson, born and raised in Kansas City, has lived in District 23—which encompasses parts of the northeast side of town—for most of his life, and he wouldn’t have it any other way. He’s beyond proud of his district and the people he’s represented since 2021. “I would do it for free, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law School Deans Have ‘Grave Concerns’ About California Bar Exam]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075446</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/law-school-deans-have-grave-concerns-about-california-bar-exam/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T20:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law school deans think that change is coming too quickly to the California bar exam.
The post Law School Deans Have ‘Grave Concerns’ About California Bar Exam appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, Trump’s Spokesperson Is Not An Above The Law Columnist Despite What You Might’ve Seen On Theo Von’s Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075467</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/no-trumps-spokesperson-is-not-an-above-the-law-columnist-despite-what-you-mightve-seen-on-theo-vons-podcast/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T20:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technically, Trump spokespeople have been columnists here, but not THIS time.
The post No, Trump’s Spokesperson Is Not An Above The Law Columnist Despite What You Might’ve Seen On Theo Von’s Podcast appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Is Suing Elon Musk Today? Cards Against Humanity, COME ON DOWN!]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075460</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/who-is-suing-elon-musk-today-cards-against-humanity-come-on-down/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T19:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay, they're technically suing SpaceX. Po-tay-to, po-tah-to.
The post Who Is Suing Elon Musk Today? Cards Against Humanity, COME ON DOWN! appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri’s gubernatorial debate explored four wildly different perspectives for 2025 and beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850111</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missouris-gubernatorial-debate-explored-four-wildly-different-perspectives-for-2025-and-beyond/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T19:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Rudi Keller, Missouri Independent. Missouri gubernatorial candidates met for forums Friday, Sept. 20, in Springfield, sponsored by the Missouri Press Association. Present onstage were Republican and current Lieutenant Governor Mike Kehoe, Democrat and current House minority leader Crystal Quade, libertarian and business owner Bill Slantz, and Green Party candidate Paul Lehmann, a retired farmer and minister. Here...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For My Republican Friends]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075439</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/for-my-republican-friends/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T18:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time to stop foaming at the mouth and start influencing.
The post For My Republican Friends appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Herrmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is The YSL RICO Trial A Court Proceeding Or A Reality Show?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075452</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/is-the-ysl-rico-trial-a-court-proceeding-or-a-reality-show/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T17:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flavor of QZ has a ring to it. 
The post Is The YSL RICO Trial A Court Proceeding Or A Reality Show? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nationals End Season By Demoting Leadoff Hitter Who Was In A Casino Until 8:00 A.M.]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167991</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nationals-end-season-by-demoting-leadoff-hitter-who-was-in-a-casino-until-800-a-m"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T17:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Nationals made a sudden and alarming roster move on Friday, optioning 23-year-old all-star shortstop C.J. Abrams to their Triple-A team in Rochester. If the Nationals were good—if they were overstocked with primo young hitting talent, like, say, the Baltimore Orioles—it would be possible to slide this move by as an unfortunate consequence of roster crunch. And, indeed, the Orioles also optioned a talented youngster on the same day, sending hulking 22-year-old infielder and reigning organizational Minor League Player of the Year Coby Mayo back to Norfolk, effectively ending his season. Good teams can have reasons for making painful late-season roster moves that are, if not entirely wholesome, at least coherent within the context of a competitive enterprise. This is not that.
The Nationals are not good, and there's no one anywhere in the organization to slide all that comfortably into Abrams's spot in the field or in the lineup. Abrams's demotion is a disciplinary measure: As first reported by Cody Delmendo of CHGO Sports and later confirmed by Jesse Rogers of ESPN, Abrams was seen living it up at a Chicago casino until 8:00 a.m. Friday morning, and then had to suit up for a 2:00 p.m. game against the Cubs that same afternoon. After the game—Abrams went 0-for-3 with a walk in the leadoff spot, in a 3–1 loss—Nationals coach Davey Martinez pulled Abrams into a long and emotional meeting and informed him that his season was over. The Nationals haven't exactly ratted Abrams out, but everything in their tone and demeanor confirms the scoop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Arkansauce jam up recordBar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850347</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-arkansauce-jam-up-recordbar/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T17:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arkansauce. // photo by Allison Scavo Arkansauce recordBar Friday, September 20 Arkansauce is a progressive newgrass jam band with a blend of traditional slap-grass known to headline festivals. The improvisional string quartet came through Kansas City on their tour where they play a myriad of songs from their vast repertoire. The venue was packed in shoulder-to-shoulder as Saucers stomped the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Scavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Biglaw Firm Announces Merger With Top Midsize Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075449</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/top-biglaw-firm-announces-merger-with-top-midsize-firm/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T17:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mergers, mergers, and more mergers! Biglaw firms really have the urge to merge in Q4.
The post Top Biglaw Firm Announces Merger With Top Midsize Firm appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antonio Pierce Abruptly Realizes He Is Coaching The Raiders]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168014</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/antonio-pierce-abruptly-realizes-he-is-coaching-the-raiders"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To take the old saying and mangle it in the back shop a bit, you cannot hope to beat the Las Vegas Raiders because they are so easy to contain. The latest person to learn this lesson is their 12-game-old head coach.
Antonio Pierce was advertised as the franchise’s latest savior, the coach that this historically listless roster would respond to after enduring The Josh McDaniels Experience; with Pierce setting the example, the team would vibrate with joyful devotion to the greater cause. So trusting. So naive. But these are the Raiders, who have talked it while steadfastly refusing to walk it for two full decades and change now. This is an organization that goes from "Hey, who's the new guy?" to "Hey, when are we getting a new guy?" with uncommon swiftness. It's why, since they lost Super Bowl The 37th back in 'Ought Two, Raiders coaches have averaged 26 games between hiring and firing. That's barely a season and a half.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alleged ‘predatory’ contracts continue to surface in Missouri social-equity marijuana program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850215</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/alleged-predatory-contracts-continue-to-surface-in-missouri-social-equity-marijuana-program/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:49:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The microbusiness program was sold to Missouri voters as a way to help victims of the war on drugs get a toehold in this burgeoning industry (Rebecca Rivas/Missouri Independent) Destiny Brown thought she had been recruited last year to own and operate a small-scale Missouri cannabis dispensary — and get paid $200,000 to do it. Cannabis investor Michael Halow told...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Rivas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cope Is A Terrible Way Not To Die]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167825</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cope-is-a-terrible-way-not-to-die"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:29:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the things that has always been captivating to me about the TV show Alone is how it illustrates our endless capacity for invention in the absolute worst of times. It's a reality show about survival, but really what that means is adaptability. When you lose a supply of arrows, can you fashion more from branches and scavenged parts? Do you know how to use sphagnum moss to treat a wound after an unfortunate ax misadventure? If a crafty vole has raided your stores of fish, will you be able to find more food or resort to gnarly bark-based teas and intermittent fasting as the frost sets in?
It's a manufactured danger. But part of the appeal is that there's no one coming to the rescue. Ultimately you survive and win, or wind up another sucker ferried back to civilization after an intense flirtation with giardia. Either way, these people have to figure out a new way to live every day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Firm Facing Public Corruption Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075448</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/biglaw-firm-facing-public-corruption-investigation/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firms is cooperating with the inquiry.
The post Biglaw Firm Facing Public Corruption Investigation appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jhy Coulter’s new venture Orange By: Devoured bites into Kansas City’s Martini Corner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=847818</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/jhy-coulters-new-venture-orange-by-devoured-bites-into-kansas-citys-martini-corner/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pizza at Orange By Devoured // Photo By Tiffany Watts Kansas City’s Martini Corner, known for its vibrant energy and eclectic mix of dining and nightlife options, just got a new neighbor—Orange By: Devoured. Opened on August 15, 2024, this fresh, creative pizzeria is the latest venture by Jhy Coulter, an entrepreneur, chef, and visionary whose love for food, travel,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal-Manchester City Clash Ruined By Premier League’s New Focus On Delays Of Game]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167946</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/arsenal-manchester-city-clash-ruined-by-premier-leagues-new-focus-on-delays-of-game"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T15:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the Premier League's marquee showdown of the weekend, last year's number one and number two faced off in an early clash of titans that already had title implications. Arsenal retooled this summer in order to better pursue Manchester City for a third straight season, bringing in defender Riccardo Calafiori, midfielder Mikel Merino, and forward Raheem Sterling. Sunday was Arsenal's first crack at City this season, and though the visiting side gave up a goal to—who else—Erling Haaland in the ninth minute, the Gunners took control of the match with goals from two defenders: Calafiori tied it up in the 22nd with an incredible rocket from outside the box, and then Gabriel gave Arsenal the lead in the first minute of first half stoppage time with a rising header off a corner.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R4eXMyqrGVg]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Documentary Shows How Musician Clawed Back Rights To Number 1 Hit After Decades Of Being Paid Nothing]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075444</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/documentary-shows-how-musician-clawed-back-rights-to-number-1-hit-after-decades-of-being-paid-nothing/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T15:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A feel good story about the 1976 Copyright Act!
The post Documentary Shows How Musician Clawed Back Rights To Number 1 Hit After Decades Of Being Paid Nothing appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lando Norris Is Nearly Perfect]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167915</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lando-norris-is-nearly-perfect"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T15:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were some recognizable elements of the Singapore Grand Prix this year: a night race with hot weather, heavy humidity, a dew point no doubt off the charts. Correspondingly, there was tired, occasionally frustrated driving on a street circuit not built for overtakes, though this year they tried to rectify this issue by increasing the total number of DRS zones to four. Four! The saving grace for Singapore has also been its most defining characteristic: its propensity for safety cars. But this year, with some luck and a lot of engine reliability, there was nothing. 
This year's race was won or lost in discrete moments. Ferrari lost it after a horrific qualifying; you can't recover from P9 and P10 on the grid on a track like Singapore. Lewis Hamilton lost it after a call to put him on old soft tires to start the race; he failed to grab the all-important track position on the opening lap, and didn't have the tires to last him to the end. And Lando Norris won it by finally converting pole position to a lap-one lead for the first time so far this season, putting to bed—or, at least, a nap—one of the most persistent criticisms levied at his driving this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Sept. 23: Peach Turnover]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167953</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-sept-23-peach-turnover"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T15:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time to get in gear and solve our Monday crossword. This week's puzzle was constructed by Hanh Huynh and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Hanh is a bankruptcy attorney who lives in Brooklyn, N.Y. with his wife and two kids, 10 and 12. His parents fled Vietnam with him and his siblings, eventually arriving in America as refugees. Hanh was an infantryman in the U.S. Army before going to law school. He enjoys bowling and playing Roblox BedWars with his kids.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up a Wild (Card) Final Week]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=446874</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/setting-up-a-wild-card-final-week/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T15:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The division races have more or less been decided, but each league offers some intrigue when it comes to the Wild Card berths.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Jaffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is It Possible To Create Anticapitalist Work On Social Media?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167570</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/is-it-possible-to-create-anticapitalist-work-on-social-media"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T15:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the weather cools and the kids return to school, my social media feeds have been inundated with fall trend forecasting: "What cool girls will be wearing this fall" and "The Row Margaux dupe you NEED." 
Nearly as prevalent in my feeds are the de-influencing videos. While influencers work to persuade their audience to buy products they may or may not need in the hopes of getting a few cents of commission, de-influencers remind people why they don’t need to spend their money. De-influencing material ranges from explaining why individual viral products aren't worth buying to entire accounts built to remind audiences that hauls aren't normal and call out undisclosed ads or partnerships with brands. De-influencing is part of a larger populist turn I've noticed in response to the omnipresent commercialization of the social internet, but it also exemplifies one of the internet's signal conundrums: Is it possible to create anticapitalist work on social media?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Penalties For Violating Biglaw Office Attendance Mandates May Soon Have More Bite]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075447</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/penalties-for-violating-biglaw-office-attendance-mandates-may-soon-have-more-bite/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T14:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Additional bonus penalties may be coming for those who don't go to the office.
The post Penalties For Violating Biglaw Office Attendance Mandates May Soon Have More Bite appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 White Sox Have Achieved The Abominable]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167922</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-2024-white-sox-have-achieved-the-abominable"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T14:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["No loss is good," said Chicago White Sox interim manager Grady Sizemore, a statement which, rather than defusing the potency of Sunday's milestone loss, merely diffuses it across a season: If no loss is good, then each loss is bad, which means 120 losses are a death march unseen in the days of widespread color TV. That's 120 days of feeling bad at the ballpark; 120 unsatisfied nights, wishing for a better tomorrow that rarely comes. Thirty-six chances for the South Side to stand up, weighed against 120 blunt remonstrances to remain seated.
The 43-119 Detroit Tigers of 2003 are now in the rearview mirror, still notable for possessing the last 20-game loser in Mike Maroth but no longer for owning the AL's worst record of the modern era. The 40-120-1 New York Mets of 1962 are next up. One of the first expansion teams, before MLB had balanced its expansion rules to avoid putting out true stinkers, those Mets were wretched but charmingly pitiable, like an Instagram chihuahua. They made their own manager ask, "Can't anybody here play this game?" They were and are baseball's touchstone for terrible. And they were a better team than the 2024 Chicago White Sox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[195 Congress Members Call For Extension Of Enhanced Premium Tax Credits]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075430</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/09/congress-enhanced-premium-tax-credits/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T14:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In two letters, U.S. representatives and senators called for an extension of the enhanced premium tax credits, which are set to expire in 2025 and have lowered costs for those purchasing coverage on the marketplace.
The post 195 Congress Members Call For Extension Of Enhanced Premium Tax Credits appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MARISSA PLESCIA - MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: The String Cheese Incident defies genre at The Midland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850351</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-the-string-cheese-incident-defies-genre-at-the-midland/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T13:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The String Cheese Incident. // photo by Allison Scavo The String Cheese Incident The Midland Thursday, September 19 Since 1993, the String Cheese Incident has been combining a love for all music lovers into one mega genre. Much like the food, String Cheese Incident pulls one part into several others – one note can extend into reggae, yacht rock, jazz,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Scavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Jinkies! Coffee and Hangout’s Madi and Lisa Dombrowski]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=847571</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-jinkies-coffee-and-hangouts-madi-and-lisa-dombrowski/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T13:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Madi and Lisa Dombrowski If the Brady’s, the Partridge’s, and Charlie’s Angels found themselves in need of a jolt of java, they’d no doubt pick Jinkies! Coffee and Hangout in Overland Park. The retro-esque ’70s-inspired coffeehouse—which opened in Jan. 2021—is owned and operated by the mother/daughter duo of Madi and Lisa Dombrowski. “It’s been an incredible journey,”...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Aces Come From Every Direction]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167921</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-aces-come-from-every-direction"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T12:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of the first quarter of their opening playoff game against the Las Vegas Aces, the Seattle Storm couldn't have found themselves in a much better position. They were leading 18-9, having held the Aces to just 11 percent shooting from the field. Unanimous MVP A'ja Wilson, who had just received her trophy in a pregame ceremony, was 1-of-8. The Storm were cooking.
If a blueprint exists for Seattle getting past Vegas in this best-of-three first-round matchup, it looks a lot like what happened in that first quarter. The Storm, always a defense-first unit, were playing with an intensity and speed that totally discombobulated the Aces' offense. Even without defensive anchor Ezi Magbegor, Seattle's collection of defensive hawks were switching and sliding and blitzing fast enough to make Wilson and the Aces look slow and ponderous. Every shot at the rim was contested, and Seattle's traps and rotations fired so quickly that they looked less like a basketball team scrambling to cover the court than a well-drilled soccer team executing a perfect counter-press.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 09.23.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075441</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/morning-docket-09-23-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T12:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Judge says law firm "defiled the very temple of justice." [Bloomberg Law News]
* Our national nightmare is over: law firm's Rosie the Ve-LAW-ciraptor mascot returned after being stolen two years ago. [KWTX]
* FTC sues pharmacies over measures designed to inflate insulin prices. [Reuters]
* Law school deans worried about California's future bar exam, but in fairness they were worried about its past bar exam so this is an ongoing issue. [ABA Journal]
* Even this Supreme Court is tired of dealing with Jill Stein. [Courthouse News Service]
* Is distinguishing between website advertising and social media advertising the same as putting Big Macs and Whoppers in separate markets? The judge in the Google ad case didn't seem to think so. [Law360]
* Judge blasts plaintiffs in intellectual property lawsuit over Meta's AI training. Lawyers say they'll bring in new team. See, this is why you need to train people with the best material available. [Corporate Counsel]
The post Morning Docket: 09.23.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eagles Remember They Should  Give The Ball To Saquon Barkley More]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167892</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/eagles-remember-they-should-give-the-ball-to-saquon-barkley-more"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T23:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through the better part of three quarters of football on Sunday afternoon, the Philadelphia Eagles and New Orleans Saints were locked in a world's ugliest dog contest. Just one week earlier the Saints were rolling over the haunted remains of the Cowboys and everyone got a piece of the action; Alvin Kamara got four touchdowns, quarterback Derek Carr threw for 243 yards and two touchdowns and even got in on a QB sneak on the way to a 44-19 win. 
On Sunday they led 3-0 thanks to an early field goal and Eagles coach Nick Sirianni's commitment to salvaging genius from ineptitude. The birds had three blown fourth downs early in the game: a blocked punt, a Jalen Hurts sack after a too many men on the field penalty, and a busted run play at the end of the first half in place of an easy field goal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dukes Ran The Tar Heels Out Of Their Own Building]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167861</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-dukes-ran-the-tar-heels-out-of-their-own-building"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T19:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fifty-three points. That's how much Sun Belt juggernaut James Madison University had at halftime against the University of North Carolina on the way to a 70-50 blowout. But that final score does no justice to the absolute ass beating that the Dukes conveyed in Saturday's matchup.
That 53 points scored in a half is the most points James Madison has ever scored in one half and the most points North Carolina has ever allowed in a half. It's also the most points a power conference team has given up to a Group of 5 team since 2012. James Madison forced four turnovers, including a pick-six and a blocked punt return for a touchdown in just the first half. The Dukes notched five turnovers in total and for added measure—or humiliation—recovered their own surprise onside kick. James Madison quarterback Alonza Barnett III finished the game with seven total touchdowns, breaking the record for most touchdowns by a Dukes quarterback in a single game, going 22-for-34 and 388 total yards, adding two touchdowns off 64 yards on the ground.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>