<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-07-26T10:18:49.332Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HYDRANYM No. 9: Vote!]]></title>
        <id>6883cecc19c0620001df97c9</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hydranym-no-9-vote/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-26T00:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by The Editors

It is your solemn duty to select the victor of Hydranym No. 9, from among the 21 best entries received this week on the theme of
MEETING
HYDRANYM is the Creative Writing word game especially for Flaming Hydra subscribers (RULES appear below). Join in by subscribing! It&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gratuitous gratuities]]></title>
        <id>6883cf6419c0620001df9806</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-368/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-26T00:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[George Orwell’s days scrambling for tips, by Diana Moskovitz]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tipping George Orwell]]></title>
        <id>68827f4e19c0620001df7c81</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/tipping-george-orwell/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-26T00:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[George Orwell was just 26 in 1929, when, the story goes, he had nearly all his money stolen from his digs in Paris. He was a middle-class, well-educated young man who could almost certainly have gotten help from his aunt Nellie, who lived in the French capital. But instead he]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need To Talk About Sloppers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/we-need-to-talk-about-sloppers-b732</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/we-need-to-talk-about-sloppers-b732"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T20:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best ever death metal bot out of Denton]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dominique Malonga Gets It Done In Small Doses]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196725</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dominique-malonga-gets-it-done-in-small-doses"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T19:58:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dominique Malonga is an unusual player in unusual circumstances for a rookie. Most lottery picks are consigned to at least one year of joker teammates, demoralizing blowouts, and moral victories only. “Being bad” is generally the reason teams end up in the lottery at all. First-overall pick Paige Bueckers, for instance, will almost surely lose more games with the Dallas Wings this year than she did in her entire UConn career. To the extent that there’s any silver lining in playing on a loser, it’s the chance to get lots of low-stakes reps in different roles and alongside different people. Bueckers is also averaging nearly 35 minutes a game, fourth-most in the league, more than the likes of Napheesa Collier, Breanna Stewart, Alyssa Thomas and A’ja Wilson, the usual workhorse suspects.
Malonga, who went second-overall to the Seattle Storm, is not quite averaging 10 minutes a game this year. That’s no huge surprise. Bueckers entered her rookie season as a polished plug-and-play guard four years Malonga’s senior. And from draft night, it was pretty clear that the timelines of the 19-year-old Malonga and of the Seattle core—Nneka Ogwumike, Skylar Diggins, Gabby Williams, and Ezi Magbegor—might be slightly misaligned. But this isn’t a terrible fit for a raw young player who’s evoked some “baby giraffe” comparisons as she gets used to the pace and intensity of WNBA basketball.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Designate Cavan Biggio For Assignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=860570</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/royals-dfa-cavan-biggio.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T19:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced Friday that infielder/outfielder Cavan Biggio has been designated for assignment. His spot on the 40-man roster will go to reliever Hunter Harvey, who has been reinstated from the 60-day injured list. Righty Jonathan Bowlan has been optioned to Triple-A. Biggio, 30, signed a minor league deal with the Royals in the offseason.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Such Brave Girls’ Wants To Trauma Bond With You]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196729</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/such-brave-girls-wants-to-trauma-bond-with-you"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T17:58:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there’s a line that sums up Such Brave Girls, it might be this one: "Remember the family crest: Ignore, Repress, Forget." The extremely British show, now in its second season on Hulu, isn’t one to let subtlety get in the way of its satire.
Such Brave Girls follows the all-girl Johnson family in the aftermath of the man of the house abandoning them after popping out for some tea bags. There’s single mom Deb (Louise Brealey), left in debt, who can't stand her cheap, moronic boyfriend but suffers through it with an eye on his huge house. There’s older sister Josie (show creator Kat Sadler) who is a lesbian with a case of clinical depression/anxiety and a simpering, actively oblivious boyfriend. And there’s younger, hyper-femme sister Billie (Lizzie Davidson), the real-life sister of Sadler and an unhinged highlight, who is chasing after her own useless drug-dealing boyfriend. “Ultimately the show is a family sitcom about trauma," Sadler has said, "but it’s more about us being narcissistic losers who are pathetically obsessed with what people think about us.” The second season opens with Josie in an art theory lecture as her mother and sister burst in, throw a hood over her head, and abduct her, only to remove the hood when they arrive at ... her wedding day. "This is the happiest day of your life, Josie," her mother says, holding up a white dress like it's a threat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is No Tour de France Without The Tour de Brands]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196720</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/there-is-no-tour-de-france-without-the-tour-de-brands"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T17:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALBERTVILLE, France — Hours before the start of Stage 19 of the Tour de France, the day's real competition is already well underway. Civilians and workers alike stalk the caravan, seeking goodies. A gendarme engages in barter with a representative from La Vache Qui Rit (the Laughing Cow). Each side wants what the other has: merch. 
Ultimately, the cop trades two official Tour de France police patches and two bananas for a dozen cycling caps adorned with the beautiful laughing cow logo and as many t-shirts. I have been trying to secure a shirt for a week, but when we beg for some, the representative offers a chagrined smile and tells us he is out, as he hands us hat after hat. On the hats is the eponymous laughing cow, wearing earrings of the brand's trademark cheese wheels, each featuring a laughing cow of their own, who is wearing the earrings as well—an infinitely recursive abyss of bovine mirth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Pursuit Of Personal Taste]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196473</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/in-pursuit-of-personal-taste"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T16:51:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Listening Habits, a column where I share the music I’ve been fixated on recently.
Like everything else in 2025, algorithms and social media deeply influence how people experience the arts, music most of all. In light of these invisible hands that more or less dictate online music exploration, and the growing desire to rebel against them as seen in the comeback of physical media, it is worth thinking about what "personal taste" really means today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What The Hell Is Going On With Marc-André ter Stegen?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196618</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-the-hell-is-going-on-with-marc-andre-ter-stegen"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T16:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, longtime Barcelona goalkeeper Marc-André ter Stegen announced via an open letter to the club's fans that he will undergo back surgery, and that as a result he will miss "about three months." A short while later, the club reportedly leaked through Catalonian radio station RAC1 that, contrary to ter Stegen's announcement, it regards his recovery time as "between 4–5 months."
An athlete announcing their own surgical recovery timetable isn't unheard of, but it is slightly unusual; typically that sort of thing goes through an organization's official communications shop. An athlete and an organization publicly disagreeing on a player's surgical recovery timetable, likewise, is pretty rare relative to the total number of pro athlete surgeries, but not really remarkable. What's interesting and worth examining in this instance is indicated by the fact that Barcelona's projected recovery timetable for ter Stegen is longer than ter Stegen's. Usually, you'd expect it to be the other way around, for easily legible reasons: The club would like its worker back at the revenue-generating part of their job as soon as possible rather than collecting paychecks for physical therapy, and the worker—the one of the parties, after all, who endures the pain and surgery and recovery, and whose career prospects are affected by injury—would like maximum security against having to go through it all again. In this case it's the player saying he'll be back in three months, and the club saying no, it'll be more like four or five. What's this all about?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Does The NFLPA Represent?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196676</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/who-does-the-nflpa-represent"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T16:07:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gene Upshaw would come to town once a year, usually in the middle of the week. There we were, the Denver Broncos, an NFL football team going through the routine of our football preparation, speaking football language, watching football film, taking football hits, and training our football bodies. But on this one day each year, after all the football things were done, we stayed in our seats in the team meeting room for a different type of discussion. 
Upshaw was an imposing presence. He had been a shit-kicking lineman for the Raiders for 15 seasons, and upon retirement, became the NFLPA’s shit-kicking executive director. He held the post for 25 years. We trusted him. After all, he was one of us. And yet, there he’d be, standing in front of us on a Thursday, explaining in detail some of the very important issues we had to face, including the emergence of withheld data about concussions and the impending CBA negotiations, and no one in the room was listening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Jackson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Feels Like An Occupation]]></title>
        <id>6883892319f1d000010a3432</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/it-feels-like-an-occupation/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T14:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every facet of American life is being taken over by people who recognize no limits on their power or reach]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Innovation Strikes In The Field Of Chimpanzee Rectum Adornment]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196378</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/innovation-strikes-in-the-field-of-chimpanzee-rectum-adornment"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T14:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fifteen years ago in a sanctuary in Zambia, inspiration struck a chimpanzee named Julie. She plucked a stiff blade of grass, stuck it inside her ear, and left it there. There the grass dangled as Julie played, groomed, and rested. The behavior soon spread to most of the other chimpanzees in Julie's group, called Group 4, and was adopted by her son Jack and chimps Kathy, Miracle, and Val. In the span of just one year, Julie was observed with grass in her ear 168 times; by comparison, the next most frequent observer was Kathy, with 36 grass-in-ear sightings. After Julie died in 2013, her invention lived on, with Kathy and Val carrying the torch.
Val, on trend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: New England Patriots]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196390</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-new-england-patriots"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T14:06:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the New England Patriots. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the New England Patriots. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: New England Patriots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Ugh! As If!’ Takes On The Enduring Appeal Of ‘Clueless’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196623</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ugh-as-if-takes-on-the-enduring-appeal-of-clueless"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T13:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the mid-to-late '90s, I was part of a girl gang that invaded suburban homes across the top half of New Jersey. We left our clothes strewn across various surfaces in your carpeted basements, ate your Snackwells in the wee hours, and wrote weird notes to your awkward eldest sons. Some of us stayed up all night, laughing and plotting, and some of us, inexplicably, wanted to go to bed at 9:00 p.m. For days afterwards, you would catch the faint smell of Bath & Body Works warm vanilla sugar.
It was the age of the pre-teen slumber party, and you could hear us coming from the synth riff of Kim Wilde’s “Kids in America.” It’s the song that opens Clueless, which was the preferred VHS rental for the coolest sleepovers I attended. We were the kids of America, even if we were closer to Nickelodeon’s definition than MTV’s, and Clueless offered a hopeful glimpse into life beyond middle school. We all wanted to be Cher Horowitz—beautiful, popular, rich, and, yes, even kind—and we weren’t the only ones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Annie Berke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heel, down]]></title>
        <id>6882cd8d19c0620001df7df9</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-367/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T02:42:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ian Williams, Tom Scocca, Josephine Riesman, and Maria Bustillos on the passing of Hulk Hogan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hulk Hogan, 1953–2025]]></title>
        <id>6882c3b419c0620001df7dba</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hulk-hogan-1953-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T02:39:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let me tell you something, brother]]></title>
        <id>6882bd9219c0620001df7d86</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/let-me-tell-you-something-brother/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-25T02:23:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pro wrestling is, in its structure, in its nature, a haven for thieves, rapists, murderers, con men, and perverts. Kayfabe—the great language and logic of pro wrestling—is, deep in its bones, based on ripping people off and making them like it. 
In related news, Hulk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hulk Hogan Is Dead]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196575</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/hulk-hogan-is-dead"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T20:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terry Bollea died on Thursday. The former professional wrestler was 71 years old. According to his longtime manager, Bollea died at his home in Clearwater, Fla.; different reports say that paramedics responded at dawn to an emergency call reporting that Bollea was suffering from cardiac arrest. He'd had some sort of recent neck surgery, and was rumored to be in failing health. Bollea's wife, Sky, recently batted away rumors that he was in a coma. Fellow washed-up wrestling luminary Jimmy Hart insisted Tuesday afternoon that Bollea was "doing phenomenal." That turned out to be not the case.
Reports of Bollea's poor health were first circulated by the radio personality Bubba the Love Sponge Clem. Followers of Bollea's post-wrestling career will recall that Clem and Bollea were once good friends and sometimes appeared together on Clem's Tampa-area radio show. In 2012, the two made headlines when Gawker reported that Clem had recorded a clandestine video of his wife, Heather, having sex with Bollea. A separate recording that became public years later captured Bollea making vile and racist remarks while in conversation with Heather.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Can You Trust? With Pablo Torre]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196525</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/who-can-you-trust-with-pablo-torre"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T19:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's just a lot to walk around with. You still have to walk around, naturally, there's stuff that needs doing and nothing is really gained by sitting around thinking about how stupid and crooked and venal everything is, and about the confluence of cultural forces conspiring to make it all dumber and nastier and worse, or about the erosion of the institutions and mores that ideally would stem that degradation. And yet, if you're the someone who thinks about that sort of thing—and if you are aware of it, it does tend to clatter around in your brain even if just as highly intrusive background noise—you can't just not think about it. The challenge, if you are aiming to remain sane, is in how you spin it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Tour de France Lunches, Reviewed]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196573</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/my-tour-de-france-lunches-reviewed"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T19:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[COURCHEVEL, France — Lunch: indisputably one of the top-three meals of the day, but at the Tour de France, not always something the intrepid reporter can afford to prioritize. Most days involve some degree of frantic scurrying between the start and finish, hitting the road early to go stand around the team buses and ask as many people as possible, "What's going to happen today?" (this often works, somehow) before scrambling to beat the peloton to the finish and ask them what happened today. Breakfast is typically one pastry, eaten in the car, and dinner is something to be taken seriously here in France, so it is good. In between, there is not much time.
However! The Amaury Sport Organization (ASO), the Tour's organizing body, provides a press room for journalists to in theory write and in practice annoy each other in like seven different languages, and the press room usually has food. I am not in the press room every day, especially on mountainous days, because it is quite often far from the finish line, which is where the interesting stuff happens. Those days, I eat either the world's driest sandwich from a French gas station or the world's least flavorful salad from a French gas station. Other days, I eat in the press room.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five Players Found Not Guilty In Hockey Canada Sexual Assault Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196539</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/five-players-found-not-guilty-in-hockey-canada-sexual-assault-trial"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T19:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five former NHL players and members of Hockey Canada's 2018 World Juniors championship team were found not guilty of sexual assault in a London, Ontario, courtroom Thursday, with the presiding judge stating, "I do not find the evidence of [the accuser] to be either credible or reliable." Dillon Dubé, Cal Foote, Michael McLeod, Alex Formenton, and Carter Hart had been accused of assaulting a 20-year-old woman in a hotel room while celebrating their tournament win on June 18, 2018.
"Having found that I cannot rely upon the evidence from [the accuser] and considering the evidence in this trial as a whole, I conclude that the Crown cannot meet its onus on any of the counts before me," Justice Maria Carroccia said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jesse Chavez Announces Retirement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=860364</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/jesse-chavez-announces-retirement.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T18:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right-hander Jesse Chavez announced his retirement on Foul Territory today. He was on the Braves’ roster until recently but was designated for assignment a week ago when that club acquired Dane Dunning. Chavez elected free agency after clearing waivers and has apparently decided to hang up his spikes in recent days. “I don’t think we’re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: New York Giants]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196442</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-new-york-giants"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T17:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the New York Giants. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the New York Giants. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: New York Giants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spain Won An Ugly Game Thanks To Moments Of Splendor]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196547</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/spain-won-an-ugly-game-thanks-to-moments-of-splendor"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T16:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's exceedingly rare to see a side enter an international tournament and manage to play its best, most aesthetically pleasing soccer for the entire month-long affair. It does happen—the Spanish men absolutely steamrolled Euro 2012, and the USWNT did the same at the 2019 World Cup—but more often than not, exhaustion, nerves, and tough matchups will force a team to win ugly on the way to the trophy. In Wednesday's Euro 2025 semifinal against Germany, Spain won ugly, as ugly as I've seen during the team's ongoing run of dominance, though La Roja did manage to sneak some real transcendence into a long and draining night in Zurich.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-Q3G9BW0Ba0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do I Find A Non-Fiction Book I Won’t Hate?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196334</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-do-i-find-a-non-fiction-book-i-wont-hate"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T15:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Ask The Book Doctor, a recurring series about books and reading them.
It can be nice to have a solid brand. For example, I always order the same drinks at the bar, so if I am running late, and I ask someone to order for me, I always get what I want, because I always want the same thing. But because I am consistent, people sometimes freak out when I choose something else. A week or so ago, I ordered a different drink at the bar, and everyone acted like I had two heads! The expectations people have of what I like, then, are determining the kinds of recommendations and information people give to me. No one told me the fancy little whiskey cocktail was so good, because no one thought I would want it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Hill Is Alive With the Sound of Scream-Grunts]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=468662</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/rich-hill-is-alive-with-the-sound-of-scream-grunts/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T15:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With songs he has sung for a thousand years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davy Andrews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat McAfee Declares Himself A “Girl Dad” In Apology To Harassed College Student]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196528</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/pat-mcafee-declares-himself-a-girl-dad-in-apology-to-harassed-college-student"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T13:27:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pat McAfee ended his daily ESPN show on Wednesday by finally addressing the role he played in ruining a college student's reputation. To nobody's surprise, he was extremely annoying about it.
Back in February, McAfee used his show to amplify a rumor about Ole Miss student Mary Kate Cornett having an affair with her boyfriend's dad. The rumor had already gone viral on social media, with Cornett's name attached, and McAfee's decision to discuss it on air—during an interview with NFL insider Adam Schefter, of all people—made things much worse for her. Cornett's phone number was posted online, her mother's house was swatted, and she received so many threats that she had to switch to online courses and move into emergency housing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get the quote / Read the book]]></title>
        <id>6881422919c0620001df650e</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-366/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T02:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Philip Bump in conversation with Maria Bustillos, and an announcement from Luke O’Neil]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking the Measure of Philip Bump]]></title>
        <id>6881680b19c0620001df6642</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/taking-the-measure-of-philip-bump/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T02:09:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Bustillos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s also quite funny to be clear]]></title>
        <id>688160a219c0620001df65fd</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/its-also-quite-funny-to-be-clear/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T02:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke O'Neil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest On Seth Lugo’s Trade Candidacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=860257</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/latest-on-seth-lugos-trade-candidacy.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-24T00:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seth Lugo reeled off another productive start this afternoon, tossing six innings of two-run ball to earn the win at Wrigley Field. The veteran right-hander now carries a 2.95 earned run average with a 22% strikeout rate. This was his 11th quality start in 19 appearances. Kansas City took two out of three from the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Hill Is BACK]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196498</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rich-hill-is-back"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T19:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On May 21, Defector's Ray Ratto informed you that it was time to start the "Rich Hill is BACK" countdown. A little over three months later, on July 23, I am happy to inform you that the Rich Hill is BACK countdown has officially ended, because Rich Hill is BACK, and this time with the Kansas City Royals!
Since signing his Minor League deal, the 45-year-old Hill has put up a 5.22 ERA over 11 starts in the minors. Two of those starts came at the Rookie ball level—where, according to Baseball-Reference, he is 23.9 years older than the weighted average age of players in Rookie ball—while the remaining nine came in Triple-A, where he is a mere 17.5 years older than the average. While the ERA is less than ideal, Hill averaged a little less than six strikeouts per start.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In The Face Of Chaos, England Kept Calm And Carried On Into The Euros Final]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196496</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/in-the-face-of-chaos-england-kept-calm-and-carried-on-into-the-euros-final"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T18:07:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GENEVA — If it weren’t for the crystal-blue lake and rugged mountains that sandwich the city, I’d have thought I was in London. In the 36 hours before England’s Women’s Euro semifinal match against Italy, downtown Geneva was crawling with English accents and white kits with leonine crests. The only thing more prevalent than England fans was the ample signage around the city promoting the tournament.
As I walked around, I began to wonder if, come match time, the stadium would be a sea of white, with nary an Italian fan in sight. I kept an eagle eye out for blue Italy jerseys, and found only enough to count on one hand. In fact, I spotted more German and Spanish kits than those for the Azzurre, and that semifinal is across the country. Even on game day, as I merged into the mass of fans streaming into the stadium, only specks of blue shone through the white.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abigail Segel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The First-Place Dodgers Are In Relative Trouble]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196455</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-first-place-dodgers-are-in-relative-trouble"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T17:07:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday night brought another rough loss for the Los Angeles Dodgers—one of a whopping 43 they've already suffered so far this year. Facing the Minnesota Twins at home, the defending champions got absolutely blown out of the ballpark in a three-run loss. Surely no team has ever faced adversity like this.
On Teoscar Hernández's bobblehead night (he was benched), the score was even at 3-3 through five, with starter Yoshinobu Yamamoto getting tagged for a couple of unearned runs in a tricky second inning. Once he exited, however, L.A. completely lost the plot. Ben Casparius, the first reliever out of the pen, looked hurt as he failed to get any of his four batters out, and he'll get an MRI. Alexis Díaz was unable to strand two of the runners he inherited. And after Will Klein walked three straight in the seventh, Edgardo Henriquez entered the game and generously turned a Royce Lewis check-swing chopper into a three-bagger with a wild throw into the right-field corner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: Cleveland Browns]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196428</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-cleveland-browns"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T16:48:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the Cleveland Browns. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the Cleveland Browns. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: Cleveland Browns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jerry Jones Is Negotiating With Himself, As Usual]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196467</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jerry-jones-is-negotiating-with-himself-as-usual"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T16:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the NFL's loudest, goofiest, and by far richest general manager, Dallas Cowboys owner Jerry Jones is always positioned for the camera, any camera. His singular and long-running M.O.—the tough-talking soft touch in contract negotiations—has always been a comedic staple. It allows him to be a hawk and a kitten on player deals simultaneously.
As a result, his circumnavigations regarding super-de-duperstar defensive end Micah Parsons are made more interesting by the way that Jones gave in most recently, which was on Dak Prescott's $240 million deal, which guaranteed $231 million in salary, a year ago. On the one hand, Parsons not yet having a contract is not yet officially a pressing matter; Dallas' first loss of the season, at Philadelphia in the first game of the season, is still six weeks away. On the other, Jones sounds like he is taking the NFL's not-so-secret aggression against guaranteed money to spleen, if not necessarily to heart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals To Acquire Joey Krehbiel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=860169</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/rays-trade-reliever-joey-krehbiel-royals.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T15:26:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10:26am: The Royals are sending cash to the Rays, reports Ken Rosenthal of The Athletic. 10:16am: The Royals are acquiring right-handed reliever Joey Krehbiel from the Rays, reports Marc Topkin of the Tampa Bay Times. The 32-year-old Krehbiel is not on Tampa Bay’s 40-man roster. He’s been pitching with their Triple-A affiliate in Durham after…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I’ll Never Stop Bragging About Seeing Ozzy On The Most Metal Tour Of All Time]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196414</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ill-never-stop-bragging-about-seeing-ozzy-on-the-most-metal-tour-of-all-time"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T15:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No record ever spoke to me more than Southern Rock Opera by the Drive-By Truckers. It’s a concept album released in 2001 that has lots of songs about growing up in the South in the late '70s and not having much going on besides power drinking and rock and roll. That record could be my life. And of all the period-piece vignettes, none hit me where I live more than a verse in "Let There Be Rock" where frontman Patterson Hood bragged about a concert the rock gods blessed upon him back in the day: “I sure saw Ozzy Osbourne,” Hood warbled, “with Randy Rhoads in ‘82 right before that plane crash.”
Well, me too: On February 24, 1982, I caught Ozzy’s Diary of a Madman tour when it stopped in Lubbock, Texas. Ozzy wielded an oversized crucifix while doddering around a stage that had been tarted up to look like a medieval castle. Headbangers heaven.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France Finally Has Something To Smile About At The Tour]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196344</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/france-finally-has-something-to-smile-about-at-the-tour"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T14:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MONT VENTOUX, France — "I had goosebumps in the moment, it was so incredible," Soudal-QuickStep team photographer Wout Beel said the morning of Stage 17. "I am getting goosebumps again just talking about it, look!" he said, showing me his arm. It's true, he was. One day earlier, one of his team's riders had won the stage—but not just any rider, and not just any stage. Finally, the French had gotten on the board.
With each dominant Tadej Pogacar win and each successive anonymous performances from the hometown teams, you could feel the anxiety building. Heading into a punishing third week of the Tour, a French rider had not won a stage at the 2025 Tour de France. Marc Madiot's considerable eyebrows scrunched together with extra verve, the man who dresses as a king in the fan zone looked slightly less vainglorious, and the French press seemed somehow even more dour with each passing day. The French have only failed to win a stage three times, and a fruitless Tour on the 40th anniversary of the last time a French rider won the yellow jersey would have prompted a fresh round of French hysterics. That gnawing anxiety is partially what made Julian Alaphilippe's premature celebration so painful, and partially what made Valentin Paret-Peintre's victory on Mont Ventoux one stage later so cathartic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WNBA Players Want To Share In The League’s “Hypergrowth”]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196258</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/wnba-players-want-to-share-in-the-leagues-hypergrowth"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T13:13:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What money are WNBA players owed? The league’s biggest names got people asking this question Saturday night, when they all wore “Pay Us What You Owe Us” warmup T-shirts before the All-Star Game in Indianapolis. Two days earlier, the players and the league met for their first in-person collective bargaining session, which players generally left feeling frustrated.
“Based on their most recent proposal, we just aren’t able to get to a place where we’re actually even talking about the same thing,” Breanna Stewart said the day after the meeting. The stakes are big. The labor deal will govern what WNBA commissioner Cathy Engelbert called the league’s “hypergrowth,” a moment of huge new valuations, a $2.2 billion media rights deal set to kick in next year, and a round of expansion that will seriously change the league’s scope. Negotiations for the last CBA lasted into the winter, but the current agreement technically expires at the end of October. Ahead of a big free-agency period in February and the upcoming Toronto and Portland expansion drafts, there's some pressure to get this done before then.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leave abuse / Take love]]></title>
        <id>6880128b19c0620001df4d55</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-365/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T00:54:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Myriam Gurba in conversation with Lindsey Boylan; a new home for S.I. Rosenbaum]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaring All the Right People]]></title>
        <id>687fde3c19c0620001df4cbc</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/scaring-all-the-right-people/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T00:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview with Lindsey Boylan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Myriam Gurba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRANSMIGRATIONS]]></title>
        <id>6880161619c0620001df4d82</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/transmigrations/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T00:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>S.I. Rosenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HYDRANYM No. 9]]></title>
        <id>6880217119c0620001df4e2b</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hydranym-no-9/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-23T00:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by The Editors

Subscribe to Flaming Hydra to play HYDRANYM! And tell your friends who love WORD GAMES who might, for any number of reasons, be looking out for a new word game to play online. 

[countdown to 2025-07-24 12:00am PDT]
Excelsior!
COME BACK THURSDAY, JULY 24
TO CHOOSE]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Designate Tyler Gentry For Assignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=860095</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/royals-designate-tyler-gentry-for-assignment.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T20:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced Tuesday that they’ve designated outfielder Tyler Gentry for assignment. His spot on the 40-man roster goes to left-hander Rich Hill, whose previously reported promotion from Triple-A Omaha is now official. Righty Andrew Hoffmann was optioned to Omaha to open an active roster spot for the 45-year-old Hill. Gentry, 26, made his big…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ozzy Osbourne Was The Frontman Of The Future]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196357</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ozzy-osbourne-was-the-frontman-of-the-future"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T20:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine it is December 1970. "I Think I Love You" by the Partridge Family was just atop the charts. Billboard would soon name "Bridge Over Troubled Water" the most popular song of the year. If you listen to music, that's mostly what you are hearing: flowery pop or earnest folk. Then, you go to a show, and you see this: 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K3b6SGoN6dA&ab_channel=BlackSabbath]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The News]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/the-news-305f</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/the-news-305f"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T19:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious ‘ship goo’ creates everyday painkiller in your sinuses—from yogurt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuck The iPad Ordering Kiosk]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196313</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/fuck-the-ipad-ordering-kiosk"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T19:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about cleaning up before dying, ketchup, being a new stepdaddy, and more.
Sorry for the abbreviated bag today, but Why Your Team Sucks has begun and I need to stay on point for it. But don’t worry, the bag will return to its normal length soon enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nerves, Nerves, Nerves]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196351</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nerves-nerves-nerves"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T18:32:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On autobiographies of trans female sexuality]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Zhou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phillies Implement Forbidden Catcher’s Interference Strategem To Walk Off Red Sox]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196319</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/phillies-implement-forbidden-catchers-interference-strategem-to-walk-off-red-sox"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T16:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The advent of the ghost runner made it possible to score a run in baseball without ever getting on base: In extra innings now, a bunt and a sac fly will do the trick. To truncate years-old discourse, this is a clear affront to the principles of baseball. What the Philadelphia Phillies did to the Boston Red Sox in the bottom of the 10th inning of Monday night's game is more old-fashioned than that.
It has always been possible to score a run in baseball without ever hitting the ball into play, though it requires so many walks—or so many wild pitches—within an inning that its accomplishment could hardly be credited to the hitting team. To do it requires the full cooperation, intentional or not, of the opposing pitcher. It would be more accurate to place the bulk of the responsibility for what fans had to witness on Monday night not on the Phillies, who were attempting to commit one atrocity and instead committed another, or the ghost runner, though it lowered the difficulty by one walk, but on the Red Sox and relief pitcher Jordan Hicks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Tour de France Is For The Polyglots, For Now]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196303</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-tour-de-france-is-for-the-polyglots-for-now"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T16:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VAISON-LA-ROMAINE, France — On the morning of Stage 15 of the Tour de France, I was strolling the paddock with a colleague when we happened upon the fan who'd had her cardboard signed turned into jersey fluff by Julian Alaphilippe on the top of the Tourmalet. Clara came from Barcelona to watch the Tour, cheer for her favorite rider, and cheekily propose holy matrimony to him via cardboard sign. "I wanted him to read it quickly, because he is tired," she said. Did she think it would work? "No, I don’t think so, but I have to try." Her first language is Spanish, she told me in English, and she wrote her sign in Dutch. Asked in French if she spoke Dutch, she said no, she had to work out the translation. 
Any given exchange at the Tour might involve this amount of translingualism. I have talked to Belgians in Spanish and Norwegians in English, and have tried and failed to talk to anyone in French, often resorting under duress to a dogmouthed combination of the three. Still, I have been surprised at how easy it's been to get around with only English and Spanish. The Tour itself is conducted in French and English, though obviously French takes precedence. Official communiques are issued first in French, race radio is mostly in French, and the English translations have a charming clunkiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Craig Finn Can Write A Great Song, But Can He Write A Good Short Story?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=194229</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/craig-finn-can-write-a-great-song-but-can-he-write-a-good-short-story"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T15:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Craig Finn is the poet laureate of people who just can’t make it work. His songs are full of burnouts and failures, hard drinkers and rough sleepers, the lagging and the left behind. Their successes evaporate, and their mistakes linger. The narrator of “God in Chicago” has to move a baseball-sized package of heroin left behind by his dead friend Charlie. Every part of the deal—his unemployment, his busted car, the dealer who ruined his chance at college—reminds him of how poorly his life has gone. He makes the trip with Charlie’s sister, they sell the drugs, they get drunk and spend the night together. By the time they get home, she’s sobbing. There is no escape, no solution, no catharsis, and he knows it. “This isn’t the movies.”
This unsentimental compassion, with its humanistic care for those making wrong but necessary choices, is maybe my favorite thing about Finn’s music, but then there’s a lot to like. He’s been making music for more than 30 years with the bands Lifter Puller and the Hold Steady, and he’s been putting out a solo record every two or three years since 2012. Deploying a distinctly novelistic irony, he allows his listener to indulge alongside his characters, and then pulls back to survey the wreckage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Rubsam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Team Sucks 2025: Tennessee Titans]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196233</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-your-team-sucks-2025-tennessee-titans"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T13:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are fans of the Tennessee Titans. But many, many more people are NOT fans of the Tennessee Titans. This 2025 Defector NFL team preview is for those in the latter group. Read all the previews so far here.
Your team: The Tennessee Titans, who are currently attempting to prevent the Houston Texans from using Houston Oilers blue. Jesus Christ Titans, just go back to being the Oilers already. The Houston Oilers’ signature accomplishment, blowing a 35-3 lead in a playoff game, is still a better legacy than anything the “Titans” have “accomplished” in their quarter century-plus as an ongoing NFL concern. The only time the outside world pays attention to these slobs is when Tennessee wears Oilers throwbacks, and you know why? Because it helps them forget that the Titans exist. I’d rather wear a dead skin mask than a Titans jersey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's One Long Joke]]></title>
        <id>687e942619f1d000010a2c2b</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/its-one-long-joke/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T11:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["[Fascists] are amusing themselves, for it is their adversary who is obliged to use words responsibly, since he believes in words."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Agree To Deals With First-Round Picks Sean Gamble, Josh Hammond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=860017</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/royals-agree-to-deals-with-first-round-picks-sean-gamble-josh-hammond.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T04:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals agreed to deals with first-round selections Sean Gamble and Josh Hammond, reports Jim Callis of MLB Pipeline. Kansas City also has deals with second-rounders Michael Lombardi and Justin Lamkin, Callis adds. Gamble was selected with the 23rd overall pick, K.C.’s standard first-round selection. Hammond went 28th with a supplemental selection that the Royals received under the Prospect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perverse verse / Creative instinct]]></title>
        <id>687ed09f19c0620001df3a60</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-364/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T01:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jídé Salawu investigates a faux-Nigerian literary hoax, and Anna Merlan takes in an art exhibit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Poetry Swindler]]></title>
        <id>687eb6ab19c0620001df39aa</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-poetry-swindler/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T01:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, July 17, 2025, my friend Hussain Ahmed sent me a Daily Mail article written by Sonya Gugliara headlined, “Straight white author’s career finally takes off after he tells woke publishers he’s gender queer Nigerian.” The piece describes the exploits of literary hoaxer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jídé Salawu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Artist Is Present]]></title>
        <id>687e9d1f19c0620001df392a</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-artist-is-present/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-22T01:32:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The artist has embarked on a dazzling constellation of experimental works that stretches the boundaries of genre, performance, and commentary. 

Prey 
The artist endlessly chases a cloth-covered beast through a domestic tableau vivant in a manifestation of the predatory nature of the art world. The quarry is permeated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Merlan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heavyweight Champ Oleksandr Usyk Finally Reveals He’s A Bad, Bad Man]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196281</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/heavyweight-champ-oleksander-usyk-finally-reveals-hes-a-bad-bad-man"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T19:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once upon a time, the world heavyweight champ was the most famous man on Earth. But other than hardcore fight fans, nobody can even pick Oleksandr Usyk out of a lineup. And he’s held the belt for nearly four years. But the spotlight could soon shine on the 38-year-old Ukrainian, who remained undefeated and retained his undisputed heavyweight title Saturday night in London with a beautifully brutal defeat of English challenger Daniel Dubois, 
Usyk to this point’s been seen as a fighter’s fighter, far more a technician than a bully. The boxing public prefers that artistry be left to little guys. Whoever wears the heavyweight belt has one job: to knock mofos out. Usyk moved from cruiserweight to heavyweight in 2019, and before this weekend had only knocked out one mofo since moving up. That came in August 2023 in Poland, when he stopped Dubois in a controversial bout tainted by a crucial referee’s decision in Usyk’s favor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Is Trying To Extort The Washington Commanders Into Making It 1989 Again]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196275</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/donald-trump-is-trying-to-extort-the-washington-commanders-into-making-it-1989-again"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T19:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a moment, it almost looked like the current president of our kleptocracy was veering toward a good deed. Fortunately for every American who knows better than to ever get their hopes up regarding this kind of thing, he caught himself and swiftly tied that deed to something retrograde, smallminded, and cheap.
First, Old Squatty said he would interject himself into the potential Washington area football stadium, and do so in a way that was unkind to the owners of the local football factory. As with everything else Trump does or says, it was inevitable that there would be a catch, or just an angle for graft. But in the broadest strokes, it could almost have passed for some fiscal responsibility from the least responsible rich guy of them all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals To Select Rich Hill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=859943</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/royals-to-select-rich-hill.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T18:23:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Hill is headed back to the majors for a 21st season. The Royals plan to select Hill’s contract from Triple-A Omaha, Robert Murray of FanSided reports, and he could pitch for them as soon as tomorrow. Hill signed a minor league contract with Kansas City back in May, and he’s been pitching with their…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Anatomy Of The Doping Story That Has The Tour de France Press Room Buzzing]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196141</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-anatomy-of-the-doping-story-that-has-the-tour-de-france-press-room-buzzing"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T16:58:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MONTPELLIER, France — Fifteen stages and two rest days into the Tour de France, the talk of the press room is not Tadej Pogacar rampaging towards his fourth yellow jersey, brave Kevin Vauquelin trying for an unlikely top-five finish, or Jonas Vingegaard's absurd time-trial helmet. The story that has everyone buzzing concerns events that happened 13 years ago. It is interesting in substance, though its form is the aspect that demands attention. What may seem at first blush like a straightforward story about someone breaking the rules in a different era of cycling is in fact a neat encapsulation of the fraught dynamics between power, media, and performance in cycling; the tension between cycling's dirty past and its supposedly clean present; and the necessity of squaring the two eras.
The story begins in Feb. 2019, when Austrian cross-country skier Johannes Dürr blew the whistle on a German physician named Mark Schmidt, accusing the latter of running a systematic blood doping ring. Schmidt had previously worked for the scandal-plagued Milram and Gerolsteiner cycling teams; in 2009 Austrian cyclist Bernard Kohl had accused him of running doping practices for those teams, though he didn't face any consequences until the Dürr revelations. The investigation came to be known as Operation Aderlass, German for "bloodletting."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secret Brotherhood Of The Phantom Ballplayers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=193799</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-secret-brotherhood-of-the-phantom-ballplayers"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T16:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Marcus Walden was called up by the Toronto Blue Jays in early 2014, nearly seven years after being drafted by the club, everything went more or less as you might expect for a big league promotion. For Father’s Day, Walden gifted his dad the first jersey he ever wore on a big league field; in his hometown of Fresno, Ca. his spot in history was solidified. “After 2014, when I came home, they put up a sign at my high school, number 67,” Walden told Defector. “And at my college they have a wall with every guy who made it to the big leagues out of Fresno [City College] and I was put up there.” This is how it is supposed to go, and the congratulations and honors that are supposed to be bestowed on a player whose dream is coming true. “It was great,” Walden said, “except the issue was I never played.”
In the history recognized by Major League Baseball through to the moment this story is published, 23,522 players have been called up to the highest level of play and participated in at least one game for their team. A little bit deeper in the annals of baseball history, unrecognized by Baseball-Reference, FanGraphs, or Major League Baseball itself are the hundreds of players who were called up to the majors, wore their team’s uniform, had their names written on the lineup card, brought their families to the stadium, and spent at least one full game as an active player on the roster. The one catch, in this case, is that these players were never put into a game before being sent back down to the minors. Because of this, their status as a major leaguer exists in an odd in-between, a limbo of conflicting emotions and almosts. These phantom ballplayers made it to the pinnacle of the sport, but not quite across the threshold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Braves Coach In Hot Water Over Battle Of Gestures]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196238</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/braves-coach-in-hot-water-over-battle-of-gestures"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T15:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thing that the New York Yankees are doing is not sign-stealing. For one thing, it is entirely independent of the communications of their opponents, which raises it entirely above the board, according to both the rules and the traditions of baseball. For another, professional baseball no longer has signs for the swiping. A team could theoretically hack the PitchCom—the Houston Astros probably have a whole secured campus of evil nerds working on this opportunity—but until someone finally figures out how to bug one of those little suckers it will remain impossible to intercept and decode the signals between a catcher and a pitcher. 
Sign-stealing, among fans, was always considered a touchy, somewhat gray area of gamesmanship. Still, what the Yankees are doing would be considered at the honorable end of things even if it did involve decoding signals. They aren't being subtle about it at all: The guy on second base communicating the pitch selection to his teammate in the batter's box is doing everything short of holding up a gigantic poster. Against the Seattle Mariners, back on July 10, Trent Grisham and Cody Bellinger were gesturing so blatantly during New York's late comeback that a baseball non-knower might reasonably have deduced that they were doing aerobics out there. It was a delightfully elaborate system: First the runner on first base had to peek into the glove of Mariners reliever Andrés Muñoz and spot his grip, in the seconds before the pitch was thrown. They were on the lookout for sliders; when Muñoz's slider grip was identified, the runner on first had to then give a clear hand signal to the runner on second base, whose job was to relay this signal to the batter, in many cases as Muñoz was delivering the pitch. In order to pull it off, Grisham and then Bellinger resorted to what I think we can describe as an "inflated tube man" gesture, designed to be unmistakable for a batter whose attention is directed elsewhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trade Deadline Outlook: Kansas City Royals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=859389</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/07/trade-deadline-outlook-kansas-city-royals.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T15:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals are running out of time.  After starting the second half by losing two of three games to the Marlins, Kansas City is now 48-52, and 5.5 games back of the final AL wild card position.  While the club's recent transactions indicate that they're not ready to wave the white flag just yet, it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collective Amnesia]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196252</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/collective-amnesia"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T15:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump was good friends with the notorious sex trafficker Jeffrey Epstein for many years, the New York Times reported over the weekend, a friendship that included Trump hosting Epstein at "raucous parties with cheerleaders and models." The Times wrote that one "woman has said that Mr. Trump groped her when Mr. Epstein brought her to Trump Tower in Manhattan to meet him." Also: "Another accuser recalled being eyed by Mr. Trump during a brief encounter in Mr. Epstein’s office, and claimed that Mr. Epstein had told Mr. Trump at the time that 'she’s not for you.'"
Furthermore, the Times wrote:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, July 21: One By One]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196225</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-july-21-one-by-one"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T15:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you been counting down the days until our Monday crossword? This week’s puzzle was constructed by Daniel Hrynick and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Dan lives in Winnipeg, where he works as a laborer for Public Works. A commenter on his previous puzzle mentioned that they were disappointed that the clue for MOOG referenced the synthesizers and not Andy Moog. That comment was on his mind when he clued 1-Across in this puzzle.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE. Note that our submissions are closed through July 31.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Julian Alaphilippe Loses, Celebrates, And Learns To Smile About It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196200</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/julian-alaphilippe-loses-celebrates-and-learns-to-smile-about-it"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T14:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CARCASSONNE, France — It is hard to know what is going on in the Tour de France, even if your job is to work on the Tour de France. The end of every stage includes a familiar ritual, with team employees and journalists gathering around phones and tablets, squinting into the harsh sunlight to try and figure out what the hell is happening. The team cars on the road are listening to race radio—which, as I learned yesterday, can be imprecise—or watching the race on their phones in the car; I have heard anecdotes about team car drivers getting info relayed to them by colleagues watching the broadcast from home. That information desert enfolds for the riders, too. This truth was most harshly embodied by former French darling Julian Alaphilippe on Stage 15 of the Tour de France.
The Tour de France's 15th stage was unremarkable. Everyone was tired from three big days in the Pyrenees, and with a rest day approaching before a Mont Ventoux summit finish, the stage was the most obvious breakaway day in the roadbook. Both Visma and UAE even had riders in the day's big break, as nobody had the energy to spend on chasing them through a hot day in Occitanie. UAE breakaway specialist Tim Wellens, free from a day of Tadej Pogacar duty, slipped away from a small group on a long stretch of rolling road 44 kilometers from the finish and soloed his way in to complete his trilogy of Grand Tour stage wins. Ninety seconds later, Victor Campenaerts crossed the line for second, and he was followed eight seconds later by a large group of breakaway survivors. Watching at the Intermarché bus, we joked about Astana doing a full lead-out to secure maximum UCI points for third, because while it's a result worth sprinting for, it's not one anyone will remember.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NFL Players Association Is Falling Apart When It Needs Solidarity The Most]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196218</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-nfl-players-association-is-falling-apart-when-it-needs-solidarity-the-most"/>
        <updated>2025-07-21T13:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything about the NFL Players Association sludgeslide seems so predestined and unavoidable. The usual predicament has been made worse by disgraced former union chief Lloyd Howell getting confused about what side he works for and former president J.C. Tretter misunderstanding how work stoppages are supposed to happen, but for as lurid and goofy as the details have been, and with all due respect to the innovation of holding four-figure team-building exercises at a strip club, none of it quite qualifies as surprising. In the broadest sense, this is just the sort of thing that conflicted and ineffective unions do.
If only life in the labor trenches was as easy as the WNBPA makes it seem. They figure out what they want in a negotiation, slap it on a T-shirt, and have every member wear one; at WNBA All-Star Weekend, that message read "Pay Us What You Owe Us." The T-shirt is not the important part, though. The key here is the phrase "every member."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding Henri Rousseau]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196194</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/finding-henri-rousseau"/>
        <updated>2025-07-20T21:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can't remember exactly what I was thinking about when I first saw them. It was one of those summer days that was defined chiefly by its sprawl. I had spent the morning at the gym; every year my trainer holds a charity competition for his clients, and this year's was called Bench-A-Palooza. (Because I know our commentariat will ask: I went for reps and benched 95 pounds 14 times.) The ache in my arms hadn't set in yet, though that maybe had more to do with the drinks we'd all had afterwards, crowded onto wooden benches in the sunshine. I'd stayed longer than I'd planned to, and evening was approaching by the time I said my goodbyes and started my walk home with two of my best friends by my side. We meandered slowly, luxuriating in each other's presence. When our trio formed, we'd been young, and free enough to spend hours together every week. Now, these sorts of sidewalk chat were the norm: rarer, more precious.
So maybe that's what I was thinking about when I saw the Henri Rousseau prints, custom framed and matted as if they were waiting for me. Or maybe I was thinking about how empty my fridge was after two weeks of travel. Or how mad my cat Oliver would be because my sprawling, luxuriant summer day had left him without lunch. Whatever it was that I had been thinking left my head immediately upon seeing the prints; the jungle greens were rendered exuberantly enough to be recognizable from half a block away. I approached slowly, as surprised as the tiger that I'd later learn lends one of these paintings its name. Another of Rousseau's images came to mind, that of a woman and a lion in a moonlit desert. I have a miniature of that one stuck to my fridge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[39 Years Ago, Four Mets Fought The Cops At A Houston Bar Named Cooter’s]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196197</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/39-years-ago-four-mets-fought-the-cops-at-a-houston-bar-named-cooters"/>
        <updated>2025-07-20T20:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before the Mets' game against the Houston Astros on July 18, 1986, Tim Teufel passed out cigars in the team's locker room. The platoon second baseman was rejoining the team after staying behind in Connecticut to be with his wife while she gave birth to their first child. Teufel, who was by all accounts a stand-up guy, made for an odd cultural fit with a Mets team that would become legendary and was already renowned in that moment for high-intensity dirtbaggery; Jeff Pearlman's 2004 book about the team, The Bad Guys Won, revealed that Darryl Strawberry frequently bullied Teufel by calling him "Richard Head" until Teufel confronted him. "There’s a breaking point to every person in their pride and character and who they are," Teufel told Pearlman. "No man is going to just sit there and be a marshmallow." 
That Friday night, Teufel went hitless in three plate appearances in a Mets loss. Later that Friday night, after closing time and a couple of hours into Saturday, Teufel was beaten up by a bunch of Houston police officers outside of a bar called Cooter's Executive Games And Burgers; Ron Darling, who pitched seven strong innings in that loss, was thrown through a plate-glass door by another member of Houston's police department, and two other Met Cooter's patrons, Bobby Ojeda and Rick Aguilera, were also arrested. That happened around two in the morning on Saturday the 19th, and the players were held for 11 hours before being released on bond. This was a long time ago. Darling is in his 25th year as a television analyst; the former Cooter's is now a TJ Maxx parking lot; it has been a decade since the son whose birth Teufel stayed behind to witness wrapped up his five-year minor league career. But another way to know how long ago it was is that the news that four Mets players had been booked after fighting the cops didn't break until the next day—Sunday July 20, 1986.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Day Inside The Tour de France From The Neutral Service Car]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196169</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-day-inside-the-tour-de-france-from-the-neutral-service-car"/>
        <updated>2025-07-20T13:49:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BAGNERES-DE-LUCHON, France — As we descend off the back of the Col du Tourmalet, a fan clasps her hands to her head, mouth gaping in disbelief at our speed. Markus Hoelgaard nearly overcooks a wet corner and unclips to stabilize his balance at the last second, with our car and two motos bearing down on him a scant few meters behind. Alexey Lutsenko raises his hand to signal a problem with his front wheel, we pull over on a negative-eight percent gradient, and Kevin Poret pops out of the back seat with a fresh wheel. I time his work from the front seat: 21 seconds.
I spent the 2025 Tour de France's fourteenth stage inside the race, in the Shimano neutral service car. It's the closest I could have gotten to the racing without being on two wheels. A charming property of the Tour de France is that the closer you get to the action, the less of the race you'll see. Proximity has an inverse relationship with context. I wanted to see what it was like to have both, and to understand the work of the mechanics who are closer to the action than anyone. Luckily, I was able to do so on the hardest stage of the Tour's Pyrenean turn, a 182-kilometer beast with four categorized climbs, each of which has its own place in Tour de France lore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Art’s sake]]></title>
        <id>687abab118410e000135ae14</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-363/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T23:06:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nathan Munn knows what Art is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Taste of Creation]]></title>
        <id>687a67df18410e000135abfd</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-taste-of-creation/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T23:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a long time there was a small purple ice cream cone on the back of my phone, delicately crafted in a child's cross-hatch—a homemade sticker given to me by my nine-year-old daughter. Nestled in the cone, rather than a scoop of something delicious, was the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Munn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s No Longer Bills Week]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196096</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-no-longer-bills-week"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T21:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you just hear that loud noise? That was me banging the gavel on Bills Week. I'll do it again: Bang! Bills Week is now over.
Thanks for joining us during this year's theme week, and for your continued support of Defector. Catch up on any Bills Week posts you might have missed right here. And be sure to check out the exciting announcements we made this week, if you haven't already. Onward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Bill Paxton’s ‘Frailty,’ Certainty Is The Scariest Thing There Is]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196079</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/in-bill-paxtons-frailty-certainty-is-the-scariest-thing-there-is"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T21:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As he told the story, Bill Paxton came to the movies as a teenager more or less how all teenagers discover things: by being startled out of laziness by an urge and interest that they didn't expect. Paxton credited a challenging drama teacher at his Fort Worth high school for part of this, and the rest—the rest of the story, and a film career that unfolded over four decades, until Paxton's death at 61 in 2017—was a matter of chasing his urge to make something with his friends. Before he went to Hollywood, Paxton shot movies on Super 8 film with similarly film-obsessed Texas friends he met while studying abroad in England after high school. "We made films because we liked to blow stuff up," Paxton told Texas Monthly in 1997.
At the time, he was promoting Traveller, the first movie Paxton had produced after what was already a long career that began with his father finding him work as a set-dresser on Encyclopaedia Britannica educational films, Paxton finding his way into the orbit of exploitation film maestro Roger Corman, and parlaying his jittery charisma into gradually bigger roles. By 1997, Paxton had already spent more than a decade poised somewhere between character actor and star. The friends with whom Paxton had snuck around railroad tracks and movie theaters two decades earlier had credits on Traveller, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billie Marten’s Music Makes Loneliness A Thrill]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196041</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/billie-martens-music-makes-loneliness-a-thrill"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T20:49:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billie Marten's new record, Dog Eared, is a pretty major departure from her prior output. We do not hear a solo, cleanly produced acoustic guitar at any point on it. Our girl got an electric axe, a chorus pedal, a few more people, and did not look back. And I'm not judging! It's delightful. The record has the sound that tumbling down a flight of stairs in a Dr. Seuss book might have. It wants to maximize the whimsy found in its sadness, which requires a rather particular mindset. While the sound is quite different, Marten's writing typically conveys a loneliness that can rend your soul. Some people make music for being in bed with someone else. She makes music for being in bed all by yourself.
Back to me. The woman who introduced me to Billie Marten some years back did so while we were theoretically sharing a bed, though in hindsight I think I may have just been a way to get out of the house for her. She was living with her ex-boyfriend and his parents, but claimed to have seen the light and realized she was a lesbian. She told me (unprompted) that she wasn't ready to start a new relationship until she moved out of the house of the old one. Then she hit me up out of the blue a few months down the line to alert me that she was now dating another man. I wish I could say that shit like this still fucked me up, but it doesn't really—not because I think being used to this sort of thing is bad or a sign of the times, but just because I really enjoy getting in my feelings every now and again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Bloom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaires Destroyed American News Media On Purpose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.todayintabs.com/p/billionaires-destroyed-american-news-media-on-purpose-7d91</id>
        <link href="https://www.todayintabs.com/p/billionaires-destroyed-american-news-media-on-purpose-7d91"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T19:59:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not a conspiracy, it's simply what happened.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rusty Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[William F. Buckley’s Bill Never Came Due]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196120</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/william-f-buckleys-bill-never-came-due"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T19:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps the highest praise I can offer a book that took 27 years to complete and runs over 1,000 pages is that I can see why, and that it doesn’t feel like it. Sam Tanenhaus’s extremely long and anxiously awaited biography of the man who founded National Review, and is often regarded as the architect of modern American conservatism, arrived with a resounding thud on my doorstep. There is no way that a book the size of Buckley: The Life and The Revolution that Changed America could arrive quietly. It is, in many ways, a remarkable accomplishment: exhaustive but not tiring, serious yet lively, both affectionate and suspicious. It is almost dizzyingly populated with recognizable characters—the result of Buckley’s famed and enormous social influence—which offers regular satisfaction both to readers who like knowing what Sylvia Plath thought of the Buckley family home, and ones who yearn to learn more about cranky Viennese ex-Leninists. Most of all, Buckley is very clearly the result of slow thinking and methodical research, which makes it precisely the sort of work that its subject could never produce. 
William F. Buckley Jr. went for quantity instead. He wrote dozens of books, including non-fiction and a bestselling series of spy novels, both of which were mainly dashed off while on skiing vacations in Gstaad. He also produced three columns a week for decades, generated prodigious written correspondence, and appeared in 1,504 episodes of Firing Line, all while editing the magazine and accepting regular speaking gigs. For years, Buckley promised to write a serious work of political theory—he managed to produce thousands of words railing against his liberal enemies, but was ultimately thwarted by his inability to offer a coherent elaboration of what conservatives were really about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Jensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Liams Week In Ireland]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196106</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-liams-week-in-ireland"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T18:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liam Gallagher won out over Liam MacCarthy. And so the All-Ireland hurling final, traditionally a fall classic, will be played this weekend at Croke Park in Dublin, as the hallowed Dublin stadium gears up for Oasis reunion shows. 
But seasonal shift or no, Cork vs. Tipperary promises to be a supernova of a tilt, and the toughest ticket in town, notwithstanding the upcoming concerts from the reunited Manchester band, led by Liam and Noel Gallagher. This is a mashup of historic hurling powerhouses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bills Players Among Many In Need Of New Union Head]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196086</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bills-players-among-many-in-need-of-new-union-head"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T18:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a month of controversy, Lloyd Howell Jr. resigned from his post as the NFL Players Association executive director on Thursday night, effective immediately. “It’s clear that my leadership has become a distraction to the important work the NFLPA advances every day,” Howell wrote in a statement announcing his decision. “I hope this will allow the NFLPA to maintain its focus on its player members ahead of the upcoming season.”

https://twitter.com/NFLPA/status/1946037991035613238?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1946037991035613238%7Ctwgr%5Ef02c3db0e23267b55144cb4a17ab3cd5d060ec01%7Ctwcon%5Es1_c10&ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2Fathletic%2F6501428%2F2025%2F07%2F17%2Fnfl-nflpa-union-lloyd-howell-steps-down%2F]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Brains Will Be Cooked Until Further Notice]]></title>
        <id>68792501bc051b000154f230</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/the-brains-will-be-cooked-until-further-notice/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T18:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can't be afraid of social media rules and regulations forever. It's the only way to dismantle the right's unreality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just What You Wanted: A Bill Belichick TV Show]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196040</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/just-what-you-wanted-a-bill-belichick-tv-show"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T17:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Belichick, aging boyfriend to emerging media mogul Jordon Hudson, will be the subject of an upcoming Hulu docuseries, per reporting by Front Office Sports.
Back in March, HBO, NFL Films, and the University of North Carolina were working out a deal to make Belichick's Tar Heels football team the focus of a season of the Hard Knocks series. That deal reportedly fell through very late in the process, with Belichick insisting, unconvincingly, that there was never much mutual interest. "The Hard Knocks thing, you know, like, just for the record, Hard Knocks is training camp,” Belichick told The Pivot Podcast, in May. “And we’re not training camp. We’re just not. That’s not what we are. You know, the drama of training camp, the who’s gonna cut and all that. Like, we’re a season, and they don’t want that." The New York Times reported days later that NFL Films kiboshed the deal not over anything having to do with the inherent drama of training camp, but because Hudson—who at 24 years old is less than a third the age of her doddering old lover—demanded content approval and "partial ownership of the show."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Veeck’s Goofy, Gag-Filled Baseball Book Was Ahead Of Its Time]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195806</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bill-veeck-goofy-gag-filled-baseball-book-was-ahead-of-its-time"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T17:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What I knew of the eccentric baseball owner Bill Veeck, I knew only from stray web searches at White Sox games. What was a shower stall doing on the concourse? What are those pinwheel things above the scoreboard? While the trainer came out to check on Yoan Moncada or the pitching coach asked Michael Kopech to throw strikes, the answers to these questions were easy to find, read, and forget. Usually the research never went much further; my curiosity is no match for bad ballpark WiFi and dwindling phone battery. And usually, Michael Kopech continued to not throw strikes.
Last summer, Veeck popped up on my phone again for a different reason. On a slow news day in Chicago, he was the subject of a heated sports talk radio rant: The just-hired White Sox play-by-play guy had mispronounced his name.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atrocious England-Sweden Penalty Shootout Has Wild Bill Hickok Turning Over In His Grave]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=196015</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/atrocious-england-sweden-penalty-shootout-has-wild-bill-hickok-turning-over-in-his-grave"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T16:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While watching the Euros quarterfinal between Sweden and England with an eye toward covering it, I kept changing my mind on what to write about. This is a side effect of my job and my brain, both of which combine to help me begin to see narratives as soccer matches burn through their allotted time. Some matches are straightforward in this way: One team controls the game and takes the win, and isn't that just the most boring thing to write about? Others, though, rocket between extremes, making it almost impossible to pre-write, even in my mind, what I'm going to take away from a match. Those are fun, I enjoy the challenge. There is, however, a third kind of match, unique to knockout soccer, in which penalty kicks arrive and suddenly, everything I had thought over 120 minutes of play gets thrown out the window, and all you are left with is picking up the pieces of a shootout. Sweden-England was, unequivocally, that third type of match.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iBKz8GPFj44]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will A Will Ever Become A Bill?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195937</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/will-a-will-ever-become-a-bill"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T16:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I do not usually have a fear that my friends will change, in whatever facets they may. Change is just an inevitable, wonderful part of getting older. There is, however, one exception: I have recently developed a fear that my friend Will, whom I have known since middle school, will eventually become a Bill, and as such, I will have to refer to my friend Will as "Bill." This fear has led me to realize that I don't know much about the machinations of the William Nickname League.
My family only ever uses my English name in the third person, so any nicknames on Kathryn in my life have arisen out of some sort of contrivance with my friends. As a side effect, you can figure out when and how someone came to know me by how they refer to me. Will, like Kate or Joe, can be a given name but generally is a nickname—specifically a hypocoristic, a shortened form without a diminutive suffix (-ie or y or whatever). How does one become a Will from, presumably, William? (I think about names a normal amount.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2025 Replacement-Level Killers: Designated Hitter]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=468274</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/the-2025-replacement-level-killers-designated-hitter/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T16:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Closing out the annual series with a look at contenders who could really use an extra bat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Jaffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Nye Isn’t Fun Anymore]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195470</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bill-nye-isnt-fun-anymore"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T15:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before Bill Nye was a Science Guy, he was the pride of Seattle. Shit, he was Seattle, in many senses. He worked as an engineer for Boeing, yet harbored delusions of grandeur—first of being an astronaut despite not being a deranged military test pilot, and later, even more embarrassingly, of being a successful comedian. In 1986, he met John Keister after an open mic, which would lead to his first television role. Almost Live. Almost Live! was a Seattle-area sketch comedy show which would air either directly before or after SNL. It really can't be overstated how big of a deal Almost Live! was in Seattle. You talk to anyone in the area over a certain age, and they have a favorite bit.
I'm a little too young to remember watching Almost Live! live, but I do still have a favorite. "COPS in [Seattle neighborhood]" was a recurring sketch lampooning the show COPS and Seattle, but it is also a near-perfect time capsule. Here is "COPS in Wallingford," with Keister patrolling the neighborhood that neighbors the university and was the home of many of the town's artsier types:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Bloom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feral Belgians, Superfan Gendarmes, And Tattered Cyclists At The Tour de France’s First Summit Finish]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195828</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/feral-belgians-superfan-gendarmes-and-tattered-cyclists-at-the-tour-de-frances-first-summit-finish"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T15:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HAUTACAM, France — "Fuck, what a shit birthday," Laurence Pithie gasps. The Kiwi rider from Red Bull has just summited the Hautacam, a winding, rolling, and, today, infernally hot Pyrenean climb that takes roughly 40 minutes. A better verb for what he did might be survived, as he finished 63rd, more than 31 minutes behind the winner, and he is currently stuffing his jersey full of ice. I ask him how old he is turning (23) and wish him a happy birthday. In response I receive the most venomous "Thank you" of my life.
"Shit birthday" is a great, punchy descriptor for 2025 Tour de France's first climbing day: a party that drives you mad. The gathered thousands love it; the riders, not as much. As we'd threaded our way up the Hautacam amid clueless fans riding their bikes as if trying to get squished, children screamed at us and dirtbag French guys squirted water into my open window. My comrades and I are denied turns on a luge ride reserved for VIPs. Riders cross the finish line excreting and then gulping various salts and are swarmed by TV cameras. Jonas Vingegaard nearly runs me over seconds after finishing. Emmanuel Macron has flown to the top of the Hautacam in a helicopter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Hall Put It Together]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195381</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bill-hall-put-it-together"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T13:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of every baseball career, everyone is pretty much guessing. From a certain perspective, the work of that career amounts to generating enough information—filling out the back of a baseball card, coloring in a Savant page, being transacted upon in the ways that baseball players are—that it can all be evaluated in the end. That is not my perspective, personally, but it is very much a purpose that baseball has served for some of those who are served in some way or another by caring about the game. A career is a career, it's a life in the sport, but it is also both an accumulation of evidence and a story told all the way through to a conclusion. They all end, and a striking number of the illustrious ones end in the same way as the more prosaic ones, with one or two or three last thwarted tries to see if that's really everything there was to find or know.
But at the beginning, no one knows very much at all. Teams drafting or signing amateur players do so based on information that, for all the ways in which the process has been smoothed and sharpened by technology over time, is necessarily incomplete. The statistics don't really mean very much; potential Major Leaguers are sufficiently different from the people they play baseball against even in college that their statistics often wind up so outsized that they're impossible to parse. This can be as true for a high school player who hits .575 against other teenagers who will never play another meaningful baseball game in their lives as it is for an SEC pitcher who gets drafted despite putting up an ERA in the mid-sevens. Teams, or anyway smarter and more ambitious teams, tune the numbers out, or just down. The other stuff is what matters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are The Epstein Files, And How Much Should You Care About Them?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195889</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-are-the-epstein-files-and-how-much-should-you-care-about-them"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T13:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have once again noticed that a lot of people on TV, the internet, and in your real life are talking about files. The Epstein files. They want them released! They want Donald Trump in jail! They want to know what the hell is going on! Seriously, though, what the hell is going on?
As Defector's chief file-explainer, I am here to once again tell you all you need to know about the latest files.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trading in fluids / Dealing in lives]]></title>
        <id>6876c3ccefa3900001458b36</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-362/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T01:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arwa Mahdawi brings news from Gaza; Jennie Rose Halperin faces family secrets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Price of Survival]]></title>
        <id>687149aed2c01800010a17d4</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/the-price-of-survival/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T01:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liza and Adam, my grandmother’s best friends and neighbors, used to tell a dramatic—if somewhat vague—story about their lives in World War II. In their telling, Adam had jumped off a cattle car heading to Auschwitz in late 1944 and fought his way through]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennie Rose Halperin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pregnant Women in Gaza Are Selling Urine to Survive]]></title>
        <id>6871755dd2c01800010a186c</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/pregnant-women-in-gaza-are-selling-urine-to-survive/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T01:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been over 21 months since Israel started its genocidal campaign in Gaza. Most of the region has been turned into rubble, and into a mass grave. And still our elected officials are cheering it on. Lawmakers are not the only ones complicit in this genocide. Well-paid consultants]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arwa Mahdawi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HYDRANYM No. 8: Vote!]]></title>
        <id>68795d4418410e0001359808</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/hydranym-no-8-vote/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-18T01:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You are charged, esteemed comrades, with the solemn duty to select, from among the 21 best entries received this week on the theme of
LETTERS 
the victor of Hydranym No. 8. 
HYDRANYM is the Creative Writing word game especially for Flaming Hydra subscribers. Please join in by subscribing! It’]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Bustillos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Aimless Suns Settle Bradley Beal’s Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195931</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-aimless-suns-settle-bradley-beals-bill"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T18:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, the Phoenix Suns agreed to a buyout of Bradley Beal's contract, ending a putrid era that amounted to very little. The team traded for Beal in the summer of 2023 to play alongside Kevin Durant, who was traded to Houston in June, and Devin Booker, the last one standing, having just signed an extension in Phoenix. Their skillsets were redundant, their chemistry depressing, and, despite their three salaries adding up to 107 percent of the salary cap in the 2024-25 season, they never won a single playoff game together.
Beal had reportedly been unhappy in Phoenix for a long time; since-fired coach Mike Budenholzer even yanked the guard out of the starting lineup for six weeks. But Beal's contract had a no-trade clause, narrowing the Suns' options for offloading him. The solution: a gigantic buyout. Per The Athletic, Beal was owed $110.8 million over the remaining two years of his contract. He agreed to forgo $13.8 million of it, and will see the remaining $97 million stretched over the next five seasons. Beal's agent Mark Bartelstein told ESPN that he took "intense conversations" to pull off the buyout; it's worth remembering that he was negotiating against his son Josh, who is the CEO of the Suns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hazards Of Bob Nutting Mindset, With Justin Halpern]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195867</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-hazards-of-bob-nutting-mindset-with-justin-halpern"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T18:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was a moment, near the end of my week-plus in Maine, when I could actually feel myself Becoming Normal again. The combination of relatively healthy activities, reduced screen-time, and a spike in omega-3 fatty acids due to increased seafood intake chipped some of the barnacles off my brain; detaching from the news cycle to some extent did the rest. I mention this not just to tell you how my vacation went, but because it was in listening to this episode that I realized how fleeting that moment truly was. We're back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calvin And Hobbes’s Gruesome Snowmen Were A World All Their Own]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195691</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/calvin-and-hobbess-gruesome-snowmen-were-a-world-all-their-own"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T17:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are only two pieces of media that have made me wistful for a small-town/suburban childhood I didn't have: A Christmas Story, and Calvin And Hobbes. Before you accuse me of specifically longing for the tract housing of Ohio, if I interrogate this a little further it turns out that what I really wanted was a yard. Because I wanted to shoot a BB gun at imaginary bandits like Ralphie did, and, like Calvin, I wanted to build demented snowmen.
Bill Watterson knew, or at least captured better than anyone, the private derangement of the average 6-year-old boy. Imagination is one thing: Monsters lived under the bed, dinosaurs roamed the Earth, teachers were misshapen alien monsters in disguise, Tracer Bullet charges $50 per day plus expenses. But somewhere beyond those fairly standard fantasy worlds lies the grisly id of the artist, and the snow is his canvas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2025 Replacement-Level Killers: Left Field & Right Field]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=468176</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/the-2025-replacement-level-killers-left-field-right-field/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T16:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A supersized list of teams struggling for production at one outfield corner — or both.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Jaffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do Flamingos Eat So Weird?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195570</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-do-flamingos-eat-so-weird"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T16:39:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2019, Victor Ortega Jiménez was visiting the Atlanta zoo with his family when he became mesmerized by a flock of Chilean flamingos. The flamingos were feeding, their long necks squiggled into the water and flat feet stomping in a kind of dance. Ortega Jiménez noticed the flamingo heads produced capillary waves, concentric ripples on the water's surface. "What is happening inside of the water?" he wondered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Wild’s Offseason Has Been Pretty Tame]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195825</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-wilds-offseason-has-been-pretty-tame"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For Bill Guerin, who's been GM of the Minnesota Wild since 2019, the beginning of this month must have felt like finally taking off an extremely tight pair of pants after a very long day. As a consequence of the team buying out both Zach Parise and Ryan Suter, they were stifled by three years of salary cap weight totaling over $10 million annually. That burden severely limited the Wild's ability to build around superstar winger Kirill Kaprizov, particularly in a 2023–24 campaign where his 46 goals went to waste without even a playoff appearance. Now, however, the impact of the Parise and Suter contracts is negligible on Minnesota's finances, so Guerin is free to do deals without those 30x30 skinny jeans crushing his waist. The results? Well, actually, not that much so far.
The one thing you need to know, if you want to know anything about the Minnesota Wild, is that they are the most "slightly above average" franchise in the history of the NHL. Dating back to 2013, they have missed the postseason only twice. But in that time, they have won exactly two playoff series, and none since 2015. Their regular seasons are usually pretty solid, but time and again they get walloped in a best-of-seven. By the time trophies are being polished, nobody anywhere is thinking about the Wild.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How ‘Kill Bill’ Changed The Action Blockbuster]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195534</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-kill-bill-changed-the-action-blockbuster"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T15:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's face it, we have been living through a pop cultural age—particularly in cinema—made in Quentin Tarantino's image. Before Marvel, before George Lucas sold Star Wars to Disney, Tarantino made nerd culture mainstream, showing that a movie- and culture-obsessed kid could bring that obsession to life in their own art, to great success.
Tarantino wasn't the only one, of course. He was part of a generation of auteurs who were the right age to have grown up watching TV their whole lives, who made post-modernist art that seemed to be just as much a commentary on the things they consumed as they were new and unique works in their own right. Tarantino was just the first one to hit the jackpot, emerging in the early '90s with a showy directorial debut Reservoir Dogs and two buzzy scripts eventually adapted by big-name filmmakers Tony Scott and Oliver Stone. Then in 1994 he cemented his place at the front of this new wave with Pulp Fiction, one of the finest independent films of the decade, a cultural earthquake that is still felt to this day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cultural Capitulation]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195493</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cultural-capitulation"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T15:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was originally published on the author's Substack on June 24. It has been republished here in conjunction with Bills Week. 
Everybody knows about the MAGA hat. It’s red. It says what it says on it. The content of the MAGA hat is obvious. It’s a team hat, a cult uniform, a panting, sniveling dare for you to say something about it. It is, for better or worse, iconic at this point, the single image or object that exemplifies this movement, the illustration that will appear in future history books so long as Elon Musk hasn’t had Grok “rewrite the entire corpus of human knowledge” by then. But its iconicity is not just limited to its color and its catchphrase. The FORM of this hat matters, in part because it’s such a telling one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Maciak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Should Never Argue With A Crazy M-M-Music Club]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195882</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/you-should-never-argue-with-a-crazy-m-m-music-club"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T14:27:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You oughta know by now: This is Defector Music Club, where a number of our writers get together to dish about an album. Today, in honor of Bills Week, Dave McKenna, David Roth, and Lauren Theisen debate Billy Joel's 1977 smash The Stranger.
McKenna: Stunning how few rock and roll Bills are out there! But Lauren’s suggestion that we take up Billy Joel and The Stranger took me back. Everything takes me back at this age, sure, but this record hit the bins at the end of the Summer of 1977, which I spent with my cousins in Astoria, Queens, when my feelings for Billy Joel were their fondest. I was into guitars and dirtball rock. The only keyboard guys I gave my time to were bombastic longhair prog rockers with walls of organs and synths, like Rick Wakeman of Yes or Keith Emerson of Emerson, Lake and Palmer. (This nostalgia wave got me to dig out the Yes belt buckle I bought on Steinway Street in Astoria for $5 that summer.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Inspiring Soccer Odyssey Of The Man They Call Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195592</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-inspiring-soccer-odyssey-of-the-man-they-call-bill"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T13:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To call it a "pleasant surprise" wouldn't quite be right. As someone with an abiding interest in the colorful names and nicknames of Brazilian athletes—my all-time favorite remains that of Leandro Matos Souza, who went by "Gatorade"—I had a hunch that a particular theme week–inspired Google search would turn up the result I was hoping for. So, while certainly pleasant, it was hardly surprising that typing "bill footballer" into my search bar brought me to not one, but two mononymous Brazilian Bills.
Though I'm sure the player Wikipedia designates "Bill (footballer, 1999)" has an interesting story of his own, today we are going to focus on the life and times of one Rosimar Amâncio, the better known of the two Bills. Our chosen Bill is a 41-year-old striker who has traversed the globe in one of those far-flung journeyman careers that are pretty unique to a certain class of Brazilian player. Brazil not only produces more professional-caliber soccer players than any other country, but the nationality itself, with its redolence of jogo bonito and World Cup wins and flashy tricks and Pelé and Romário and Ronaldinho and Neymar and the like, means that the Brazilian player is highly coveted globally both for what they can do and for what they represent. Couple that with the Brazilian economy, which is relatively advanced but nevertheless struggles to provide a comfortable living for its entire population, and you can understand why it's so common to find a handful of Portuguese names on the rosters of tertiary soccer leagues the world over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Remember Some Bills]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=195785</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lets-remember-some-bills"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T13:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Buffalo Bills of my childhood are not the Buffalo Bills I live with now. They are certainly not the Buffalo Bills I’ve written about before on this website.
It’s weird to think about in retrospect. The Bills went from clockwork ineptitude to clockwork competence with only a handful of transition years in the middle, from the team I finally saw suit up for a playoff game when I was 19 years old to the team that has won five division titles in a row. From the basement to the top of the league.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Zeller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trade Season Comes in Like a Lamb]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=468145</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/trade-season-comes-in-like-a-lamb/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T13:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're giving up nothing to upgrade a position of weakness, make sure you're actually upgrading the position and actually giving up nothing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Baumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Norms Respecters Have To Be Stopped]]></title>
        <id>68780216bc051b000154ec20</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/the-norms-respecters-have-to-be-stopped/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T12:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What will it take for liberals to see there is no returning to political norms?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fragile refuge]]></title>
        <id>68781c5518410e00013582ae</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-361/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T00:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan M. Katz remembers the Hotel Oloffson, Port-au-Prince]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Lost Haven in Haiti]]></title>
        <id>6877ef5418410e0001358148</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/a-lost-haven-in-haiti/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-17T00:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was a place in Port-au-Prince called the Oloffson. It housed a nearly century-old hotel, but it was more than that. Earlier this year, amid the spiraling gang war that has seized almost all of Haiti’s capital, the hotel’s enigmatic last owners, Richard and Lunise Morse,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan M. Katz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>