<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-10-22T10:16:41.431Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Firm Sets The Record Straight On Layoffs — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076466</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/biglaw-firm-sets-the-record-straight-on-layoffs-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T23:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goodwin Is Watching Fishbowl & Reddit: And they're setting the rumors straight on layoffs.
Reconsider Studying At Harvard: Law students get in trouble for having a study group. This is what we're calling a protest now?
That's Some Expensive Parchment!: SNL has a recommendation on how to use your JD. I would avoid it.
Judge Cleans Up DeSantis's Stupidity: Maybe one day he'll understand how the First Amendment works.
Does Any Competent Lawyer Care?: World's richest goofball really could use some help.
The post Biglaw Firm Sets The Record Straight On Layoffs — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offhand Lie About Central Park 5 Lands Trump Back In Legal Trouble]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076464</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/offhand-lie-about-central-park-5-lands-trump-back-in-legal-trouble/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T23:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He is really good at being demonstrably wrong in public! 
The post Offhand Lie About Central Park 5 Lands Trump Back In Legal Trouble appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The City That’s The Exception To The Biglaw Lateral Partner Hiring Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076462</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-city-thats-the-exception-to-the-biglaw-lateral-partner-hiring-boom/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lateral party missed this city.
The post The City That’s The Exception To The Biglaw Lateral Partner Hiring Boom appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet The First-Ever Openly Transgender Lawyer To Argue Before SCOTUS]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076427</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/meet-the-first-ever-openly-transgender-lawyer-to-argue-before-scotus/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T21:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations on this outstanding accomplishment.
The post Meet The First-Ever Openly Transgender Lawyer To Argue Before SCOTUS appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: KC Mavericks claim a demanding victory over Wichita in home-opener]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857023</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-kc-mavericks-claim-a-demanding-victory-over-wichita-in-home-opener/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T21:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City Mavericks versus Wichita Thunder on Saturday, Oct. 19, 2024. // Photo by Eli Ralls The Kansas City Mavericks take down the Wichita Thunder 5-2 in home-opener of the ECHL 2024 Season on Saturday, Oct. 19. The boys in orange and white wasted no time getting the goals rolling this season, scoring their first of the game in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Ralls</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So Much For Free Speech: Harvard Law Students Punished For Reading Together At Campus Library]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076445</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/so-much-for-free-speech-harvard-law-students-punished-for-reading-together-at-campus-library/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T20:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even study groups are complex now. 
The post So Much For Free Speech: Harvard Law Students Punished For Reading Together At Campus Library appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Played Pretend In A McDonald’s I Once Knew Intimately]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170996</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/donald_trump_mcdonalds_feasterville_playing_pretend"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T20:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I will admit that it has shaken me to my very core, or at least to the point where I have not been able to get through a post that was supposed to be mostly jokes. On Sunday, Donald Trump went to a McDonald’s in Feasterville, Pa., that I have previously visited plenty of times, a McDonald’s just down from the restaurant where my high school girlfriend worked. (That restaurant is now an AutoZone.)
Trump was there for a photo op designed to push the story, which has been a favorite among the sort of people that would like this kind of thing, that Kamala Harris never worked at McDonald’s. Though there’s no record of that gig—paper short-term employment records from 1983 wouldn’t have been kept, I am forced to explain seriously—the Washington Post writes that McDonald’s “accepts” that Harris worked there. Trump's stunt was obviously a bit of pointless political theater; Trump was there for a photo op that would be considered embarrassing were it done by anyone else on the planet but the planet’s most embarrassing man. It was nonetheless covered pretty straightforwardly by the media, as they tend to do with Trump. He pretended to be a McDonald’s employee for 15 minutes; many news outlets used a headline that he “worked” there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Jayhawks try to turn season around with win over Houston at Arrowhead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856552</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-jayhawks-try-to-turn-season-around-with-win-over-houston-at-arrowhead/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T20:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas Jayhawks versus Houston Cougars on Saturday, Oct. 19. // Photo by Tarik Sykes The Jayhawks took over Arrowhead on Saturday, Oct. 19, as they clashed heads against the Houston Cougars. Both teams have underperformed this season, but KU comes out on top with a 42-14 win over the Texas school. Jalon Daniels and Devin Neal led the squad to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarik Sykes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conquering Conferences: The Art Of The Graceful Exit]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076299</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/conquering-conferences-the-art-of-the-graceful-exit/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T20:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knowing how to bow out gracefully is key to maintaining your social finesse.
The post Conquering Conferences: The Art Of The Graceful Exit appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEJAL PATEL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Temwa Chawinga shatters more records as Current breeze to victory on Saturday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856532</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-temwa-chawinga-shatters-more-records-as-current-breeze-to-victory-on-saturday/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T19:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KC Current versus San Diego Wave on Saturday, Oct. 19, 2024. // Photo by Tarik Sykes KC Current took down San Diego Wave in a dominant fashion on Saturday, Oct. 19, capping the game off with four goals scored, only letting up one in minute 88 of the match. The balls began flying into the back of the next in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarik Sykes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Rebukes DeSantis Admin: ‘It’s The First Amendment, Stupid.’]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076441</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/judge-rebukes-desantis-admin-its-the-first-amendment-stupid/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T19:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not 'speech,' it's 'sanitary nuisance!'
The post Judge Rebukes DeSantis Admin: ‘It’s The First Amendment, Stupid.’ appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SNL Nails The Dumbest Thing To Do With Your JD]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076446</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/snl-nails-the-dumbest-thing-to-do-with-your-jd/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T18:29:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Put your law degree to work -- but not like that.
The post SNL Nails The Dumbest Thing To Do With Your JD appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Southampton Is Too Stubborn For The Premier League]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171058</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/southampton-is-too-stubborn-for-the-premier-league"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T18:28:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Promotion from the Championship into the Premier League is a double-edged sword. On the one hand, it is the greatest financial boost in world soccer, one that can change a club's entire future. On the other, the clubs that make the trip into the top division often have to throw out everything that worked in the Championship in order to survive.
It's not too bold to say that teams reliant on possession in their chase for promotion must quickly adapt to playing without the ball against the Liverpools and Arsenals of the world. This is a lesson that Southampton is learning ever so painfully at the start of this season, and whether the club takes it to heart or not will likely dictate whether the Saints go marching back to the Championship next season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Judges Lays Into Biglaw Attorneys For Running Up Legal Bills]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076443</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/federal-judges-lays-into-biglaw-attorneys-for-running-up-legal-bills/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T17:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Benchslapped over an effort to 'gum up the works.'
The post Federal Judges Lays Into Biglaw Attorneys For Running Up Legal Bills appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bayern Munich Updates Colors to Comply With New German Accessibility Law]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82758</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/21/bayern-munich-updates-colors-to-comply-with-new-german-accessibility-law/soccer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T17:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[German Accessibility Improvement Act brings country's law into alignment with European Accessibility Act and includes guidelines on contrast ratio between colors on digital platforms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mets Ran Out Of Magic]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170974</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-mets-ran-out-of-magic"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T17:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's no percentage in being right about a baseball team you care about. It's nice to feel smart, I guess, but "feeling smart" and for that matter "being right" are not really what I got into any of this for. Those are for gamblers and pedants, and of all the reasons that have made me care about the New York Mets during my life—habit and family custom and various personality defects specific to me, including but not limited to stubbornness and fatalism and whatever it is that makes people bite their fingernails—it has never crossed my mind that doing so was somehow a reasonable thing to do.
In a sense, being right about the team you care about is the last thing a person would want. Again, pedants and gamblers will differ on this, but they're in it for different reasons. It fits, in a bleak sort of way, that those are the types of fans sports leagues seem to be selecting for, or actively trying to create; owners, being owners, would naturally prefer that their fans be consumers instead of ... whatever this other way of caring is. The consumer relationship is easier to produce and reproduce, and much more readily leveraged. It reflects the way in which owners and executive types understand more or less everything, but also it makes a sort of pragmatic sense. It is easier to understand a baseball team as an expensive entertainment product that generates revenue on various platforms than it is as a machine that helps people become insane in ways of their choosing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Biglaw Firm Shuts Down Layoff Rumors By Issuing Statement On Fishbowl, Reddit]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076428</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/goodwin-shuts-down-layoff-rumors-by-issuing-statement-on-fishbowl-reddit/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T17:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contrary to what you may have heard, there are no layoffs going on at Goodwin right now. 
The post Top Biglaw Firm Shuts Down Layoff Rumors By Issuing Statement On Fishbowl, Reddit appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If You Must Gamble, Gamble In Person, Like An Adult]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170863</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/if-you-must-gamble-gamble-in-person-like-an-adult"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again it is time for the Defector staff to go into seclusion for our annual company meetings and fall frolic. This year we are gathering in Atlantic City, America's abandoned playground. We decided to hold a mini theme week to keep the site robust and full of blogs while we're in meetings. This year's theme: Risk!
As a general rule, risk is overrated, both as a spur to future success and as a general way of life. The myth that risk begets reward has always been a self-aggrandizing lie told by the ones who won and stood on the skulls of the ones who didn't. The thought that risk is an excellent provider of adrenaline is actually provable nonsense. Risk, put simply, sucks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Notes]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170985</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/programming-notes-6"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello. Prepare to receive precious information. This week, the staff of Defector is once again gathering in a secret location to hold our all-company meetings. We are not going to the woods this year. Instead, we are going somewhere awful, because we are stupid. You know the drill by now. Due to these meetings, we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Liberty Were Built, Bought, And Blessed]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170999</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-liberty-were-built-bought-and-blessed"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a relief when it all ended: An ugly overtime. A straight-up bad Game 5. A gripping Finals series. The greatest, noisiest WNBA season in memory. And for the New York Liberty, winners of their first-ever championship on Sunday night, a decades-long tradition of heartbreak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Needs People Who Care About Him… And Have Law Degrees]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076437</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/elon-musk-needs-people-who-care-about-him-and-have-law-degrees/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk's new voter registration lottery is... certainly not what a lawyer would recommend.
The post Elon Musk Needs People Who Care About Him… And Have Law Degrees appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep Them Coming: Familiar Stranger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851106</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/keep-them-coming-familiar-stranger/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kristen Thomas // Photo by Nicole Bissey Role-play serves as a gateway between imagination and desire. Your brain is your biggest sex organ, so role-play offers a way to use it to build a highly erotic encounter. Whether you’re in a relationship and you two (or more) work together to formulate a playful time, or you’re single and turning to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristen Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Thomson Reuters Supercharged CoCounsel With Gen AI Advances [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076356</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/how-thomson-reuters-supercharged-cocounsel-with-gen-ai-advances/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T15:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CoCounsel 2.0 is a faster, more integrated, and smarter AI legal assistant.
The post How Thomson Reuters Supercharged CoCounsel With Gen AI Advances appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Took A TikTok Class. What Happened Next Blew My Mind]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170900</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-took-a-tiktok-class-what-happened-next-blew-my-mind"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T15:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inside me there are two wolves. The first is super embarrassed to admit that I paid lots of money to an influencer to teach me how to make TikToks this summer. The only thing less cool than putting effort into your social media presence is paying someone to teach you how to put effort into your social media presence. The second wolf is the one who writes this column, who is curious about the way the attention economy has led many of us to commodify our identities online, the way that commodification can translate directly to money, and how requisite it's all starting to feel.
Parasocial appeal is the core of what constitutes success on the internet right now. Are you able to convey your personality in such a condensed way that strangers feel like they know you, and even like you? Can you quickly tell the story of who you are through videos and images? It’s harder than it looks. If you don’t believe me, open up your front-facing camera right now and try recording yourself telling a funny story. Now, hit post. It’s miserable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thirteen Times Athletes Wore Typos on their Uniforms]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82753</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/21/thirteen-times-athletes-wore-typos-on-their-uniforms/featured/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T15:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typos on Jerseys? It happens! Here's a look at thirteen times players wore spelling errors during an actual game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Creamer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Oct. 21: Sub-liminal Messages]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171033</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-oct-21-sub-liminal-messages"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T15:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Man cannot live by bread alone, but maybe he can live by crosswords alone. This week's puzzle was constructed by Malaika Handa and Stephen Lurie, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Malaika has been publishing crossword puzzles since 2021, and currently contributes to Vulture's daily puzzle. Stephen has been publishing crossword puzzles since *checks calendar* October 21, 2024. You can find both of them in Brooklyn, where this puzzle will be financing a tasty treat.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Impossible Question Each For Harris And Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076424</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/one-impossible-question-each-for-harris-and-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T14:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You could ask Trump or Harris hard questions in interviews, but you'd never hear an answer. 
The post One Impossible Question Each For Harris And Trump appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Herrmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let Me Push The Win Button]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170998</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/let-me-push-the-dodgers-win-button"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T14:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear the Dodgers,
I saw that you have a Win Button, a button that Dodger Stadium music director/organist Dieter Ruehle hits when you win. This button is intriguing to me.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: At least there are some rain chances (MON-10/21)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3703246</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-at-least-there-are-some-rain-chances-mon-10-21/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T14:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's going to be another warm and breezy day for late October, with average highs in the mid-60s. Today, we will easily exceed those values as highs soar to around 80° or so before the end of the afternoon. While the records are in the 89° range for highs, and we won't get close to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedge Fund Manager Suggests Index Funds If You’d Like To Make Some Money]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076417</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/10/hedge-fund-manager-suggests-index-funds-if-youd-like-to-make-some-money"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T14:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As long as it lasts, because David Einhorn's sure as hell not gonna make any for the foreseeable future.
The post Hedge Fund Manager Suggests Index Funds If You’d Like To Make Some Money appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[History Is For The Dead And The Boring]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170976</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dodgers-yankees-world-series"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T13:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lots of fans can claim to be "long-suffering" as a labeling fetish, even if they aren't. New York Liberty fans, for instance, were long-suffering—until Sunday night, when they cashed in their 28 years without a championship and transitioned into "deliriously smug, smugly delirious, and not even pissed at Sabrina Ionescu any more." It happens that fast. The previous almost-three decades notwithstanding, they got their money's worth, and then some.
And then there's this World Series, which is the dead opposite, and more's the pity. Nothing will leaden eyelids quite like listening to Yankee fans and Dodger fans grind on the rest of us civilians about their respective places on the double-decker throne, let alone their shared hearkening back to their joint heritage as the keepers of the sport back when baseball had not yet cracked the Pacific Time Zone. A nation already hopelessly fractured and ready to go even more Serb and Croat two Tuesdays from now can safely unite as one, however briefly, in our hatred of both teams. The prognosis wasn’t good regardless, but expect the next fortnight to be hell with a Bob Costas voiceover. Fox has the games, but it's not his voice that offends, you see; rather the subject matter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.21.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076423</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-21-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T13:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Former Biglaw partner sentenced to 16 months in prison. What's the matter number on that time? [ABA Journal]
* Prosecutor sues Georgetown over data breach in rare instance where a Georgetown graduate doesn't want everyone to know about it. [Reuters]
* With a new film out there about Trump's relationship with Roy Cohn, the Advocate has a deep dive into the famed lawyer's life and times. [Advocate]
* Oklahoma is asking the Supreme Court to force the federal government to give back funding for medical services that it withheld after Oklahoma declared that it wasn't going to allow those medical services. [Law360]
* Law school clinic working on Supreme Court case aimed at protecting the rights of... straight people? [Balls and Strikes]
* FTC's new merger rules exemplify ongoing fight within the agency. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Biglaw firms building out alumni programs. [American Lawyer]
The post Morning Docket: 10.21.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Overland Park Convention Center’s Executive Chef David Ruiz]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855565</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-overland-park-convention-centers-executive-chef-david-ruiz/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T13:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of David Ruiz Listen up, foodies—Kansas City just upped the culinary ante when the Overland Park Convention Center hired David Ruiz as the venue’s new executive chef. Ruiz—a James Beard Foundation competition winner—has quite the impressive culinary background. From Aspen to Albuquerque, he’s honed his craft working in several award-winning restaurants. He quips his style meets at the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crying Deshaun Watson Carted Off Field After Non-Contact Leg Injury]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170948</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/crying-deshaun-watson-carted-off-field-after-non-contact-leg-injury"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T19:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deshaun Watson's stomach-churning presence in the NFL appears to have been put on a long hiatus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Sharp Withdraws Name From Giants’ GM Search]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=827702</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/scott-sharp-withdraws-name-from-giants-gm-search.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T15:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Giants continue their search for a new GM to take over for Pete Putila and serve as Buster Posey’s second-in-command following his installation as president of baseball operations, The Athletic’s Ken Rosenthal reports that one name under consideration has withdrawn himself from the mix for the job: Royals assistant GM Scott Sharp, who…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Temwa Chawinga Has Conquered The NWSL]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170943</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/temwa-chawinga-has-conquered-the-nwsl"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T15:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How would you imagine the greatest individual season in NWSL history? Our hypothetical player would need to score a lot of goals, obviously. Breaking Sam Kerr's single-season scoring record (18) would certainly get plenty of attention, so let's put that at the top of the list. How about assists? Assists are important, too. Let's say this player has ... five of those. Five sounds good. 
Let's go back to the goals for a second. We know that all goals aren't created equal, and that poachers and penalty specialists can often sneak their way to the top of the leaderboard. That just won't do—we're talking about the best season in history, here—so let's make sure our player didn't score any of her goals from the spot, and is out-performing her expected goals tally by two. We need more, though. Let's get crazy and say that this player is an NWSL rookie, and arrived from Chinese Women's Super League at age 25 to blitz the NWSL with the league's first 20-goal season. We'll need a fun, quirky statistic, too, so let's say this player became the first in league history to score a goal against every team. And we need moments. Like, what if the record-breaking goal happened to be a 25-yard strike that makes a convincing case for being the hardest a soccer ball has ever been struck by a woman in a professional match? What if that goal looked something like this:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Yankees Have Power In All The Right Places]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170938</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-yankees-have-power-in-all-the-right-places"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T13:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The playoffs tend to provide certain reminders about how postseason baseball works. The Yankees, in completing their 4-1 series win over the Cleveland Guardians to advance to the World Series, provided one about the importance of power. Hit 10 home runs in five games, as the Yankees did in this series, and you can overcome all manner of base-running errors, scuffed defensive work, and late-inning meltdowns. Just keep hitting the ball over the fence, and good things will happen for you.
Here's another reminder: There is probably no hitter in baseball more terrifying to pitch to in a high-leverage situation than Juan Soto. The Yankees right fielder came to the plate in the top of the 10th inning, with the score tied 2-2, two men on base, and two outs. Soto was looking for a fastball from Hunter Gaddis, and he wasn't going to let the at-bat end until he got one. What must it feel like to pitch to a locked-in Juan Soto, who possesses not only all the confidence and power that makes for a great clutch hitter, but one of the games most discerning eyes. I imagine it feels like being asked to chop down a redwood with a hatchet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL Week 7 Uniform Schedule: Packers Debuting White Helmets, Steelers Wearing Throwback Uniforms]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82746</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/20/nfl-week-7-uniform-schedule-packers-debuting-white-helmets-steelers-wearing-throwback-uniforms/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T07:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our weekly series that looks at every uniform matchup across the NFL continues with the Green Bay Packers debuting their new white alternate helmets and the Pittsburgh Steelers wearing throwback uniforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arizona Wildcats To Wear Iconic Cactus Logo On Helmets For Homecoming]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82738</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/19/arizona-wildcats-to-wear-iconic-cactus-logo-on-helmets-for-homecoming/college/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T20:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Arizona football program will wear the iconic cactus logo that used to be displayed on the basketball court at the McKale Center on its helmets during Saturday's Homecoming matchup with Colorado.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Lynx And Liberty Are Getting Too Close For Comfort]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170930</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-lynx-and-liberty-are-getting-too-close-for-comfort"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T19:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS — Somehow, this will end, though your guess is as good as mine. In Game 4 on Friday night, the Lynx and Liberty arrived in a familiar place by unfamiliar means. Neither team bothered with the pretense of an early lead or deficit. This time, they played a game that from tip to buzzer felt true to the series: weird, tense, a matter of execution more than scheme. A Jonquel Jones layup and-one to even things up, 80-80, with a minute left, was the 13th tying score of the game. With 18 seconds left, the Lynx searching for a last shot, Bridget Carleton grabbed an offensive rebound and was fouled on the putback attempt. She made two free throws for a 14th and final lead change, 82-80. The WNBA’s two best teams head where they have long seemed destined, to a decisive Game 5 in New York on Sunday night. 
Lynx head coach Cheryl Reeve explained the game’s closeness in terms of “information gathered.” Game 5 will be the ninth time these teams have played each other this season, and the familiarity is starting to show. “Everything is getting harder,” Reeve said. “There’s no secrets at this point.” The teams’ de facto captains, products of the same college program and models of the league’s richness at power forward, pose identical matchup problems to each other. The lead guards can claim crowning moments. Last night, the two starting centers traded threes. Styles make fights, maybe, but never discount the thrill of a pointing Spider-Man series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offseason Outlook: Kansas City Royals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=827533</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/offseason-outlook-kansas-city-royals-14.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T15:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Royals added 30 wins relative to the prior season, going from 56 to 86 and sneaking into the playoffs for the first time since their World Series win in 2015. Now they'll go into the winter as clear contenders for the first time in a while, but still with lots of uncertainty ahead.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developments In Equity Partnerships! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076391</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/developments-in-equity-partnerships-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T23:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mergers Bring Rank Changes: Biglaw firm decides on all-equity partnerships.
That's One Way To Get Lawyer's Fees: Screwing the judge has its benefits.
Speaking Of Priming The Judge: Elon pushes X cases toward one of his gaveled Texan fanboys.
Can't Jump The Line On Justice: State Supreme Court justice caught trying to rush investigation on her husband.
Another One Shuts The Door: Skadden cuts ties with Shanghai.
The post Developments In Equity Partnerships! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not Exactly A Shining Example Of The Legal Profession]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076371</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/not-exactly-a-shining-example-of-the-legal-profession/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T23:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But he is entertaining.
The post Not Exactly A Shining Example Of The Legal Profession appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Trump & Harris Stand On Payers, AI, Drug Pricing, And CMS]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076336</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/10/healthcare-president/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T22:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts from BRG recently discussed the two presidential candidates' stances on key healthcare issues, including drug pricing, Medicaid, and AI.
The post Where Trump & Harris Stand On Payers, AI, Drug Pricing, And CMS appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KATIE ADAMS - MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Purdue Boilermakers To Wear New All-Black Uniforms Against Oregon Ducks]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82656</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/18/purdue-boilermakers-to-wear-new-all-black-uniforms-against-oregon-ducks/college/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T22:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Purdue will debut new all-black uniforms during Friday night's game against second-ranked Oregon, which kicks off at 8 p.m. ET on FOX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secrets To Success In Legal Tech Implementation]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076311</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-secrets-to-success-in-legal-tech-implementation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T21:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some lessons from the trenches.
The post The Secrets To Success In Legal Tech Implementation appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SUMI TROMBLEY AND BRIAN HUPP</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General Counsel Can’t Believe The Rate Hikes They’re Seeing From Biglaw Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076364</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/general-counsel-cant-believe-the-rate-hikes-theyre-seeing-from-biglaw-firms/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T20:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pricing variation across firms is confusing and 'utterly bewildering,' says an industry insider.
The post General Counsel Can’t Believe The Rate Hikes They’re Seeing From Biglaw Firms appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Throws Tantrum Over Nothing Burger Special Counsel Disclosures]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076393</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/trump-throws-tantrum-over-nothing-burger-special-counsel-disclosures/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T20:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the volume is stuck at 11.
The post Trump Throws Tantrum Over Nothing Burger Special Counsel Disclosures appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Supreme Court Justice Charged With Felonies For Trying To ‘Wrap Up’ Her Husband’s Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076368</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/state-supreme-court-justice-charged-with-felonies-for-trying-to-wrap-up-her-husbands-investigation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T20:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, that's not how spousal privilege is supposed to work. 
The post State Supreme Court Justice Charged With Felonies For Trying To ‘Wrap Up’ Her Husband’s Investigation appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Staff Chat Starts Now!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170909</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/staff-chat-starts-now"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T19:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well would you look at that, it's time for another Defector staff chat. We'll be hanging out in the comments section for the next hour or so, waiting to answer your questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Appealing Weekly Roundup]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076355</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/how-appealing-weekly-roundup-91/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T19:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The week in appellate news.
The post How Appealing Weekly Roundup appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOP AGs Argue States Have Compelling Interest In Getting Teen Girls Pregnant!]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076385</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/gop-attorney-general-teen-pregnancy-abortion/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T18:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abortion pill case continues and the GOP can't stop shooting itself in the foot.
The post GOP AGs Argue States Have Compelling Interest In Getting Teen Girls Pregnant! appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stat(s) Of The Week: That’s What I Want]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076314</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/stats-of-the-week-what-motivates-lateral-move/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T18:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The factors that prompt Biglaw lawyers to make a lateral move.
The post Stat(s) Of The Week: That’s What I Want appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vera Djordjevich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 5 Biglaw Firm Closes An Office, Conducts Layoffs Across China]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076353</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/top-5-biglaw-firm-closes-an-office-conducts-layoffs-across-china/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T17:43:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S.-based firms are still hightailing it out of China.
The post Top 5 Biglaw Firm Closes An Office, Conducts Layoffs Across China appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Candidates Have Nothing Left To Tell You]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170891</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-candidates-have-nothing-left-to-tell-you"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T17:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter, examining the apocalyptic politics and coverage of Campaign 2024.
"There are a lot of things that people want to learn about you and your policies," Bret Baier of Fox News said to Vice President Kamala Harris Wednesday. By that point, the interview segment between the Republican TV host and the Democratic nominee was nearly over; moments before, it had devolved into Baier saying "Hezbollah, Hamas, and Houthis" over Harris saying "'suckers' and 'losers.'"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Have To Read The Texts Uncovered In The Judge/ Biglaw Partner Romantic Scandal]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076350</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/you-have-to-read-the-texts-uncovered-in-the-judge-biglaw-partner-romantic-scandal/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T17:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['Talked to Jones. He’s got us.'
The post You Have To Read The Texts Uncovered In The Judge/ Biglaw Partner Romantic Scandal appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Anora’ Gets Lost In Its Own Excess]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170841</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/anora-gets-lost-in-its-own-excess"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T16:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At times, Anora comes across like a movie designed to attract the extremely online crowd, much in the same way as Charli XCX's Brat, or Greta Gerwig's Barbie, or the Safdies' Uncut Gems all did. It has all of social media's favorite thematic elements: sex work, wealth and excess, class commentary, hot people, "bisexual lighting," Tumblr-baiting images. It's hard not to feel a little cynical when a movie so readily, gleefully plays the hits, though perhaps that is the point—the late-millennial/Gen Z cheese to lure in that audience and trap them into its fable about the limits of transactional fantasies.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8m6UrWMl18M]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OHL’s Ottawa 67s to Celebrate Coach Kilrea’s 90th Birthday With Pair of Special Jerseys]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82727</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/18/ohls-ottawa-67s-to-celebrate-coach-kilreas-90th-birthday-with-pair-of-special-jerseys/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T16:42:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ontario Hockey League’s Ottawa 67s are bringing back a “killer” logo to celebrate a legendary head coach’s milestone birthday this weekend. The 67s will don two separate special edition jerseys on Sunday afternoon at TD Place to mark the 90th birthday of longtime coach Brian “Killer” Kilrea. They’ll wear]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teenage Grandmaster Christopher Yoo Booted From U.S. Championships, Arrested After Post-Loss Meltdown]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170798</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/teenage-grandmaster-christopher-yoo-booted-from-u-s-championships-arrested-after-post-loss-meltdown"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T16:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Saint Louis Chess Club announced Wednesday night that 17-year-old grandmaster Christopher Yoo had been expelled from the U.S. Chess Championships for "gross violations of our Code of Conduct and the U.S, Chess Safe Play Policy" after he crumpled up his scorecard, stormed off, and allegedly "struck a videographer from behind" following his fifth-round loss to Fabiano Caruana. Per local NBC station KSDK, the cops said that Yoo was arrested and charged with fourth-degree assault. They identified the victim as a 24-year-old woman and confirmed that Yoo was released as the case will be dealt with in the juvenile court system.
While Yoo's scorecard meltdown was captured on video, no recording of the full incident has been made public from which we can contextualize the somewhat vague verb "struck." This has prompted some players such as former World Championship challenger Ian Nepomniatchi to wonder whether Yoo getting fully booted from the tournament was an overreaction. That's a fair question—though, according to both KSDK and arbiter Chris Bird, Yoo outright punched the videographer, with Bird calling the punch "completely unprovoked, from behind and in no way accidental." Levon Aronian, currently competing in the championships, said he saw a video of the "awful" punch and called it a "well prepared punch to a completely innocent person."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Changes X Terms To Push All Disputes Toward Tesla-Investor Federal Judge]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076319</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/elon-musk-changes-x-terms-to-push-all-disputes-toward-tesla-investor-federal-judge/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T16:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you clicked 'accept' you agreed to a new courthouse.
The post Elon Musk Changes X Terms To Push All Disputes Toward Tesla-Investor Federal Judge appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Questions To Make Digital Vaults Your Competitive Advantage [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076294</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-questions-to-make-digital-vaults-your-competitive-advantage/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T15:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A law firm success checklist from our friends at Thomson Reuters. 
The post The Questions To Make Digital Vaults Your Competitive Advantage appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>THOMSON REUTERS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: So about that rain chance (FRI-10/18)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3700925</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-so-about-that-rain-chance-fri-10-18/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T14:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City will continue with a warming trend heading into the weekend with rain chances returning on Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newly Merged Biglaw Megafirm Moves To All-Equity Partnership Model, Adopts New Partner Pay System]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076337</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/newly-merged-biglaw-megafirm-moves-to-all-equity-partnership-model-adopts-new-partner-pay-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T14:46:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While many firms are introducing non-equity partnerships, this firm is going all in for all-equity.
The post Newly Merged Biglaw Megafirm Moves To All-Equity Partnership Model, Adopts New Partner Pay System appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are All the New Kits For the 2024-25 Men’s and Women’s A-League Seasons in Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82569</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/18/here-are-all-the-new-kits-for-the-2024-25-mens-and-womens-a-league-seasons-in-australia/soccer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T14:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A-League Men kicks off on Saturday, October 19, while A-League Women starts two weeks later; Auckland FC joins A-League Men as 13th team and second based in New Zealand]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Likely FCC Boss, Brendan Carr, Tries To Undermine Popular Infrastructure Bill Broadband Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076351</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/trumps-likely-fcc-boss-brendan-carr-tries-to-undermine-popular-infrastructure-bill-broadband-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T14:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[States are poised to receive $42.5 billion in broadband grants thanks to the 2021 infrastructure bill. While a lot of this money will be going to the usual entrenched monopoly incumbents, a lot of it is also going to a growing list of popular cooperatives, municipalities, and city-owned utilities to expand affordable fiber. This Broadband Equity Access and Deployment (BEAD) program is going […]
The post Trump’s Likely FCC Boss, Brendan Carr, Tries To Undermine Popular Infrastructure Bill Broadband Improvements appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Techdirt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Point/Counterpoint: Friday Night Playoff Games]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170836</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/point-counterpoint-friday-night-playoff-games"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T14:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Point: Friday playoff games are terrible, by Barry Petchesky
I sit here exhausted: glassy eyed, cotton-brained, every synapse a misery. I watched seven consecutive hours of baseball last night, most of them emotionally disastrous to my rooting interests. It kept me up several hours past my usual bedtime, and tossing and turning in much of my ostensible sleep. Today I feel like I got hit by a truck. I feel alive. This is how the postseason should feel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opponents of Missouri Abortion Rights Amendment turn to anti-trans messaging and misinformation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856478</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/opponents-of-missouri-abortion-rights-amendment-turn-to-anti-trans-messaging-and-misinformation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T13:59:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billboards undermining support for an abortion rights amendment and asking people to “vote no” have popped up around Missouri. // Photo illustration by ProPublica. Source image: Jeremy Kohler/ProPublica. The billboards have popped up along both Interstates 55 and 170 around St. Louis. They’re along I-70 between Columbia and St. Charles, in central Missouri. And there’s one across from a shopping...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Kohler, ProPublica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas voters signal measured support of abortion rights ahead of fall election in new survey]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856466</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kansas-voters-signal-measured-support-of-abortion-rights-ahead-of-fall-election-in-new-survey/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T13:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rose Conlon/Kansas News Service In the two years since the U.S. Supreme Court overturned Roe v. Wade, tens of thousands of women have traveled to Kansas seeking abortions that have become banned in their home states, according to estimates by multiple research groups. Missouri and Oklahoma banned the procedure with few exceptions, as did nearby Texas, Arkansas and Louisiana. A...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rose Conlon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Statewide candidates in Missouri run cheap campaigns while ballot measures spend heavily]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856457</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/statewide-candidates-in-missouri-run-cheap-campaigns-while-ballot-measures-spend-heavily/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T13:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lt. Gov. Mike Kehoe, left, and state Rep. Crystal Quade, the Republican and Democratic candidates for Missouri governor. As ballot measure campaigns fill the airwaves with seven-figure ad wars alongside Missouri’s U.S. Senate race, the state seems about to experience the cheapest campaign in years for other statewide offices. On Tuesday, Lt. Gov. Mike Kehoe, the Republican nominee for governor,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rudi Keller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.18.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076347</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-18-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T13:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* The rate increases will continue until morale improves. [American Lawyer]
* Indian foreign intelligence official charged with attempting to assassinate New York attorney. See... this is why you have to be careful about rate increases. [Law360]
* Just when you thought the "bankruptcy judge living with an attorney practicing before him" story couldn't get worse... this happens. [Bloomberg Law News]
* It turns out that, no, Ron DeSantis cannot threaten to prosecute TV stations for airing ads encouraging people to vote against his preferred ballot measure. [CNN]
* Man charged in the Trump golf course assassination plot asks Aileen Cannon to recuse herself on the grounds that Trump's incessant praise of her creates the appearance of impropriety. Her rulings in the documents case remove all doubt about the impropriety but he's showing respectful restraint. [Politico]
* Execution based on debunked science halted by Texas Supreme Court when a bipartisan group of state legislators sought to block the killing after the US Supreme Court shrugged on Thursday. [CBS]
* Former partner suspended for telling junior to lie to client. [Roll on Friday]
The post Morning Docket: 10.18.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The past, present, and future of cassette tapes from Maxell’s Kyle McCord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856016</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/the-past-present-and-future-of-cassette-tapes-from-maxells-kyle-mccord/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T13:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Maxwell A recent New York Times article, Marc Hogan’s “As Cassettes Come Back, the Dilemma Is Finding a Tape Deck,” makes the point that, “If Spotify killed the iTunes star, and vinyl is increasingly a high-priced luxury item — never mind CDs for the moment — then cassettes could be the cockroaches that outlive them all.” Last...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dodgers Lifehack: Just Don’t Chase, Dummy]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170833</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dodgers-lifehack-just-dont-chase-dummy"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T12:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Approaching José Quintana's pitching should be relatively straightforward: Do not chase. The man does not throw strikes. Only about 41 percent of his pitches in 2024 have been in the zone, which ranks dead last among all MLB pitchers who threw at least 1500 pitches last season. 
That is just about the most aggravating archetype of pitcher to watch mow through your team's lineup, but for all the readied complaints about plate discipline or sloppy hitting, suffering at the hands of Quintana was not a unique experience: Quintana had looked unhittable since late August. Clearly if the advice is, "Please stop chasing," looking at batters trying to hit against Quintana leads to the conclusion that it's not that easy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Nilüfer Yanya brings more than method acting to the Bottleneck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856299</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-nilufer-yanya-brings-more-than-method-acting-to-the-bottleneck/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T12:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nilüfer Yanya. // photo by Nick Spacek Nilüfer Yanya with Angélica Garcia and Lutalo The Bottleneck Sunday, October 13 Touring in support of her new album, My Method Actor, released last month via Ninja Tune, singer-songwriter/guitarist Nilüfer Yanya made a stop at the Bottleneck Sunday night. Richmond singer-songwriter Angélica Garcia and indie rocker Lutalo, touring in support of their Gemelo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Whitney Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gastonia fans choose Ghost Peppers after a season of what-ifs]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82662</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/17/gastonia-fans-choose-ghost-peppers-after-a-season-of-what-ifs/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T01:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The independent Gastonia Baseball Club, a North Carolina-based team in the Atlantic League of Professional Baseball, played the 2024 season in a series of seven potential identities, giving fans the chance to see them in action before voting for a permanent brand. That vote is in the books, and the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Caputo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Orleans Saints To Wear 1967-68 Throwback Uniforms On Thursday Night Football]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82701</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/17/new-orleans-saints-to-wear-1967-68-throwback-uniforms-on-thursday-night-football/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T23:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New Orleans Saints will wear their 1967-68 throwback uniforms during Thursday night's matchup with the Denver Broncos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Knew The Simpsons Were So Educational? — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076325</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/who-knew-the-simpsons-were-so-educational-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T23:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patty And Selma School Judge On Con Law: D'oh!
Who Is Getting The Good Jobs?: Here's a breakdown of the booming 2023 hiring cycle.
Trump Lawyers Try The Normalcy Gambit: Let's see how far it gets them.
Former Partner Tells Tall Tales: Gotta love election denial coming from the big wigs!
DLA Piper Fires Mother-To-Be: They explain it away because of her performance, but the timing is mighty odd.
The post Who Knew The Simpsons Were So Educational? — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Law School Is Getting A Lot Of Supreme Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076322</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/this-law-school-is-getting-a-lot-of-supreme-experience/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T22:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The law school's clinics are getting comfortable in front of the High Court.
The post This Law School Is Getting A Lot Of Supreme Experience appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>