<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-09-24T06:22:24.177Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young America Is Right To Reject Traditional News]]></title>
        <id>200151663</id>
        <link href="https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/09/23/young_america_right_to_reject_traditional_news_151663.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T01:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's become a truism in the past few years that younger people get their news predominantly, if not entirely, from social media. Turns out it's true, but it may not be an information crisis, as some would have you believe.
Of course, as an old-time newspaperman, I was one of those who thought that the country was not being served well by this increasing dependency on unvetted news sources and the implied repudiation of traditional media. How could the country survive if the next generations turned their back on the trusted voices of the New York Times, the Washington Post, CBS, NBC, ABC, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Miele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Library activist Amanda Jones speaks in KC on dismantling motivations behind national wave of book bans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850326</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/library-activist-amanda-jones-speaks-in-kc-on-dismantling-motivations-behind-national-wave-of-book-bans/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T23:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy of Kathryn & Traveis Photography Louisiana librarian Amanda Jones, recipient of the 2020 School Librarian of the Year and the 2021 School Library Journal Librarian of the Year, is headed to the Kansas City Public Library Sept. 25 to discuss her memoir That Librarian: The Fight Against Book Banning in America.  The public event comes as Jones is preparing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soffia Hernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merging Up The Ranks — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075471</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/merging-up-the-ranks-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T23:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Midsize Firm Merges Its Way Up: The new firm will have over 1000 lawyers, climbing higher in the Am Law 100!
New YSL RICO Witness Turns Heads: What did he just say?!
Dentons Is Getting Some Bad Publicity:They've being investigated on corruption charges.
Play If You Want To: Return to office policies are growing teeth.
Mess With Musicians, Face The Music: Recording artist goes to court over his music rights.
The post Merging Up The Ranks — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good News For Biglaw Associates — If You’re In The Right Practice Areas]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075458</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/good-news-for-biglaw-associates-if-youre-in-the-right-practice-areas/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T22:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lateral opportunities for some.
The post Good News For Biglaw Associates — If You’re In The Right Practice Areas appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantastic Fest 2024: Art the Clown comes home for the hellidays in Damien Leone’s Christmas bloodbath Terrifier 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850299</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/fantastic-fest-2024-art-the-clown-comes-home-for-the-hellidays-in-damien-leones-christmas-bloodbath-terrifier-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T22:12:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Fantastic Fest 2024 This is part of our coverage from Fantastic Fest 2024 in Austin, TX where genre films are debuting before they get wider release. Check out all of our coverage here.  Clowns. Some people love them. Some people hate them. Some people love to hate them. Other people, like Terrifier filmmaker Damien Leone, want to build the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Torres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantastic Fest 2024: Yugo Sakamoto’s Baby Assassins: Nice Days continues to bring trademark charm and ass-kicking in equal measure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850275</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/fantastic-fest-2024-yugo-sakamotos-baby-assassins-nice-days-continues-to-bring-trademark-charm-and-ass-kicking-in-equal-measure/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T22:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Fantastic Fest This is part of our coverage from Fantastic Fest 2024 in Austin, TX where genre films are debuting before they get wider release. Check out all of our coverage here.  For the last several years, Japanese film fans have been delighted by the delirious writer/director Yugo Sakamoto’s entertaining and enthralling Baby Assassins films. Following the antics of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Torres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marketing Roundup: Leadership Styles, Competitive Intelligence, Leveraging Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075368</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/marketing-roundup-leadership-styles-competitive-intelligence-leveraging-tech/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T21:32:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LMA shares insights on handling AI with outside vendors and leveraging firm culture for business development.
The post Marketing Roundup: Leadership Styles, Competitive Intelligence, Leveraging Tech appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KATHERINE HOLLAR BARNARD</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rep. Michael Johnson of District 23 unpacks views on abortion, education, and gun laws ahead of election]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=848019</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/rep-michael-johnson-of-district-23-on-his-views-on-abortion-education-gun-laws-and-more-ahead-of-election-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T21:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Michael Johnson’s Instagram Representative Michael Johnson, born and raised in Kansas City, has lived in District 23—which encompasses parts of the northeast side of town—for most of his life, and he wouldn’t have it any other way. He’s beyond proud of his district and the people he’s represented since 2021. “I would do it for free, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law School Deans Have ‘Grave Concerns’ About California Bar Exam]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075446</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/law-school-deans-have-grave-concerns-about-california-bar-exam/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T20:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law school deans think that change is coming too quickly to the California bar exam.
The post Law School Deans Have ‘Grave Concerns’ About California Bar Exam appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, Trump’s Spokesperson Is Not An Above The Law Columnist Despite What You Might’ve Seen On Theo Von’s Podcast]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075467</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/no-trumps-spokesperson-is-not-an-above-the-law-columnist-despite-what-you-mightve-seen-on-theo-vons-podcast/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T20:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technically, Trump spokespeople have been columnists here, but not THIS time.
The post No, Trump’s Spokesperson Is Not An Above The Law Columnist Despite What You Might’ve Seen On Theo Von’s Podcast appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Is Suing Elon Musk Today? Cards Against Humanity, COME ON DOWN!]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075460</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/who-is-suing-elon-musk-today-cards-against-humanity-come-on-down/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T19:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay, they're technically suing SpaceX. Po-tay-to, po-tah-to.
The post Who Is Suing Elon Musk Today? Cards Against Humanity, COME ON DOWN! appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri’s gubernatorial debate explored four wildly different perspectives for 2025 and beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850111</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missouris-gubernatorial-debate-explored-four-wildly-different-perspectives-for-2025-and-beyond/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T19:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Rudi Keller, Missouri Independent. Missouri gubernatorial candidates met for forums Friday, Sept. 20, in Springfield, sponsored by the Missouri Press Association. Present onstage were Republican and current Lieutenant Governor Mike Kehoe, Democrat and current House minority leader Crystal Quade, libertarian and business owner Bill Slantz, and Green Party candidate Paul Lehmann, a retired farmer and minister. Here...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For My Republican Friends]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075439</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/for-my-republican-friends/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T18:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time to stop foaming at the mouth and start influencing.
The post For My Republican Friends appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Herrmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is The YSL RICO Trial A Court Proceeding Or A Reality Show?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075452</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/is-the-ysl-rico-trial-a-court-proceeding-or-a-reality-show/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T17:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flavor of QZ has a ring to it. 
The post Is The YSL RICO Trial A Court Proceeding Or A Reality Show? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nationals End Season By Demoting Leadoff Hitter Who Was In A Casino Until 8:00 A.M.]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167991</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nationals-end-season-by-demoting-leadoff-hitter-who-was-in-a-casino-until-800-a-m"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T17:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Nationals made a sudden and alarming roster move on Friday, optioning 23-year-old all-star shortstop C.J. Abrams to their Triple-A team in Rochester. If the Nationals were good—if they were overstocked with primo young hitting talent, like, say, the Baltimore Orioles—it would be possible to slide this move by as an unfortunate consequence of roster crunch. And, indeed, the Orioles also optioned a talented youngster on the same day, sending hulking 22-year-old infielder and reigning organizational Minor League Player of the Year Coby Mayo back to Norfolk, effectively ending his season. Good teams can have reasons for making painful late-season roster moves that are, if not entirely wholesome, at least coherent within the context of a competitive enterprise. This is not that.
The Nationals are not good, and there's no one anywhere in the organization to slide all that comfortably into Abrams's spot in the field or in the lineup. Abrams's demotion is a disciplinary measure: As first reported by Cody Delmendo of CHGO Sports and later confirmed by Jesse Rogers of ESPN, Abrams was seen living it up at a Chicago casino until 8:00 a.m. Friday morning, and then had to suit up for a 2:00 p.m. game against the Cubs that same afternoon. After the game—Abrams went 0-for-3 with a walk in the leadoff spot, in a 3–1 loss—Nationals coach Davey Martinez pulled Abrams into a long and emotional meeting and informed him that his season was over. The Nationals haven't exactly ratted Abrams out, but everything in their tone and demeanor confirms the scoop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Arkansauce jam up recordBar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850347</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-arkansauce-jam-up-recordbar/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T17:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arkansauce. // photo by Allison Scavo Arkansauce recordBar Friday, September 20 Arkansauce is a progressive newgrass jam band with a blend of traditional slap-grass known to headline festivals. The improvisional string quartet came through Kansas City on their tour where they play a myriad of songs from their vast repertoire. The venue was packed in shoulder-to-shoulder as Saucers stomped the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Scavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Biglaw Firm Announces Merger With Top Midsize Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075449</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/top-biglaw-firm-announces-merger-with-top-midsize-firm/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T17:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mergers, mergers, and more mergers! Biglaw firms really have the urge to merge in Q4.
The post Top Biglaw Firm Announces Merger With Top Midsize Firm appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antonio Pierce Abruptly Realizes He Is Coaching The Raiders]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168014</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/antonio-pierce-abruptly-realizes-he-is-coaching-the-raiders"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To take the old saying and mangle it in the back shop a bit, you cannot hope to beat the Las Vegas Raiders because they are so easy to contain. The latest person to learn this lesson is their 12-game-old head coach.
Antonio Pierce was advertised as the franchise’s latest savior, the coach that this historically listless roster would respond to after enduring The Josh McDaniels Experience; with Pierce setting the example, the team would vibrate with joyful devotion to the greater cause. So trusting. So naive. But these are the Raiders, who have talked it while steadfastly refusing to walk it for two full decades and change now. This is an organization that goes from "Hey, who's the new guy?" to "Hey, when are we getting a new guy?" with uncommon swiftness. It's why, since they lost Super Bowl The 37th back in 'Ought Two, Raiders coaches have averaged 26 games between hiring and firing. That's barely a season and a half.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alleged ‘predatory’ contracts continue to surface in Missouri social-equity marijuana program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850215</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/alleged-predatory-contracts-continue-to-surface-in-missouri-social-equity-marijuana-program/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:49:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The microbusiness program was sold to Missouri voters as a way to help victims of the war on drugs get a toehold in this burgeoning industry (Rebecca Rivas/Missouri Independent) Destiny Brown thought she had been recruited last year to own and operate a small-scale Missouri cannabis dispensary — and get paid $200,000 to do it. Cannabis investor Michael Halow told...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Rivas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cope Is A Terrible Way Not To Die]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167825</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cope-is-a-terrible-way-not-to-die"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:29:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the things that has always been captivating to me about the TV show Alone is how it illustrates our endless capacity for invention in the absolute worst of times. It's a reality show about survival, but really what that means is adaptability. When you lose a supply of arrows, can you fashion more from branches and scavenged parts? Do you know how to use sphagnum moss to treat a wound after an unfortunate ax misadventure? If a crafty vole has raided your stores of fish, will you be able to find more food or resort to gnarly bark-based teas and intermittent fasting as the frost sets in?
It's a manufactured danger. But part of the appeal is that there's no one coming to the rescue. Ultimately you survive and win, or wind up another sucker ferried back to civilization after an intense flirtation with giardia. Either way, these people have to figure out a new way to live every day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Firm Facing Public Corruption Investigation]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075448</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/biglaw-firm-facing-public-corruption-investigation/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firms is cooperating with the inquiry.
The post Biglaw Firm Facing Public Corruption Investigation appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jhy Coulter’s new venture Orange By: Devoured bites into Kansas City’s Martini Corner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=847818</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/jhy-coulters-new-venture-orange-by-devoured-bites-into-kansas-citys-martini-corner/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pizza at Orange By Devoured // Photo By Tiffany Watts Kansas City’s Martini Corner, known for its vibrant energy and eclectic mix of dining and nightlife options, just got a new neighbor—Orange By: Devoured. Opened on August 15, 2024, this fresh, creative pizzeria is the latest venture by Jhy Coulter, an entrepreneur, chef, and visionary whose love for food, travel,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal-Manchester City Clash Ruined By Premier League’s New Focus On Delays Of Game]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167946</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/arsenal-manchester-city-clash-ruined-by-premier-leagues-new-focus-on-delays-of-game"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T15:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the Premier League's marquee showdown of the weekend, last year's number one and number two faced off in an early clash of titans that already had title implications. Arsenal retooled this summer in order to better pursue Manchester City for a third straight season, bringing in defender Riccardo Calafiori, midfielder Mikel Merino, and forward Raheem Sterling. Sunday was Arsenal's first crack at City this season, and though the visiting side gave up a goal to—who else—Erling Haaland in the ninth minute, the Gunners took control of the match with goals from two defenders: Calafiori tied it up in the 22nd with an incredible rocket from outside the box, and then Gabriel gave Arsenal the lead in the first minute of first half stoppage time with a rising header off a corner.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R4eXMyqrGVg]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Documentary Shows How Musician Clawed Back Rights To Number 1 Hit After Decades Of Being Paid Nothing]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075444</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/documentary-shows-how-musician-clawed-back-rights-to-number-1-hit-after-decades-of-being-paid-nothing/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T15:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A feel good story about the 1976 Copyright Act!
The post Documentary Shows How Musician Clawed Back Rights To Number 1 Hit After Decades Of Being Paid Nothing appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lando Norris Is Nearly Perfect]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167915</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lando-norris-is-nearly-perfect"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T15:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There were some recognizable elements of the Singapore Grand Prix this year: a night race with hot weather, heavy humidity, a dew point no doubt off the charts. Correspondingly, there was tired, occasionally frustrated driving on a street circuit not built for overtakes, though this year they tried to rectify this issue by increasing the total number of DRS zones to four. Four! The saving grace for Singapore has also been its most defining characteristic: its propensity for safety cars. But this year, with some luck and a lot of engine reliability, there was nothing. 
This year's race was won or lost in discrete moments. Ferrari lost it after a horrific qualifying; you can't recover from P9 and P10 on the grid on a track like Singapore. Lewis Hamilton lost it after a call to put him on old soft tires to start the race; he failed to grab the all-important track position on the opening lap, and didn't have the tires to last him to the end. And Lando Norris won it by finally converting pole position to a lap-one lead for the first time so far this season, putting to bed—or, at least, a nap—one of the most persistent criticisms levied at his driving this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Sept. 23: Peach Turnover]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167953</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-sept-23-peach-turnover"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T15:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time to get in gear and solve our Monday crossword. This week's puzzle was constructed by Hanh Huynh and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Hanh is a bankruptcy attorney who lives in Brooklyn, N.Y. with his wife and two kids, 10 and 12. His parents fled Vietnam with him and his siblings, eventually arriving in America as refugees. Hanh was an infantryman in the U.S. Army before going to law school. He enjoys bowling and playing Roblox BedWars with his kids.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is It Possible To Create Anticapitalist Work On Social Media?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167570</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/is-it-possible-to-create-anticapitalist-work-on-social-media"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T15:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the weather cools and the kids return to school, my social media feeds have been inundated with fall trend forecasting: "What cool girls will be wearing this fall" and "The Row Margaux dupe you NEED." 
Nearly as prevalent in my feeds are the de-influencing videos. While influencers work to persuade their audience to buy products they may or may not need in the hopes of getting a few cents of commission, de-influencers remind people why they don’t need to spend their money. De-influencing material ranges from explaining why individual viral products aren't worth buying to entire accounts built to remind audiences that hauls aren't normal and call out undisclosed ads or partnerships with brands. De-influencing is part of a larger populist turn I've noticed in response to the omnipresent commercialization of the social internet, but it also exemplifies one of the internet's signal conundrums: Is it possible to create anticapitalist work on social media?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Penalties For Violating Biglaw Office Attendance Mandates May Soon Have More Bite]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075447</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/penalties-for-violating-biglaw-office-attendance-mandates-may-soon-have-more-bite/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T14:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Additional bonus penalties may be coming for those who don't go to the office.
The post Penalties For Violating Biglaw Office Attendance Mandates May Soon Have More Bite appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 White Sox Have Achieved The Abominable]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167922</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-2024-white-sox-have-achieved-the-abominable"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T14:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["No loss is good," said Chicago White Sox interim manager Grady Sizemore, a statement which, rather than defusing the potency of Sunday's milestone loss, merely diffuses it across a season: If no loss is good, then each loss is bad, which means 120 losses are a death march unseen in the days of widespread color TV. That's 120 days of feeling bad at the ballpark; 120 unsatisfied nights, wishing for a better tomorrow that rarely comes. Thirty-six chances for the South Side to stand up, weighed against 120 blunt remonstrances to remain seated.
The 43-119 Detroit Tigers of 2003 are now in the rearview mirror, still notable for possessing the last 20-game loser in Mike Maroth but no longer for owning the AL's worst record of the modern era. The 40-120-1 New York Mets of 1962 are next up. One of the first expansion teams, before MLB had balanced its expansion rules to avoid putting out true stinkers, those Mets were wretched but charmingly pitiable, like an Instagram chihuahua. They made their own manager ask, "Can't anybody here play this game?" They were and are baseball's touchstone for terrible. And they were a better team than the 2024 Chicago White Sox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[195 Congress Members Call For Extension Of Enhanced Premium Tax Credits]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075430</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/09/congress-enhanced-premium-tax-credits/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T14:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In two letters, U.S. representatives and senators called for an extension of the enhanced premium tax credits, which are set to expire in 2025 and have lowered costs for those purchasing coverage on the marketplace.
The post 195 Congress Members Call For Extension Of Enhanced Premium Tax Credits appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MARISSA PLESCIA - MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: The String Cheese Incident defies genre at The Midland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850351</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-the-string-cheese-incident-defies-genre-at-the-midland/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T13:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The String Cheese Incident. // photo by Allison Scavo The String Cheese Incident The Midland Thursday, September 19 Since 1993, the String Cheese Incident has been combining a love for all music lovers into one mega genre. Much like the food, String Cheese Incident pulls one part into several others – one note can extend into reggae, yacht rock, jazz,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Scavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Jinkies! Coffee and Hangout’s Madi and Lisa Dombrowski]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=847571</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-jinkies-coffee-and-hangouts-madi-and-lisa-dombrowski/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T13:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Madi and Lisa Dombrowski If the Brady’s, the Partridge’s, and Charlie’s Angels found themselves in need of a jolt of java, they’d no doubt pick Jinkies! Coffee and Hangout in Overland Park. The retro-esque ’70s-inspired coffeehouse—which opened in Jan. 2021—is owned and operated by the mother/daughter duo of Madi and Lisa Dombrowski. “It’s been an incredible journey,”...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Aces Come From Every Direction]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167921</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-aces-come-from-every-direction"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T12:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of the first quarter of their opening playoff game against the Las Vegas Aces, the Seattle Storm couldn't have found themselves in a much better position. They were leading 18-9, having held the Aces to just 11 percent shooting from the field. Unanimous MVP A'ja Wilson, who had just received her trophy in a pregame ceremony, was 1-of-8. The Storm were cooking.
If a blueprint exists for Seattle getting past Vegas in this best-of-three first-round matchup, it looks a lot like what happened in that first quarter. The Storm, always a defense-first unit, were playing with an intensity and speed that totally discombobulated the Aces' offense. Even without defensive anchor Ezi Magbegor, Seattle's collection of defensive hawks were switching and sliding and blitzing fast enough to make Wilson and the Aces look slow and ponderous. Every shot at the rim was contested, and Seattle's traps and rotations fired so quickly that they looked less like a basketball team scrambling to cover the court than a well-drilled soccer team executing a perfect counter-press.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 09.23.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075441</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/morning-docket-09-23-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T12:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Judge says law firm "defiled the very temple of justice." [Bloomberg Law News]
* Our national nightmare is over: law firm's Rosie the Ve-LAW-ciraptor mascot returned after being stolen two years ago. [KWTX]
* FTC sues pharmacies over measures designed to inflate insulin prices. [Reuters]
* Law school deans worried about California's future bar exam, but in fairness they were worried about its past bar exam so this is an ongoing issue. [ABA Journal]
* Even this Supreme Court is tired of dealing with Jill Stein. [Courthouse News Service]
* Is distinguishing between website advertising and social media advertising the same as putting Big Macs and Whoppers in separate markets? The judge in the Google ad case didn't seem to think so. [Law360]
* Judge blasts plaintiffs in intellectual property lawsuit over Meta's AI training. Lawyers say they'll bring in new team. See, this is why you need to train people with the best material available. [Corporate Counsel]
The post Morning Docket: 09.23.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eagles Remember They Should  Give The Ball To Saquon Barkley More]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167892</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/eagles-remember-they-should-give-the-ball-to-saquon-barkley-more"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T23:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through the better part of three quarters of football on Sunday afternoon, the Philadelphia Eagles and New Orleans Saints were locked in a world's ugliest dog contest. Just one week earlier the Saints were rolling over the haunted remains of the Cowboys and everyone got a piece of the action; Alvin Kamara got four touchdowns, quarterback Derek Carr threw for 243 yards and two touchdowns and even got in on a QB sneak on the way to a 44-19 win. 
On Sunday they led 3-0 thanks to an early field goal and Eagles coach Nick Sirianni's commitment to salvaging genius from ineptitude. The birds had three blown fourth downs early in the game: a blocked punt, a Jalen Hurts sack after a too many men on the field penalty, and a busted run play at the end of the first half in place of an easy field goal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dukes Ran The Tar Heels Out Of Their Own Building]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167861</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-dukes-ran-the-tar-heels-out-of-their-own-building"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T19:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fifty-three points. That's how much Sun Belt juggernaut James Madison University had at halftime against the University of North Carolina on the way to a 70-50 blowout. But that final score does no justice to the absolute ass beating that the Dukes conveyed in Saturday's matchup.
That 53 points scored in a half is the most points James Madison has ever scored in one half and the most points North Carolina has ever allowed in a half. It's also the most points a power conference team has given up to a Group of 5 team since 2012. James Madison forced four turnovers, including a pick-six and a blocked punt return for a touchdown in just the first half. The Dukes notched five turnovers in total and for added measure—or humiliation—recovered their own surprise onside kick. James Madison quarterback Alonza Barnett III finished the game with seven total touchdowns, breaking the record for most touchdowns by a Dukes quarterback in a single game, going 22-for-34 and 388 total yards, adding two touchdowns off 64 yards on the ground.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colorado’s Never Boring That’s For Sure]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167854</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/colorados-never-boring-thats-for-sure"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T17:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last night, going into the midnight hour, I found myself gripped by a Big 12 conference game between two unranked, mediocre teams. This isn't atypical for me, particularly this season, but what is unusual is how many others seemed to be watching alongside me based on social media. That's the thing about the Colorado Buffaloes, despite how average they are, people can't stop watching. We're all waiting for something: an implosion, an explosion on the field, a rapper on the sideline, two of the best players in college football, or the Deion reaction cam and postgame presser bait. Most importantly, we're watching to see if they win or if they lose.

https://youtu.be/TLKBWE35FRQ?feature=shared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Liberty Have A Lot To Prove]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167850</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-liberty-have-a-lot-to-prove"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T14:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t long ago that the Liberty were down bad. In 2017, owner James Dolan kicked the Liberty out of Madison Square Garden and sent them to the Knicks’ G-League arena in White Plains, New York, where they played in front of crowds that you would expect at a rural high school basketball game. The roster fell apart and between 2018 and 2022 they won 47 of 158 games.  
What a difference a change in ownership makes. In 2019, Dolan sold the team to Joseph and Clara Wu Tsai, who moved the Liberty to Brooklyn in 2021. They immediately got to work turning New York into a WNBA super team, plucking MVP winners Breanna Stewart and Jonquel Jones out of free agency, teaming them up with 2020 No. 1 overall pick Sabrina Ionescu and champion point guard Courtney Vandersloot. The results in 2023 were everything they could have expected in the regular season. The Liberty’s quad-star lineup went 32-8 and they outscored opponents by an average of 8.6 points per game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Coller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[City Journal Delves Into the Crisis of Liberal Education]]></title>
        <id>200151662</id>
        <link href="https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/09/22/city_journal_delves_into_crisis_liberal_education_151662.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T06:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The degradation of liberal education in America is anything but a niche public-policy concern.
Like all rights-protecting democracies - and especially as a 21st-century great power with globe-spanning interests - the United States requires a host of highly-trained individuals to keep its government functioning, military operating, economy churning, and civil society thriving. Essential men and women perform manual labor, offer basic services, and run small businesses. In addition, the nation needs physicists, chemists, and biologists; lawyers, doctors, and business executives; teachers,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Berkowitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: KC Current shut out Washington Spirit in 3-0 match]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=849730</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-kc-current-shut-out-washington-spirit-in-3-0-match/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T21:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Current clinched a spot in the 2024 NWSL Playoffs last night with a dominant 3-0 win over the Washington Spirit. Forward Nichelle Prince opened the scoring with her first goal for the club, becoming the 18th different goalscorer for the club this season. Midfielder Lo’eau LaBonta doubled the lead, and forward Temwa Chawinga secured the win in the second...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarik Sykes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mining the News (9/21/24)]]></title>
        <id>https://fantasy.fangraphs.com/?p=161499</id>
        <link href="https://fantasy.fangraphs.com/mining-the-news-9-21-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T17:49:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just catching up on the news.
Source]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Zimmerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shots Heard From The Judge’s Chambers — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075426</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/shots-heard-from-the-judges-chambers-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T22:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sheriff Allegedly Shot Judge In His Chambers: The sheriff surrendered shortly after.
Put This In Your Outline: Law Professor visually assaults students deploys legitimate pedagogical tactic of teaching via hardcore pornography.
Democracy Matters: Amy Coney Barrett sings democracy's praises. Wish her jurisprudence did the same.
Feels And Judgement: Do judicial feelings determine legal outcomes?
Honestly, Nevermind: Charlie Adelson renegs on the waiver letting his mom borrow his lawyer.
The post Shots Heard From The Judge’s Chambers — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revoked Conflict Waiver Means Delays In Slain Law Professor Case]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075418</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/revoked-conflict-waiver-means-more-delays-in-slain-law-professor-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T22:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another setback for the high profile case. 
The post Revoked Conflict Waiver Means Delays In Slain Law Professor Case appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bracing Yourself For The First Monday In October (AKA The Start Of The Supreme Court Term)?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075420</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/bracing-yourself-for-the-first-monday-in-october-aka-the-start-of-the-supreme-court-term/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T21:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Supreme Court wasn't always a "fall thing."
The post Bracing Yourself For The First Monday In October (AKA The Start Of The Supreme Court Term)? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Appealing Weekly Roundup]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075398</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/how-appealing-weekly-roundup-87/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T20:36:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The week in appellate news.
The post How Appealing Weekly Roundup appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amy Coney Barrett Encourages Open Democracy… That Is, If She Hasn’t Already Impinged With Your Right To Vote]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075397</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/amy-coney-barrett-encourages-open-democracy-that-is-if-she-hasnt-already-impinged-with-your-right-to-vote/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T19:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DEADLOCK premieres tonight on PBS.
The post Amy Coney Barrett Encourages Open Democracy… That Is, If She Hasn’t Already Impinged With Your Right To Vote appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law School Con Law Class Shows Porn So You Know It When You See It]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075411</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/law-school-con-law-class-shows-porn-so-you-know-it-when-you-see-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T19:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Radical concept, but maybe the students could figure out the law without having to experience the fact pattern first-hand.
The post Law School Con Law Class Shows Porn So You Know It When You See It appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sonia Sotomayor’s Just Ask! helps teach youth inclusive and empathetic curiosity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=849053</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/sonia-sotomayors-just-ask-helps-teach-youth-inclusive-and-empathetic-curiosity/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T19:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supreme Court Justice Sonia Sotomayor reads her book, Just Ask! to a group of children at Kansas City’s Central Library. She was in town to see a staged reading of a musical version of the book that will debut at The Coterie in Jan. // Photo by Beth Lipoff The Coterie’s new world premiere of Just Ask!  is still in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Lipoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Documentary About Simone Biles Might Save Jordan Chiles’s Bronze Medal]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167471</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-documentary-about-simone-biles-might-save-jordan-chiless-bronze-medal"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T18:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's good to be friends with Simone Biles. Many of the reasons are obvious: Biles is the greatest gymnast of all time, she comes off as cool as hell in interviews, she threw an Instagram funeral for her history-making vault, and she has stood up against both athlete abuse and also her haters. But now add this to the list: She's the reason video evidence exists that might be key to Jordan Chiles getting her bronze Olympic medal restored. 
A little refresher: Chiles competed in the floor competition in Paris this summer, and her preliminary score put her in fifth. Afterward, one of her coaches, Cecile Landi, challenged her score. It worked; after reviewing one element of Chiles's routine, a Gogean, the judges bumped up Chiles's difficulty score by 0.1, which put Chiles in third place and pushed Romanian athlete Ana Barbosu down to fourth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing The 2024 Legal Tech Buyer’s Guide!]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075361</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/introducing-the-2024-legal-tech-buyers-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T18:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ensure your firm is on the cutting edge with this brand new primer on doc management, AI, CRM, billing and payments, and more.
The post Introducing The 2024 Legal Tech Buyer’s Guide! appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘New York’ Suspends Olivia Nuzzi Over “Inappropriate Relationship” With Robert F. Kennedy Jr.]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167826</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/new-york-suspends-olivia-nuzzi-over-inappropriate-relationship-with-robert-f-kennedy-jr"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T18:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Media reporter Oliver Darcy broke the astonishing news late Thursday night that star New York political correspondent Olivia Nuzzi had been suspended by the magazine after she disclosed to the magazine that she'd engaged in an inappropriate relationship with a subject of her reporting. That subject, according to several reports, is none other than failed presidential candidate and notable animal corpse defiler Robert F. Kennedy Jr., who was the subject of a November 2023 Nuzzi profile.
Per a statement from New York's comms department, Nuzzi has been placed on leave while the magazine conducts a third-party review. Nuzzi told Darcy after his story broke that "earlier this year, the nature of some communication" between herself and a subject "turned personal." She said the relationship was "never physical but should have been disclosed to prevent the appearance of a conflict." In a note to New York staff, editor David Haskell said Nuzzi, 31, claimed not to have used Kennedy, 70, as a source during their relationship, which started in December 2023 and ended in August. Kennedy's people denied the existence of such a relationship and merely told Darcy, "Mr. Kennedy only met Olivia Nuzzi once in his life for an interview she requested, which yielded a hit piece."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drink This Now: Hank American lager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=849706</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/drink-this-now-hank-american-lager/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T18:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hank // Photo by Sarah Sipple Meet Hank. Hank is a family name for Eric Flanagan, owner of Crossroads bars King G and Jim’s Alley Bar, and the future Hank’s Garage and Grill in Shawnee. Hank is also the name of a new beer brewed in partnership with Hank’s and Alma Mader Brewing.  Hank (the beer) is relaxed but not...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warning For Pro-Trump Attorneys This Election Season]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075410</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/warning-for-pro-trump-attorneys-this-election-season/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T17:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don't be like Rudy.
The post Warning For Pro-Trump Attorneys This Election Season appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Derek Carr Is Officially Too Racy For The NFL]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167834</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/derek-carr-is-officially-too-racy-for-the-nfl"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T17:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The National Football League rarely displays a sense of humor on any topic, largely because the people who run the sport are 74 years old going on 103. People that old and rich are rarely amused, and even more infrequently amusing. Any attempt by this cohort to understand what people less comfortable and death-adjacent consider funny would, ironically enough, be pretty amusing.
Thus the news-to-be that Derek Carr, the FDA's most effective over-the-counter antidote to cool, is going to be fined $14,000 for a) celebrating the New Orleans Saints' pivotal fifth touchdown in a 44-19 thrashing of the Dallas Cowboys, and b) using a vintage Michael Jackson dance move to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stat(s) Of The Week: Wish We’d Never Met]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075382</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/stats-of-the-week-genz-tiktok/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T17:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the popularity of TikTok, many Gen Z-ers might not regret a shutdown.
The post Stat(s) Of The Week: Wish We’d Never Met appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vera Djordjevich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunset Rubdown’s Spencer Krug Doesn’t Want To Live In The Past Forever]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167382</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/sunset-rubdowns-spencer-krug-doesnt-want-to-live-in-the-past-forever"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T17:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sunset Rubdown was a shooting star. The band began as a solo project for Spencer Krug's bedroom recordings, and expanded into one of the weirdest, densest, most essential bands of the late 2000s. As one of Wolf Parade's vocalists and creative forces, Krug was already building some buzz for himself as a vital voice in the burgeoning indie rock moment, but he had too many ideas for even that once-prolific band. That's where Sunset Rubdown came in.
Following the project's solo and lo-fi debut album, 2005's Snake's Got A Leg, the band released as strong a trilogy of albums as any act to come out of the music-blog era. Shut Up I Am Dreaming, from 2006, was the breakout, landing on year-end best-of lists, thanks to its simultaneously glittering, brooding, and claustrophobic sound, and its expansive instrument collages. As an aside, this is where I hopped aboard the Sunset Rubdown train, having heard the album shortly into my first semester of college a year after its release. For someone only just starting to broaden his musical horizons, Shut Up I Am Dreaming was a sledgehammer to the brain. (I mean that as a compliment.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Republic, If You Can Keep It]]></title>
        <id>200151661</id>
        <link href="https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/09/20/a_republic_if_you_can_keep_it___151661.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T16:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Friday, Sept. 20. Interestingly, Election "Day," which is now a profound misnomer, begins today: In Virginia, Minnesota, and South Dakota, citizens 18 and older can begin voting in the 2024 presidential election.
Today is also the day of the week when I share a quote intended to be uplifting or educational. Earlier this week I wrote about Constitution Day, which fell on Tuesday, although the administration encourages us to think of this as "Constitution Week."
I'm all for that, especially since the proclamation issued in President Biden's name reprised the famous Benjamin Franklin "a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl M. Cannon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC pharmacist walkout a year ago highlighted industry troubles. Problems haven’t gone away]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=849677</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-pharmacist-walkout-a-year-ago-highlighted-industry-troubles-problems-havent-gone-away/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T16:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After pharmacist walkouts last year, CVS Pharmacy officials said they added staff to help alleviate customer waits (Scott Canon/The Beacon) A year ago this week, 27 pharmacists walked off their jobs in and around Kansas City to protest understaffing, low technician pay and burdensome workloads at some CVS-owned pharmacies. Their action forced about a dozen Kansas City-area pharmacies and 10...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suzanne King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Campaign Happenings; Political Humor; Quote of the Week]]></title>
        <id>200151660</id>
        <link href="https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/09/20/campaign_happenings_political_humor_quote_of_the_week_151660.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T16:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good morning, it's Friday, Sept. 20. Election Day, which is now a profound misnomer, begins today: In Virginia, Minnesota, and South Dakota, citizens 18 and older can begin voting in the 2024 presidential election.
Today is also the day of the week when I share a quote intended to be uplifting or educational. Earlier this week I wrote about Constitution Day, which fell on Tuesday, although the administration encourages us to think of this as "Constitution Week."
I'm all for that, especially since the proclamation issued in President Biden's name reprised the famous Benjamin Franklin "a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carl M. Cannon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Will It Take To Improve Healthcare Cybersecurity?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075394</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/09/healthcare-cybersecurity-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T16:40:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During a panel discussion at MedCity News’ INVEST Digital Health conference, three healthcare leaders shared their expert insight on what needs to change in order to improve the industry’s cybersecurity strategy.
The post What Will It Take To Improve Healthcare Cybersecurity? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KATIE ADAMS - MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conquering Conferences: Responding To Rejection And Approaching The Group Chat]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075366</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/conquering-conferences-responding-to-rejection-and-approaching-the-group-chat/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T16:03:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we're preparing for the group networking waltz.
The post Conquering Conferences: Responding To Rejection And Approaching The Group Chat appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEJAL PATEL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Small Town Shocker: Sheriff Allegedly Marches Into Judge’s Chambers And Shoots Him]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075399</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/small-town-shocker-sheriff-allegedly-marches-into-judges-chambers-and-shoots-him/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T15:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sheriff has been charged with murder.
The post Small Town Shocker: Sheriff Allegedly Marches Into Judge’s Chambers And Shoots Him appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Football Will Live Or Die With Its Rivalries]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167625</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/football-will-live-or-die-with-its-rivalries"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T15:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first two annual football rivalries that I can remember haven’t occurred for years now. In Worcester, where I grew up, St. John’s and St. Peter’s played each other at the end of every football season for almost a century. It was the longest-running Catholic high-school rivalry in the country. They played every Thanksgiving morning at Fitton Field, the home ground of the Holy Cross Crusaders, about whom more anon.
The two schools had stood as monuments to the massive Irish diaspora to Worcester of which my family was a part. I went to St. Peter’s for elementary school and to St. John’s for high school. St. John’s moved to the suburbs in 1959, which turned out to be a fateful move for both schools and fatal for their rivalry. St. Peter’s stayed in Worcester, but it merged with a girls’ high school and became St. Peter-Marian. St. John’s gradually grew beyond St. Peter’s in every way, including in its football program. The two schools ended the rivalry with their 95th meeting in 2019. St. John’s won, 35-12.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charles P. Pierce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slipknot’s Clown opens up behind the mask ahead of this weekend’s Knotfest in Des Moines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=849643</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/slipknots-clown-opens-up-behind-the-mask-ahead-of-this-weekends-knotfest-in-des-moines/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T15:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slipknot // Photo Courtesy of Jonathan Weiner Since the release of their self-titled debut in 1999, metal band Slipknot has been  known as a live act with which to reckon. From their incendiary live sets to their iconic masks, the sprawling band has acquired a legion of fans, affectionately known as “Maggots,” who make the band as much of a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are The Supreme Court Justices’ Opinions Emotionally Charged And Does It Matter?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075400</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/are-the-supreme-court-justices-opinions-emotionally-charged-and-does-it-matter/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T14:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The justices clearly are emotional actors and so Supreme Court opinions are not even nearly devoid of emotional language. It is also clear that the justices’ relative use of emotional language varies quite a bit, both between cases and between justices. 
The post Are The Supreme Court Justices’ Opinions Emotionally Charged And Does It Matter? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Adam Feldman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To The Future Bench Heroes Of The 2024 WNBA Playoffs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167433</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-guide-to-the-future-bench-heroes-of-the-2024-wnba-playoffs"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T14:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This WNBA playoff preview is dedicated to those without a shoe deal—the X-factors, the microwave scorers, the glue gals. I’ve chosen eight who could rise to the occasion this fall, paired by first-round matchups. May they make these playoffs theirs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congress Poised To Bring Back Unfettered Patent Trolling]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075396</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/congress-poised-to-bring-back-unfettered-patent-trolling/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T13:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the all-trolling-all-the-time-act dept
The post Congress Poised To Bring Back Unfettered Patent Trolling appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Techdirt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Racism Goes To Become Rhetoric]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167811</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/where-racism-goes-to-become-rhetoric"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T13:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter, examining the apocalyptic politics and coverage of Campaign 2024.
Wednesday night, in Long Island's 16,000-seat Nassau Coliseum, Donald Trump told the crowd at a rally for his presidential campaign that the United States—and particularly New York City, a few miles away—had been overrun with criminal immigrants, "people coming from jails out of the Congo in Africa."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is The Cost Of A Woj Bomb?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167671</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-is-the-cost-of-a-woj-bomb"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T13:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sports media was subject to profound changes throughout the 17 years that Wojnarowski spent working for Yahoo Sports and ESPN, changes he typified, accelerated, and ultimately abandoned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with local glassmaker Kari Heybrock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=849625</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-local-glassmaker-kari-heybrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T13:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Kari Heybrock With the 2024 Plaza Art Fair only hours away, glassmaker Kari Heybrock is gearing up for a lucrative—and hectic—few days. She’s one of around 25 metro artists showing off their wares at the prestigious annual event. (You’ll spy her in booth #106.) To hear her tell the tale, it seems her career field was predestined. “I believe...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 09.20.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075393</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/morning-docket-09-20-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T12:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Paul Weiss offers professional attire stipend to vacation scheme interns. It would be better if they'd hired Nina Garcia and the Twitter Workwear Guy as consultants but this is a start. [LegalCheek]
* For the Civil Procedure buffs, hot minimum contacts precedent just dropped. [Reuters]
* Law professor who admits to sleeping with 1Ls can't block the Title IX investigation. [Law360]
* Right as yesterday's crazy news day came to a close, newly filed court documents say Matt Gaetz took a high school junior to a coke-filled sex party. [Mediaite]
* Dentons being looked at in connection with South Africa corruption probe. [Roll on Friday]
* Interesting story about rising the Biglaw ranks with a stutter. [American Lawyer]
* Robot Picasso still has no rights. [Bloomberg Law News]
The post Morning Docket: 09.20.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shohei Ohtani Is Playing A Sport Of His Own]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167778</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/shohei-ohtani-is-playing-a-sport-of-his-own"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T12:42:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shohei Ohtani is the first player in baseball history. It doesn't matter how you complete that sentence; it has a solid chance of being right. He is Bill Brasky in spikes. This year, a one-way year as he recovers from Tommy John surgery, he just up and decided to double his previous stolen base high, because I guess he was bored not pitching. Sure, why not. Next year he might play goal for the Kings. It feels just as realistic. He makes baseball seem like a matter of willpower. If you can dream it, he might do it, and he might do the undreamt too. The 50/50 club—50 home runs, 50 stolen bases—was not a thing. No one was in it. Those are two very different skills, and guys who hit for power don't tend to run well, and vice versa. Whatever. Ohtani did it. I think he can do anything.
Except be patient, perhaps. When he joined the 40/40 club last month, 21 games faster than anyone had ever done so, he said he felt relief, as all the pending pomp was getting in the way of the thing he really wants to do: step into the box and hit the dang ball. “It was something I wanted to get over as soon as possible because the balls were being exchanged every time I was up to bat," he said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New federal lawsuit pins blame for inmate’s death on Missouri prison officials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=849689</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/new-federal-lawsuit-pins-blame-for-inmates-death-on-missouri-prison-officials/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tammy Reed, center, is suing the Missouri Department of Corrections for wrongful death of her son, Brandon Pace, at Tipton Correctional Center. In January, she was joined by Tina Burger, left, and her daughter, Bethany Pace, at a memorial service for the 382 Missourians who died in department custody in 2021, 2022 and 2023 (Rudi Keller/Missouri Independent). Missouri corrections officers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rudi Keller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Had Minority Journalists at &#039;Hello&#039;]]></title>
        <id>200151654</id>
        <link href="https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/09/20/kamala_harris_had_minority_journalists_at_hello_151654.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T07:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The easiest thing in the world to predict is that Vice President Kamala Harris is going to be coddled by minority journalists. If you speak the mantra "diversity, equity, inclusion" -- and let's add "history" -- you're rooting for a Harris victory.
So when Harris finally consented to a sit-down with three liberals at a Philadelphia NPR station for the National Association of Black Journalists, the title of the event could have been "You Had Me at 'Hello.'" Not every question was a softball -- they pushed back from the Left on handgun control and denying aid to Israel. But nobody wanted her...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For More Civics in Schools, Dial Down the Controversy]]></title>
        <id>200151651</id>
        <link href="https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/09/20/for_more_civics_in_schools_dial_down_the_controversy_151651.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T07:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's election season. Too bad a study this year from the U.S. Chamber of Commerce found that more than 70% of respondents failed a basic U.S. civic literacy quiz, with over 30% not knowing that there are three branches of government, much less what those branches are and what they do. 
Other studies and tests continue to reveal this same sad truth: We Americans don't know civics. This is especially the case for younger Americans, who research has shown to be less informed about civics than their older counterparts. 
Obviously, there is a need for more and better civic education in schools, a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam Julian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voters Don&#039;t Want Harris&#039; or Trump&#039;s Campaign Policies]]></title>
        <id>200151656</id>
        <link href="https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/09/20/voters_dont_want_harris_or_trumps_campaign_policies_151656.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T07:11:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neither Vice President Kamala Harris nor former President Donald Trump, The Wall Street Journal reported on Wednesday's front page, has any proposals to cut the rapidly increasing national debt. Instead, both are proposing to hand out goodies to strategically positioned voters.
Harris, with an eye on polls showing young voters not as pro-Democratic as in the past, has been talking about providing $25,000 for down payments to first-time homebuyers. With an eye on young families and single parents, she has also called for restoring part of the refundable child tax credit that was part of what...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Barone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris Allies Continue Calling Trump &lsquo;Threat to Democracy&rsquo;]]></title>
        <id>200151652</id>
        <link href="https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/09/20/harris_allies_continue_calling_trump_threat_to_democracy_151652.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T07:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two assassination attempts against former President Donald Trump have not clarified the Democratic position on whether that Republican represents an existential threat to democracy. The White House still calls him a threat. Vice President Kamala Harris, meanwhile, has mostly discarded that talking point.
Trump wants it to stop either way. At least, when directed towards him.
"It is time to stop the lies, stop the hoaxes, stop the smears, stop the lawfare or the fake lawsuits against me, and stop claiming your opponents will turn America into a dictatorship. Give me a break," the Republican...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Wegmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Are the Nutjobs Trying to Kill Political Opponents All Left-Wingers?]]></title>
        <id>200151657</id>
        <link href="https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/09/20/why_are_the_nutjobs_trying_to_kill_political_opponents_all_left-wingers_151657.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T07:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Aug. 2012, a left-wing MSNBC afficionado named Floyd Lee Corkins armed himself with a handgun and extra magazines. He drove to the Washington, D.C., headquarters of the socially conservative Family Research Council, planning to shoot it up. Corkins, who later cited the Southern Poverty Law Center for the proposition that the FRC is an "anti-gay" organization, was also carrying 15 Chick-fil-A sandwiches, which he hoped to stuff in his dead victims' mouths. Corkins, who served as a volunteer at a local LGBT community center, was stopped by an unarmed security guard.
In June 2017, a left-wing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hammer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liberal Neighbors to JD Vance -- Hillbilly, Go Home]]></title>
        <id>200151653</id>
        <link href="https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/09/20/liberal_neighbors_to_jd_vance_--_hillbilly_go_home_151653.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T07:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ALEXANDRIA, Va. -- The park next to JD Vance's house in Alexandria, Virginia, is closed. After two assassination attempts against former President Donald Trump, security is tight near the Vance home in Del Ray, the upscale, family-friendly neighborhood that leans very much to the left.
There are security barriers and men and women in uniforms. Neighbors who have talked to the press understand. The Secret Service "is doing what they need to do," Del Ray resident Erica Toler told ALXnow. "We look forward to getting our park back in a few months."
Del Ray has not been particularly friendly to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Debra Saunders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progressives Lied. A Woman Died. Republicans Were Blamed.]]></title>
        <id>200151655</id>
        <link href="https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/09/20/progressives_lied_a_woman_died_republicans_were_blamed_151655.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being a progressive means you can lie with impunity and the media will declare you a truth-teller. The other day on CNN, Democrat strategist Elliot Williams defended Democrat claims that Donald Trump is a "threat to democracy" because of Trump's refusal to accept election results. Hillary Clinton, Stacey Abrams and every Democrat who thinks George W. Bush stole the 2000 election from Al Gore get a pass. But Trump is a threat to democracy. Democrats get to lie, and the media blesses their lies as truth.
In Springfield, Ohio, Republicans conjured up stories of stolen pets being eaten by...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erick Erickson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Abortion, Kamala Harris Is the Extremist]]></title>
        <id>200151658</id>
        <link href="https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/09/20/on_abortion_kamala_harris_is_the_extremist_151658.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T07:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At one point during the Sept. 10 presidential debate, former President Donald Trump accused Democrats of not only supporting unlimited third-trimester abortions but the "execution" of babies after birth.
Once Trump wrapped up his rant, Linsey Davis, one of the ABC News moderators, "fact-checked" the former president, helpfully noting that "there is no state in this country where it is legal to kill a baby after it's born."
If Trump had been better prepared, he could have pointed out that a senator named Kamala Harris, while running for president in 2020, opposed legislation that would have...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Harsanyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Harris&#039;s Cynical, Run-Out-The Clock Campaign Succeed?]]></title>
        <id>200151659</id>
        <link href="https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/09/20/can_harriss_cynical_run-out-the_clock_campaign_succeed_151659.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T07:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cynically running out the clock has been the overarching principle of the entire abbreviated 105-day presidential campaign of Vice President Kamala Harris -- ever since President Joe Biden, at the 11th-hour, dropped out in July.
Harris seems unwilling or unable to answer any impromptu question that she has not been previously prepped for. Her answers at the debate were memorized and canned. They never addressed the questions asked.
Her single, 11-minute post-debate Philadelphia interview was a shipwreck of dodging and dissimulating -- even though the host was sympathetically left-wing.
Even...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Davis Hanson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Creeps Feel Slighted — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075385</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/the-creeps-feel-slighted-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T23:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Did You Get This Number?: Female law professors and students keep getting creepy messages from salty loser.
The Order Of Things: California needs to focus on procedure before they replace the bar.
He Doth Compliment Too Much: Lawyer gets accused of inflating his Avvo reviews.
Move Over, Florida Man!: Alaskan dude indicted over Supreme Court threats.
The post The Creeps Feel Slighted — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Big Thanks To Our Advertisers]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075344</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/a-big-thanks-to-our-advertisers-20/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T23:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's so great working with you!
The post A Big Thanks To Our Advertisers appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clerkships Are Certainly One Good Way To Start An Elite Legal Career]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075375</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/clerkships-are-certainly-one-good-way-to-start-an-elite-legal-career/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T22:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, they already knew where the bathrooms were when they started as Supreme Court justices.
The post Clerkships Are Certainly One Good Way To Start An Elite Legal Career appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kira Spin-Off Zuva Unveils New Contract Review AI For In-House Legal Teams, Zuva Analyze]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075345</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/09/kira-spin-off-zuva-unveils-new-contract-review-ai-for-in-house-legal-teams-zuva-analyze.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T22:18:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developed by the same team that originally created Kira, Zuva Analyze uses generative AI and machine learning to give reliably accurate and granular results over large numbers of documents, the company says.
The post Kira Spin-Off Zuva Unveils New Contract Review AI For In-House Legal Teams, Zuva Analyze appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Nonequity Partnership Tier Won’t Impact The Number Of New Equity Partners At This Biglaw Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075341</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/a-nonequity-partnership-tier-wont-impact-the-number-of-new-equity-partners-at-this-biglaw-firm/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T21:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This firm is still committed to awarding equity partnerships to hardworking senior associates.
The post A Nonequity Partnership Tier Won’t Impact The Number Of New Equity Partners At This Biglaw Firm appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Styx’s Lawrence Gowan on embracing classic rock pomposity ahead of Saturday’s show]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=849653</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/styxs-lawrence-gowan-on-embracing-classic-rock-pomposity-ahead-of-saturdays-show/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T21:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Styx (left to right: Todd Sucherman, Lawrence Gowan, Chuck Panozzo, James “JY” Young, Tommy Shaw, Terry Gowan, Will Evankovich). // Photo Courtesy of Jason Powell Formed in Chicago in 1972, classic rock band Styx is a perennial summer staple on the Kansas City concert calendar. Fresh off this summer’s co-headlining tour with fellow rockers Foreigner, the band comes to Cable...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California Needs To Focus On Procedurals Before Administering Bar Replacement]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075374</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/california-needs-to-focus-on-procedurals-before-administering-bar-replacement/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T20:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So much for minimum competency! 
The post California Needs To Focus On Procedurals Before Administering Bar Replacement appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mild Card Season, With Maitreyi Anantharaman]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167476</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mild-card-season-with-maitreyi-anantharaman"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T20:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is the nature of a podcast to unravel, or anyway it's mostly the way that ours works. We start out trying to be normal, with a rundown of topics to address and a sense of roughly how long we have to discuss them, and then it all kind of unspools and derails and malfunctions and by the end I am singing the "they got a pepper bar" song from those weird Quiznos ads while Drew names different Vikings interior linemen as our guest feigns technical difficulties. Listeners know this; presumably some of them even like it. I mention this only because this week's episode, in which we are joined by Defector's own Maitreyi Anantharaman, unfolds more or less in reverse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Not Believe In The Seattle Mariners]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167697</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/do-not-believe-in-the-seattle-mariners"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T20:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, Victor Robles was hit by a Luis Gil pitch, and jogged at the mound—to give Gil a half-hug. After a couple of walks and flyouts, Robles made his way to third. And with the bases loaded, two outs, and Justin Turner working Gil to a 3-0 count, Robles took off for home as Gil reached for his rosin bag, and was easily caught stealing to end the inning. It was the complete Robles experience. Here's a lovable guy with enough pathos to befriend a wild praying mantis, and also a guy who will follow it up with one of the worst base-running experiences you've ever witnessed, all within the very first inning of the game. The Mariners went on to lose 11-2, which is one point in Robles's defense: It probably wouldn't have mattered anyway.
On Thursday, the Mariners were tied 1-1 with the Yankees when, in the bottom of the 10th inning, Randy Arozarena struck out swinging on a dropped third strike. His bat went sailing over the third-base line and nearly took out Julio Rodríguez, who danced out of the way and then forgot that the ball was still in play. He took a wide jog about the base, turning to the dugout, while Jazz Chisholm Jr. stood on base and called for the ball. It took a few beats for Yankees catcher Austin Wells to make the throw, but Rodríguez was still doubled off easily. The Mariners went on to lose this game, 2-1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Partner’s Dedication To Giving Students The Opportunities That Shaped His Career]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075302</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/managing-partners-dedication-to-giving-students-the-opportunities-that-shaped-his-career/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T20:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of lawyers started out in competitive debate. Stuart Singer spent the last several years working to keep that option alive at overlooked schools.
The post Managing Partner’s Dedication To Giving Students The Opportunities That Shaped His Career appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tennessee’s “Talent Fee” For Tickets Is The First Domino]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167703</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tennessees-talent-fee-for-tickets-is-the-first-domino"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T20:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As reported by ESPN, the University of Tennessee, as part of its future plans for revenue-sharing with players in 2025, will tack a 10 percent "Talent Fee" onto the ticket prices. The university announced this in an email to football season-ticket holders this week, complete with a video from athletic director Danny White, in which he describes the new fee as "part of an extensive plan to continue our dominance in college athletics and build something like never seen before."

https://youtu.be/TV-ZzeJxWIQ?feature=shared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: Lei Away, rum punch parties, and a new coffee patio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=849642</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-lei-away-rum-punch-parties-and-a-new-coffee-patio/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T19:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Looking for delicious plans? Whether you want to impress a date, show your fam the best of KC, or just get out of the house, we’ve got you covered… all while supporting (mostly) local.  Here is your weekly roundup of the best food and drink offerings around Kansas City. Cheers! Something New Taco Republic: Taco Battle...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alaska Man Indicted Over Supreme Court Assassination Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075369</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/alaska-man-indicted-over-supreme-court-assassination-threats/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T19:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He allegedly threaten to 'lynch' and 'put a bullet' in Supreme Court justices and their family members.
The post Alaska Man Indicted Over Supreme Court Assassination Threats appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real Madrid Must Learn How To Walk Before It Can Run]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167590</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/real-madrid-must-learn-how-to-walk-before-it-can-run"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T19:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you think about it, it's a bit strange that the best team in the world added the best player in the world, thereby forming a potentially era-defining superteam, and yet it doesn't seem like the union between Real Madrid and Kylian Mbappé has been received as the monumental occasion it truly is.
Part of it comes from the collective exhaustion with the endless will-they-or-won't-they dynamic between player and club. Watching the two make goo-goo eyes at each other from across the Pyrenees for four years straight bled the courtship of all its titillation, even now that they're finally fucking. The other part is probably a response to the infinitely impressive but still somewhat dulling nature of Madrid's success. So you're telling me the reigning Champions League champions, winners of six of the last 11 European Cups, are the favorites to win the Champions League again?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyer Accused Of Being His Own Marketing Department]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075359</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/lawyer-accused-of-being-his-own-marketing-department/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T18:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embarrassing to get caught tooting your own horn. 
The post Lawyer Accused Of Being His Own Marketing Department appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>