<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-12-25T20:16:14.688Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Can A Life Be Wonderful?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177081</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-can-a-life-be-wonderful"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T14:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was originally published on Flaming Hydra on Dec. 4. If you like it, we encourage you to visit their site and subscribe.
For so long I avoided It’s a Wonderful Life—it was too bruising, its redemptions too meager for the guy I was in my 20s, with all those grand plans of his own. I always found myself wishing for more for poor George Bailey, I guess is what I’m saying. Trampled by bad luck, by his own virtue and his begrudging loyalties, stalled out at every moment of departure and always left to clean up someone else’s mess. And worst of all, tormented by the horrible Mister Potter, who creaks through Bedford Falls threatening foreclosures and buyouts in that blubbery old whine of his. I saw Potter as a special kind of real-world doom—a man so powerful you cannot fight against him, only beg him for mercy, as George’s father had done before him and as his children almost certainly will after. The Potters won’t live forever, but there is always another one on their way, with the cops and the bank examiner all working for them too. They weren’t going anywhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Saward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Did We Get Stuck In Our Rectums Last Year?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=175016</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-did-we-get-stuck-in-our-rectums-last-year-5"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you realize that this is the 12th year we've run this series? Time really flies when you don't have something lodged up your butt. But for those of you who do, read on to see if you made this year's list of the weirdest stuff that entered America's orifices. If not, there's always next year.
All reports are taken from the U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission's database of emergency room visits, all descriptions are verbatim, and all the entries below involved some very poor decisions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Lunch meetings at Made In KC Cafe and Al’s Bar & Grill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866040</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-made-in-kc-cafe-taproom-and-als-bar-grill/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Made In Kc Cafe Taproom // Photo By Tiffany Watts Made In KC Cafe & Taproom In the heart of Downtown Kansas City, Made in KC Café & Taproom offers a little bit of everything—coffee, local craft drinks, and a welcoming space to gather. It’s a spot that brings together coffee lovers, craft beverage enthusiasts, and anyone looking for a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Season’s Greetings from LinuxLinks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139997</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/seasons-greetings-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T08:41:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year from everyone at LinuxLinks.
The post Season’s Greetings from LinuxLinks appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Off until Mon, 1/6]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/off-until-mon-16</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/off-until-mon-16"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T05:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flow State will be off for holiday break until Monday, 1/6/25.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Where have the December snows gone? (TUE-12/24)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3768510</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-where-have-the-december-snows-gone-tue-12-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Temperatures this month are trending a bit above average right now, and with the forecast for most of the rest of the month pretty mild, that will continue to grow to some degree over the next week or so. What has been interesting to me though is that we're losing out on our previous December [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Where have the December snows gone? (TUE-12/24)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3768510</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-where-have-the-december-snows-gone-tue-12-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Temperatures this month are trending a bit above average right now...and with the forecast for most of the rest of the month pretty mild, that will continue to grow to some degree over the next week or so. What has been interesting to me though is that we're losing out on our previous December snows [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Narrative Is All That Matters]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177048</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/blake-lively-justin-baldoni-mess-narratives"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T15:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s easy to hate Blake Lively. She's beautiful. She's tall. Her hair is so lush. Her skin is so smooth. She's married to a damn Marvel actor, and they have beautiful children. Her best friend is Taylor Swift. In a world of demure, close-lipped smirks, Lively has a megawatt full-teeth smile. She was born in Los Angeles and raised by a talent scout and an actor. She was a cheerleader in high school. Relative to a celebrity like Jennifer Lawrence, Lively does not seem particularly approachable or down-to-earth; she seems much more like a goddess sent to give you body dysmorphia. She's the popular girl, and always has been. But those are all reasons based in envy.
Then, of course, there are the real reasons to hate her. Lively has been in the spotlight since Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants premiered in 2005, almost two decades ago. That's a lifetime in Hollywood, and plenty of time to make mistakes that everyone can see. And Lively's actual mistakes have been bad ones. In 2012, she married Ryan Reynolds on a plantation in South Carolina, a decision she apologized for eight years later in 2020. This was, somehow, not a one-off; in 2014, Lively launched a (very short-lived) online lifestyle magazine called Preserve, which included a spread titled “Allure of Antebellum.” As Kara Brown wrote for Jezebel at the time, “Anyone who romanticizes our nation's Antebellum period as some sort of marker of style and taste is definitely white and probably an asshole.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parabolic – tool to download web video and audio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139976</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/parabolic-tool-download-web-video-audio/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T14:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Parabolic is a Qt and GTK-based utility which is a frontend for yt-dlp, a feature-rich audio/video downloader.
The post Parabolic – tool to download web video and audio appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Be Merry In The Christmas Open Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177152</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/be-merry-in-the-christmas-open-thread"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T14:32:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy holidays, everyone! Feel free to hang out here and exchange glad tidings with your fellow commenters while the site enters a bit of a slumber for the next few days. 
Don't worry, there will still be some blogs under the tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Watches A Christmas Movie: ‘The Merry Gentlemen’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176461</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-watches-a-christmas-movie-the-merry-gentlemen"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T14:24:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the time of year when the best, biggest, and most ambitious movies come out. Not Oscar season, but rather that stretch when the halls of streaming services are decked with the brightly lit, thinly disguised advertisements that are the year's new Christmas movies. There are more than 100 new Christmas films to watch this holiday season, and whether that number horrifies or excites you depends upon how much of a freak you are for the festive. Sabrina is proud to say they are a real Christmas freak, and this year they asked some of their colleagues to watch some of the most, uh, available new holiday movies. The final movie in our lineup is The Merry Gentlemen, Netflix's answer to the longstanding question: How will Chad Michael Murray withstand the ravages of time?
Sabrina: Well, well, well. It’s come to this: the finale of Defector Watches A Christmas Movie. Thank you both for experiencing this movie with me, and thank you Justin for shepherding this series. Let’s get right to it: This movie operates on the premise that a big-city girl must help save her parent’s local small-town nightclub. Did your hometowns have a local nightclub? Did you ever go there, and would you consider it worth saving?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help Our Site: Suggest an Open Source Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140012</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/suggest-open-source-program/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T13:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please complete the form if you'd like us to add an open source program to our compilations.
The post Help Our Site: Suggest an Open Source Program appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flow State Best of 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-best-of-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-best-of-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T08:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s our list of our 50 favorite albums released in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Takes What He Can Get]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177133</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/elon-musk-takes-what-he-can-get"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T20:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday of last week, the richest person in the world seized control of the government of the United States. It's going to be helpful, over the next four years, to note down the events that happen, when they happen, before the next events come along.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Racing With Mortality In Norman Maclean’s ‘Young Men And Fire’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177064</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/racing-with-mortality-in-norman-macleans-young-men-and-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T19:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rachelle Hampton: Can I just say I’m so honored to be taking part in my very first DRAB? This was one of the series I was most jealous of before I joined Defector because it seemed so fun. That maybe makes it even funnier that the very first book I suggested (and the one we ended up choosing) is the biggest bummer DRAB has ever seen.
I first came across Young Men And Fire in a McNally Jackson earlier this year; I remember my attention being caught by the promise of an in-depth look at the Smokejumpers, who I’d been sort of lowkey obsessed with since reading Nora Roberts’ Chasing Fire. I’d never heard of the Mann Gulch fire or Norman Maclean really, though I realized after we picked this book that he also wrote A River Runs Through It, which I’ve seen the movie adaptation of. All to say, I was pretty stoked when y’all agreed to read it. What piqued y’alls interest?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Things We Saw In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176589</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-best-things-we-saw-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T17:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is what the Defector staff saw and enjoyed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liverpool Has The Premier League In A Stranglehold]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177051</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/liverpool-has-the-premier-league-in-a-stranglehold"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T16:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's start with a flaw. Liverpool's defense is still the best in the Premier League, having allowed 13 goals in 15 matches entering Sunday's trip to North London for a match against often-feisty but currently-shambolic Tottenham Hotspur. Virgil van Dijk is back to world-beating form, and his various partners in the center—often Ibrahima Konaté, though not for the past two months, thanks to a knee injury—have been competent enough to lead the league in goals against. However, there have been some cracks showing, and Liverpool's two previous league matches saw that dominant defense give up five combined goals to Newcastle and Fulham.
Both of those matches ended in draws, only the third and fourth blemishes in Liverpool's league season so far, and though it is unfair to put the entirety of the blame on the defense, it certainly didn't help. And so, if one were to look at just how many goals Liverpool gave up on Sunday against Tottenham, it would read like another bad day at the office for van Dijk and co. Thankfully, soccer is played in both directions, and Tottenham's three goals on its home ground only felt like feeble attempts at holding off the siege that was Liverpool's high-line-abusing attack, which scored six goals but probably could have scored 10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Dec. 23: Parting Ways]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177052</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-dec-23-parting-ways"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get your head in the game—it's time to solve the Monday crossword. This week’s puzzle was constructed by Jesse Cohn and Hoang-Kim Vu. Jesse, an oncology consultant, lives in Austin, Texas with his family and his derpy dog, and has been dunked on by two NBA players. Kim works in global public health in Washington, D.C., and is a member of the crossword editing team at Defector and AVCX. His puzzles have appeared in numerous outlets, including the New York Times, Los Angeles Times, and USA Today. 
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Got Inside Tyson Fury’s Head For A Change]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177045</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/oleksandr-usyk-got-inside-tyson-furys-head"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T15:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tyson Fury once broke an opponent’s spirit with a story. He was set to fight Wladimir Klitschko, who’d been in possession of at least one major heavyweight belt for a full decade, looking near invincible throughout his run. Few expected Fury to do much before getting knocked out. Then, in a sit-down face-off, Fury recounted a tale of a long-ago training camp in which he outlasted Klitschko in a sauna, making it out to be a battle of wills. Just before Fury revealed that Klitschko departed the hot box first, Wlad gulped like somebody was holding him at gunpoint. Fury was equally effective in the ring, so bamboozling Klitschko with feints and twitches that the longtime champion seemingly forgot to throw punches. Fury won, then rubbed a tub of salt into the wound by serenading his wife with a harrowing version of Aerosmith’s “I Don’t Want To Miss a Thing.” Klitschko stood feet away, perhaps daydreaming of new career paths and better singers.
Fury figured never to meet an opponent he couldn’t out-talk. He approached the brash knockout artist Deontay Wilder with a furious torrent of psychological warfare, then knocked him out twice in their trilogy. He surely has said the word “dosser” more than any other boxer, or Earth resident. He could be at turns nasty, earnest, bigoted, kind, or silent, but he inevitably snuck into his foes’ heads and mangled their brains before he even started punching them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Owen Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Mild week with bigger changes ahead (MON-12/23)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3767671</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-mild-week-with-bigger-changes-ahead-mon-12-23/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T15:20:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mild weather will continue for the rest of the year. There are signs of changes coming through to start 2025 and stronger signs of much colder air coming down from Canada and elsewhere to be a big player in returning to not only cold but occasional snow chances as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector’s Favorite Sports Moments Of 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176562</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/favorite-sports-moments-of-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T13:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are the sports moments from 2024 that the Defector staff enjoyed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Microsoft Calendar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139971</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-microsoft-calendar/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T13:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Calendar is a personal calendar application which offers synchronization with various calendar services. We recommend the best free and open source alternatives.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Microsoft Calendar appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hop – terminal based file explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139967</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/hop-terminal-based-file-explorer/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T11:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hop is a terminal based file explorer designed to be fast, simple and user friendly. Hop runs on any operating system.
The post Hop – terminal based file explorer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guest rec from Illuminati Hotties]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/guest-recs-from-illuminati-hotties</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/guest-recs-from-illuminati-hotties"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T08:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we have a guest recommendation from Sarah Tudzin, the American producer and frontwoman of illuminati hotties and author of IH In Motion. Her new album, POWER, is available now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Tudzin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pages CMS – content management system for static site generators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139962</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pages-cms-content-management-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T07:39:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pages CMS is a content management system for GitHub. It is well suited for static site generators (e.g. Jekyll, Next.js, VuePress, Hugo).
The post Pages CMS – content management system for static site generators appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[D Roll]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3028/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3028/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-23T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jhon Durán Can’t Stop Putting Goals On Film]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177025</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jhon-duran-cant-stop-putting-goals-on-film"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T22:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Such is the strength of the hellish vortex Manchester City is presently trapped in—Saturday's loss at Aston Villa gives the Mancs just one win from their last 12—that you almost have to start taking performances against them with a pinch of salt. City has shat the bed so regularly, keeping just one clean sheet over this stretch of misery, that it's risky to read too much into what otherwise might appear to be a statement win against the Citizens. For proof of this notion, look no further than Tottenham.
With that in mind, when you look at the scoresheet from that 2-1 Villa win and see Jhon Durán's name there, you may be tempted to discount what the goal says about the forward's talent. This would be a mistake, because Durán is scoring all the time, against everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[13 Best Free and Open Source Linux Clocks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=5847</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/clocks/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T19:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The clocks featured in this article are more sophisticated than the basic tray clock.
The post 13 Best Free and Open Source Linux Clocks appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blaze UI – framework-free UI toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139953</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/blaze-ui-framework-free-ui-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T19:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blaze UI provides structure for building websites quickly with a scalable and maintainable foundation.
The post Blaze UI – framework-free UI toolkit appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deepin Picker – simple color picker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139951</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/deepin-picker-simple-color-picker/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T19:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deepin Picker is billed as the simplest color picker.
The post Deepin Picker – simple color picker appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The College Football Playoff’s Shitty First Weekend Did Its Job]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177020</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-college-football-playoffs-shitty-first-weekend-did-its-job"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T18:48:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The College Football Playoff is a wild hit so far, in that everyone hates it. Notre Dame beat Indiana Friday in a spectacular nothingburger that turned out to be the closest game of the weekend, and the three Saturday games were the competitive equivalent of Week 2 bodybag games decided by an aggregate score of 118-51. Even the gambling conglomerates were screaming and flipping off their gigantic monitors.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=09BXg7fhijA]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rickey Henderson Believed In Rickey Henderson]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177017</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rickey-henderson-believed-in-rickey-henderson"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T15:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arrogance is that most remarkable of pejoratives because it wears Janus's mask—a bad thing in normal society but an absolute requirement in all the arts. It is never enough to have the gift; one must strut it as well. There's way more money in being the guest of honor and the DJ simultaneously, even if the self-promotional moves are now boilerplate behavior for those who have to pimp their own ride.
Which is why, in the end, Rickey Henderson, who died Friday at 65 years old, was not merely arrogant and justifiably so, but the next step beyond merely arrogant. He had the gift, but he also knew that he didn't need to sell himself except to himself, because (a) he was his own best audience, as great performers tend to be, and (b) he figured that eventually everyone else would have to see it his way. And in this case, he was right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[talking-clock – highly configurable talking clock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139945</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/talking-clock-highly-configurable-talking-clock/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T15:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[talking-clock is a highly configurable clock written in bash with soundpack and voice options. It's written in Bash.
The post talking-clock – highly configurable talking clock appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vrite – collaborative developer content platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139941</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/vrite-collaborative-developer-content-platform/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-22T07:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vrite is a collaborative space to create, manage, and deploy product documentation, technical blogs, and knowledge bases.
The post Vrite – collaborative developer content platform appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Best Free and Open Source Shutdown Timers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=96721</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-shutdown-timers/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T20:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux is blessed with an abundance of useful utilities. We feature interesting shutdown timers. Open source goodness as you'd expect.
The post 4 Best Free and Open Source Shutdown Timers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[littleutils – utilities for file compression, file manipulation, text cleanup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139935</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/littleutils-utilities-file-compression-file-manipulation-text-cleanup/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T19:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[littleutils include duplicate file finders, image optimizers, file rename tools, archive recompressors, a tempfile utility, and others.
The post littleutils – utilities for file compression, file manipulation, text cleanup appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[kleur – Node.js library for formatting terminal text with ANSI colors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139930</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/kleur-node-js-library-formatting-terminal-text/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T19:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[kleur bills itself as the fastest Node.js library for formatting terminal text with ANSI colors. It's written in JavaScript.
The post kleur – Node.js library for formatting terminal text with ANSI colors appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best Free and Open Source Replacements for ls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=70404</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-replacements-ls/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T18:48:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When invoked without any arguments, ls lists the files in the current working directory. We recommend some great replacements.
The post 10 Best Free and Open Source Replacements for ls appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shutdown Scheduler – schedule shutdown and restart tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139925</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/shutdown-scheduler-schedule-shutdown-restart-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T18:15:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shutdown Scheduler is a simple cross-platform application that uses system utilities for scheduling shutdown and restart tasks.
The post Shutdown Scheduler – schedule shutdown and restart tasks appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals, Junior Fernández Agree To Minor League Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=835404</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/12/royals-junior-fernandez-agree-to-minor-league-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T17:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have signed right-handed pitcher Junior Fernández to a minor league deal, the team announced. He last pitched in MLB during the 2022 season. Fernández signed with the Cardinals as an international free agent in 2014 and made his MLB debut in St. Louis five years later. Unfortunately, he was never able to establish…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leo Morgenstern</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making spirits bright: Our exhaustingly festive list of holiday pop-up bars in Kansas City]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862594</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/making-spirits-bright-our-exhaustingly-festive-list-of-holiday-pop-up-bars-in-kansas-city/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T15:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miracle // Photo by Sarah Sipple We’re not sure how this list continues to grow each year. Nevertheless, Kansas Citians are clearly clamoring for the merriment, and we’re here for it. From Olathe to North KC, food and drink-focused festivities abound in the KC metro. Here, The Pitch has gathered the important details, done a vibe check, and included some...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City's oldest restaurants: Where you can still eat your way through city history]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2024-12-21/oldest-restaurants-kansas-city-barbecue-history</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2024-12-21/oldest-restaurants-kansas-city-barbecue-history"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T14:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some restaurants across the Kansas City metro are still running strong after more than 100 years in business, serving up delicious meals and defining the culinary landscape for generations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hannah Bailey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Best Free and Open Source GUI Tools for System Resources Monitoring in Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139904</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-gui-tools-system-resources-monitoring/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-21T08:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tools featured in this roundup are targeted at a desktop user who wants to monitor resources being used on their machine.
The post 6 Best Free and Open Source GUI Tools for System Resources Monitoring in Linux appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>