<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-05-28T18:24:07.095Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can The NBA Still Produce Interesting Coaches?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190753</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/can-the-nba-still-produce-interesting-coaches"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T17:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like brother Magary, I have been re-energized as a fan by this year’s NBA playoffs, although I do admit that watching Jayson Tatum take one of Paris’s arrows harshed my mellow considerably—classical allusion courtesy of the Society of Jesus, circa 1974. It  was partly un-harshed by the emergence of Luke Kornet, Force of Nature. But, otherwise, it has been a voyage of discovery. I knew Anthony Edwards because my friend Tom Crean had recruited him at Georgia, but Jaden McDaniels was a complete mystery to me. I couldn’t keep Luka Doncic and Nikola Jokic straight for the longest time. Tyrese Haliburton might have been the lead singer for the Spinners for all I knew.
When did Shai Gilgeous-Alexander get this good?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charles P. Pierce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christine Brennan Won’t Rest Until Caitlin Clark’s Muscle Strain Is Treated As A National Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190789</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/christine-brennan-caitlin-clark-quad-strain-national-crisis"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T16:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Credit where credit is due: USA Today sports columnist Christine Brennan has tried very hard to establish herself as the nation's foremost Caitlin Clark alarmist. Whenever something routine for a pro athlete happens to the Indiana Fever's star, Brennan's job is to turn it into a matter of existential concern for the WNBA, a league that has 12 other teams. This week's news provided another opportunity. Crisis alert: Caitlin Clark has strained her quad. Can women's basketball as a whole possibly soldier on?
The tone of Brennan's latest column might mislead the reader into thinking that Caitlin Clark has died. In reality, the Fever guard is only sidelined for at least a couple of weeks; after Tuesday's practice she was casually putting up three-pointers. In Brennan's reality, this is a recession-level event for the WNBA:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oh God, Stuart Skinner Controls The Oilers’ Destiny]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190800</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/oh-god-stuart-skinner-controls-the-oilers-destiny"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T16:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stuart Skinner offers little in the way of championship onomatopoeia, which is to say his name does not suggest athletic greatness. It suggests the secretary-treasurer of the chess club, or an unprepared con artist trying to spontaneously impersonate Tampa Bay Rays owner Stuart Sternberg.
But Skinner owns, for now, the Stanley Cup fate of the Edmonton Oilers, and by extension the possibility that a Canadian team might win it all for the first time since 1993. As the Oilers' goaltender he has defined both the glories and horrors of being an Oil fan, because there is never a guarantee of what level of quality he will provide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s A Great Time To Be A Pathetic Loser]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190777</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-a-great-time-to-be-a-pathetic-loser"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:16:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump released yet another deranged statement on Tuesday, demanding that a transgender high school student be barred from participating in the California state track and field championships, which are scheduled to be held this weekend in Clovis, Calif. The inane thoughts that make their way from Trump's obviously diminished mind onto his Playskool social media platform should not demand the attention of any right-thinking Americans, and yet in this case the California Interscholastic Federation (CIF) snapped to attention, rewriting its qualification rules in an attempt to appease those behind what's become a national hate campaign directed at a 16-year-old high school student.
The student Trump was referring to in his post is named AB Hernandez. She is set to compete in the high jump, triple jump, and long jump at the state championships, and she has spent the past few months being harassed by a local group of bigots. This group is led by Sonja Shaw and Jessica Tapia, both members of the Save Girls Sports association. Shaw is currently running for California superintendent of public instruction, and Tapia was recently fired from her teaching position at Hernandez's high school for refusing to respect trans and nonbinary students' pronouns. At a qualification meet earlier this month, Tapia and Shaw led a group that spent hours heckling and harassing Hernandez as she competed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Champagne Socialist And The Espresso Martini Capitalist]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190785</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-champagne-socialist-and-the-espresso-martini-capitalist"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Junior high is tough for everyone. Shifting friendships! Being stuck somewhere between childhood and adolescence! All those hormones! If you’re lucky, you don’t also have to manage a parent who thinks they can backseat-drive you through all the challenges that come with being 13. 
This week, we’re off to a prestigious private school in the West Village, where our friend-of-a-friend Ellen will have to figure out how involved she wants to get in her daughter’s 8th-grade fundraising competition. Unfortunately, it seems like Ellen’s mom-nemesis, Hazel, has no intention of playing by the rules. Would it be moral to just let Hazel get away with that?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faster Is Better]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190769</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/faster-is-better"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T12:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pattern was: The New York Knicks would scramble the length of the floor in desperation—frantic, wide-eyed, bolts rattling loose, spotting passing and dribbling lanes just as they snapped shut—in search of a bucket. When they got one, it scanned most credibly as an accident. Then, whether the Knicks got one or not, the Indiana Pacers would breeze unimpeded the other way and Tyrese Haliburton would create a wide-open, high-value shot for himself or somebody else within seven seconds. That pattern leads where anybody would expect it to go. The Pacers won Game 4 of the Eastern conference final Tuesday night, 130–121, and now lead the series three games to one.
When the Pacers wasted any tightly distributed handful of the approximately infinite good looks they enjoyed on the night, the Knicks could hang around, aided by 39 free-throw attempts and an unaccountable second-quarter stretch in which they wiped away a 10-point deficit and took a one-point lead with Delon Wright on the floor and Jalen Brunson off it. (Wright found time to commit a double-dribble violation in there, and played a shade under two minutes in the second half.) But the Pacers never relented so long that they couldn't just breeze back out to a multi-possession lead with 90 seconds of focus once they locked back in. Haliburton in particular delivered what's probably, given the circumstances, the best game of his career so far: 32 points, 15 assists, 12 rebounds, four steals, and not a single turnover, despite doing the vast bulk of Indiana's ball-handling and creating over his 38 minutes. Even as his shooting cooled off after a bonkers first quarter, he maintained Indiana's lunatic pace, kept the buzzsaw whirring, and sectioned New York's defense to toothpicks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shelf abuse / Initial effort]]></title>
        <id>68364194e506350001724041</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-327/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T01:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jennie Rose Halperin on the women trying to protect the Library of Congress; a new word game for subscribers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defending the Library of Congress]]></title>
        <id>68364325e50635000172404f</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/defending-the-library-of-congress/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T01:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On May 8, Librarian of Congress Carla Hayden received an email from Trent Morse, the deputy director of White House personnel, in which he fired her with no cause “effective immediately,” “on behalf of President Donald J. Trump.” Hayden, who was nominated to serve by President]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennie Rose Halperin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing: HYDRANYM]]></title>
        <id>68362da5e506350001723fba</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/introducing-hydranym/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T01:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A word game for subscribers of FLAMING HYDRA]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dodgers So Desperate For Starting Pitching They Turn To DH]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190709</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dodgers-so-desperate-for-starting-pitching-they-turn-to-dh"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T17:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let us approach Shohei Ohtani as naively as possible, while admitting that in the case of Ohtani this decision can hardly be anything but a ruse. For the span of time that he has been on the Los Angeles Dodgers, Ohtani has been a designated hitter, and a very good one: He won the MVP last year in spite of being a designated hitter, and this year has been, depending on how you count, either the second- or third-best offensive player in MLB. The best is Aaron Judge, who is doing Aaron Judge things; the other second- or third-best player is, naturally, Ohtani's teammate Freddie Freeman; Ohtani currently has both of them, as well as every other player in MLB, beat on home run tally.
Here is what that looks like over the course of a long weekend. The Dodgers came into it in a bit of a mire: a four-game loss streak, followed by a three-game win streak, followed in turn by another loss. Then their designated hitter opened up the final game of their series against the New York Mets by doing this:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jim Irsay Can’t Meddle With The Colts Anymore, But His Kids Can]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190718</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jim-irsay-cant-meddle-with-the-colts-anymore-but-his-kids-can"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T17:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about method acting, fickle stovetops, the Colorado Rockies, and more.
Brendan:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hurricanes Avoided The Garbage Can]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190708</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-hurricanes-avoided-the-garbage-can"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T16:44:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Florida Panthers, as terrifying a hockey team as they are, have made a bit of a habit out of elongating their playoff series. Take their slow start in Toronto last round, or the three they lost while up 3-0 to the Oilers last Stanley Cup Final. In all likelihood, their shutout loss on Monday night will be just another snooze button. But after a trio of wins in the Eastern Conference Final where the Panthers used the Hurricanes like a bonfire does newspaper, the Canes earned at least one victory to hang their helmets on. If nothing else from this series goes Carolina's way—and so far, it hasn't—they'll at least have the excellent stretch of hockey that eventually delivered the game-winner in Game 4.
This action was tense until a pair of empty-netters carried the Hurricanes to a 3-0 final. But Carolina did a spectacular job limiting the defending champions' chances on net. Keeping the ice tilted has been the team's personal path to victory year after year, but against the fury, physicality, and plain old talent of Florida, the Canes shrunk into something unrecognizable as they lost three games by a combined score of 16-4. Here, however, the team out-efforted the Pants, particularly from the midpoint of the first period through a Carolina penalty late in the second. In that time, Florida produced absolutely nothing of note on offense and relied on Sergei Bobrovsky to be tidy in goal. At 0-0 with the clincher in sight, Florida might still have felt fairly comfortable, but it was Logan Stankoven who ensured that his Hurricanes' momentum would not go wasted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Maurice Is The Jack Adams Of Not Being A Jackass]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190715</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/paul-maurice-is-the-jack-adams-of-not-being-a-jackass"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T15:12:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The end of this clip is why Paul Maurice is the greatest coach of all time in any sport, in one specific category: lectern domination. The whole thing is worth a watch, as all his pressers are, pregame, postgame or even off-day, but the last 10 seconds are killer, especially if you keep in mind that his team just lost a chance to clinch a trip to the Stanley Cup Final by playing a game he admitted he "didn't like."

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pt87itZr_kc]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Overcompensating’ Is Not A Joke]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190710</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/overcompensating-is-not-a-joke"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T14:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I went into Overcompensating knowing very little, except that it was a vehicle for comic Benito Skinner. I know Skinner, like most people know him, through his @bennydrama7 Instagram account. He started it while still a high school student in Ohio—seven was the number on his football jersey—but only began posting his celebrity impressions and campy sketches as a college student at Georgetown. I specifically know him for one of my favorite bits of satire ever. I cannot for the life of me find it anymore, and my description won't do it justice, but it's basically Skinner parodying the work of Brampton bard Rupi Kaur—no one calls her that; all you need to know is that she's an extremely famous extremely terrible Instagram poet (example: “a man who cries – a gift”) who comes from a town near e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That’s What We All Want To See]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190700</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/thats-what-we-all-want-to-see"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T13:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At some point near the start of the fourth quarter of Game 4 of the Western Conference Final, in which the Oklahoma City Thunder defeated the Minnesota Timberwolves, 128-126, a thought occurred to me: These teams are playing too hard. It just didn't seem possible that an NBA game could withstand that much sustained frenzy and focus from its participants. I had a vision of several players suddenly collapsing on the floor, all of their mental and physical energy spent. I saw the fans in the arena becoming nauseous, unable to safely metabolize the potency of the basketball that was unfolding before them. Adam Silver was going to rush the court and put a stop to everything. No, no, you can't do this, he'd shout. You're going to ruin the rest of the games.
Monday's game was unquestionably the best we've had so far in these playoffs. That's an achievement in and of itself, considering how inert this series felt after the first two games, in which the Thunder seemingly established themselves as several classes above their opponent. But Minnesota caught Oklahoma City with all sorts of haymakers in Game 3, winning that one by 42, and so they came into Game 4 at the very least convinced that they could stand and trade. What resulted from that belief meeting the Thunder's resolve to avenge the embarrassment of Game 3 was a game that reached and stayed at the highest levels of intensity for 48 minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's What A Left-Wing Joe Rogan Might Sound Like]]></title>
        <id>6834ba23f649e30001830614</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/heres-what-a-left-wing-joe-rogan-might-sound-like/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T11:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The idea of a Rogan-style podcaster sympathetic to liberal causes betrays a misunderstanding of Rogan himself]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Select John Rave]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=853300</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-select-john-rave.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T16:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that they have selected the contract of outfielder John Rave. Infielder Cavan Biggio has been optioned to Triple-A Omaha as the corresponding active roster move, which was reported yesterday. The Royals had three vacancies on their 40-man roster due to Luke Maile, Chris Stratton and Hunter Renfroe recently being designated for assignment.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, May 26: Ball Don’t Lie (Themeless)]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190688</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-may-26-ball-dont-lie-themeless"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T14:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time to wrap up the month with a challenging themeless. Keep an eye out for tricky clues and fun wordplay. This week's puzzle was constructed by Geoffrey Schorkopf and Brian Callahan, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Geoffrey is an Atlanta Hawks fan. Brian is a Chicago Bulls fan. In addition to making crosswords together, they’ve bonded over mediocre basketball.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Reportedly Option Cavan Biggio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=853276</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-reportedly-option-cavan-biggio.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-26T00:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals optioned infielder Cavan Biggio to the minor leagues following the club’s game against the Twins today, according to a report from Anne Rogers of MLB.com. As a player with five years of service time, Biggio has the ability to refuse an optional assignment, and Rogers reports that he’ll be able to decide between…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Natasha Cloud Is A Kid In New York’s Candy Store]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190665</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/natasha-cloud-is-a-kid-in-new-yorks-candy-store"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T21:43:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Natasha Cloud has stopped smiling at all since mid-March, she has done so only in the privacy of her own home. She beamed when she met Ellie the Elephant at Liberty training camp last month. She and Breanna Stewart laughed it up on Cloud’s Instagram stories during a recent team excursion to Yankee Stadium. After New York’s home opener against the Aces, the crowd cheered at the sight of Cloud’s happy face on the jumbotron; she finished with 22 points, six rebounds and nine assists.
And can you blame her for smiling through it all, in disbelief of her life? The trade that sent her from Phoenix to Connecticut in exchange for Alyssa Thomas this past February scrambled the 33-year-old point guard’s plans. “I just want to be in an organization that truly invests from top to bottom: facilities, team, location, all of that. I want to compete for championships,” she said after the trade, which definitely stood in the way of all that. But then came a second trade, the biggest glamor upgrade she could hope for. Shuffled from a middle-of-the-pack Mercury team to a tanking Sun team to the defending champion Liberty, Cloud was so over and so back in the span of two months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal Met The Moment And Became Champions]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190667</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/arsenal-met-the-moment-and-became-champions"/>
        <updated>2025-05-25T20:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knockout-tournament soccer is the best soccer because of how it amplifies the sport's essence. The magic of the game lies in the tension between unpredictability and mastery. On one foot, the game is so difficult, so low-scoring, and played over such a relatively short timespan, that in 90 minutes truly anyone can beat anyone. On the other, the best players and teams are so good at dictating the encounter's terms and appearing in the match's few critical moments with touches of brilliance, that the outcome is rescued from a randomness that might render it meaningless and becomes imbued with real significance. The knockout tournament heightens both sides of this tension. Teams that reach the final do so by proving their ability to conquer entropy, but they only achieve glory by winning one last game, where anything can happen.
On Saturday, Arsenal pulled off a monumental upset by defeating Barcelona in the Women's Champions League final. While this doesn't make the Gunners necessarily the best team, it does I think make them the perfect winners of the club game's best competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suspect device]]></title>
        <id>6830e7d98d87ce0001fca408</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-326/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T00:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maria Bustillos on Sam Altman, Jony Ive, and money]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOVIE REVIEW: Sam & Jony]]></title>
        <id>6830c8608d87ce0001fca22f</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/movie-review-sam-jony/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-24T00:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Bustillos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Acquire Diego Castillo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=852993</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-acquire-diego-castillo.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T22:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have acquired infielder Diego Castillo from the Mets, according to his transactions tracker at MLB.com. He has been assigned to Triple-A Omaha. The log doesn’t specify what the Mets are receiving in return but it seems likely to be a cash deal. Castillo is a 27-year-old infielder and not to be confused with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Investigates: Is Jon Heyman Paying Too Much For Blueberries?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190590</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/is-jon-heyman-paying-too-much-for-blueberries"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a general rule, you do not want to know what sportswriters are eating. Assume that it's happening at strange times and in strange ways. Some of this is due to the specific pressures of the job; some of it is just because sportswriters are strange. Sportswriters, on balance, are probably not as strange about food as the people that talk about sports on TV—Jim Nantz orders his toast briquette style; Ian Eagle claims that he has never "ingested" a condiment; Michael Kay once said he had never tried coffee or soup, and didn't eat an egg until he was 62 years old—but sportswriters do not get paid as much, either. Just know that there are a lot of finicky habits in this industry. (Not me, though. I am normal.)
In one sense, the strangest thing about the grocery run that New York Post baseball columnist Jon Heyman posted on Twitter on Thursday is that the order itself is not very strange at all. It's the sort of stuff that a sportswriter might enjoy while writing about sports: a big container of blueberries, popcorn (unpopped), Diet Coke, and cashews. Surely Heyman has peers whose last grocery receipts are far more unsettling. But think about the items above, and how much you would pay for them at the store. Would it be nearly $50? Would you be so upset about how close it is to $50 that you post about it online?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Do You Do About A Declining President?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190645</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-do-you-do-about-a-declining-president"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T20:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter.
On Wednesday, President Donald Trump sat down for a public meeting with Cyril Ramaphosa, the president of South Africa. Perched on an armchair in the Oval Office, with the White House's newly installed gold-tone decorations stuck to the mantlepiece behind him, Trump declared that Ramaphosa is "a man certainly in some circles really respected, other circles a little bit less respected, like all of us."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dumbass Irish Rule Forcing Female Athletes To Wear Skirts Finally Repealed]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190550</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dumbass-irish-rule-forcing-female-athletes-to-wear-skirts-finally-repealed"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T17:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most embarrassing of athletic debates is over: As of midnight last night, camogie players are free to sport the bottoms of their choosing. 
At an emergency meeting of the Camogie Association held last night in Dublin to quell increasingly loud protests, delegates repealed an antiquated rule that prohibited players of the ancient Gaelic game from wearing shorts, as their male counterparts always could. The vote was one-sided: The Camogie Association said after the meeting that 98 percent of the delegates at its hastily called Croke Park summit voted to do away with the misogynistic mandate immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Mission: Impossible’ Must Finally Reckon With Tom Cruise’s Ego]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190604</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mission-impossible-must-finally-reckon-with-tom-cruises-ego"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T16:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a pleasing symmetry to the Mission: Impossible brand cycle: 30 years between the 1966 debut of the original CBS television series created by Bruce Geller to the 1996 cinematic reboot starring Tom Cruise, and again between that first film and what would appear to be the final installment of the franchise this summer with Mission: Impossible–The Final Reckoning. A childhood favorite of Cruise’s, the original show is, for anyone tempted to look back, a portal to an era of American television that was willing to be goofy. Still, Mission: Impossible was always a heist series at heart. Inspired by the 1964 film Topkapi, which features a team of thieves attempting to steal from the titular palace of Sultan Mahmud I, Mission: Impossible the show melded the heist plot with obligatory espionage elements at a time when James Bond and Get Smart followed similar trends. 
By now, almost no one thinks of the television series, so wholly has the film franchise and its zealous lead actor taken over the past three decades, weathering seachange after seachange in the already turbulent, risky landscape of Hollywood. Behind it all, of course, is Cruise himself, who began Mission: Impossible as the first project for the now-defunct Cruise/Wagner Productions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Designate Hunter Renfroe For Assignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=852981</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-dfa-hunter-renfroe.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T16:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced Friday that they’ve designated veteran outfielder Hunter Renfroe for assignment. Infielder Nick Loftin has been recalled from Triple-A Omaha in a corresponding move. Renfroe is being paid $7.5MM in the second season of a two-year, $13MM contract and will very likely be released in the coming days. More to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colossal Biosciences Can’t Have It Both Ways]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190548</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/colossal-biosciences-cant-have-it-both-ways"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:57:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 7, the New Yorker and Time ran nearly identical stories that might be better described as press releases for the de-extinction company Colossal Biosciences. The two stories differed slightly: the New Yorker's headline proclaimed "The Dire Wolf Is Back," whereas Time's announced "The Return of the Dire Wolf." While the New Yorker led with a photo of a cub, Time led with a photo of a fully grown wolf. But the effect of these stories was the same, both creating the impression that the dire wolf is indeed back after 10,000 years of extinction.
What these stories seemed less interested in was the fact that the dire wolf was, in fact, not at all back, nor will it return anytime soon. Colossal is a company that runs on PR stunts, and the latest hoopla instigated a wave of criticism from scientists seeking to set the record straight: The "dire wolf" on the cover of these glossy magazines was not a dire wolf, meaning an individual of the extinct canine species Aenocyon dirus. Instead, the "dire wolf" was a modern wolf with 20 genetic edits, none of which involved the splicing of actual dire wolf DNA. "It’s not a dire wolf. It’s misleading to call it that," Vincent Lynch, an evolutionary biologist at the University at Buffalo, told Chemical and Engineering News. “I can't explain how pissed off it made me, because they're still saying this stuff, and they know it to not be true.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rockies Fans’ Best Hope Might Be More Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190561</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rockies-fans-best-hope-might-be-more-losses"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It can be hard to tell when it is safe to officially declare a bad baseball team a historically bad one. You usually kind of know it when you see it, but passing certain mile markers allows you to affirmatively point the finger and declare: These men belong in the piss pot of history.
One such signpost arrives when words like "worst" and "since" start popping up alongside years that start with 18. The Colorado Rockies hit that point on Thursday night, after losing 2-0 to the Philadelphia Phillies to push their season record to 8-42. The Rockies are now sole owners of the worst 50-game start in baseball's modern era. You have to go all the way back to the 1895 Louisville Colonels, who started 7-43, to find a team that performed worse through its first 50 games. This team is squarely on the path trodden by the 2024 White Sox, who spent a good chunk of that campaign threatening to break the 1899 Cleveland Spiders' record for most losses in a season (134), but ultimately had to settle for the modern-era record (121). The Rockies are currently on pace to blow past the White Sox and pip the Spiders with 136 losses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Substantial Speech Seemingly Saves Sport’s Shove]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190558</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/substantial-speech-seemingly-saves-sports-shove"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two main reasons for Philadelphia Eagles fans to hate Jeffrey Lurie: He’s a billionaire, and he owns the Eagles. Under Lurie, who bought the team in 1994 from car dealership magnate Norman Braman, the Eagles have been one of the best and best-run teams in the NFL.
Whatever. It does not matter that the Eagles have won two Super Bowls in eight seasons. It does not matter that the previous owner charged players for their own socks and pads, or that the owner before that tried to sneak the team out of town. Lurie is a Philadelphia sports team owner. You should hate him! Every Philly sports fan thinks they could do a better job owning the teams they hate and care about than the people that currently own them. I myself have so many ideas. The Eagles would win eight Super Bowls in eight seasons under my ownership. I will not give any of them away here to preserve my advantage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Maurice And The Panthers Do Not Care If You’re Having Fun]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190566</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/paul-maurice-and-the-panthers-do-not-care-if-youre-having-fun"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T14:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Paul Maurice was hired out of retirement to heal the Florida Panthers' multitude of competitive leprosies, he was called in some corners "the enemy of fun." This happened because of the way he likes to play—simple, direct, minimizing open-ice flair, and emphasizing all things heavy. He is not a brutish tactician, but he recognized, without ever having the CV to prove it, that winning in April, May, and June requires a devotion to power, persistence, and crowd control in front of the net that hockey’s regular season dilettantes never seem to fully grasp.
But, and we're being fair here, Paul Maurice is indeed also the enemy of fun. We can say this because the Panthers' Eastern Conference Final series against the Carolina Hurricanes is already deeply and profoundly un-fun, in the classic only-one-team-is-getting-its-way way. Beating the 'Canes on Thursday night by the frankly rude score of 5-0 was lopsided enough, but other than an offside call that negated Carolina's only real chance of the night, that score was actually a kindness. Put another way, through the first 40 minutes, the only two differences between the 'Canes and Angel Reese were a) there were 17 more of them than her, and b) she got off more shots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Music Club Really Really Really Really Really Really Likes Carly Rae Jepsen]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190523</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-music-club-really-really-really-really-really-really-likes-carly-rae-jepsen"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T14:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Defector Music Club, where a number of our writers get together to dish about an album. Today, Kathryn Xu, Lauren Theisen, Luis Paez-Pumar, and Kelsey McKinney reminisce over Carly Rae Jepsen's underappreciated pop classic Emotion, which is about to turn 10 years old.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pirates Avoid Historic Humiliation, Suffer Regular Kind Instead]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190552</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/pirates-avoid-historic-humiliation-suffer-regular-kind-instead"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T12:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pittsburgh Pirates scored more than four runs in a baseball game for the first time in a month, but because they are the Pittsburgh Pirates, the price of that victory was not only that it was actually another defeat, but that anyone who went to PNC Park to watch it had to sit through a one-hour, fifty-minute rain delay to find out that they can still make five runs look like two. The fan giveaway for the night was a dose of the flu, which all things considered is a metaphorical kiss on the top of the head.
Yes, it's Pirates Baseball in 2025, where the "don't mind me, I'm just cowboy-sneezing in your beer" coupon is included in the price of the ticket.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Release Chris Stratton]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=852454</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-designate-chris-stratton-for-assignment.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T03:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 22: Stratton was released as expected, according to the MLB.com transaction log. May 18: The Royals announced that right-hander Chris Stratton has been designated for assignment.  Fellow righty Jonathan Bowlan was called up from Triple-A in the corresponding move. The DFA probably closes the book on what has been a disappointing season-plus for Stratton…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Police theories]]></title>
        <id>682fcd7c8d87ce0001fc903f</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-325/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T02:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arwa Mahdawi on the 1996 disappearance of Susan Walsh]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Solve a Murder: Part Six]]></title>
        <id>682facb08d87ce0001fc8fca</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/how-to-solve-a-murder-part-six/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T02:09:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 1996, 36-year-old Susan Walsh supposedly left her house in New Jersey and never came back. She is presumed dead but a body has never been found. This is Part Three of a series on my five-year investigation into her unsolved disappearance.
To catch up, here are Part]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arwa Mahdawi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bread And Butter And Bad Faith]]></title>
        <id>682f662df649e3000182fa4d</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/bread-and-butter-and-bad-faith/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T20:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez is the ultimate “kitchen table” politician, whether Republicans like it nor not (they do not).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bread And Butter And Bad Faith]]></title>
        <id>682f662df649e3000182fa4d</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/bread-and-butter-and-bad-faith/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T20:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez is the ultimate “kitchen table” politician, whether Republicans like it nor not (they do not).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes Of Sparkling Authoritarianism, With Jason Steinhauer]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190445</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/notes-of-sparkling-authoritarianism-with-jason-steinhauer"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T18:54:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems safe to say, at this point, that the retrospectively rather quaint debate over whether Trumpism, as a political movement and a politics in itself, could or should be described as "fascist" has been settled. The bad news is in how we got to that answer, and in the bad news that every day brings. And with that colossally dispiriting answer come a whole bunch of new questions about what is to be done, and where we actually are, and how to get from here to the other side of things. This week, we were joined by Jason Steinhauer, the historian behind the History Club newsletter and the bestseller History, Disrupted, to discuss those questions, and the historical and cultural forces that created them, and to start working toward some answers. Also, hilariously, we discussed the NBA playoffs at the end.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations, You Are Officially Having A Better Day Than Several Celebrities]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190527</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/congratulations-you-are-officially-having-a-better-day-than-several-celebrities"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrities are human beings, sure, but they don't move through life like the rest of us do. They will feel sadness and pain and disappointment many times during their years on Earth, just like you and I, but unlike you and I they will maintain access to all the blessings that money and talent and beauty bring them. For the most part, we only ever get to see them in the latter state, and it's easy to conclude that all that good stuff they have makes their lives invariably better than ours on a day-to-day basis.
Sports can be an equalizer in this regard. Think about how bad the days after your worst moments as a sports fan felt. Every time my favorite team gets eliminated from the playoffs, I end up going through the next day in a sickly daze, feeling much like I did the morning after the 2016 election. This is not rational, but it is what being a sports fan does to my brain. Now imagine how much more intense that awful feeling is hitting Knicks fans today, hours after they witnessed their team cough up a playoff game in unthinkable fashion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Goals, Six Minutes, No Response]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190524</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/three-goals-six-minutes-no-response"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T17:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hockey's longstanding fetish for self-effacement got its best material reward in years on Wednesday night, thanks to an amazing comeback win that was at best fifth on the list of anyone’s notice, and that includes you finally doing your laundry. The Dallas Stars parlayed a well-earned 3-1 deficit through two periods of Game 1 of the Western Conference Final into a hilarious 6-3 victory over the much better regarded Edmonton Oilers, and what do they get as the new day dawns?
Crickets in a coma, that's what they get.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Earned Time Act Would Bring Freedom To Those Who Need It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190516</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-earned-time-act-would-bring-freedom-to-those-who-need-it"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:35:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April 2025, The Earned Time Act was approved by the New York State Corrections Committee, a small but meaningful step in the proposed law's arduous legislative pathway. This bill, which still needs to pass through the Assembly and Senate before being signed by the Governor and enacted into law, expands the amount of "good time" prisoners can earn off our sentences when we avoid disciplinary sanctions and complete our mandatory programs. Currently, New York State prisoners serving time for violent offenses can earn up to 15 percent of good time. Under the new law, we will be able to earn up to 50 percent of good time, along with an additional 25 percent of "merit time" for those who obtain a college degree or complete other volunteer programs, such as providing long-term tutoring for pri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Pastore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Slogged Its Way To Glory]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190489</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tottenham-slogged-its-way-to-glory"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T16:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know what I expected from a European final between the 16th- and 17th-placed teams in the Premier League, but it wasn't that. Maybe I was fooled by the stature of Tottenham Hotspur and Manchester United as two of the biggest clubs in England, or maybe I figured that a final would bring out the best of two sides just crawling through a doomed domestic season in hopes that summer cures all ills. Instead, the 2025 Europa League final was ass. Butt. Garbage. Nevertheless, at the end of 90 painful minutes, there was a light at the end of this sewage pipe of a match: For the first time since 2008, Tottenham won a trophy.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ORAVVJvpHt0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rockies: While Other Cartoons Are Zany, Snoopy Reminds Us Of The Horrors Of World War I]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190491</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rockies-while-other-cartoons-are-zany-snoopy-reminds-us-of-the-horrors-of-world-war-i"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Colorado Rockies are 8-41. Wednesday night’s 9-5 loss to the Phillies was their fourth in a row. Their .163 winning percentage is the worst in baseball. They have scored 164 runs and allowed 321. No one on the team’s hitting over .288; Ryan Feltner is the only starter with an ERA under 5.00. They are really bad.
This naturally makes it hard for in-house media to find anything positive to say about the team. By going out there every day and Being The Rockies, the worst team in the sport seems to have broken the brains of its PR team. Purple Row writer Renee Dechert snapped this photo at last night’s game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Close Reading Is For Everyone]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190204</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/close-reading-is-for-everyone"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T14:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Sigrid Nunez’s 2018 novel The Friend, a famous writer kills himself. Not long before, he complains to the narrator about readers: “People talking about a book as if it were just another thing, like a dish, or a product like an electronic device or a pair of shoes, to be rated for customer satisfaction—that was just the goddamn trouble.” Students submit papers that say, “I hate Joyce, he’s so full of himself.” Online reviewers imply, “if a book didn’t affirm what the reader already felt—what they could identify with, what they could relate to—the author had no business writing the book at all.” The famous author quits teaching, quits writing. The state of the novel, its place in the world, is too depressing.
“But hasn’t it always been this way?” asks the narrator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Sinykin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What The Hell Is Going On Here?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190478</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-the-hell-is-going-on-here"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T13:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I made a fateful decision ahead of the Eastern Conference Finals. I think it was Sunday. The night before, the New York Knicks had finished off the defending champion Boston Celtics. The Indiana Pacers were already waiting around, having thrashed the East's top seed in five games. It took me into Sunday to go huh, Pacers-Knicks. Do I care about that? I considered this deeply, the way one might ponder a puppy in a pet-shop window. Am I prepared to give my heart to this stupid thing? I decided, yes, I would buy the puppy. I activated the button inside my brain that allows for a feeling of cheesedness to adhere to a matchup between these two specific franchises, in a conference final, in 2025.
You see, I am old enough to remember a little thing we used to call the 1990s. The Knicks and Pacers were good teams then, back when making the playoffs used to mean something. There was a stretch, starting in 1993, when these two teams eliminated each other six times in eight years. Do not look up how many titles they combined to win over this period! The point is that a great deal of animosity built up between them, and many goofy narratives blossomed from the rivalry, and the whole era kicked ass. These teams played to Game 7s in 1994 and 1995 (and again last year), and met in consecutive conference finals in 1999 and 2000. Reggie Miller became a folk hero; guys like Dale Davis, Charles Smith, and Travis Best were pressed temporarily but firmly into mainstream basketball discourse. John Starks brushed perilously close to bozodom. Yes, I am now openly pandering to readers of my generation, but such is my prerogative. Basketball was aesthetically better in 1997! No one can stop me! Ha ha!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diplomatic interpreter / Ambassador Hotel]]></title>
        <id>682e4462d6420400019d1cec</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-324/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T22:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Egyptian writer Ibrahim Fawzy talks with Kọ́lá Túbọ̀sún; Jack Pendarvis and Ace on condiments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ace Goes to Hollywood: Episode 6]]></title>
        <id>682e3ebad6420400019d1c8a</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/ace-goes-to-hollywood-episode-6/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T22:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ace Goes to Hollywood is a continuing transcript of a ride from Oxford, Mississippi, to Memphis, Tennessee, during which Jack Pendarvis interviewed Ace Atkins about his work on the Pauly Shore film Jury Duty.
Episode 6: I Want to Talk About Mayonnaise
JACK: I’m already running out of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Pendarvis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Translating Africa]]></title>
        <id>682ca429d3456a00019444af</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/translating-africa/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T22:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ibrahim Fawzy is an award-winning Egyptian writer and literary translator. His recent translation of Hassan Akram’s “A Plan to Save the World” was published in the 2025 edition of Best Literary Translations, which I co-edit; “When We Left Home” by Yousri Alghoul was published]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kọ́lá Túbọ̀sún</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Walker Buehler Gets Tossed Early, Posts Through It Late]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190430</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/walker-buehler-gets-tossed-early-posts-through-it-late"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T19:43:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday’s Mets-Red Sox game marked a return to action for both Red Sox starter Walker Buehler and manager Alex Cora. Buehler was put on the IL with a shoulder injury on May 2; the inflammation cleared up fast enough that he was activated Tuesday morning without any rehab assignment. Cora’s absence was even briefer: To the ire of one Boston talk radio guy, Cora missed Monday’s game to attend his daughter’s college graduation.
“It’s not like they need him there to make the pitching change or lay down the bunt. It’s the leadership and optics of the whole thing,” 98.5 The Sports Hub host Michael Felger said. I can understand being hard up for story ideas; a Boston radio host probably didn’t think he’d have to talk baseball in late May.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Packers Attempt To Get Tush Push Banned, Fail To Convert]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190446</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/packers-attempt-to-get-tush-push-banned-fail-to-convert"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T19:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten NFL teams voted against banning the Tush Push today, leaving the Philadelphia Eagles free to convert short-yardage plays at will. Somewhere inside of a Tilted Kilt, a freshly extended Nick Sirianni busts out his finest shit-eating grin in exultation.
As befitting the play itself, the Eagles had to grind this one out. The Tush Push was in grave danger of being outlawed two months ago when the Green Bay Packers had seemingly amassed a quorum of votes (24 were needed) to get their No Butt Stuff proposal approved at the NFL owners meetings. At the time, Packers coach Matt LaFleur derided the Tush Push as being too “rugby”-ish to belong in football (American football has its origins in rugby). The organization also considered the play a safety risk (competition committee chairman Rich McKay said there was no statistical evidence that the play is more dangerous than any other) and caused “pace of play” issues (uh, OK). No sane person bought any of those arguments. Whether the Packers were acting on their own behalf or at the nudging of commissioner Roger Goodell, who is rumored to abhor the Tush Push, the intent was always transparent: We can’t keep letting the Eagles get away with this. Given what I know about the Eagles and their fans, that’s normally a sentiment I’m down with. But not this time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Time To Start The “Rich Hill Is BACK” Countdown]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190440</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-time-to-start-the-rich-hill-is-back-countdown"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T17:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody takes a hint less well than Rich Hill, and conversely nobody proves prevailing wisdom wrong more often than Rich Hill. With this in mind, we can again say one of the best-loved and certainly most frequently repeated sentences in contemporary baseball: Rich Hill is BACK!
His generic name aside, Rich Hill has been eased out of more throwing-related major league jobs than anyone this side of Josh Johnson, though in fairness this is Hill’s 24th year in professional baseball, and he is 45 years old. But when he signed a minor league deal with the injury-ravaged Kansas City Royals, it just felt right. When he pitched his first game for the Royals' Arizona Complex League team yesterday against the Chicago Cubs' representatives, it went swimmingly—four innings, 12 hitters, 12 outs, seven strikeouts. There is more work to be done, but go ahead and say it: Rich Hill is totally BACK!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journalism’s Slop Crisis Started Long Before That AI-Generated Summer Insert]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190366</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/journalisms-slop-crisis-started-long-before-that-ai-generated-summer-insert"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T17:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The saddest stories in local news are the ones where the body has been left to sit for a while. I worked in local news for the first decade of my journalism career, and that often meant writing about people who died. Sometimes people died after a long and glorious life; all too often, they died far too young, and in easily avoidable tragedies. But every now and then a news release would come across my desk from local law enforcement asking for help identifying a body that they had found, and along with it a slew of horrible questions: How long had this person been dead? Did anyone notice they were gone? Death comes for all of us, but not all deaths are equal. Some are more cruel than others.
I remembered that feeling Tuesday, when news broke that the Chicago Sun-Times and The Philadelphia Inquirer had both published a special section—HEAT INDEX Your Best of Summer Guide—whose recommended summer reading list included a bunch of made-up books by real authors, the names and titles thrown together seemingly at random. It got worse from there. When reporters from 404 Media and later The Atlantic contacted the person who wrote the summer book list, he explained that he wrote it—or, anyway, put it together—using ChatGPT, and then had just forgotten to double check the work before submitting it to the company that had commissioned it, King Features, a division of newspaper publisher Hearst. The words, seemingly still unread by anyone who'd notice or care that they were mostly nonsense, then got shoveled along. Hearst packaged the words, then licensed the section to various newspapers, which duly printed it out and included it in their Sunday editions. If anyone did notice the many mistakes along the way, they sure didn't stop them. No surprise, a lot of writers and readers got very mad about this online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spike Lee’s Malcolm X Still Lives]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190274</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/spike-lees-malcolm-x-still-lives"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T16:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spike Lee didn't invent the floating dolly shot, but he did make it his signature move. It's not just in his repeated use of the technique, but rather in his understanding of its storytelling potential. In Mo' Better Blues, the dolly shot captured Bleek's obsession with his trumpet and how it mirrored the devotion he brought to sex with his two girlfriends. In Clockers, the dolly showed how Strike's lifestyle of selling drugs, running from the cops, and being accused of a murder was destroying him both physically and mentally. In 25th Hour, the dolly captured both Mary's drunken euphoria as a young woman at a party as well as Jacob's out-of-body experience after abdicating responsibility for a moment. Spike uses the dolly to help him imbue his characters with depth, psychology, and conflict without uttering a word. In other hands, the dolly is often deployed at significant moments, or sometimes at seemingly mundane ones just to add some visual flair. Rarely does a Spike joint use the dolly as the definitive moment of his work. In fact, as far as I can remember there is only one Spike Lee movie in which the entirety of the film builds up to one particular dolly shot.

https://youtu.be/YPyrYP7kku4?feature=shared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brie Is A Promise]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190420</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/brie-is-a-promise"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my friends loves to say “buy the ticket, take the ride”—usually referencing the giant smothering cloud of apprehension and nausea that hits before the good part of the shroom trip (not that I’d know anything about that). But I feel as though this is a lesson that people who do it for the plot need to learn. If you take a bold stance or make a grand gesture, that’s an invitation to the world to match your freak. 
I can get behind the decision to have a sweet little date night with someone you just met while traveling abroad. I feel like there’s a Linklaterian mutual romanticization that can happen easily under those circumstances, and you can part ways feeling proud of your adventuresome spirit. But my sympathy ends there. When you decide to set up a surprise breakfast picnic for your date the next day, complete with soft cheese and flowers, you are buying a ticket. And today, dear listeners, you are in for a ride.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helen Frankenthaler Is A Reason To Go To Rochester]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190259</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/helen-frankenthaler-is-a-reason-to-go-to-rochester"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank god my Amtrak was only 20 minutes late.
I arrived in Rochester on Friday afternoon ahead of a top-secret non-Defector work mission, and my train stopped just in time for me to hustle over to the city's Memorial Art Gallery. I'm never good at determining in advance if a museum is the kind you spend one hour at or a whole day inside, so I was pleasantly surprised by the depth of Rochester's collection—an absorbing first floor of American art (including Nick Cave's ornithophilic "End Upheld") and a beautiful second floor of historical international pieces with a baroque Italian organ at the center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For The Panthers And Thunder, The Worse The Better]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190403</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/for-the-panthers-and-thunder-the-worse-the-better"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rule is simple and straightforward, and it rarely proves anything but true: Judgments made after Game 1 of any series will tend to return to embarrass the impulsive jurist who made them. Still, both in Oklahoma City and Raleigh last night, we learned one distinct commonality between the Thunder and Florida Panthers. While playing entirely different sports in different locations, they maintain the same general philosophical approach, which is to make your experience as an opponent so unpleasant that their experience as a combatant comes to be defined by yours as the supplicant.
In other words, they win by making you miserable. If they happen to elevate the art of their respective games along the way, well, that would be a happy but entirely unintended consequence of the main task. Their joy is in your frustration. Their satisfaction is derived from your impotence. The worse it gets, the better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shai Gilgeous-Alexander Makes It Feel Bad]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190387</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/shai-gilgeous-alexander-makes-it-feel-bad"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T14:41:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was a sequence in the first quarter of Game 1 of the Western Conference Finals where the Oklahoma City Thunder used a drive-and-kick and a swing pass to get the ball to versatile young noodleman Chet Holmgren, who'd floated to a whiteboard-perfect shooting position out above the break. Naz Reid of the visiting Timberwolves hastened to close out on Holmgren, who is a danger from deep. Holmgren showed a decent enough pump-fake to cause Reid to overcommit, and then darted to his right for a straight-line drive to the cup. Chasing a ball-handler from 27 feet is a tall ask for a big man, and here Reid was cleanly beaten. Holmgren's handles are certainly adequate to this task, and anyway all he needs is one dribble to get from the arc to a controlled one-foot gather. The last man back was Donte DiVincenzo, and DiVincenzo was late. This looked like a dunk.
Reid is quicker than Holmgren, and his movement patterns are more recognizably humanoid, so he was never far from the play. As Holmgren gathered for take-off, Reid sprinted on an intercepting path and used his chest to deflect Holmgren off of the runway. The impact slowed Holmgren's momentum—Holmgren still has the physique of someone who needs to speed-eat 100,000 beef sandwiches—which allowed Reid to make a reasonably controlled contest of what became a stalled, off-balance layup. The ball rimmed out, the Timberwolves gathered the defensive rebound, and the action flowed the other way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poll: Should The Royals Be Worried About Salvador Perez?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=852632</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/poll-should-the-royals-be-worried-about-salvador-perez.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T21:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran catcher Salvador Perez is the face of the Royals franchise, the last man standing from the club’s 2015 World Series team, and a nine-time All-Star with five Gold Gloves and five Silver Sluggers to his name. He’s one of the most important players in the organization’s history, and in that sense the 35-year-old’s legacy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juan Soto’s Mets Era Is Off To A Slow, Silly Start]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190229</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/juan-sotos-mets-era-is-off-to-a-slow-silly-start"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T21:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Mets are in a chumpy way at the moment. They have scored 10 runs in their last six games and have just one home run over that stretch. If you look at this from the perspective of wanting the Mets to score runs, that is annoying, but it is also probably not very important. Even very good teams will phase in and out of chump mode over the course of a long season, because that is the nature of the baseball season and also the nature of baseball. This doesn't make it less annoying when it happens to a team you care about, and sometimes teams that are expected to be good really do turn out not to be. But because this sort of thing is so inextricably a part of baseball, there's nothing to do but figure out how to discern what's noise and what isn't, and then get to work ignoring everything that deserves to be ignored.
For instance: the Los Angeles Dodgers have allowed 32 runs in their last 36 innings, which covers a four-game losing streak during which they were swept in a three-game series at Dodger Stadium, by the Angels; in a loss on Monday night, they swung at 42 of Diamondbacks starter Brandon Pfaadt's 93 pitches, didn't miss any of them, and had a .000 batting average on balls in play. They have 29 wins, a .604 winning percentage, and are in first place in the National League West. They have real problems—a number of starting pitchers with a number of variously severe or worryingly vague injuries, most notably—but they are not bad. It would be reasonable for a fan to get mad, watching this highly credentialed team blast one Brandon Pfaadt pitch after another directly at a waiting Diamondback fielder. Anything more than that would be ... well, no one gets into being a fan of a baseball team to be reasonable. But it would be excessive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are We Human, Or Are We Slayer?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=189963</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/are-we-human-or-are-we-slayer"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:34:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For over four decades, I was terrified of Slayer. This isn’t terribly surprising because Slayer is Slayer and, more important, I was a child of the 1980s. We 80ennials were taught to fear many things: strangers with candy, masked serial killers, drugs, drug dealers, and hot sex. Anything in the cultural firmament that wasn’t a rerun of Happy Days could corrupt your innocence permanently.
Popular music wasn’t immune to this cultural puritanism. The Tipper Gores of the country were barnstorming the media throughout that whole decade, warning American families that Ozzy Osbourne was biting the heads off of bats, that Judas Priest was encouraging kids to commit suicide, and that Madonna was dry humping award show stages. These artists were poisoning young minds, and something had to be done to prevent it. Perhaps a very small warning label on every album cover would do the trick.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unkindly cut]]></title>
        <id>682c914037814f000188af10</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-323/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T19:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yemisi Aribisala on the difficulty of keeping one’s head]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Violence Against Hair]]></title>
        <id>682a5c8237814f000188995d</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/violence-against-hair/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T18:56:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My revenge, I decided very early, would be to achieve a power which outlasts kingdoms. 		— James Baldwin
The young lady’s parents turned up on a whim to visit her. Or so it seemed, but the drive from Lagos to the university in the city of Ile-Ife was]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yemisi Aribisala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chicago Sun-Times And Philadelphia Inquirer Publish Huge Summer Insert Of Pure, Uncut Chatbot Slop]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190271</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/chicago-sun-times-and-philadelphia-inquirer-publish-huge-summer-insert-of-pure-uncut-chatbot-slop"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:57:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over this past weekend, the Chicago Sun-Times and Philadelphia Inquirer's weekend editions included identical huge "Best of Summer" inserts; in the Inquirer's digital edition the insert runs 54 pages, while the entire rest of the paper occupies 36. Before long, readers began noticing something strange about the "Summer reading list for 2025" section of the insert. Namely, that while the list includes some very well-known authors, most of the books listed in it do not exist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ange Postecoglou, Tottenham’s Lovably Embattled Idealist, Stands On The Brink Of Redemption]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190268</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ange-postecoglou-tottenhams-lovably-embattled-idealist-stands-on-the-brink-of-redemption"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Hotspur has lost 21 times this season and sits 17th in the Premier League table—unimaginable for a club of its size and resources. While attempting to play the progressive attacking game mandated by their second-season manager Ange Postecoglou—an enigmatic style known as Angeball—Spurs’ players have often looked like they have forgotten, and possibly never knew, how to pass at all. Against Chelsea in April, Tottenham's own fans chanted "you don't know what you're doing" at the manager. For months, the pundits have screeched a common refrain: "Why hasn’t Ange been fired already?"
And on Wednesday, when Tottenham plays Manchester United in the Europa League final, Ange has a chance to salvage it all. A win would be the club’s first trophy in 17 years, its first European trophy since 1984, and would spell a return to the Champions League. It’s a ridiculous situation made even more so by the manager’s early-season reference to his track record: at every team he’s ever managed for multiple years—Australian clubs South Melbourne and Brisbane Roar, the Australian national team, Japan’s Yokohama F. Marinos, and Scotland’s Celtic—he’s won something in his second year. To the last few hardcore Angeball defenders still out there among Spurs fandom, myself among them, it would be sweet redemption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amos Barshad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Of Basketball’s Brightest Young Stars Will Compete For More Than A Trip To The Finals]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190262</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/two-of-basketballs-brightest-young-stars-will-compete-for-more-than-a-trip-to-the-finals"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T17:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the NBA conference finals matchups set, the most interesting narrative question of these playoffs has been answered. Would the veteran-laden squads who'd done it before triumph again, or would the new generation put their elders out to pasture? The second round was a clear referendum in favor of the zoomer uprising, with the last three champions—the Boston Celtics, Denver Nuggets, and Golden State Warriors—getting eliminated. 
When the confetti falls a month from now, the seventh different champion in as many years will hoist the trophy. The four remaining teams have won one title between them—two if you feel that the 1979 Seattle SuperSonics title travels (the Oklahoma City Thunder themselves don't wear the gold patch)—and that one was over 50 years ago. Something new is going to happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Put Pete Rose In The Hall Of Fame So That I Can Forget About Him]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190264</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/put-pete-rose-in-the-hall-of-fame-so-that-i-can-forget-about-him"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T16:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about weed, old man smell, dying in a tornado, and more.
Ben:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Injuries Are Really Starting To Crank on the Royals Rotation]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=463997</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/injuries-are-really-starting-to-crank-on-the-royals-rotation/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With two more starters out hurt, the team's rotational depth could turn from a question mark into one of those question marks that's directly followed by an exclamation point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davy Andrews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jessica Berman Makes Her Priorities Clear]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190256</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jessica-berman-makes-her-priorities-clear"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T14:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the 74th minute of Angel City’s May 9 game against the Utah Royals, Angel City defender Savy King collapsed on the field. She was immediately tended to by medical staff, who performed chest compressions. Once she was stable, she was carted off the field and transported to a hospital by ambulance. Other players appeared emotional during the stoppage of play. Ten minutes after King collapsed, the match continued. 
After the game finally ended, players hugged and cried. Utah player Alex Loera, who was teammates with King last year at Bay FC, led the teams in a prayer circle. Shortly after that, Christen Press was interviewed on the broadcast. She had scored her first goal of the season—it was a signature Press how’d you make that ball move like that? shot—just a few minutes before King collapsed. But her focus wasn’t on the win at all. “I think this game has been very emotional, very tough. All of us are praying for Savy, our teammate. … She is on our hearts and minds and that’s really all I can think about right now,” Press said. “It was a really, really emotional game.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abigail Segel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ten Frames Of Time Travel]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190233</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ten-frames-of-time-travel"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T13:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[METRO DETROIT — It’s early Sunday evening on the last weekend of April, and I’m perched beside a currently-out-of-use lane in a dimly lit section of Thunderbowl Lanes in Allen Park, Mich. On this particular weekend, Thunderbowl was the site of the Professional Bowlers Association’s Battle of the Brands, and after a raucous finale, the hubbub has subsided. The crew members are switching off the bright lights that illuminated the lanes for TV. Pro bowlers quietly weave in and out of the event zone to collect their ball bags. Most of the adoring fans who packed the stands have headed home. A few remain, eagerly waiting along the edge of barricaded lanes with signs and jerseys, hoping for a parting memory with their bowling heroes. Then there is my mother, sunken into the bleachers, heart heavy with history as she takes in the scene. But we’ll get back to that.
My gaze wanders across the massive bowling center—in modern-day bowling parlance, bowling alley is out, and bowling center is in. Thunderbowl Lanes is a curious convergence of future and past. The laneside computers are up-to-date, the screens work, the place is clean and more than equipped to host events like Battle of the Brands. But the carpet has a busy retro pattern, the bartop tables whisper echoes of the 70s, and the lettering out front eschews modern minimalism for a nostalgic chunky design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Bice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Wizard of X Has Been Exposed]]></title>
        <id>682c99c7faf3c400018a308c</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/the-wizard-of-x-has-been-exposed/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That someone was caught manipulating an AI chatbot to push a fascist agenda is a big deal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty Schmidt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Wizard of X Has Been Exposed]]></title>
        <id>682c99c7faf3c400018a308c</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/the-wizard-of-x-has-been-exposed/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That someone was caught manipulating an AI chatbot to push a fascist agenda is a big deal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dusty Schmidt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Designate Luke Maile For Assignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=852571</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/05/royals-designate-luke-maile-for-assignment.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T19:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that right-hander Taylor Clarke has been reinstated from the paternity list. Catcher Luke Maile has been designated for assignment as the corresponding move. The club’s 40-man roster count drops from 39 to 38. Maile, 34, signed a minor league deal with the Royals in the offseason and was selected to the big…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remote underground / Readers’ choice]]></title>
        <id>6827a3b837814f0001889619</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-322/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brian Hioe on the distant music scene in China; POLL results!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Listening from Afar]]></title>
        <id>6827967937814f000188958f</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/listening-from-afar/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My latest thing to listen to while working has been online Chinese underground electronic music streaming programs. I’ve always liked streaming programs, in which you can see the DJ playing live and sometimes a live crowd in the background. The most famous of them, I believe, is Boiler]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Hioe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[POLL results!!]]></title>
        <id>682b376837814f0001889a45</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/poll-results/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T18:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a fiery writer-owned cooperative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Orioles Are Nowhere]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190126</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-orioles-are-nowhere"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T17:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Mansolino has been put in a tough position. It is his job today to engineer a turnaround for the most disappointing team in baseball. The Baltimore Orioles fired manager Brandon Hyde Saturday morning, after the team played sloppily and stranded a billion baserunners in a loss Friday night, their fourth in a row and 10th in 12 games. No one on earth could credibly claim that Hyde is bad at managing a baseball team: He took over in Baltimore when they were hopeless garbage, stuck it out through years of deliberate organizational ass-shitting, and then notched a dominant 100-win season the very first time he was handed a genuinely professional-grade roster. Along the way Hyde earned some managerial accolades and helped the O's to just their second first-place finish of this millennium. There is no question that Hyde can lead a very good baseball team.
The Orioles of 2025 stink real bad. They're 10th-worst in the majors by team OPS, and are second-worst in the majors by team ERA. Hunt around in the cool math if you must—Orioles hitters are generally underperforming their perfectly respectable expected numbers, per Statcast—but the very basic formula there is pretty straightforward: Baltimore's pitching staff allows too many runs, and their vaunted lineup is not doing anywhere near enough slugging to make up the difference. This team was talked-up as a World Series contender. With their eerily homogenized core of ultra-hyped position players, 2025 should be safely inside the early part of a long championship-or-bust era. Instead they are a last-place team, 11.5 games back of the Yankees and with a run differential that is second-worst in the majors, ahead of only the Colorado Rockies, who are a blight on the sport.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Stage Is Set For A Wild Serie A Finale]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190127</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-stage-is-set-for-a-wild-serie-a-finale"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T17:03:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Across Europe's so-called top five men's leagues—the Premier League, La Liga, Serie A, Ligue 1, and the Bundesliga—there is little intrigue left in the season. Germany and France both wrapped up their 34-match leagues this past weekend, crowning familiar champions in Bayern Munich and Paris Saint-Germain with plenty of time left over. Liverpool clinched the Premier League title at the end of April, and Barcelona claimed its trophy last Thursday.
While there are still some battles to be had over Champions League qualification in England—where five teams vie for three spots—and a relegation struggle between Espanyol and Leganés in Spain, there's not much action at the top of European soccer heading into the final weekend of the season, save for in Italy, where there's a title race, a fight for the Champions League places, and a five-team brawl to escape relegation. The best drama coming up in this final weekend of domestic soccer will be in Italy, and there's so much to play for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Short Farewell To The NHL’s Second-Round Losers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190148</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-short-farewell-to-the-nhls-second-round-losers"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T16:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're down to four teams in the NHL playoffs, and they are without a doubt deserving contenders. Before I get too excited about the hockey to be contested in Stars-Oilers and Hurricanes-Panthers, however, I want to briefly look back at every squad that got knocked out in the second round. Here they are, in chronological order of the ends of their seasons.
Vegas Golden Knights]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carlos Alcaraz Keeps Smiling At Jannik Sinner’s Expense]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190174</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/carlos-alcaraz-keeps-smiling-at-jannik-sinners-expense"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carlos Alcaraz’s shotmaking style is of the gonzo variety: He’ll opt for the unlikely winner attempt whenever possible, even when safe options are available. As a consequence, Alcaraz at his best is among the most viscerally thrilling spectacles in sports. At his worst, he could play against a potted plant and enable convincing arguments that the plant has better court sense. Through six points of his first-set tiebreak with No. 1-ranked Jannik Sinner in the Italian Open final on Sunday, Alcaraz had seemingly heeded his critics and pursued reliable patterns. He opened up a 4-2 lead with a backhand pass just good enough to force an error, then a few big serves sprinkled on top. Very effective, nothing that made the highlight reel. 
Then the players switched ends of the court, and Alcaraz couldn’t help reverting to type. He double faulted. He mashed an errant forehand down the line instead of hitting the appropriate, neutral ball crosscourt. But on set point, Alcaraz conjured a masterpiece. He took immediate control of the point despite Sinner landing a first serve, slashing heavy forehands deep into the court that forced Sinner back. He fired a backhand down the line, stretching Sinner out just a bit, then pranced to the net. While running to his right, Alcaraz chopped his volley short and gentle to his left, working against all his forward momentum. Airborne on the follow-through, his right foot flew up almost to head-height. Nothing about it looked right. It worked perfectly. Alcaraz won the tiebreak with that on-brand brilliance, then tore through the second set, 6-1, to win his first Italian Open title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Owen Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Something’s Over In Toronto]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190122</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/somethings-over-in-toronto"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about the last decade of Maple Leafs hockey can be found in the Panthers' third and backbreaking goal of Florida's Game 7 shitkicking. Toronto was getting outskated, and under fire in a barrage unequaled by any team all year. They had held, until they hadn't: two goals four minutes apart had stunned the building into a queasy silence. The next one felt like the decider for this game—and this series, this season, this era. A Leafs goal would put them right back in it; a Cats tally the bursting of floodgates. The deluge did not let up, Florida's relentless forecheck making it an ordeal to simply exit one's own zone.
John Tavares, who was the expensive but inevitable "final piece" seven long years ago, handed off the "C" before this season, and is now officially back on the market, was harassed by a pair of Panthers as he tried to bring the puck out. A sloppy and precarious pass along the boards was swiped by a hustling Seth Jones, who cleverly avoided triggering an offside call until Jonah Gadjovich touched up. Then, doing a U-turn to get back on defense, Morgan Rielly, the blueline representative of Toronto's homegrown core four, just ... fell down? For no reason?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, May 19: Squared Away]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190157</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-may-19-squared-away"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Be first out of the box to solve our Monday crossword! This week's puzzle was constructed by Hannah Slovut-Einertson and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Hannah works in data and lives in Minnesota with her wife, cat, and dog.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven Is The Leafs’ Unlucky Number]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190110</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/seven-is-the-leafs-unlucky-number"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lure of a Game 7 is typically so much more appealing than its actual delivery. Hockey manages this better than basketball, to be sure (the seventh games in the NBA Playoffs this decade have an average final score of 113-95), but it still has the Toronto Maple Leafs and their self-administered crises of confidence with which to contend. With all due respect to the Washington Wizards, Miami Marlins, and New York Jets, nobody does fatalism like the Leafs, because nobody fails the big moments like the Leafs.
That said, Sunday night's 6-1 loss to the blatantly superior Florida Panthers came as a blow to even the most easily disillusioned Leaf supporters. Even if those fans were skeptical at best about their heroes' chances going into the arena, they still crashlanded midway through the second period into the standard Torontonian response to games gone bad and hopes turned sad—19,000 people sitting in pouty silence, at least until the end of the game when their silence turned to boos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Thunder Tried Really Hard]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=190109</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-thunder-tried-really-hard"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It took the Oklahoma City Thunder about four minutes to kill the Denver Nuggets dead. With just over three minutes left to play in the second quarter of Sunday's Game 7, the Thunder were leading, 42-41. By the time there was 10:59 left to play in the third quarter, they were up 66-46 and the game was undeniably over.
The Thunder do this a lot. A team will start out fairly well against them, maybe even keep the game close all the way into the fourth quarter, but then OKC will turn on what Patrick Redford calls the steals-and-dunks machine, which does exactly what it says on the box. The Thunder will pick a moment in the game to raise their always-high defensive intensity to another level, and before the other team can really understand what's happening, they have been buried under an avalanche of turnovers and transition buckets. The Thunder turned Denver over five times during that four-minute stretch of Game 7, shot 9-of-10 from the field, and outscored them 24-5. It just kept going like that for the rest of the game, until the Nuggets emptied the bench and voluntarily initiated garbage time with 9:36 left to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Posts From The Glorious Future: How Abortion Became Legal Again]]></title>
        <id>682b1bbc7bab250001b2f03b</id>
        <link href="https://badfaithtimes.com/blog-posts-from-the-glorious-future-how-abortion-became-legal-again/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:49:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the Great Redo reforms, conservatives begged for Roe. We said no.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Posts From The Glorious Future: How Abortion Became Legal Again]]></title>
        <id>682b1bbc7bab250001b2f03b</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/blog-posts-from-the-glorious-future-how-abortion-became-legal-again/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:49:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the Great Redo reforms, conservatives begged for Roe. We said no.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>