<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-04-28T06:31:57.733Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Knicks Got Away With That One]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188058</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-knicks-got-away-with-that-one"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T21:44:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a just world, Tim Hardaway Jr. makes that three-pointer from the corner, and the Detroit Pistons beat the New York Knicks, 96-94. Not, "In a just world, David Guthrie calls that foul," even though he performed that rarest of mea culpae: the official's admission of doctrinal error. This may seem like a needle's-eye distinction, but we're not here to indulge a rant about bad officiating. If that's you, you deserve to drink alone, outside. In a hailstorm. In Scotland.
But we're also willing to say that in a just world, Cade Cunningham makes that 14-footer seven seconds earlier, and the Pistons beat the Knicks, 95-94. Not because we care about the Pistons, or for that matter the Knicks. In a good and entertaining series, the team that is behind should always tie the series up to increase the chances of Game 7 Christmas, and Knicks-Pistons is indeed that. That New York survived Sunday, 94-93, and took a 3-1 lead over Detroit is not good, not good at all, because it could make Game 5 on Tuesday the clincher, and there has never been a seven-game series that ends in five that has been worth a damn or remembered as anything special.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Belichick Brings His Trademark Charm To Excruciating CBS Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188048</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bill-belichick-brings-his-trademark-charm-to-excruciating-cbs-interview"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T20:44:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former New England Patriots head coach Bill Belichick isn't one for non-mandatory media appearances, but those with a book to sell don't really have a choice. The North Carolina football coach sat down with Tony Dokoupil for a CBS Sunday Morning conversation that started out as routine and then turned agonizing when the interviewer began to ask questions that might actually interest the public.

https://youtu.be/ZStmSZoc_Ps?si=BBK1DGv1xK_wzP04&t=328]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Was A Polite Guest For Liverpool’s Title Party]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188051</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tottenham-was-a-polite-guest-for-liverpools-title-party"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T19:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NBC football gabbler Jon Champion said it early in Liverpool's crowning achievement on Sunday: "Tottenham is in many ways the ideal opponent for this occasion." Even though it wasn't a stretch to realize that, he nailed it, for it was the sentence that served both as an upraised finger to celebrate the Reds' Premier League championship nearly two hours before it was made official, and a thumb straight in the eye of a Tottenham side that fully laid down to insure the title celebration.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3POvYkYFo30]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eugenio Suárez Picked A Bad Day To Hit Four Homers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188044</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/eugenio-suarez-picked-a-bad-day-to-hit-four-homers"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T16:18:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Eugenio Suárez had his preference, he might have chosen a different day to hit four home runs in a game. But given that he entered Saturday's game batting .167 for the season, he was in no position to be picky. To his credit, neither he nor the Arizona Diamondbacks are so ungracious.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Gordon Bails Out Nuggets With Buzzer-Beating Dunk]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188037</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/aaron-gordon-bails-out-nuggets-with-buzzer-beating-dunk"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T14:51:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nikola Jokic knew his shot wasn't going in. After the conclusion of Game 4 on Saturday, he shared his thoughts while the ball traveled through the air: "This is gonna be bad." He was correct. But out of nowhere, his teammate Aaron Gordon arrived to turn an airball into a buzzer-beating dunk, allowing the Denver Nuggets to escape with a 101-99 win that guaranteed at least two more games in an incredible series against the Los Angeles Clippers.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N0PE3BwrJIQ]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shedeur Sanders’s Weekend Of Humiliation Ends With Him Going To The Browns]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=188031</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/shedeur-sanders-nfl-draft-cleveland-browns"/>
        <updated>2025-04-27T14:11:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hours before the NFL Draft began on Thursday, Shedeur Sanders expressed his readiness. "I’m built for whatever today may bring," the quarterback prospect tweeted. After the first round ended without a team picking Sanders, the gag wrote itself: What about tomorrow? When nobody selected him in the second or third rounds on Friday, and a prank caller interrupted his live-streamed draft party to deliver false hope, it all became a bit sad.

https://www.youtube.com/shorts/a49Qsn4poAE]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formless evil]]></title>
        <id>680bebb80d4ed50001614cf9</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-307/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T22:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In-flight superhero analysis with Brian Hioe]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Airplane Movies]]></title>
        <id>680be7ee0d4ed50001614c92</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/airplane-movies/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T22:42:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a collective of 60 writers, on fire and hard to kill]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Hioe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seal Up The Pit That Contains Fox Sports 1]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187969</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/seal-up-the-pit-that-contains-fox-sports-1"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T20:36:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even by the standards of Fox Corp, Fox Sports 1 seems like a pretty sinister place for an employee. Over the past few months, enough lawsuits, complaints, and allegations have emerged to suggest that the workplace environment is so rotten and sinister that it might be best to raze it and start over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only Kevin Roose’s Editors Despise Him More Than I Do]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187970</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/only-kevin-rooses-editors-despise-him-more-than-i-do"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T18:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grave editorial failure only seldom can be located in something as precise as a single word choice. The following block-quoted sentence, from a Thursday article by New York Times technology reporter Kevin Roose, contains one, and it feels like journalistic malpractice that his editor or editors let him type it. I bet you can spot the word:
There is a small body of academic research on A.I. model welfare, and a modest but growing number of experts in fields like philosophy and neuroscience are taking the prospect of A.I. consciousness more seriously, as A.I. systems grow more intelligent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia’s Latest Boxing Spectacle Is A Times Square Fight Card With No Start Time And No Tickets]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187927</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/saudi-arabias-latest-boxing-spectacle-is-a-times-square-fight-card-with-no-start-time-and-no-tickets"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T16:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boxing needs big events. And here comes one, maybe: A three-fight card made up of some of the biggest names in the game–Teofimo Lopez, Devin Haney, and headlining headcase Ryan Garcia–is scheduled for Friday, May 2, outdoors in Times Square. 
The bill is intriguing enough. Garcia, who somehow remains a sympathetic figure despite being a very insistent and public asshole coming off a cheating suspension, is as compelling a character as the fight game offers these days. But the Times Square setting takes things to another level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For 20 Minutes, The Memphis Grizzlies Were Actually In It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187960</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/for-20-minutes-the-memphis-grizzlies-were-actually-in-it"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T15:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was a 20-minute window on Thursday night when the Vancouver Grizzlies looked like they very much belonged in the NBA Playoffs. And yeah, we said Vancouver. That was the uniform they wore for this one, and the name across that uniform's front. You want to be Memphis, make a uniform you like.
Then again, maybe Memphis should stay in their Vancouvers. Because other than those 20 minutes, give or take, in the first half Thursday night, their team has gotten out-and-out Wizarded by the Oklahoma City Thunder. That a Grizzlies team that tailspun its way into the playoffs would get wiped out by the top seed in the Western Conference isn’t a surprise, but they’re getting wiped out in a weird way, and Thursday night's 114-108 loss to the 'Der was both the worst and weirdest of the three losses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vegas Can’t Answer The Call Of The Wild]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187944</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/vegas-cant-answer-the-call-of-the-wild"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T15:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The numbers and the highlights agree: The Minnesota Wild's top line is the league's most dangerous right now. High-scoring wingers Matt Boldy and Kirill Kaprizov, centered by Joel Eriksson Ek, are dominating play every minute they're on the ice, outshooting opponents 21-13 at 5-on-5 and outchancing them 26-11. This is no mean feat coming largely against Vegas's own formidable first line of Barbashev-Eichel-Stone, all of whom have yet to score a point through three games of the series. The Wild forwards are imposing their will in every zone, and executing on a level that makes even their most optimistic efforts result in legitimate chances.
If you're not watching the Minnesota Wild because of their historic Minnesota Wildness, you're missing out on some of the most confident offensive hockey being played. Take this saucer breakout from Kaprizov on Tuesday, which Boldy called "the best pass I've ever seen."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Leafs Are In Uncharted Territory]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187930</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-leafs-are-in-uncharted-territory"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T14:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let someone else be the one to parse out Shedeur Sanders Agonistes. Meanwhile, on the internet's version of Page 8, there is the news that the Toronto Maple Leafs have now played three full playoff games and haven't lost one yet. Nothing raises suspicion quite like a perennial un-winner suddenly seeming to reconstruct its historical effluent, and while it's way early, these are still the Leafs. They are to be trusted with good fortune the way Pete Hegseth is to be trusted with troop deployments.
Yet with Thursday’s 3-2 overtime win over the Senators in Game 3 of the Great Ontario Wank they have become the first team to take a 3-0 series lead, and toward that end have taken a 3-0 lead in a four-game series for only the second time since Canada became fully independent from Queenie Liz in 1982. The Leafs are Canada's team and Canada's banana peel, because the playoffs are their goal and their undoing, and have been since 1967.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Draft Tunnel Is Too Long]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187929</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-draft-tunnel-is-too-long"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T13:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFL draft coverage has long been an industry unto itself for pundits and networks, but judging by the aerial shots over Green Bay, Wis., where last night's opening round was held, it’s also become something like sports-nerd Coachella. Some 200,000 people showed up to watch what is ultimately a boring product, only slightly more interesting than Marvel livestreaming a bunch of chairs with actors' names on it. But the draft thrives as an event for two reasons: 1) it sells hope, and sports fans love hope 2) it makes for a long TV broadcast, and the league loves its long TV broadcasts, so much so that it will go out of its way to lengthen the proceedings through brute geographical force.

https://youtu.be/7-02YJAiA1M?feature=shared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BFT Podcast: Leaky Pete Is Mad]]></title>
        <id>680a8157db769a000141cb93</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/bft-podcast-leaky-pete-is-mad/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T11:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pete Hegseth is breaking barriers in levels of being not mad at all]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Notes: Caglianone, Ragans, Marsh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=849615</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/royals-notes-caglianone-ragans-marsh.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-25T03:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Royals top prospect Jac Caglianone is playing right field for Double-A Northwest Arkansas tonight. It’s the first career outfield work for the lefty power hitter, who had played exclusively first base since being drafted with the #6 overall pick last summer. Caglianone had been a two-way star at the University of Florida, but his only defensive…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking Ahead To Club Options: AL Central]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=849577</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/looking-ahead-to-club-options-al-central.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T23:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MLBTR continues our division by division look at next year’s team/mutual option class with the AL Central. Virtually all of the mutual options will be bought out by one side. Generally, if the team is willing to retain the player at the option price, the player will decline his end in search of a better…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complex fats]]></title>
        <id>680aa2350d4ed50001613aa6</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-306/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T22:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yemisi Aribisala on the temptations of rage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Of Men and Palm Oil]]></title>
        <id>680a9fb70d4ed50001613a36</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/of-men-and-palm-oil/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T22:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In February 2021, Evan Kleiman, a North American chef and radio personality broadcasting from Santa Monica, California, asked me about palm oil. She said “It’s such an intrinsic part of your cuisine, not at all what we think about when we think of palm oil. Explain the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yemisi Aribisala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hilary Knight’s Not Rested, But She Is Ready]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187811</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/hilary-knights-not-rested-but-she-is-ready"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T21:32:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PWHL season resumes on Saturday after a three-week international break for the Women’s World Championship in Czechia. In the absence of play, there has still been some action: The league announced plans to expand to Vancouver next season, at a press conference this week. But people around the PWHL have come to question the breaks, which accommodate an international tournament schedule designed before the league existed. “It's a long three weeks,” Marie-Philip Poulin told The Canadian Press, adding that it might make more sense to reschedule the international tournaments so they are not happening, say, right in the middle of a playoff push. 
If nothing else, the break makes for a fun, weird wrench in the season. For the league-leading Montréal Victoire, whose games before the break were tense and sluggish, maybe it was needed. For the New York Sirens, winners of back-to-back regulation games before the break, maybe it was ill-timed. When teams take the ice again, all of them but Montréal still vying for the spot in the four-team playoff, they'll have three regular-season games left to play before the postseason starts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shannon Sharpe Stepping Away From ESPN Following Sexual Assault Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187853</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/shannon-sharpe-stepping-away-from-espn-following-sexual-assault-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T20:22:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESPN host Shannon Sharpe released a statement Thursday announcing that he will "step aside temporarily" from his role at the network. It came four days after Sharpe was sued by a Nevada woman who said that he raped her twice.
According to the lawsuit, filed in Clark County District Court, the woman met Sharpe when she was 19 at a Los Angeles gym in 2023. The suit said the two began "a rocky consensual relationship" that lasted nearly two years, but Sharpe became increasingly controlling and violent as time went on. Sharpe choked and hit her on multiple occasions, the suit said, and also threatened to kill her for accusing him of infidelity and resisting his sexual advances. The lawsuit claimed that Sharpe raped the woman once in October 2024, and again in January 2025. It asked for $50 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journey Within The Football Guy Brain, With Mike Tanier]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187773</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/journey-within-the-football-guy-brain-with-mike-tanier"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T19:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You could hear it on the horizon, getting louder as the hour and object drew closer. It was the sound of Drew, on his way back from vacation, making the NFL Draft chime at peak volume as he prepared to return to the podcast in time for the beginning of the draft. Drew loves it enough for the both of us and also a decent number of you all as well, so there was no way that we weren't going to Talk Football upon his return from Puerto Rico. After a brief discussion of his vacation misadventures, highlighted by him groaning through watching Gabriel Iglesias complain about wokeism and pronouns, and immediately after a stirring a capella version of that very same NFL Draft chime from Drew, we did just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jalen Green Stops Killing The Rockets Long Enough To Kill The Warriors Instead]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187825</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jalen-green-stops-killing-the-rockets-long-enough-to-kill-the-warriors-instead"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T18:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a backhanded compliment: The Houston Rockets have been one of the most fascinating teams in the league all year. The competitive dynamic of basketball is changing, and the Rockets epitomize the trajectory of that shift, with their deep rotation of committed hellraisers and one of the game's category-busting Thompson twins. What fascinates is that they won 52 games with depth, cussed determination, and an objectively bad half-court offense. 
The Rockets have built an incredible roster, stocked with all the sorts of players needed to win big except for the most important one. That deviant style stuff is fun and cool and has not tended to work in the playoffs, where defenses lock in and erase a lot of easy effort buckets. What matters here, to be reductive, is how good your best perimeter offensive player is. How relieving for Houston then that Jalen Green had himself a fantastic Game 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Vermilion Vanguard Is On The March]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187833</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-vermilion-vanguard-is-on-the-march"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T18:08:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TORONTO — For a moment, there was silence. Not even two minutes into AFC Toronto's inaugural match in the National Super League, Canada's brand new professional women's soccer league, Tanya Boychuck had taken advantage of a nervy mistake to put Montréal Roses FC ahead 1–0. Boychuck was stunned, and so was the sold-out crowd at BMO Field. The hush was biting, but it was soon replaced by what had been there before the goal: singing. 
The song was coming from section 114, where the Vermilion Vanguard stood. The Vanguard is a new independent supporters' group founded by a dedicated set of AFC Toronto fans. It was a windy day at the lakeside, but their chants of "A-F-C TOR-ONT-O," to the tune of the chords of "Seven Nation Army" by the White Stripes, were clear enough for me to hear them from the press box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abigail Segel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With A Fired USDA Agricultural Engineer]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187395</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-interview-with-a-fired-usda-agricultural-engineer"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T16:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Matt O'Malley was forced out of his position at the National Resources Conservation Service, he didn't just lose a job: He lost a job he'd worked toward for 15 years.
O'Malley first learned about the NRCS as an undergraduate. The agency, which is a part of the United States Department of Agriculture, helps landowners conserve their natural resources. He studied biological systems engineering, which would allow him to focus his work on helping farmers and agricultural producers achieve a more sustainable relationship with their land. To him, working for the NRCS would mean "looking towards the public good and working with typically smaller farmers who don't have access to the same type of inputs and opportunities that larger commercial farms do, helping them succeed, and doing it in a way that also helps the land."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secrets Of The World’s Foremost NFL YouTube Grinder]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187787</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/secrets-of-the-worlds-foremost-nfl-youtube-grinder"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T15:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
I’m one of those people now. For nearly two decades, I have treated some of the primary actors in the NFL Draft process—the anonymous scouts, the combine interrogators, the Andy Benoits—with the disdain that they have richly deserved. These are the people who, come early spring, fill the great sucking void in the NFL news cycle with their pettiest gripes regarding top prospects. Before he was drafted first overall and went on to have a borderline Hall of Fame career, Cam Newton accounted for some of the most truly deranged pre-draft analysis I’ve ever had the displeasure of reading. You probably remember those Cam takes, just as you remember Bill Polian suggesting that Lamar Jackson should play wideout, or Mike Mayock publicly marveling at Andrus Peat’s bubble butt. All of these men were not only socially ignorant, but often quite wrong about the very men they were attacking. I enjoyed being above them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fatal Flaw Of 'Dark Woke']]></title>
        <id>680a4e47db769a000141c602</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/the-fatal-flaw-of-dark-woke/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T15:19:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mockery, not viciousness and mean-spiritedness, has proven far more effective in beating back autocracy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Oilers Are Getting Carved Up Like A Moist And Tender Turkey]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187784</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-oilers-are-getting-carved-up-like-a-moist-and-tender-turkey"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T13:59:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'd rather gaze directly upon the opening of the Ark of the Covenant than spend too much time looking at Stuart Skinner's horrid numbers in the early (but getting late fast) postseason going. The Oilers goalie has allowed 11 goals on just 58 shots over, functionally, five and a half periods, surrendering six to the Kings in a wild Game 1 and five Wednesday night before being yanked for Calvin Pickard. Pickard promptly allowed a goal on the first shot he faced, which, if it was a salve to Skinner's wounded pride, was gifted not netminder-to-netminder, but by an Edmonton defense that is playing like it holds a grudge against its own backstop.
Pickard will almost surely get the start in a must-have Game 3 back in Edmonton, after the Kings took care of business, 6-2. I am not convinced it will matter. "No team in this league can give up the amount of Grade As and high-danger chances that we've been giving up," Darnell Nurse said. "We've been hanging our goalie out to dry."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mets Invincible, Phillies On Bullet-Train To Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187756</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mets-invincible-phillies-on-bullet-train-to-hell"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T12:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is possible to accurately calculate the Philadelphia Phillies' record based only on the current state of the team's NBC Sports Philadelphia postgame show, but doing so requires context: It is late April, and the Phillies have just gotten swept by the Mets, who, in the interest of not burying the lede, currently have the best record in all of Major League Baseball; and we are talking about Philly local sports media. So while, say, a 10–15 record would be a perfectly reasonable guess for the day after a postgame commentator asks if it's "time to sound the alarm," astute advanced models will be sure to recalibrate to a much more average 13–12. Which happens to actually be the team's record! Congratulations to all parties involved.
John Kruk, Phillies color commentator and noted voice of reason, tried his best to slow the show's roll. "I don't know how you make up three games in 130 games left, or 130-something games left," he said on Tuesday night, sarcastically, in response to the sound-the-alarm question. "It's going to be tough when the season's winding down like it is." (At the time, the Phillies had 138 games left to play.) He continued, "My God, what are we talking about?" An excellent philosophical question, as initially posed by Raymond Carver: What do we talk about when we talk about late-April baseball?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Death watch]]></title>
        <id>68095cf70d4ed500016123dd</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-305/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T00:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ana Marie Cox on death and salvation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inheritance]]></title>
        <id>6808f2590d4ed500016122f9</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/inheritance/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T00:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve known since she died that the horror of my mother’s death was a gift. The images of my beautiful mother with her hands drawn up into claws, her lips pale and unrouged, the light out in her eyes, the soft and hesitant way she looked]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ana Marie Cox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cubs Love To Get Crooked]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187729</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-cubs-love-to-get-crooked"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T20:39:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Against the Dodgers last night, the Cubs gave up three runs in the top of the first, scored five runs in the bottom of the first, and none of it really mattered, because what happens at the beginning of a Cubs game has little bearing on what happens at the end. There is no lead so great it can’t be frittered away. There is no deficit too imposing. In the span of five days, they’ve won two of the wackiest games of the MLB season to stay on top of the NL Central. “It’s a fun team to watch play, that’s what I’d tell you,” manager Craig Counsell said after Tuesday’s 11-10 walk-off win, wearing a slightly rattled and unconvincing smile. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zn_KjpuEWuI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Horny Sports Blogging Makes A Bewildering Return To Sports Illustrated]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187724</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/horny-sports-blogging-makes-a-bewildering-return-to-sports-illustrated"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T17:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been more than 60 years since the first Sports Illustrated swimsuit issue hit newsstands, a moment in history that bound the business of sports journalism to the business of making sports fans horny.
What started as a way for bored SI editors to amuse themselves during the slow period of the sports calendar soon grew into an annual event capable of subsidizing much of the rest of the magazine. When sports bloggers eventually rose to power in the 2000s and early 2010s, they internalized the lessons of the swimsuit issue, and ate into SI’s subscription and advertising revenue. In their heyday, these bloggers’ randy posts about WAGs, cheerleaders, and random college students were given prominent placement on popular sports sites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Shultz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enjoy The Agustín Ramírez Show For As Long As It Lasts]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187717</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/enjoy-the-agustin-ramirez-show-for-as-long-as-it-lasts"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T16:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the tenets of being a Miami Marlins fan is that the future will always be presented as the appeal. The Marlins have made it a habit to trade away star after star for prospects who could eventually become stars, only to then be traded away for more prospects. Logic and reason would lead the team's fans to develop commitment issues, and in turn perhaps shy away from any promising young player, knowing that his time with the Marlins begins to come to an end the second he starts pitching well, or hitting like a machine.
Fortunately, "logic" and "reason" rarely exist in sports fandom, which is why I believe Agustín Ramírez will slug 1.000 and live forever. The 23-year-old catcher came to South Florida as another star left the Marlins: He was one of the New York Yankees' prospects in the trade for Jazz Chisholm Jr. last July. After a solid second half of the season with the delightfully named Triple-A affiliate Jacksonville Jumbo Shrimp, and a brief stint at the same club to start this year, Ramírez was called up on Monday as the Marlins began a three-game series against the Cincinnati Reds. After only two games, Ramírez has already found himself in the franchise's record books, and he's become the new promising young player to enjoy for an indeterminate amount of time. Given that he's only on the roster due to injuries to catchers Nick Fortes and Rob Brantly, Ramírez's monster debut is found money for a team that currently has few options behind the plate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fine Line Between A Prank And A Crime]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187736</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-fine-line-between-a-prank-and-a-crime"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T15:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing puts the icing on a mistake like having time to squirm. Desperately brainstorming ways to set things right before your error is discovered gives you a waking-life taste of that nightmare feeling, doesn’t it? 
Turns out heists are baby shit. It’s the reverse heist—delicate operations performed under the emotional weight of both fear and regret—that really puts you in another league. Today we bring you a tale of immaculately curated decor, a beautiful Border Collie, and a prank gone wrong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Wood Is A Special Case]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187708</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/james-wood-is-a-special-case"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T14:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Wood, 22-year-old outfielder for the Washington Nationals, is mighty big and mighty strong. I think we've been very clear on this matter. Washington's offense, to date, isn't much—they rank eighth worst in the majors both by Statcast's Weighted On-base Average and by Baseball Reference's OPS+—but you cannot blame this on Wood, who is ranked third in the National League in home runs (7) and is 10th in runs batted in, and whose OPS Wednesday morning is a robust .902. Tuesday night Wood batted leadoff in the opening game of a series against the Baltimore Orioles, and had three hits, two doubles, and scored a pair of runs, and the Nationals won for the third time in four games.
Another area where our record here at Defector is unimpeachable: We have always been very up front about the fact that Wood, when he hits the ball, tends to hit the dick off of it. His average exit velocity this season is 94 miles per hour, per Statcast, in baseball's sixth percentile and better than such so-called strongmen as Vladimir Guerrero Jr., Bryce Harper, Elly De La Cruz, and Juan Soto. Tuesday's performance, though dingerless, was a showcase of power: The three balls that Wood put in play averaged 108.3 miles per hour off his bat. The 109-mph double he pounded off the wall in the fifth inning only failed to reach the stands due to its screaming 21-degree launch angle. His second-inning single was hit at 107.6 miles per hour and stayed on the infield, but ate up Orioles shortstop Gunnar Henderson, allowing Wood to beat the throw to first. Oh right, Wood is also fast as hell, ranking in baseball's 77th percentile by sprint speed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Paranoid Fantasies Of ‘October 8’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187677</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-paranoid-fantasies-of-october-8"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T13:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What you need to understand about the Zionist propaganda project October 8 (originally titled October H8te) is that calling it a film at all is generous.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Romm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold and empty]]></title>
        <id>6807fcfae515060001208f95</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-304/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T00:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Talia Lavin on finding the words; Carrie Frye talks The Awl: The Book]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wordless]]></title>
        <id>68080c71e515060001208fda</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/wordless/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T00:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Russian, writer’s block is known as “fear of the white page.” Or the white screen, in my case. When I sat down to write, my hands shook, in time with the blinking cursor. In the days after Donald Trump’s second inauguration, the sense]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Talia Lavin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PODCAST Round Table! Episode 8: Internet Pals]]></title>
        <id>68082425e515060001209044</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/podcast-round-table-episode-8-internet-pals/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T00:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maria Bustillos gabs with Carrie Frye about The Awl and the new THE AWL: THE BOOK! Joe MacLeod pressed the RECORD button.
Listen on Apple/Spotify/RSS/plus more options at pod.link

Episode 8: Internet pals
Carrie Frye and Maria Bustillos talk about THE AWL]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carrie Frye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PODCAST Round Table! Episode 3: Internet Pals]]></title>
        <id>68082425e515060001209044</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/podcast-round-table-episode-3-internet-pals/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-23T00:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maria Bustillos gabs with Carrie Frye about The Awl and the new THE AWL: THE BOOK! Joe MacLeod pressed the RECORD button.
Listen on Apple/Spotify/RSS/plus more options at pod.link

Episode 8: Internet pals
Carrie Frye and Maria Bustillos talk about THE AWL]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carrie Frye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Henry Blodget Invents, Hires, Sexually Harasses, Blogs About Nonexistent AI Subordinate]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187617</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/henry-blodget-invents-hires-sexually-harasses-blogs-about-nonexistent-ai-subordinate"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T19:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever been lonely? I mean really lonely. Think of the loneliest you ever were. Transpose that experience of loneliness to the bottom of a mineshaft. Oof, right? Anyway, bear that in mind.
Former Business Insider CEO and co-founder Henry Blodget, these days the sole proprietor and staffer of the blog/media company Regenerator, published a curious blog on his website on Monday. In it he details the events of an afternoon he spent on his laptop in a Brooklyn coffee shop prompting the ChatGPT program to generate and impersonate four members of an "AI team" he would employ at Regenerator, which the company's sole human employee had decided would now be a "native-AI newsroom," and then interacting with the four personas the chatbot adopted in response to his prompts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mavericks Just Keep On Sending Nico Harrison Out There]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187660</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-mavericks-just-keep-on-sending-nico-harrison-out-there"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T18:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever Nico Harrison did that made it so that he would have to destroy himself so publicly rather than just have everyone else do it for him, it must have been a doozy. But even if Harrison did nothing to offend a vengeful deity or the universe at large and has just been the designated corporate crap-catcher for the Dallas Mavericks organization all along, he is out there destroying himself in public all the same. And yet the story of the Luka Doncic trade simply won't go away, despite the Mavericks themselves having been swept brusquely out of the play-in, solely because the people who run the team keep bringing it up. This suggests that they think Harrison having to eat garbage by the shovelful, on camera and on the record, is good off-season marketing.
That can be the only reason that the Harrison Self-Abasement Tour continues, even to the point that Charles Barkley interrupts TNT's apology for accidentally killing the still very much alive Billy Ray Bates to tell Harrison, whom Barkley said he “considers a friend,” to stop being a public figure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jalen Brunson Is The NBA’s Premier Falling-Down Artist]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187627</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jalen-brunson-is-the-nbas-premier-falling-down-artist"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T17:51:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you simply looked at the box score from Game 2 of the Detroit Pistons–New York Knicks series and tried to reverse-engineer some narratives, you would probably look at Jalen Brunson's 37 points and seven assists (both game-highs), Karl-Anthony Towns's 10 anonymous points in 33 minutes, and the final score showing a 100–94 Pistons win and conclude that Brunson had a great game and that the Knicks dropped a game at home because his bum-ass teammates didn't step up. Wrong! Let's check the highlight reel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let Travis Hunter Be Football Ohtani]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187595</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/let-travis-hunter-be-football-ohtani"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T17:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about smoking, swingers, eating fishing lures, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hobbled Braves Are Hanging In There]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187600</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-hobbled-braves-are-hanging-in-there"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T16:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, the Atlanta Braves won a game! Not just one, either: Nine of them, while you were off oiling your disgusting mustache. Nine of 15, in fact. Over the weekend they won their second series of the season, sweeping the visiting Minnesota Twins, and then Monday they triumphed in a rousing 7-6 effort against the dreaded St. Louis Cardinals. After a hateful start to the season that saw the Braves get wiped out in consecutive road series against the cream of the National League West, they have started to get healthy, literally and figuratively, against the merely human, and are on the move.
Their latest win was a fun one. Braves hitters had a normal amount of trouble across six innings against St. Louis starter Erick Fedde, plating a pair of runs in the third on an Austin Riley sockdolager but otherwise looking generally punchless. This is both because Fedde is good and because Atlanta's offense—even while managing to outscore opponents more often than not since opening week—has not yet hit its stride. With the Cardinals up a run in the bottom of the eighth, a hard-chugging Riley beat out an infield single, and two batters later Matt Olson drove him home with a single through the right side. A walk and a sacrifice fly put the Braves up a run and brought Sean Murphy to the plate. Murphy's power bat has been everything the Braves could've hoped for since returning from injury, and he came up huge in this spot, leveling a mighty rip at a meatball of a first-pitch changeup from Cardinals reliever JoJo Romero and crushing a three-run dinger to left. Atlanta's bullpen tried to blow the lead but could not, and today the very same Braves who opened the season 0–7 are sitting on a four-game win streak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Guys Are So Soft]]></title>
        <id>68079a95c3c2590001577733</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/these-guys-are-so-soft/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T16:39:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In three months we've seen Elon Musk go from planning a thousand year autocratic regime to retreating to play with his rockets and cars]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Shows Kids Collectible Card With Photo Of Him Being Shot]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187579</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/trump-shows-kids-collectible-card-with-photo-of-him-being-shot"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T16:26:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monday was the White House Easter Egg Roll, an annual event in which children gather on the lawn and get to meet the president, first lady, and Easter Bunny. Then they all roll eggs down the lawn, I guess—I dunno, I’ve never really seen the thing. Presumably there’s a winner, someone who rolls the most eggs, or rolls them the furthest or the most accurately or just the most to the liking of the president, first lady, and Easter Bunny. I assume this year’s prize was the opportunity to join a group chat dedicated to discussing the U.S. military’s next airstrike.
But this year’s event had an extra plum for all the children in attendance, and not just because there were corrupt sponsorships. At one point Donald Trump approached a group of children, knelt down and showed them a collectible trading card with a photo of himself on it. You know the photo: the one in which he was raising his fist in the air after being shot. Hey, the children have to learn about assassination attempts at some point; why not from a man who survived one himself?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Sinners’ Is A Worthy Blockbuster]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187520</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/sinners-is-a-worthy-blockbuster"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T14:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the entirety of his career so far, there has been some consternation over Ryan Coogler's gifts as a director. His major debut Fruitvale Station was admirable and exciting, but was also a classic first-time director indie film. Creed was a lightning-rod moment: the revitalization of a dormant and dead-seeming IP in Rocky, the comeback of Sylvester Stallone as serious actor, and the validation of both Coogler and his muse Michael B. Jordan as Hollywood mainstays. But it is IP, and it is as much about the Rocky formula as it is about the filmmakers. And, obviously, there were Marvel's Black Panther films, which for all of their virtues remain Marvel films. Coogler, like a lot of talented, capable young filmmakers, got quickly nabbed by the Hollywood system, and good for him, but there has always been a question about what he can do with his own purely original work. Finally, with Sinners, Coogler has put his decade of experience behind his own idea.
Sinners tells the story of twin brothers Elijah "Smoke" Moore and Elias "Stack" Moore (both played by Michael B. Jordan), bootlegging gangsters and WWI veterans returning home to the Mississippi Delta from Chicago in 1932. It's the opening of their new juke joint built out on former Klan property, and they plan to start off strong with music from their little cousin, Sammie a.k.a. Preacher Boy (Miles Caton), and local blues legend Delta Slim (Delroy Lindo). They have also employed Smoke's former lover Annie (Wunmi Mosaku) and Chinese shopkeepers Grace and Bo Chow (Li Jun Li and Yao, respectively). But later on in the night, everyone there gets more than they bargained for when the power of the blues seems to open a portal to hell and attract a legion of vampires, led by Irish immigrant Remmick (Jack O'Connell), who systematically picks off the entire party in pursuit of Preacher Boy and his ability to commune with the ancestral spirit through his music.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Rocks When A Hockey Game Is Funny]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187559</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/kings-oilers-wacky"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T13:47:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is, I insist, cool and good that one of the wildest and most intense playoff games in a while ended so stupidly. It rules, quite frankly, that a game which saw the Kings seemingly exorcise their Oiler-matchup demons, then collapse in the face of a sudden Edmonton onslaught, was ultimately decided by a blooper-reel goal. Hockey is a ludicrous sport sometimes, and puck often lies, and had Phillip Danault taken a normal shot, Stuart Skinner probably would have stopped it easily and Game 1 would've headed to overtime, the Oilers carrying all the momentum after erasing a four-goal deficit. But Danault fanned, and fluttered the puck with comical slowness past Skinner, who saw neither hide nor hair of it.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TwyDSh7YJLo&ab_channel=SPORTSNET]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kawhi Leonard Is Just Living With It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187560</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/kawhi-leonard-is-just-living-with-it"/>
        <updated>2025-04-22T13:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A closely contested NBA playoff game is an insanity device. Every turnover is a rake across the brain, every missed free throw a boil on the soul. Each second of game time that passes is designed to pull the contents of your guts closer and closer to the edge of your throat. If that is what it feels like to watch it, I can't imagine what it must be like on the court.
None of this applies to Kawhi Leonard. Despite his close proximity to the action, I spent most of Monday night's Game 2 clash between the Nuggets and Clippers wishing I could trade places with him. Even when he had the ball in his hands with under a minute left, readying himself to take what would be the deciding shot in L.A.'s 105-102 victory, it was impossible to imagine anyone, anywhere, more at peace than Kawhi Leonard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White fangs]]></title>
        <id>680697fc105fa700014c04e3</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-303/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T23:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maria Bustillos on 'Sinners']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Music in the Blood]]></title>
        <id>680654e1105fa700014c0360</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/music-in-the-blood/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T23:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sinners, the new vampire horror movie directed by Ryan Coogler and starring Michael B. Jordan, opened this weekend to boffo reviews and impressive global box office receipts of $61 million. Coogler’s films have made more than $2.4 billion at the box office, according to Variety, giving him]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Bustillos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kerry And Cork Redeemed A Dour Season Of Gaelic Football With One Great Game]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187537</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/kerry-and-cork-redeemed-a-dour-season-of-gaelic-football-with-one-great-game"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T19:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pope died on Sunday. Here’s hoping his holiness got to see the Kerry–Cork football match first. To call it the greatest Gaelic game of the millennium would be an understatement of Irish proportions. Or something. But as GAA+ play-by-play man Liam Aherne gushed within seconds of the game’s end: “My god!”
On a rain-soaked pitch at regal Páirc Uí Chaoimh in Cork on Saturday evening, the Kingdom advanced in the Munster Championships—one of the provincial tournaments that determines seeding for the All-Ireland Championship—by outlasting the underdog squad from the Rebel County in overtime, 3-21 to 1-25. The back-and-forth contest climaxed on a shocking goal from Kerry midfielder Joe O’Connor, who blasted a ball from 20 meters out in traffic into the Cork net late in the second extra period. The action gave fans, players, and even broadcast commentators no time to breathe from halftime to the final horn (or “hooter” in GAA parlance).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WrestleMania 41’s Two Main Events And The Risks Of Getting Epic]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187475</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/wrestlemania-41s-two-main-events-and-the-risks-of-getting-epic"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T18:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the WWE house style there are many archetypes, but nothing is more tried-and-true—or, in some cases, tired and false—than the WWE Epic Main Event. As the saying goes, you know it when you see it, but the Epic Main Event is easy enough to break down into its component pieces. An EME will have a lot of cinematic spots, usually involving weapons or the environment around the ring—tables being the main one, but oftentimes the crowd areas come into play as well. It will be a bit on the slower side, for one of two reasons, with the choice between the two depending upon how generous you want to be. Either the EME will be slow to build up the drama until it bubbles over, or it will be sluggish because WWE's main event wrestlers are generally more on the methodical side. Most relevant to WrestleMania 41's double main events is that these matches are usually over-stuffed with outside interference and mechanics that go beyond the simple foundation of wrestling, in which a wrestling match can be boiled down to some amount of performers fighting each other to prove who is best. The Epic Main Event exists because of WWE's longstanding suspicion that that isn't enough.
With that in mind, the respective main events for the two-night marathon that was WrestleMania 41 were predictably both in that WWE Epic Main Event style. Taken together, they do a rather neat job of encapsulating the good and the very bad of what that style can bring. If last year's night two main event was WWE at its most giddily excessive, this year's show offered two more measured scoops of melodrama that went down easily when they worked, and crashed and burned almost impossibly hard when they didn't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oscar Piastri Seizes The Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187465</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/oscar-piastri-seizes-the-lead"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T17:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before the third session of qualifying, Lando Norris was the fastest man at the Saudi Arabian Grand Prix. Other drivers beat him on one-off occasions—Max Verstappen in Q1, and, somehow, Pierre Gasly in FP1—but notably and most importantly, neither of those drivers were his teammate and championship rival Oscar Piastri. The Saudi Arabian GP was shaping up to be a bounce-back race for Norris across Formula 1's midseason oil-money double-header, after his comparatively disastrous P3 finish at Bahrain.
Then Norris clipped a curb on a flying lap, unsettled his car, and crashed into the left-side wall, red-flagging the session. Norris let his race engineer know that he was fine, before following up with a characteristically self-critical, "Idiot." As much as McLaren professes its car the best on the grid, it doesn't have quite the pace of the early hybrid-era Mercedes or rocket Red Bull, where, with the right driver at the wheel and right teammate up ahead, a P10 in qualifying could easily convert to a race win. And with that one mistake, Norris's race goal shifted from a win, cementing his Drivers' Championship lead, to a decent recovery drive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bud Black Has Either The Best Or The Worst Job In Baseball]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187525</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bud-black-has-either-the-best-or-the-worst-job-in-baseball"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T17:11:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of all the odd moments of a well-packed sports weekend, maybe the oddest was the debate between what is more unusual, one MLB team beating another 24-2, or an accomplished professional basketball team beating a slightly less accomplished one, in the playoffs, by 51 points. If it helps, it's about a tie.
But the sneaky third option might have been the Colorado Rockies winning the second game of their punishment doubleheader with the Washington Nationals. Here was one team with an excruciatingly bad bullpen facing a team with an excruciatingly bad everything else; by rights such a match-up should end up with each team losing once, and it did. But putting it like that diminishes the Rockies' status as an all-time cornea-searing disaster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brewers Acquire Cesar Espinal To Complete Mark Canha Trade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=849164</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/brewers-royals-mark-canha-trade-ptbnl-cesar-espinal-pitcher.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T16:51:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced Monday that minor league righty Cesar Espinal has been traded to the Brewers. He’s the player to be named later from the swap that sent Mark Canha from Milwaukee to K.C. late in spring training. Espinal is just 19 years old, but this is already the second time in his career that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O’s, No!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187455</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/os-no"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T16:44:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because it is a long enough regular season to test and re-test just about every variable, every team in baseball is going to have their wieners mangled in at least one game. Even the mighty zillion-dollar Los Angeles Dodgers recently had their tender bits forcibly run through a cheese-grater by the Chicago Cubs. It happens! Still, it's hard not to feel a little bit uneasy about the suffering delivered to the Baltimore Orioles Sunday, at home, in the rubber match of a weekend series against the Cincinnati Reds. The O's put 41-year-old Charlie Morton on the mound to start the contest, and the Reds lifted him by his ankles and drowned him in a toilet, and then spent the rest of the game mercilessly bullying an increasingly ridiculous sequence of relief pitchers, rudely flaunting MLB's lack of a mercy rule, to the tune of a 24–2 final score.
Things didn't turn fully gruesome on Morton until the third inning, when Elly De La Cruz (who also made several eye-popping plays up the middle during the very brief period when this game could be described as "competitive") socked a high heater into the stands in right field to lead off what would soon become a "Baseball Bugs" conga line for the Reds. Minutes later, struggling with command, amassing a nightmarish pitch count, having already used a mound visit, and desperate for an out by any means, a sweaty and flustered Morton attempted a pickoff move to first, missed wide, and allowed an unearned run to scamper home, the fourth of the inning. Reds catcher Austin Wynns then punched a Morton 2–2 changeup into center field to drive home another run, and Orioles manager Brandon Hyde decided to put his bumbling pitcher to bed. Reliever Cody Poteet came on and hung a 3–2 slider to TJ Friedl, who socked it deep to right; Ryan O'Hearn, who is defensively out of position at every position but especially in right field, made a hilariously feeble effort to catch the ball on the warning track, and now the flood gates were not just open but entirely gone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please Enjoy These Images Of The 2025 Corgi Derby]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187482</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/please-enjoy-these-images-of-the-2025-corgi-derby"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T15:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday was the third annual Corgi Derby, a tribute to Queen Elizabeth held at the Musselburgh Racecourse in Scotland. The little dogs that the queen loved most race each other around a 230-foot course, with the winner getting a trophy and treats delivered by Judy Murray, Andy’s mom. The winning dog's name is also printed in publications around the world. This year’s winner was named Juno. See! All you need to do to get your dog’s name in Defector is to have it win a corgi race in front of Andy Murray’s mother, and for there to be lots of cute photos on the wire. Of course your dog will never know that its name was published on Defector, but it might be nice for you.
Which reminds me: Defector has access to a lot of these cute photos, and we’d like to share them with you now. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, April 21: Happy Arbor Day]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187464</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-april-21-happy-arbor-day"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why not branch out and try our Monday crossword? This week's puzzle was constructed by Sala Wanetick and Emily Biegas, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Sala is a crossword constructor and cheesemonger based outside of Detroit. Her sports knowledge specialty areas include reality stars' romantic partners, and common crossword clues (shoutout to Mia Hamm, Pele, and Epee.) She would love to connect with solvers and constructors—Sala Wanetick on all platforms, she is the only one. Emily started constructing crosswords with Sala in 2023; they have had puzzles published in the Los Angeles Times, USA Today, and Universal. Besides crosswords, her other passion is music (shoutout to the three-letter king, ENO!) A corporate girlie by day, by night Emily plays guitar in a garage rock trio called ZEM that plays shows in and around Detroit. 
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[See What Makes The Cavaliers Special Through The Ty Jerome Game]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187451</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/see-what-makes-the-cavaliers-special-through-the-ty-jerome-game"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T14:29:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The theory of the Cleveland Cavaliers is that by virtue of being able to play at least one of Donovan Mitchell and Darius Garland at all times, they are guaranteed 48 minutes of all-star–level shot creation. That allows them to play a bunch of incredible play-finishers, like Jarrett Allen and Max Strus, who don't need to worry about dribbling the basketball unless it's into an advantage presented to them by one of their genius operators and can otherwise stick to jamming huge dunks and nailing open threes. Everything on offense is fast and so much of it easy, which starts at the top. So naturally, a point guard's big game tells the story of Cleveland's 121-100 playoff-opening win over the Miami Heat. That's right: Ty Jerome.
The little point guard has had an incredible season for the Cavs, averaging a hair over 12 points per game on 63-percent true shooting in just under 20 minutes per game for the best offense in the league. When a mildly undersized guard averages those sorts of numbers in that sort of role, you might expect their game to be built around nailing catch-and-shoot threes, attacking closeouts, and running vanilla pick-and-rolls. You know, responsible offense. Jerome is great at all of those things, but what really makes him great is his floater. There's nothing complex about it: Jerome is a floater maestro, with an uncanny sense of timing, enviable balance, and eiderdown touch. If he gets his defender on his hip, he knows exactly how to lathe out an extra six or seven feet of space, and he knows exactly when the low man is either committed to blocking his shot or too terrified of an alley-oop, and thus content to watch Jerome sail it in over his head.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Warriors And Rockets Know Each Other’s Weaknesses]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187458</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-warriors-and-rockets-know-each-others-weaknesses"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T13:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Occasionally, and by occasionally we of course mean rarely, the dumb luck of the NBA standings will create an early-round playoff series in which each team is somehow a bad matchup for its opponent. The force of the postseason naturally tends to create these as the process grinds on; to get one before things otherwise get interesting is both a gift from the universe and a pain in the ass for the teams involved. You think about a series like this, you watch it and rewatch it, and all you come away with is the brain-bending realization that the teams involved are not playing against each other so much as they are playing against their own capacity for discomfort.
And with that, we present to you Rockets-Warriors, or based on the result in Game 1 of this series, Warriors-Rockets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AL Central Notes: Carpenter, Erceg, Meidroth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=849119</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/al-central-notes-carpenter-erceg-meidroth.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-21T03:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With four outfielders already on the injured list, the Tigers might’ve lost another key contributor when Kerry Carpenter left today’s 4-3 loss to the Royals with what manager A.J. Hinch described as right hamstring soreness.  As Hinch told the Detroit News’ Chris McCosky and other reporters, Carpenter suffered the injury while running out an infield…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Knicks Gave The Pistons A Lesson In Playoff Entropy]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187437</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-knicks-gave-the-pistons-a-lesson-in-playoff-entropy"/>
        <updated>2025-04-20T16:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Detroit Pistons roster a bunch of rowdy youths fresh to a playoff atmosphere, with all that entails—good and bad. They don't know what they don't know, which is often a successful mindset: Many a game has been lost by knowing you're supposed to lose it, and many a game won by the weightlessness of happy ignorance. Expectations, too, can be a burden. But gravity-free hoopage only lasts so long. Eventually, especially on the road, the noise builds and the pressure increases and more seasoned opponents are braced against wilting, and suddenly, unawareness of "what's supposed to happen" stops working, because the thing starts happening anyway. Over a 21-0 fourth-quarter run that led to a 123-112 New York victory, the Knicks offered the Pistons a corrective for the first three quarters, a demonstration of postseason basketball's unpredictability, and a lesson that not all 48 minutes are created equal.
The Knicks' defensive strategy was obvious from the get-go: make life difficult for Cade Cunningham. The Pistons have a dearth of ways to beat teams, and the Knicks were intent with shutting down their 26-ppg primary weapon, with OG Anunoby getting frequent help from Karl-Anthony Towns whenever Cunningham broke through on a screen. But Cunningham was generally content with passing out of pressure, because his mates were hitting their shots. Tobias Harris, Tim Hardaway Jr., and Malik Beasley—the veterans on the team, probably not coincidentally—were 20-of-33 from the field after three quarters, and hitting better than 50 percent of their threes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Lakers Have Bigger Problems Than Luka Doncic Can Fix]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187433</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-lakers-have-bigger-problems-than-luka-doncic-can-fix"/>
        <updated>2025-04-20T14:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NBA is an odd amalgam of friendships and enemies' lists, alliances and rivalries, defenders and critics—all under the same jiggling tent. Thus, it should have come as little surprise that the Minnesota Timberwolves fought so brilliantly for Nico Harrison's honor when the people currently paying him are not only letting him twist in the breeze but aiming the wind machine at him to make the spinning more painful.
This is not, of course, Minnesota's prime intention. The Wolves beat the Los Angeles Lakers 117-95 Saturday night for their own glory, honor and self-esteem. They spotted the Lakers a 28-21 lead, took it away two minutes into the second with a 14-2 run, then reinforced it with a 21-6 burst to start the third. If it wasn't Jaden McDaniels crushing all before him, it was Anthony Edwards at his cheeky best, with sides of Julius Randle and Naz Reid scattered about the landscape, while the Lakers had LeBron James, Luka Doncic, and crickets. The final buzzer was an act of mercy, as was the you-can-go-to-sleep blowout at the end of a 10-hour hoopathon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That’s About As Hot As It Gets In Winnipeg]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187410</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/thats-about-as-hot-as-it-gets-in-winnipeg"/>
        <updated>2025-04-20T13:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It feels almost unfair that the Winnipeg Jets, with their all-universe goalie and their league-fewest goals allowed, are also constructed to be able to win a slugfest if necessary. Third-most goals in the NHL this year, paced as always by the dynamic Kyle Connor–Mark Scheifele duo, the Jets are very much unlike some of the defense-first rosters out there in that they can and will happily absorb a haymaker or two and answer in kind. That came in handy on Saturday, as a white-hot crowd watched the Jets trade goals with the Blues in a wild first period, only to asset their dominance as the game wore on.
The final score read 5-3 Jets, but after a 2-2 first period, it felt like it might be one of those very silly playoff openers where the combination of nerves, an extended feeling-out period, and the small sample size add up to a game with no particular contextual anchor, where everyone kind of agrees to pretend it was an anomaly that just sort of happened. "That first period it was kind of a little bit wacky and we were a little bit sloppy," Jets coach Scott Arniel said. But when Jordan Kyrou scored on the power play just 1:13 into the second to give St. Louis the lead, it was hard not to wonder if this was the return of Playoff Helle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Is No Getting Off The Russell Westbrook Rollercoaster]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187404</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/there-is-no-getting-off-the-russell-westbrook-rollercoaster"/>
        <updated>2025-04-20T13:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russell Westbrook being a man in a hurry and all, he has needed only four games to show his newest coach, David Adelman, what the full Russ Experience entails. It is, as the nine coaches before him have learned, a flight to a tropical paradise through six hours of turbulence and which may at any moment be rerouted to Gary, Indiana.
Saturday, though, it was paradise after all. Westbrook made enough superb and silly plays in tandem, including a few of each in overtime, to guide the Denver Nuggets to a 112-110 victory that was, as the Brits like to say, very much "against the run of play." Westbrook's damp dynamite stylings have led people to consider him hyperwashed for several years now because he is capable of such seismographically comedic highs and lows, and yet Adelman has come to rely upon (if not entirely trust) Westbrook. Westbrook played 34 minutes Saturday, including the final 23 minutes that encapsulated half the third quarter and all of the fourth and overtime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Busy In The NBA Playoffs Open Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=187401</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/get-busy-in-the-nba-playoffs-open-thread"/>
        <updated>2025-04-19T16:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lotsa games today! Lotsa games tomorrow, too. Feel free to hang out here and chat while you binge on all that spectacular hoops action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Option MJ Melendez To Triple-A, Activate Mark Canha From 10-Day IL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=848937</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/royals-option-mj-melendez-to-triple-a-activate-mark-canha-from-10-day-il.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-19T14:07:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that outfielder MJ Melendez has been optioned to Triple-A Omaha.  The move opens up a roster spot for Mark Canha, as the veteran outfielder/first baseman was reinstated from the 10-day injured list. More to come…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Player Option/Opt-Out Update: April Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=848721</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/04/player-option-opt-out-update-april-edition.html"/>
        <updated>2025-04-18T23:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The increasing popularity of opt-outs/player options as a means to close the gap in free agent signings and extensions has changed the face of free agency entirely. Not long ago, opt-outs were perks reserved for the game’s truly elite stars — a benefit to help differentiate nine-figure offers and secure the game’s top stars. In…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy listening]]></title>
        <id>680294b3105fa700014bef72</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/issue-302/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-18T21:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jennie Rose Halperin on the life and work of Michael Hurley]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Editors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye to the Godfather of Freak Folk]]></title>
        <id>6802b4ed105fa700014befdb</id>
        <link href="https://flaminghydra.com/goodbye-to-the-godfather-of-freak-folk/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-18T21:48:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YOU CAN SHARE THIS POST ON BLUESKY THANK YOU
I first heard Michael Hurley play in a small, mostly empty venue in Berlin in 2013. It was an early set; the bar was muted, brown, and dingy in dusty late spring light, but when he came in he lit up]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennie Rose Halperin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine A Pro-Democracy Supreme Court – If You Can]]></title>
        <id>68028ec00951470001ef0769</id>
        <link href="https://bad-faith-times.ghost.io/imagine-a-pro-democracy-supreme-court-if-you-can/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-18T18:51:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States can't be saved unless SCOTUS is saved first]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denny Carter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>