<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-10-25T12:31:12.091Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Anyone Know How To Spell It? — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076620</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/does-anyone-know-how-to-spell-it-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T23:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State Supreme Court Typo Goes Viral: The Pelican State has a red squiggly under their seal.
Green Light For The Golden State!: California Bar gets the go ahead for new testing strategy.
Prepare Your Costumes!: It's ATL's 15th LEGALLY THEMED Costume Contest!
Furrball, Esq.: Check out this cat's legal background.
More Of A Bad Thing: Former head of state gets interesting appointing advice.
The post Does Anyone Know How To Spell It? — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re Big Fans Of Our Advertisers On ATL]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076592</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/were-big-fans-of-our-advertisers-on-atl/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T23:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We really enjoy working with you!
The post We’re Big Fans Of Our Advertisers On ATL appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Bar Exam Hits Obama-Era High]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076613</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/new-york-bar-exam-hits-obama-era-high/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T23:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been a long time coming.
The post New York Bar Exam Hits Obama-Era High appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pocket Watching Trump Judge Wants To Control Law School Donations]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076610</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/pocket-watching-trump-judge-wants-to-control-law-school-donations/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T22:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Love seeing "Originalism" used as a cudgel. 
The post Pocket Watching Trump Judge Wants To Control Law School Donations appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Psychedelic Furs and co-headliners The Jesus & Mary Chain revived ’80s darkness at Uptown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857822</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/the-psychedelic-furs-and-co-headliners-the-jesus-mary-chain-revived-80s-darkness-at-uptown/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T21:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Psychedelic Furs. // photo by Nick Spacek The Psychedelic Furs with the Jesus & Mary Chain and Frankie Rose Uptown Theater Wednesday, October 23 On paper, the Psychedelic Furs headlining their tour with the Jesus & Mary Chain makes sense. They have the bigger selection of hits and arguably the more popular name recognition, but in practice, they ended...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest Future Ready Lawyer Survey From Wolters Kluwer Finds Broad Adoption Of Gen AI By Legal Professionals]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076594</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/10/latest-future-ready-lawyer-survey-from-wolters-kluwer-finds-broad-adoption-of-gen-ai-by-legal-professionals.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T21:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Latest Future Ready Lawyer Survey From Wolters Kluwer Finds Broad Adoption Of Gen AI By Legal Professionals appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Korn proved they’ve still got the life at T-Mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857817</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-korn-proved-theyve-got-the-life-at-t-mobile/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T21:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Korn. // photo by Allison Scavo Korn with Gojira and Spiritbox T-Mobile Center Friday, October 18 Photos by Allison Scavo and Zyonn Scavo Korn Allison’s photos Zyonn’s photos Korn setlist Here to Stay Dead Bodies Everywhere Got the Life A.D.I.D.A.S. It’s On! Good God Start the Healing Blind Ball Tongue Clown Shoots and Ladders Twist Make Me Bad Y’All Want...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Scavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Firms May Not Be Ready To Offer The Mental Health Accommodations Young Lawyers Want]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076596</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/biglaw-firms-may-not-be-ready-to-offer-the-mental-health-accommodations-young-lawyers-want/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T20:44:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a very big problem for Biglaw. Law firms need to adapt -- and fast.
The post Biglaw Firms May Not Be Ready To Offer The Mental Health Accommodations Young Lawyers Want appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California Bar Gets Their Supreme Court’s Go Ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076608</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/california-bar-gets-their-supreme-courts-go-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T20:03:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just in time to stay on schedule!
The post California Bar Gets Their Supreme Court’s Go Ahead appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disgraced Former Trump Attorney Has Some Interesting Advice For The Ex-President]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076607</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/disgraced-former-trump-attorney-has-some-interesting-advice-for-the-ex-president/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T19:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making federal courts even more conservative isn't a popular idea.
The post Disgraced Former Trump Attorney Has Some Interesting Advice For The Ex-President appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything I Expect From Atlantic City, Based On The ‘Rugrats’ Vacation Episode]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170524</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/everything-i-expect-from-atlantic-city-based-on-the-rugrats-vacation-episode"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T19:14:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it is time for the Defector staff to go into seclusion for our annual company meetings and fall frolic. This year we are gathering in Atlantic City, America's abandoned playground. We decided to hold a mini theme week to keep the site robust and full of blogs while we're in meetings. This year's theme: Risk!
Unless you count Chuck E. Cheese birthday parties when you were a kid (and I kinda do), I haven't spent any time in casinos. So when I heard we were trading the peaceful Poconos for glitzy Atlantic City for this year's company meeting, I wasn't sure what to expect. I scoured my long term memory for a previous experience or cultural touch point to ground my expectations and then I remembered the 1997 Rugrats episode, "Vacation."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good news! KC-area movie theatres offer early-release screenings of Wicked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857783</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/good-news-kc-area-movie-theatres-offer-early-release-screenings-of-wicked/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T19:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wicked // Courtesy Universal Pictures Fans of Wicked who are eager to see the new film don’t need a magic spell to get early access. Kansas City area B&B Theatres and AMC Theatres are offering early access screenings on November 20. The film opens in theatres across the country on November 22, 2024, but Universal Pictures has released some early...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emirates NBA Cup Courts Unveiled For All 30 Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82906</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/24/emirates-nba-cup-courts-unveiled-for-all-30-teams/basketball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:36:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courts across the league include NBA Cup trophy at center court and in lanes along with gradient concentric circles and tonal graphics covering entire floor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NetDocuments Moves To Bring Generative AI To Content… Not The Other Way Around]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076591</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/netdocuments-moves-to-bring-generative-ai-to-content-not-the-other-way-around/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's soon going to be less about having AI than where your AI lives.
The post NetDocuments Moves To Bring Generative AI To Content… Not The Other Way Around appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keyboard Cat Becomes Courtroom Star During Zoom Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076605</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/keyboard-cat-becomes-courtroom-star-during-zoom-trial/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T17:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You never know when your furry 'legal assistant' will come in handy during trial.
The post Keyboard Cat Becomes Courtroom Star During Zoom Trial appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOP Harasses Nuns In Hunt For THE FRAUDS]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076599</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/gop-harasses-nuns-in-hunt-for-the-frauds/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who picks a fight with nuns? 
The post GOP Harasses Nuns In Hunt For THE FRAUDS appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Remember Our Cars]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171234</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lets-remember-our-cars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
My first car was a Jeep. Two-door Cherokee. Black. It had a working tape deck and an eager gas pedal, which was all I required. I drove that car to college and back a hundred times. I drove it to work. I drove it to my best friend’s house. I drove it to Boston. I drove it to New York City. I drove it to see girls. I drove it to parties, houses, stadiums, and ski resorts. I almost always drove alone, and preferred it that way. If I had a trip coming up and I knew it would be just me and my car, I was content. I’d load up on shitty food, plunge a cassette into the stereo, jack the volume up to the point of pain, and tear ass up and down I-95. I loved that car.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Viral Embarrassing State Supreme Court Mistake]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076598</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-viral-embarrassing-state-supreme-court-mistake/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The typo is making the rounds on social media.
The post The Viral Embarrassing State Supreme Court Mistake appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s No Rutgers Football In The Champagne Room]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171273</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/theres-no-rutgers-football-in-the-champagne-room"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is still a mostly dead mall I have to visit and another day of meetings and such, but I'm prepared to call the Defector offsite in Atlantic City a qualified success. This is mostly because my criteria for assessing this kind of thing are kind of a mess. Seeing some dolphins horsing around more or less cancels out a hotel-wide internet outage that postponed the recording of this episode; some of the most critically dire bar vibes I have ever encountered at 10 p.m. anywhere in the world are counteracted by seeing a security guard happily dancing to Kool & The Gang's "She's Fresh" on the casino floor the next morning. None of this is reasonable, really, but that is not the kind of thing a person (or flourishing media company) comes to a place like this for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: Your curated list of what and where to eat this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857802</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-your-curated-list-of-what-and-where-to-eat-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Life in KC is decisively delicious. In fact, there is often so much going on that it can be difficult to decide where to go and what to try. That’s where I come in. By day, I am the Food & Drink Editor of The Pitch, and by night, the good food and fun overflow into...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling Hidden Deal Insights: GenAI For Powerful Negotiation And Exceptional Client Service [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076369</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/unveiling-hidden-deal-insights-genai-for-powerful-negotiation-and-exceptional-client-service/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T15:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new GenAI-powered deal point extraction tool provides big advantages in the negotiation process and beyond. 
The post Unveiling Hidden Deal Insights: GenAI For Powerful Negotiation And Exceptional Client Service appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[National Museum of Toys and Miniatures unveils new exhibit featuring dozens of regional mixed-media masterminds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858033</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/national-museum-of-toys-and-miniatures-unveils-new-exhibit-featuring-dozens-of-regional-mixed-media-masterminds/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T15:18:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of sculptor Cesar Lopez’s submissions to the Local Artists Go Miniature exhibition. // Provided by Cesar Lopez. This Friday, local artists will display their latest small-scale projects for the newest exhibition at the National Museum of Toys and Miniatures .  The Local Artists Go Miniature exhibit will feature a variety of 2D and 3D artworks of any media from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Quick hitting storms (THU-10/24)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3706544</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-quick-hitting-storms-thu-10-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T14:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have noticed a subtle change to the weather this morning... clouds. Shocking, I know but important because those clouds are a sign of moisture in the atmosphere, something that has been lacking for weeks around these parts. That moisture will help fuel a couple of opportunities for storms. One during the day, which [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ATL’s 15th Annual Legally Themed Halloween Costume Contest]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076597</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/atls-15th-annual-legally-themed-halloween-costume-contest/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T14:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you got what it takes to top the winners of years past?
The post ATL’s 15th Annual Legally Themed Halloween Costume Contest appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia Got What It Wanted From The Six Kings Slam]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171311</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/saudi-arabia-got-what-it-wanted-from-the-six-kings-slam"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T14:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I couldn’t even go a week without Turki Alalshikh, the chairman of Saudi Arabia’s General Entertainment Authority, popping up on my laptop during a live sporting event. On Oct. 12, he was in the front row for the undisputed light heavyweight championship fight between Artur Beterbiev and Dmitry Bivol, a long-awaited bout he was instrumental in putting together. (He was the third-most important character of the night, getting name-checked by the ring announcer and both fighters and promptly calling for a rematch when he disagreed with the judges’ scorecards.) Not seven days later, there Alalshikh was on the glowing rectangle again, front and center at the Six Kings Slam—an exhibition he spearheaded that featured five of the best and most famous male tennis players on the planet, and also Hogler Rune. 
Alalshikh’s place within a murderous, deeply discriminatory regime has not dissuaded boxing from working in lockstep with him, catching the money he throws in order to stage high-demand fights that would not have happened without the unlimited wealth at his disposal. But there was nothing high-demand about the Six Kings Slam. It was an exhibition event whose headlining match-ups, like Carlos Alcaraz-Jannik Sinner, were ongoing rivalries that have grown without intervention from Alalshikh or anybody else. This event happened simply because it could, and because Saudi Arabia’s sportswashing efforts are now so ubiquitous, it felt immunized from any loud complaints.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Owen Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check Out This Mind-Blowing, Highly Secretive Trading Strategy (But Don’t Adopt It Unless You Want To Get Sued)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076582</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/10/check-out-this-mind-blowing-highly-secretive-trading-strategy-but-dont-adopt-it-unless-you-want-to-get-sued"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T14:05:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you heard of a country called ‘Venezuela’? Oh, you have…
The post Check Out This Mind-Blowing, Highly Secretive Trading Strategy (But Don’t Adopt It Unless You Want To Get Sued) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Would sports betting boost Missouri school funding? There’s no guarantee, experts say.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858070</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/would-sports-betting-boost-missouri-school-funding-theres-no-guarantee-experts-say/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T13:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Students attend class year-round at Ingels Elementary School in Kansas City, part of the Hickman Mills School District. Political scientists and experts on the state budget say Missouri classrooms aren’t guaranteed more funding if voters legalize sports betting. (Vaughn Wheat/The Beacon) Missourians are being bombarded with ads promoting Amendment 2, a constitutional amendment to legalize sports betting. The betting operators...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meg Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Matter What Happens In This Election, Nobody Is Allowed To Get Mad At Me]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171282</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/no-matter-what-happens-in-this-election-nobody-is-allowed-to-get-mad-at-me"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T13:41:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are less than two weeks out from the 2024 presidential election, and it's time to take stock of the race. 
As regular readers of Defector are certainly aware, I have spent the last few months using my proprietary prediction model, which was first created to project Tom Brady's weekly levels of crud, to forecast the outcome of the upcoming election. The model has told a clear story for the last few weeks: This election is a tossup. The current state of play poses a clear problem, however. If the election is a tossup, and the model can't offer any insight other than to forecast the race with a 50-50 chance to break in either direction, then how do I get people to pay attention to me?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Crudster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Do You Risk In Revisiting A Piece of Culture You Once Loved?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171283</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-do-you-risk-in-revisiting-a-piece-of-culture-you-once-loved"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T13:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it is time for the Defector staff to go into seclusion for our annual company meetings and fall frolic. This year we are gathering in Atlantic City, America's abandoned playground. We decided to hold a mini theme week to keep the site robust and full of blogs while we're in meetings. This year's theme: Risk!
I never would have seen the paintings that probably changed the trajectory of my life if it hadn’t been for a ridiculous, almost unbelievable, amount of luck. In the Fall of 2007, I went to a Dallas Stars hockey game. It was early in the season. My hair was still stained pink from a Manic Panic decision you can only make at 16, and when we walked in the arena an older woman made eye contact with me. They were handing out the kind of gimmicky give-away that is mainly an advertisement: novelty airplane tickets. I would probably have misplaced mine but the woman was so focused and insisted that I keep track of it, that this ticket would be important. And it was. At some point in the game, I won: my ticket flashed on the screen, and was magically transformed from a piece of shiny garbage into two free tickets to anywhere American Airlines flew in the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: All the snow data for KC! (THU-10/24)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3706201</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-all-the-snow-data-for-kc-thu-10-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T13:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'll get another blog out later this morning regarding the storm threats for this evening...but in the meantime... Today I'm presenting a power point about snow climatology for Kansas City to our Integrated Warning Team (IWT) seminar and it's all about one of my favorite topics...snow! The IWT is comprised of my colleagues from the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.24.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076585</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-24-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T13:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Former OpenAI employee says the company "broke copyright law." Except he's not a lawyer and what he's describing doesn't really sound like a copyright violation. But the NY Times is suing OpenAI so... here's a splashy profile about how OpenAI broke copyright law.  [NY Times]
* Disciplinary authorities recommend suspending Montana Attorney General's law license. Which would be significant if Montana's AG dutifully acted as the state's top lawyer as opposed to wasting taxpayer dollars filing frivolous lawsuits about how voter registration is unconstitutional. [Montana Free Press]
* Law firm leadership FOMO. [American Lawyer]
* Michael Avenatti may be out of prison sooner than expected. [Reuters]
* Elite firms cooling on California hiring. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Commission accuses judge of abusing contempt power to bully courtroom. Seems like a lot of that going around these days. [ABA Journal]
* Goldman and Apple to pay for CFPB violations. [Law360]
The post Morning Docket: 10.24.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Johnson County Republicans backtrack after years of attacking abortion rights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858053</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/johnson-county-republicans-backtrack-after-years-of-attacking-abortion-rights/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T11:44:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attendees of the Kansans for Constitutional Freedom watch party celebrate after primary election results verify Kansans voted to keep abortion a constitutional right. (Lily O’Shea Becker/Kansas Reflector) TOPEKA — Johnson County voters would never know by reading campaign websites that Republicans who are seeking reelection there were among the most zealous opponents of abortion rights. Legislators who championed the anti-abortion...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sherman Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Electric Poe spotlights R.H. Wilhoit’s sinister signature in latest cemetery staging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857740</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/electric-poe-spotlights-r-h-wilhoits-sinister-signature-in-latest-cemetery-staging/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T03:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Coterie Theatre The Coterie’s annual Halloween production of Electric Poe is back this year, and once again we’ve got a review that boils down to “Stop reading this and just go see it.” For newbies, Electric Poe is a one man show that runs under an hour, where an adaptation of a few of Edgar Allen Poe’s works are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye Logic Games, Hello Law Students! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076579</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/goodbye-logic-games-hello-law-students-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T23:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More People Are Taking The LSAT After Getting Rid Of The Logic Games Section: So long, and welcome!
Prepare For The Fall: States rush to amend their Constitutions before the Supreme Court overturns gay marriage.
Put Her Back On!: Litigant petitions Supreme Court to get Pauline Newman back.
The Funding Fell From A Biglaw Tree: Attorneys are just throwing money at Kamala's campaign.
Made In Italy: Will surrogacy be targeted in the US too?
The post Goodbye Logic Games, Hello Law Students! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Wachtell Slipping?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076572</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/is-wachtell-slipping/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T22:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Biglaw firm is no longer at the top of the M&A world.
The post Is Wachtell Slipping? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venom: The Last Dance forgets its signature moves and drunkenly stumbles through the grand finale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857744</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/venom-the-last-dance-forgets-its-signature-moves-and-drunkenly-stumbles-through-the-grand-finale/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T21:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Venom: The Last Dance. // Courtesy Columbia Pictures I want to start, dear reader, by letting you know that I’m coming from a place of love. I thought 2018’s Venom was a delightfully shaggy and bizarre affair, restaurant lobster tank bathtub and all. 2021’s Venom: Let There Be Carnage was kind of all over the place, but had its charms....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patent Owner Petitions Supreme Court For Pauline Newman To Hear His Case]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076566</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/patent-owner-petitions-supreme-court-for-pauline-newman-to-hear-his-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T21:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty big praise. 
The post Patent Owner Petitions Supreme Court For Pauline Newman To Hear His Case appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Merge Or Not To Merge, That Is The Question That’s Making Law Firm Leaders Anxious]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076549</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/to-merge-or-not-to-merge-that-is-the-question-thats-making-law-firm-leaders-anxious/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:42:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing partners don't want to get 'left out' of the rush on mergers.
The post To Merge Or Not To Merge, That Is The Question That’s Making Law Firm Leaders Anxious appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America’s 250th Birthday Celebration: Will Voters Choose Genuine Joyous Patriotism Or A Sad Missile Parade?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076504</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/americas-250th-birthday-celebration-will-voters-choose-genuine-joyous-patriotism-or-a-sad-missile-parade/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of directional velocity will come from the top based on whoever wins this presidential election.
The post America’s 250th Birthday Celebration: Will Voters Choose Genuine Joyous Patriotism Or A Sad Missile Parade? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Wolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AHL’s Providence Bruins Pay Tribute to First Responders With Special Edition Jerseys]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82896</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/23/ahls-providence-bruins-pay-tribute-to-first-responders-with-special-edition-jerseys/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T19:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front of jersey features crest with colored stripes representing different branches of first responders and stars to pay respects to those who died in the line of duty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepping For The Supreme Court To Overturn <em>Obergefell</em>]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076560</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/prepping-for-the-supreme-court-to-overturn-obergefell/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T19:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conservatives are coming for same-sex marriage. These states want to be ready.
The post Prepping For The Supreme Court To Overturn <em>Obergefell</em> appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boise State Will Always Be The Greatest Underdogs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170735</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/boise-state-will-always-be-the-greatest-underdogs"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T18:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it is time for the Defector staff to go into seclusion for our annual company meetings and fall frolic. This year we are gathering in Atlantic City, America's abandoned playground. We decided to hold a mini theme week to keep the site robust and full of blogs while we're in meetings. This year's theme: Risk!
The total number of "great games" that you witness as a sports fan can only increase. But in the growing mental pile of walk-offs, hail marys, buzzer beaters, and triple overtimes, I believe that there is a solid, unchanging foundation of formative instant-classics—games that literally shaped your concept of what sports drama should be. In the same way that, per Sam Sifton, a person's first source of pizza becomes the standard against which they judge all pizza for the rest of their lives, the first time you find yourself dazzled by a seemingly impossible outcome remains a permanent reference point. When I trouble myself for a list of "great games," the memories that immediately surface aren't fresh experiences but set impressions from a decade ago or longer. I think about David Freese's Game 6 in 2011, or Landon Donovan's goal against Algeria, or Trey Burke's shot against Kansas, or Boise State beating Oklahoma with a bag of tricks in the Fiesta Bowl.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In 2024, The GOP Is A Big Fan Of Teen Pregnancy]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076563</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/in-2024-the-gop-is-a-big-fan-of-teen-pregnancy/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T18:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus the skinny on Biglaw partner compensation and a Texas court's romantic scandal gets even more wild.
The post In 2024, The GOP Is A Big Fan Of Teen Pregnancy appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Give Up A Lot To Work For The Federal Judiciary]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076550</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/you-give-up-a-lot-to-work-for-the-federal-judiciary/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T17:43:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You shouldn’t have to give up your civil rights.
The post You Give Up A Lot To Work For The Federal Judiciary appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aliza Shatzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off Scrambles To Survive Caramel Week]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171162</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-not-so-great-defector-bake-off-scrambles-to-survive-caramel-week"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T17:21:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off, where Kelsey and Chris attempt to complete the technical challenges from the newest season of The Great British Bake Off in their own home kitchens, with the same time parameters as the professional-grade bakers competing on the show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looks Like Logic Games Really Did Gatekeep The LSAT]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076556</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/looks-like-logic-games-really-did-gatekeep-the-lsat/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T17:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yay! No more sketches!
The post Looks Like Logic Games Really Did Gatekeep The LSAT appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ABC Casts Aileen Cannon As Attorney General In Trump White House 2: Nightmare On Pennsylvania Ave]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076558</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/abc-casts-aileen-cannon-as-attorney-general-in-trump-white-house-2-nightmare-on-pennsylvania-ave/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T16:15:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spooky!
The post ABC Casts Aileen Cannon As Attorney General In Trump White House 2: Nightmare On Pennsylvania Ave appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pop, fizz, and celebrate as Blanc Champagne Bar brings bubbly vibes to Kansas City]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856489</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/pop-fizz-and-celebrate-as-blanc-champagne-bar-brings-bubbly-vibes-to-kansas-city/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T16:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blanc Champagne Bar // Photo By Tiffany Watts Raise your glasses, Kansas City—Blanc Champagne Bar is popping into town, ready to make a splash! Founded by Jordin Johnson, Blanc Champagne Bar, is located at 3835 Main Street in KCMO. This multi-level spot is set to bring a bubbly experience like no other, with a focus on champagne, community, and good...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers Stand Behind Kamala Harris When It Comes To Lining Her Campaign Coffers With Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076553</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/lawyers-stand-behind-kamala-harris-when-it-comes-to-lining-her-campaign-coffers-with-cash/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T15:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers strongly favor Kamala Harris in the presidential race -- and it's obvious from the millions upon millions of dollars she's received from them.
The post Lawyers Stand Behind Kamala Harris When It Comes To Lining Her Campaign Coffers With Cash appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Always Garbage Man Appreciation Week In Our Hearts]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171243</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-always-garbage-man-appreciation-week-in-our-hearts"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T15:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a little two-question quiz for your Wednesday: What would you borrow? What would you lend? I think I’ll borrow tools. Maybe something big and unwieldy, but only if there is an established social protocol for making the inconvenience up to the owner, like using a pickup truck for the afternoon and filling the tank before I bring it back. I’ll lend books, but only if I care more about getting the other person to read the book than I do about getting my copy back. I don’t want to second-guess any of my relationships due to debt on either side. Basically, I avoid mess at all costs. So this week’s story—which involves a coworker forcing our friend-of-a-friend to borrow an heirloom Halloween costume—is a true nightmare wrapped in an obligation.
Our guest this week is none other than Alex Sujong Laughlin, Defector’s Supervising Producer and Normal Gossip’s co-creator! Kelsey finally coaxed Alex to the other side of the mic for a tale of two civic-minded girlbosses in the Department of Sanitation, a stolen cannoli and a Halloween costume.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get the Red Out: Chicago NWSL Club Rebrands to Chicago Stars FC for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82866</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/23/get-the-red-out-chicago-nwsl-club-rebrands-to-chicago-stars-fc-for-2025/soccer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T15:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New name and crest officially take effect in 2025 NWSL season, but team will "celebrate our new era" during their final regular season game of 2024 on Sunday, November 3 against Kansas City]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italy’s Historically Horrific New Surrogacy Law Is Also A Threat To U.S. Attorneys]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076300</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/italys-historically-horrific-new-surrogacy-law-is-also-a-threat-to-u-s-attorneys/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T14:46:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Italian citizenship through ancestry could, in theory, cause some problems. 
The post Italy’s Historically Horrific New Surrogacy Law Is Also A Threat To U.S. Attorneys appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ellen Trachman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Music Club Blows Up The Chicken Man]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170923</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-music-club-blows-up-the-chicken-man-bruce-springsteen-nebraska-discussion"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T14:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Defector Music Club, where a number of our writers get together to dish about an album. Today, Dave McKenna, Luis Paez-Pumar, David Roth, and Lauren Theisen explore Bruce Springsteen's 1982 cult favorite Nebraska.
David: Friends, we are gathered here today to discuss a grim, spare, old album by the foremost living New Jerseyan. The record is Nebraska, the New Jerseyan in question is Bruce Springsteen, and the whole thing is kind of haunted and half-depressed. I do not know why everyone thought I should be the first person to say something about such an album, but as the oldest and saddest New Jerseyan on the staff I was delighted that Lauren picked this record, which has fascinated me since I was a teenager. I love it but find it kind of difficult to talk about. Not because I don’t think it’s great, but because it feels somehow too on the nose for me, being who and how I am, to be like “Oh you like Bruce Springsteen’s anthems? You should really check out his Mood Disorder Album, which has virtually no instrumentation, was recorded on a four-track, and seems to have been co-produced by a ghost.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Better rain potential ahead (WED-10/23)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3705444</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-better-rain-potential-ahead-wed-10-23/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T14:21:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday it looked like Autumn, but it sort of felt like summer with temperatures in the low to mid-80s in the region ahead of a cold front that moved through last night. This front is ushering in cooler, and somewhat more seasonable, air into the region. That's why temperatures will be in the 60s today [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every NBA Uniform, Logo Change For 2024-25 Season]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82816</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/23/every-nba-uniform-logo-change-for-2024-25-season/basketball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T14:18:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A comprehensive list of every uniform, logo and court change that has taken place across the NBA for the 2024-25 season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedge Fund Accused Of Acting Like Typical Australian On South Korean Vacation]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076527</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/10/hedge-fund-accused-of-acting-like-typical-australian-on-south-korean-vacation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T14:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Loud, brash and allegedly unafraid of breaking a few rules.
The post Hedge Fund Accused Of Acting Like Typical Australian On South Korean Vacation appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animals, Ranked By How Magical They Are To See]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171202</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/animals-ranked-by-how-magical-they-are-to-see"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T13:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First there was a dolphin, a brief glimpse of its sleek, slate-gray trunk arcing across the surface, and then, before you knew it, there were so many dolphins. More dolphins than you could count. So many dolphins that as soon as one crested the waves and the cluster of Defector staffers oohed and ahhed and hollered to their comrades It's over there!, the hollering would come from another part of the boat, for another pod of dolphins. They were playing—chasing each other, leaping, flipping their flukes skyward against the setting sun. Breasting the waves for no other reason because they could, and because their bodies were designed to do it, and because their brains are designed to enjoy doing it. At one point three dolphins, side by side, so close as to be touching, emerged from the water …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Preview Of The 2024-25 NBA Season, Accurately Enumerating Everything That Will Happen In It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171095</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-preview-of-the-2024-25-nba-season-accurately-enumerating-everything-that-will-happen-in-it"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wow! They're bringing the NBA back again! Who could have imagined this would happen? No one. There was no reason to expect, nor even to theorize, that it would or could ever happen. Kind of a jerk move when you think about it.
Here at Defector, we do not let the caprice of various sports leagues give us an excuse for failing in our blog duty. If the NBA is going to have a 2024-25 season—if the powers that be are going to announce this many hours after the first games, with no warning—then we will have to "pre-view" it, for the sake of our beloved public, who can learn nothing about any of this except what we provide. From our own loins!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Fresh Donuts and Friendly Bean Coffee prove to be accurate monikers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857607</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-fresh-donuts-and-friendly-bean-coffee-prove-to-be-accurate-monikers/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T13:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh Donuts // Photo By Tiffany Watts Fresh Donuts Tucked away in the corner of a small, unassuming strip mall just off Barry Road, Fresh Donuts is the kind of place you might miss if you’re not looking for it—but trust me, you’ll want to look.  Step inside, and you’re instantly greeted by the warm, comforting aroma of freshly baked...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.23.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076541</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-23-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T12:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Law school applications are up and some suggest it might be due to the end of the logic games section. Look, logic games were dumb but if the thing holding you back from applying to law school was not wanting to deal with one LSAT section then maybe law school isn't your bag. [Reuters]
* Wait, the former CEO of a company that marketed itself with shirtless teenagers might be involved in sex trafficking? [Law360]
* Firms need to tell the truth about which partners are on salary. [Law.com]
* Law professor files ethics complaint against former legal counsel. [Columbia Daily Spectator]
* Georgia Supreme Court tosses contempt ruling against Young Thug attorney. [AJC]
* UK firms have upped billable rates by 40 percent over the last five years. [LegalCheek]
* Lawyers donate $27 million to Harris over the last two months. Sadly it did not stop the fundraising emails in their inboxes. [Bloomberg Law News]
The post Morning Docket: 10.23.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri AG in abortion pill lawsuit argues fewer teen pregnancies hurt state financially]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857700</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missouri-ag-in-abortion-pill-lawsuit-argues-fewer-teen-pregnancies-hurt-state-financially/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T12:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri’s attorney general has renewed a push to restrict access to the abortion pill mifepristone, arguing in a lawsuit filed this month that its availability hurt the state by decreasing teenage pregnancy. The revised lawsuit was filed by Missouri Attorney General Andrew Bailey, alongside GOP attorneys general in Kansas and Idaho. It asks a judge in Texas to order the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Spoerre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Previewing Upcoming Qualifying Offer Decisions: Pitchers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=827885</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/previewing-upcoming-qualifying-offer-decisions-pitchers-2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T00:49:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the baseball world’s immediate focus is on the upcoming showdown between two behemoths, the offseason looms just after the World Series. One of the first key decisions for teams is whether to issue a qualifying offer to any of their impending free agents. Clubs have until the fifth day after the conclusion of the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#1 In His Mind, But Not Where It Counts — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076512</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/1-in-his-mind-but-not-where-it-counts-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rose-Tinted Parenting Or Another Bold Lie?: Even Trump's praise needs fact checking.
No Jail Time For Steel: Georgia's Supreme Court has a much better grasp of how the courtroom should work.
Reading Is Fundamental!: Shame it took Jesse Binnall this long.
Parenting Ain't Easy: Especially when opposing counsel acts like this.
The post #1 In His Mind, But Not Where It Counts — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Short List Of Presidents That Really Understand The Supreme Court]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076513</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-short-list-of-presidents-that-really-understand-the-supreme-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T23:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They had a unique perspective on the institution.
The post The Short List Of Presidents That Really Understand The Supreme Court appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litera’s Former CEO Returns To That Role, As Current CEO Moves Into Temporary Advisory Role]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076483</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/10/literas-former-ceo-returns-to-that-role-as-current-ceo-moves-into-temporary-advisory-role.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T22:33:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avaneesh Marwaha and Litera have another surprise: He has returned as CEO 'to lead the company through the next chapter of integration and innovation,' the company said.
The post Litera’s Former CEO Returns To That Role, As Current CEO Moves Into Temporary Advisory Role appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: KU Basketball kicks off ’24-25 season with Late Night in the Phog featuring Lil Jon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857337</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-ku-basketball-kicks-off-24-25-season-with-late-night-in-the-phog-featuring-lil-jon/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T22:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lil Jon. // photo by Isabella Galvan Friday night, the University of Kansas Jayhawks kicked off basketball season with the annual Late Night in the Phog. It was the 40th annual installment of the event, which showcased both the teams on the court and the new renovations to Allen Fieldhouse, such as new scoreboards and screens and “new amenities throughout...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isabella Galvan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Lobbying Practices Bracing For Change In White House]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076486</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/biglaw-lobbying-practices-bracing-for-change-in-white-house/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will the financial picture for these practices change based on which party wins the White House?
The post Biglaw Lobbying Practices Bracing For Change In White House appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Courtroom To Center Stage: How Legal Drama And Startup Chaos Fuel ‘Dirty Legal Secrets’]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076412</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/from-courtroom-to-center-stage-how-legal-drama-and-startup-chaos-fuel-dirty-legal-secrets/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T21:28:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zhao brings a fresh, comedic, and thought-provoking look at the real-world chaos behind startup culture.
The post From Courtroom To Center Stage: How Legal Drama And Startup Chaos Fuel ‘Dirty Legal Secrets’ appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga V. Mack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruby Freeman And Shaye Moss Win Right To Collect Giuliani’s Unpaid Legal Bills From Trump Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076502</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/ruby-freeman-and-shaye-moss-win-right-to-collect-giulianis-unpaid-legal-bills-from-trump-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T20:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hourly or quantum meruit?
The post Ruby Freeman And Shaye Moss Win Right To Collect Giuliani’s Unpaid Legal Bills From Trump Campaign appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infuriating Story Of The Bullsh*t Working Parents Have To Deal With In The Legal Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076484</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/infuriating-story-of-the-bullsht-working-parents-have-to-deal-with-in-the-legal-industry/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T20:03:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It doesn't make you a worse attorney to have a modicum of compassion for your opposition.
The post Infuriating Story Of The Bullsh*t Working Parents Have To Deal With In The Legal Industry appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmarks And Outcomes — ‘Moneyball’ For GenAI (Part I)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076435</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/benchmarks-and-outcomes-moneyball-for-genai-part-i/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T19:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The movie 'Moneyball' has some lessons to impart about benchmarking AI in legal.
The post Benchmarks And Outcomes — ‘Moneyball’ For GenAI (Part I) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Crutchfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manor Records rings in seventh year of lifting local music at Friday night celebration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856519</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/manor-records-rings-in-seventh-year-of-lifting-local-music-at-friday-night-celebration/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T19:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Provided by Shaun Crowley After providing an outlet for local musicians for nearly a decade, Manor Records—a non-profit DIY record label and record store—will be celebrating its seventh birthday this Friday.  Manor Records started out as a house venue in a basement and has since become a beloved record label that supports artists across Missouri, Kansas, and Oklahoma. Manor Bands...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Your Law Degree For Good]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076497</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/using-your-law-degree-for-good/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T18:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law school clinics can be a bridge to practice.
The post Using Your Law Degree For Good appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Job, Jesse Binnall, You Finally Read The North Carolina Pleading Standards]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076493</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/good-job-jesse-binnall-you-finally-read-the-north-carolina-pleading-standards/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And you pro hac-ed in, too!
The post Good Job, Jesse Binnall, You Finally Read The North Carolina Pleading Standards appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Go Deaf]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171144</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-to-go-deaf"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T16:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew's book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you're at it. Today, we're talking about crutches, eye black, the wave, potluck, and more.
This'll be a more expedient Funbag than usual, given that I'm spending all week at the Defector offsite meetings, where we'll make subtle tweaks to our blueprint for global domination. The Jamboroo will also be lighter than usual. But don't worry, our commenters are adept at taking discussions from here and running with them. So join the scrum down below and the full-length Bag/Roo will be back before you know it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Brags That Daughter Tiffany Trump Graduated ‘No. 1’ In Class — But Georgetown Law Doesn’t Rank Students]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076487</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/donald-trump-brags-that-daughter-tiffany-trump-graduated-no-1-in-class-but-georgetown-law-doesnt-rank-students/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T16:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How completely and utterly embarrassing. Poor Tiffany Trump.
The post Donald Trump Brags That Daughter Tiffany Trump Graduated ‘No. 1’ In Class — But Georgetown Law Doesn’t Rank Students appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Global Law Firms Are Bridging Cultures With AI [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076329</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/how-global-law-firms-are-bridging-cultures-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T15:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frankie Williams of DeepL weighs in on AI-powered translation tools and the potential of emerging tech.
The post How Global Law Firms Are Bridging Cultures With AI appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ABOVE THE LAW</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Megadeth’s Big ‘Risk’ Did Not Pay Off]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169299</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/megadeths-big-risk-did-not-pay-off"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T15:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it is time for the Defector staff to go into seclusion for our annual company meetings and fall frolic. This year we are gathering in Atlantic City, America's abandoned playground. We decided to hold a mini theme week to keep the site robust and full of blogs while we're in meetings. This year's theme: Risk!
Eight years earlier, Metallica had become the biggest rock band in the world. How they did it depends on who you talk to. The self-titled "Black Album" was either softer, slower, more accessible than their previous epic thrash, a concession to the tastes of contemporary music fandom, or, if you ask an early Metallica fan, they sold out. No matter. They sold. It went 16x platinum. Metallica, once the band of nitrous-huffing burnouts and metal-militia headbangers and your older brother who can't keep a job and people who thought Guns 'n' Roses was for girls, was now MTV famous, solidly mainstream. This was absolutely not a given. It could have tanked. Their fans could have turned on them. Bruce Dickinson, frontman of Iron Maiden, gave Metallica credit for "taking the risk and deservedly reaping the enormous rewards."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fray return to Truman with nostalgic hits and post-hiatus EP tracks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857154</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/the-fray-return-to-truman-with-nostalgic-hits-and-post-hiatus-ep-tracks/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T15:03:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fray. // photo by Tommy Vean The Fray took the Truman stage Friday night, marking their first Kansas City performance since going on an indefinite hiatus in 2016. Now comprised of Joe King, Dave Welsh, and Ben Wysocki, the band returned in full form, proving that their pop-rock sound is as great as ever. Opening the night was Rett...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tommy Vean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calling All Biglaw Associates: 2024 Bonus Season Awaits]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076485</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/calling-all-biglaw-associates-2024-bonus-season-awaits/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T14:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Make your predictions and share your thoughts in our annual bonus season survey.
The post Calling All Biglaw Associates: 2024 Bonus Season Awaits appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: 2 more rain chances ahead (TUE-10/22)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3704267</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-2-more-rain-chances-ahead-tue-10-22/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T14:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well we finally cracked the dry string of days in KC! Last night while most of you were sleeping we had .05" of rain with a skinny line of showers/storms moving through quickly. That concluded our 27 day straight rain-free stretch, that while not a record in terms of all time dry stretches, certainly was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer Where A Piano-Playing Pig Once Summered]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076467</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/10/summer-where-a-piano-playing-pig-once-summered"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T14:02:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phil Falcone flogs another house.
The post Summer Where A Piano-Playing Pig Once Summered appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Cares: Housing History]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851113</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-cares-housing-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T13:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carmaletta Williams, CEO of the Black Archives of Mid-America, shows some of the objects a cabin believed to have belonged to a former slave named Lucy Willis, who lived in Missouri. // Photo by Beth Lipoff The Black Archives of Mid-America started as a collection in the trunk of a car. Now, it has its own building with numerous exhibits...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Lipoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Philadelphia Has A Lot To Lose On The New 76ers Arena]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170126</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/philadelphia-has-a-lot-to-lose-on-the-new-76ers-arena"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T13:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No $2 billion price tags or beloved local bars uprooted by eminent domain. But does that make it, you know, good?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neil deMause</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.22.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076474</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-22-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T12:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Central Park 5 have figured out what Dominion and Jean Carroll did -- Trump is a defamation machine and you don't have to take it. [NBC]
* Murdoch sues Perplexity for training on content which is dumb, but not as dumb as thinking the Wall Street Journal is good enough content to use for training. [Reuters]
* Goodwin pushes back against layoff narrative. [American Lawyer]
* Lawyer says trust accounts were needed to avoid becoming homeless. [ABA Journal]
* A government agency whose whole method of delivering results is now under siege? Which party could possibly be responsible? [Reuters]
* People having sex might not get pregnant if Joe Biden has his way. [Law360]
The post Morning Docket: 10.22.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: The Dead South at the Midland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857149</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-the-dead-south-at-the-midland/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T12:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dead South. // photo by Allison Scavo The Dead South with Henry Wagons The Midland Theatre Wednesday, October 16 The Dead South is an energetic Canadian folk-bluegrass band with haunting harmonies. Their alternative country style brings a gritty, foot-stomping sound while their distinctive attire only adds to their rustic, outlaw aesthetic. Banjo player Colton Crawford shared with us that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Scavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hickory Crawdads to play as Goat-Karts]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82791</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/21/hickory-crawdads-to-play-as-goat-karts/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T03:54:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hickory Crawdads, Single-A affiliate of the Texas Rangers in the Carolina League, introduced an alternate identity just moments ago that pays tribute one of the area’s earliest industries, as well as one of its popular contemporary pastimes. The Hickory Goat-Karts brand is an homage to both auto racing and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Caputo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Firm Sets The Record Straight On Layoffs — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076466</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/biglaw-firm-sets-the-record-straight-on-layoffs-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T23:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goodwin Is Watching Fishbowl & Reddit: And they're setting the rumors straight on layoffs.
Reconsider Studying At Harvard: Law students get in trouble for having a study group. This is what we're calling a protest now?
That's Some Expensive Parchment!: SNL has a recommendation on how to use your JD. I would avoid it.
Judge Cleans Up DeSantis's Stupidity: Maybe one day he'll understand how the First Amendment works.
Does Any Competent Lawyer Care?: World's richest goofball really could use some help.
The post Biglaw Firm Sets The Record Straight On Layoffs — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offhand Lie About Central Park 5 Lands Trump Back In Legal Trouble]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076464</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/offhand-lie-about-central-park-5-lands-trump-back-in-legal-trouble/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T23:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He is really good at being demonstrably wrong in public! 
The post Offhand Lie About Central Park 5 Lands Trump Back In Legal Trouble appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The City That’s The Exception To The Biglaw Lateral Partner Hiring Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076462</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-city-thats-the-exception-to-the-biglaw-lateral-partner-hiring-boom/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lateral party missed this city.
The post The City That’s The Exception To The Biglaw Lateral Partner Hiring Boom appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet The First-Ever Openly Transgender Lawyer To Argue Before SCOTUS]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076427</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/meet-the-first-ever-openly-transgender-lawyer-to-argue-before-scotus/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T21:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations on this outstanding accomplishment.
The post Meet The First-Ever Openly Transgender Lawyer To Argue Before SCOTUS appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: KC Mavericks claim a demanding victory over Wichita in home-opener]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857023</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-kc-mavericks-claim-a-demanding-victory-over-wichita-in-home-opener/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T21:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City Mavericks versus Wichita Thunder on Saturday, Oct. 19, 2024. // Photo by Eli Ralls The Kansas City Mavericks take down the Wichita Thunder 5-2 in home-opener of the ECHL 2024 Season on Saturday, Oct. 19. The boys in orange and white wasted no time getting the goals rolling this season, scoring their first of the game in the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Ralls</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So Much For Free Speech: Harvard Law Students Punished For Reading Together At Campus Library]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076445</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/so-much-for-free-speech-harvard-law-students-punished-for-reading-together-at-campus-library/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T20:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even study groups are complex now. 
The post So Much For Free Speech: Harvard Law Students Punished For Reading Together At Campus Library appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Played Pretend In A McDonald’s I Once Knew Intimately]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170996</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/donald_trump_mcdonalds_feasterville_playing_pretend"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T20:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I will admit that it has shaken me to my very core, or at least to the point where I have not been able to get through a post that was supposed to be mostly jokes. On Sunday, Donald Trump went to a McDonald’s in Feasterville, Pa., that I have previously visited plenty of times, a McDonald’s just down from the restaurant where my high school girlfriend worked. (That restaurant is now an AutoZone.)
Trump was there for a photo op designed to push the story, which has been a favorite among the sort of people that would like this kind of thing, that Kamala Harris never worked at McDonald’s. Though there’s no record of that gig—paper short-term employment records from 1983 wouldn’t have been kept, I am forced to explain seriously—the Washington Post writes that McDonald’s “accepts” that Harris worked there. Trump's stunt was obviously a bit of pointless political theater; Trump was there for a photo op that would be considered embarrassing were it done by anyone else on the planet but the planet’s most embarrassing man. It was nonetheless covered pretty straightforwardly by the media, as they tend to do with Trump. He pretended to be a McDonald’s employee for 15 minutes; many news outlets used a headline that he “worked” there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Jayhawks try to turn season around with win over Houston at Arrowhead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856552</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-jayhawks-try-to-turn-season-around-with-win-over-houston-at-arrowhead/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T20:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas Jayhawks versus Houston Cougars on Saturday, Oct. 19. // Photo by Tarik Sykes The Jayhawks took over Arrowhead on Saturday, Oct. 19, as they clashed heads against the Houston Cougars. Both teams have underperformed this season, but KU comes out on top with a 42-14 win over the Texas school. Jalon Daniels and Devin Neal led the squad to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarik Sykes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conquering Conferences: The Art Of The Graceful Exit]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076299</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/conquering-conferences-the-art-of-the-graceful-exit/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T20:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knowing how to bow out gracefully is key to maintaining your social finesse.
The post Conquering Conferences: The Art Of The Graceful Exit appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEJAL PATEL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Temwa Chawinga shatters more records as Current breeze to victory on Saturday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856532</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-temwa-chawinga-shatters-more-records-as-current-breeze-to-victory-on-saturday/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T19:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KC Current versus San Diego Wave on Saturday, Oct. 19, 2024. // Photo by Tarik Sykes KC Current took down San Diego Wave in a dominant fashion on Saturday, Oct. 19, capping the game off with four goals scored, only letting up one in minute 88 of the match. The balls began flying into the back of the next in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarik Sykes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Rebukes DeSantis Admin: ‘It’s The First Amendment, Stupid.’]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076441</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/judge-rebukes-desantis-admin-its-the-first-amendment-stupid/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T19:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not 'speech,' it's 'sanitary nuisance!'
The post Judge Rebukes DeSantis Admin: ‘It’s The First Amendment, Stupid.’ appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SNL Nails The Dumbest Thing To Do With Your JD]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076446</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/snl-nails-the-dumbest-thing-to-do-with-your-jd/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T18:29:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Put your law degree to work -- but not like that.
The post SNL Nails The Dumbest Thing To Do With Your JD appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Southampton Is Too Stubborn For The Premier League]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171058</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/southampton-is-too-stubborn-for-the-premier-league"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T18:28:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Promotion from the Championship into the Premier League is a double-edged sword. On the one hand, it is the greatest financial boost in world soccer, one that can change a club's entire future. On the other, the clubs that make the trip into the top division often have to throw out everything that worked in the Championship in order to survive.
It's not too bold to say that teams reliant on possession in their chase for promotion must quickly adapt to playing without the ball against the Liverpools and Arsenals of the world. This is a lesson that Southampton is learning ever so painfully at the start of this season, and whether the club takes it to heart or not will likely dictate whether the Saints go marching back to the Championship next season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Judges Lays Into Biglaw Attorneys For Running Up Legal Bills]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076443</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/federal-judges-lays-into-biglaw-attorneys-for-running-up-legal-bills/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T17:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Benchslapped over an effort to 'gum up the works.'
The post Federal Judges Lays Into Biglaw Attorneys For Running Up Legal Bills appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bayern Munich Updates Colors to Comply With New German Accessibility Law]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82758</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/21/bayern-munich-updates-colors-to-comply-with-new-german-accessibility-law/soccer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T17:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[German Accessibility Improvement Act brings country's law into alignment with European Accessibility Act and includes guidelines on contrast ratio between colors on digital platforms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mets Ran Out Of Magic]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170974</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-mets-ran-out-of-magic"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T17:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's no percentage in being right about a baseball team you care about. It's nice to feel smart, I guess, but "feeling smart" and for that matter "being right" are not really what I got into any of this for. Those are for gamblers and pedants, and of all the reasons that have made me care about the New York Mets during my life—habit and family custom and various personality defects specific to me, including but not limited to stubbornness and fatalism and whatever it is that makes people bite their fingernails—it has never crossed my mind that doing so was somehow a reasonable thing to do.
In a sense, being right about the team you care about is the last thing a person would want. Again, pedants and gamblers will differ on this, but they're in it for different reasons. It fits, in a bleak sort of way, that those are the types of fans sports leagues seem to be selecting for, or actively trying to create; owners, being owners, would naturally prefer that their fans be consumers instead of ... whatever this other way of caring is. The consumer relationship is easier to produce and reproduce, and much more readily leveraged. It reflects the way in which owners and executive types understand more or less everything, but also it makes a sort of pragmatic sense. It is easier to understand a baseball team as an expensive entertainment product that generates revenue on various platforms than it is as a machine that helps people become insane in ways of their choosing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Biglaw Firm Shuts Down Layoff Rumors By Issuing Statement On Fishbowl, Reddit]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076428</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/goodwin-shuts-down-layoff-rumors-by-issuing-statement-on-fishbowl-reddit/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T17:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contrary to what you may have heard, there are no layoffs going on at Goodwin right now. 
The post Top Biglaw Firm Shuts Down Layoff Rumors By Issuing Statement On Fishbowl, Reddit appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If You Must Gamble, Gamble In Person, Like An Adult]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170863</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/if-you-must-gamble-gamble-in-person-like-an-adult"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again it is time for the Defector staff to go into seclusion for our annual company meetings and fall frolic. This year we are gathering in Atlantic City, America's abandoned playground. We decided to hold a mini theme week to keep the site robust and full of blogs while we're in meetings. This year's theme: Risk!
As a general rule, risk is overrated, both as a spur to future success and as a general way of life. The myth that risk begets reward has always been a self-aggrandizing lie told by the ones who won and stood on the skulls of the ones who didn't. The thought that risk is an excellent provider of adrenaline is actually provable nonsense. Risk, put simply, sucks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Notes]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170985</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/programming-notes-6"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello. Prepare to receive precious information. This week, the staff of Defector is once again gathering in a secret location to hold our all-company meetings. We are not going to the woods this year. Instead, we are going somewhere awful, because we are stupid. You know the drill by now. Due to these meetings, we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Liberty Were Built, Bought, And Blessed]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170999</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-liberty-were-built-bought-and-blessed"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a relief when it all ended: An ugly overtime. A straight-up bad Game 5. A gripping Finals series. The greatest, noisiest WNBA season in memory. And for the New York Liberty, winners of their first-ever championship on Sunday night, a decades-long tradition of heartbreak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Needs People Who Care About Him… And Have Law Degrees]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076437</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/elon-musk-needs-people-who-care-about-him-and-have-law-degrees/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musk's new voter registration lottery is... certainly not what a lawyer would recommend.
The post Elon Musk Needs People Who Care About Him… And Have Law Degrees appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keep Them Coming: Familiar Stranger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=851106</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/keep-them-coming-familiar-stranger/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T16:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kristen Thomas // Photo by Nicole Bissey Role-play serves as a gateway between imagination and desire. Your brain is your biggest sex organ, so role-play offers a way to use it to build a highly erotic encounter. Whether you’re in a relationship and you two (or more) work together to formulate a playful time, or you’re single and turning to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristen Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Thomson Reuters Supercharged CoCounsel With Gen AI Advances [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076356</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/how-thomson-reuters-supercharged-cocounsel-with-gen-ai-advances/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T15:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CoCounsel 2.0 is a faster, more integrated, and smarter AI legal assistant.
The post How Thomson Reuters Supercharged CoCounsel With Gen AI Advances appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Took A TikTok Class. What Happened Next Blew My Mind]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170900</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-took-a-tiktok-class-what-happened-next-blew-my-mind"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T15:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inside me there are two wolves. The first is super embarrassed to admit that I paid lots of money to an influencer to teach me how to make TikToks this summer. The only thing less cool than putting effort into your social media presence is paying someone to teach you how to put effort into your social media presence. The second wolf is the one who writes this column, who is curious about the way the attention economy has led many of us to commodify our identities online, the way that commodification can translate directly to money, and how requisite it's all starting to feel.
Parasocial appeal is the core of what constitutes success on the internet right now. Are you able to convey your personality in such a condensed way that strangers feel like they know you, and even like you? Can you quickly tell the story of who you are through videos and images? It’s harder than it looks. If you don’t believe me, open up your front-facing camera right now and try recording yourself telling a funny story. Now, hit post. It’s miserable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thirteen Times Athletes Wore Typos on their Uniforms]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82753</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/21/thirteen-times-athletes-wore-typos-on-their-uniforms/featured/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T15:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typos on Jerseys? It happens! Here's a look at thirteen times players wore spelling errors during an actual game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Creamer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Oct. 21: Sub-liminal Messages]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171033</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-oct-21-sub-liminal-messages"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T15:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Man cannot live by bread alone, but maybe he can live by crosswords alone. This week's puzzle was constructed by Malaika Handa and Stephen Lurie, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Malaika has been publishing crossword puzzles since 2021, and currently contributes to Vulture's daily puzzle. Stephen has been publishing crossword puzzles since *checks calendar* October 21, 2024. You can find both of them in Brooklyn, where this puzzle will be financing a tasty treat.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Impossible Question Each For Harris And Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076424</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/one-impossible-question-each-for-harris-and-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T14:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You could ask Trump or Harris hard questions in interviews, but you'd never hear an answer. 
The post One Impossible Question Each For Harris And Trump appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Herrmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let Me Push The Win Button]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170998</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/let-me-push-the-dodgers-win-button"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T14:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear the Dodgers,
I saw that you have a Win Button, a button that Dodger Stadium music director/organist Dieter Ruehle hits when you win. This button is intriguing to me.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: At least there are some rain chances (MON-10/21)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3703246</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-at-least-there-are-some-rain-chances-mon-10-21/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T14:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's going to be another warm and breezy day for late October, with average highs in the mid-60s. Today, we will easily exceed those values as highs soar to around 80° or so before the end of the afternoon. While the records are in the 89° range for highs, and we won't get close to [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedge Fund Manager Suggests Index Funds If You’d Like To Make Some Money]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076417</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/10/hedge-fund-manager-suggests-index-funds-if-youd-like-to-make-some-money"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T14:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As long as it lasts, because David Einhorn's sure as hell not gonna make any for the foreseeable future.
The post Hedge Fund Manager Suggests Index Funds If You’d Like To Make Some Money appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[History Is For The Dead And The Boring]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170976</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dodgers-yankees-world-series"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T13:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lots of fans can claim to be "long-suffering" as a labeling fetish, even if they aren't. New York Liberty fans, for instance, were long-suffering—until Sunday night, when they cashed in their 28 years without a championship and transitioned into "deliriously smug, smugly delirious, and not even pissed at Sabrina Ionescu any more." It happens that fast. The previous almost-three decades notwithstanding, they got their money's worth, and then some.
And then there's this World Series, which is the dead opposite, and more's the pity. Nothing will leaden eyelids quite like listening to Yankee fans and Dodger fans grind on the rest of us civilians about their respective places on the double-decker throne, let alone their shared hearkening back to their joint heritage as the keepers of the sport back when baseball had not yet cracked the Pacific Time Zone. A nation already hopelessly fractured and ready to go even more Serb and Croat two Tuesdays from now can safely unite as one, however briefly, in our hatred of both teams. The prognosis wasn’t good regardless, but expect the next fortnight to be hell with a Bob Costas voiceover. Fox has the games, but it's not his voice that offends, you see; rather the subject matter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.21.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076423</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-21-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T13:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Former Biglaw partner sentenced to 16 months in prison. What's the matter number on that time? [ABA Journal]
* Prosecutor sues Georgetown over data breach in rare instance where a Georgetown graduate doesn't want everyone to know about it. [Reuters]
* With a new film out there about Trump's relationship with Roy Cohn, the Advocate has a deep dive into the famed lawyer's life and times. [Advocate]
* Oklahoma is asking the Supreme Court to force the federal government to give back funding for medical services that it withheld after Oklahoma declared that it wasn't going to allow those medical services. [Law360]
* Law school clinic working on Supreme Court case aimed at protecting the rights of... straight people? [Balls and Strikes]
* FTC's new merger rules exemplify ongoing fight within the agency. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Biglaw firms building out alumni programs. [American Lawyer]
The post Morning Docket: 10.21.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Overland Park Convention Center’s Executive Chef David Ruiz]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855565</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-overland-park-convention-centers-executive-chef-david-ruiz/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T13:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of David Ruiz Listen up, foodies—Kansas City just upped the culinary ante when the Overland Park Convention Center hired David Ruiz as the venue’s new executive chef. Ruiz—a James Beard Foundation competition winner—has quite the impressive culinary background. From Aspen to Albuquerque, he’s honed his craft working in several award-winning restaurants. He quips his style meets at the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>