<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-02-11T12:31:34.347Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AR Tag Placement and Finder Tool – minimalist image editor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142164</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ar-tag-placement-finder-tool-minimalist-image-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T11:34:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AR Tag Placement and Finder Tool is a minimalist image editor designed for placing augmented reality (AR) tags and QR codes, into images.
The post AR Tag Placement and Finder Tool – minimalist image editor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chirurgien – hex editor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142126</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/chirurgien-hex-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T09:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chirurgien is an hex editor and a tool for reverse engineering, analyzing, and carving binary file formats.
The post Chirurgien – hex editor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flow State Episode 264]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-episode-264</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-episode-264"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T08:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s mix opens with the “Music of Wellness” track from the TV show Severance. We play some other gentle ambient pieces by Zane Trow, Sgarz, David Bowie (produced by Brian Eno), and Yumiko Morioka. We play through recent instrumental discoveries from Rubey Hu (h/t]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Best Free and Open Source Photo Metadata Editors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=5653</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/photometadataeditors/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T07:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A metadata editor is computer software which allows users to view and edit metadata tags interactively and save them in the graphics file.
The post 7 Best Free and Open Source Photo Metadata Editors appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coulomb –  simple and elegant circuit simulator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142271</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/coulomb-simple-elegant-circuit-simulator/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-11T07:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coulomb is billed as a simple and beautiful circuit simulator app for Linux.
The post Coulomb –  simple and elegant circuit simulator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GopherDrop – Secure One-Time Secret Sharing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142156</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gopherdrop-secret-sharing/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T23:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GopherDrop is a secure, self-hostable REST API and UI for sharing encrypted one-time secrets and files.
The post GopherDrop – Secure One-Time Secret Sharing appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland Continues Moving Toward Historic Rugby Threepeat With Assist From Failed Imperialist Nation Where Game Was Invented]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181055</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ireland-six-nations-threepeat"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T21:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland came out strong and finished stronger while defeating Scotland, 32-18, in a Six Nations rugby tilt Sunday evening in Edinburgh. Ireland, the tournament's two-time defending champs, came out of the weekend as the only remaining undefeated side after only two rounds.
Ireland struggled to get going last week in Dublin in its Six Nations opener before blitzing England with 22 unanswered points to put the match away in the second half. There was no such slow start against the Scots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[qr-rs – encode URLs or text into QR codes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142170</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/qr-rs-encode-urls-text-qr-codes/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T21:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[qr-rs is a command line interface utility to encode URLs or more generally text into QR codes in various file formats and colors.
The post qr-rs – encode URLs or text into QR codes appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scenes From Broad Street And Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180971</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/scenes-from-broad-street-and-beyond"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T19:53:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA — The Philadelphia Eagles are Super Bowl champions once again. After whomping the Kansas City Chiefs 40-22, the Eagles join the ranks of teams with multiple title wins, a list that had felt incomplete without this most rabid of fanbases. While fans' celebrations for Super Bowl 59 were missing the first-time-winner chaos of the 2018 victory, there was plenty of screaming and mirth in the immediate aftermath of this one-sided ass-beating.
Following the Eagles' win, Defector Philadelphia Bureau members Kathryn Xu and Luis Paez-Pumar filtered out onto the streets of the city to capture the delight of a city in the thralls of Birdsmania. The results weren't quite as blissful or picturesque as either hoped, but one thing rang true for our intrepid reporters: Philadelphia had itself a party for the ages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Want To Go To The Wet, Empty Alley Where Kevin Burkhardt And Tom Brady Called Last Night’s Game]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181007</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-want-to-go-to-the-wet-empty-alley-where-kevin-burkhardt-and-tom-brady-called-last-nights-game"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T19:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last night Fox Sports unveiled a new graphics package, as companies tend to do for the Super Bowl, and I pretty much liked it. The main thing to notice was the score box—minimalist, clean, not too distracting. Sports broadcasts tend to clutter up the screen, and this was a nice change in my opinion. It did clash with the maximalist Super Bowl graphics, but I will be happy if that’s the route Fox is going with next season.
I will admit that it is at least a little bit sad that I care about this. Time to make things even sadder: I have one massive complaint about the Super Bowl graphics package, and I want to share it with you here. A few times per game football broadcasts will throw to the announcers in the booth, where they will deliver analysis, convey game storylines, or just yuk it up a bit on camera. With the game itself being a blowout pretty much straight through, last night's broadcast went to Kevin Burkhardt and Tom Brady multiple times. They were shown not in the booth, but in front of a green screen. More to the point, Burkhardt and Brady were in front of a green screen depicting a completely empty alleyway that had apparently just been soaked by rain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tanks of Freedom II – Indie Turn Based Strategy Game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142160</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tanks-of-freedom-ii-indie-turn-based-strategy-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T18:50:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tanks of Freedom II is a classic, turn-based strategy game with up to four armies fighting against each other. 
The post Tanks of Freedom II – Indie Turn Based Strategy Game appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kendrick Lamar Did The Super Bowl Halftime Show His Way]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180955</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/kendrick-lamar-did-the-super-bowl-halftime-show-his-way"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T18:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kendrick Lamar capped off the greatest year a rapper has had in quite some time with a Super Bowl halftime show designed specifically to piss off Drake, his fans, and Fox News conservatives alike. A week after winning five Grammys for "Not Like Us," it was pretty obvious that the smash hit was going to make an appearance, despite Drake's dogged attempts to sue damn near the entire music industry over the song. And Kendrick clearly had fun with that fact, repeatedly teasing the record at various points during the show until eventually performing it. At the song's telling moment, with a mischievous grin, Kendrick called out Drake right to camera before deftly declining to say the word "pedophile" on national TV.
"Not Like Us" quickly transcended its original context within the beef, and has since become an anthem like The Killers' "Mr. Brightside" or The White Stripes' "Seven Nation Army." It helps that its message is easily refashioned into a generalizable sentiment: THEY are not like US, whoever "they" or "us" might be. Kendrick himself has encouraged this broadening of the song's scope. "Not like us is the energy of who I am, the type of man I represent," he said in an interview with SZA in Harper's Bazaar. "This man has morals, he has values, he believes in something, he stands on something. He’s not pandering. If I’m thinking of 'Not Like Us,' I’m thinking of me and whoever identifies with that." Sure. Fine. But there is a context to it, and a fallout from it, and Kendrick brought it all up there with him on the Super Bowl stage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Scorebug Snuggery: Super Bowl 59 Goes Big And Brutalist]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180935</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-scorebug-snuggery-super-bowl-59-goes-big-and-brutalist"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T18:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Scorebug Snuggery, that place we all know of and recognize, where we discuss the artistic merit of scorebugs on sports television broadcasts. Today, we look at the Fox network's new scorebug. 
Sunday night's Big Game was one of the least suspenseful Super Bowls of the 21st century, and thus, while watching, I had plenty of time to contemplate the scorebug. Debuting on Fox was the design seen in the screenshot above, replacing the old model, displayed below in the NFC Championship Game:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Luka Doncic Trade Needed Just Three Quarters To Go From Bad To Worse]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180969</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-luka-doncic-trade-needed-just-three-quarters-to-go-from-bad-to-worse"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T17:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Relying on Anthony Davis's availability is like setting foot on a rotted, rickety trapdoor and believing you'll be able to take another step. Beneath the trapdoor, in this analogy, is hell. Nico Harrison and Mavericks owner Patrick Dumont arranged it this way: By making it about a championship window, by calling their popular world-beating superstar an unreliable toxic fatso on his way out, by shrinking the period of observation down to the near term, the Mavericks all but announced This has to work right away. It became a piece of basketball wisdom so cheap and obvious that bothering to articulate it aloud had the ironic effect of making the speaker look somehow less knowledgeable about the sport: All of whatever they imagine makes Davis more valuable than Doncic to the present-day Mavericks relies upon Davis being upright. Davis does lots of things, many of them great and wonderful, but one of the things he does a lot is get hurt. And after not even three quarters of basketball in a Mavericks uniform, Davis got hurt.
He was playing very well Saturday, dominating the Houston Rockets and helping the Mavs to a 17-point halftime lead. Davis's skill and versatility popped immediately. He opened the game with a post touch against a positional mismatch, pulled in a help defender, scanned the court, and threw a perfect lob pass to Daniel Gafford for an alley-oop. Seconds later he swatted a layup from Alperen Sengun, gathered the rebound, led the break, and dished ahead to P.J. Washington for a transition dunk. Minutes later Davis dribbled the ball into the front court, sized up another mismatch, backed his defender into the paint, and turned over his shoulder for a calm jump hook. By halftime, Davis had 24 points, 13 rebounds, five assists, and three blocks, and the Mavericks had won his 21 minutes by a convincing 17 points. Harrison, who'd relinquished his seats in the arena due to the intensity of fan backlash, was for sure hearing the swelling music, if not the actual sounds of the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Eagles Were Just So Cool]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180931</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-eagles-were-just-so-cool"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T16:22:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ron Jaworski made a great throw, and Charlie Smith was open in the end zone. The Eagles had a first-quarter touchdown—until the refs threw a flag. Harold Carmichael, who would become a Hall of Famer, went in motion before the snap. He’d left too early. The play was called back, the Eagles punted, and three plays later Oakland Raiders quarterback Jim Plunkett hit Kenny King for an 80-yard score. The Eagles lost the Super Bowl, 27-10.
That was Super Bowl 15, which was played in 1981, in New Orleans. I thought about that play during the first quarter of the Eagles’ absurd 40-22 blowout over the Chiefs last night in Super Bowl 59. I’d been thinking a lot about Super Bowl 15, the Eagles’ first and only previous New Orleans Super Bowl appearance. Never mind that it happened before I was born; oldheads in my neighborhood who had attended the game filled me in during my childhood. They talked about that Eagles Super Bowl trip as if they’d made a medieval pilgrimage to the Abbey of Saint Gall (patron saint of birds). They also complained about the penalty, still, a decade-plus after the fact. It was bullshit, they’d say, not pausing to apologize for the word. They believed that the Eagles could’ve won if they’d just been able to tie the game at 7 there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Feb. 10: Telework]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180939</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-feb-10-telework"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's no puzzle like our Monday crossword. This week's puzzle was constructed by Kate Hawkins and Rachel Fabi, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Rachel and Kate went to the same college at (mostly) the same time and then worked for the same educational nonprofit but didn't meet each other until they started making crosswords nearly a decade later. They have since met J. Smith Cameron.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Best Free and Open Source Cheatsheet Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142191</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-cheatsheet-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T15:40:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cheatsheet is a concise set of notes used for quick reference. We recommend the best cheatsheet tools for Linux.
The post 6 Best Free and Open Source Cheatsheet Tools appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sled – embedded database]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142154</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/sled-embedded-database/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T15:32:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sled is an embedded database that's written in the Rust programming language.
The post sled – embedded database appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Win The Draft And You Can Beat Everyone’s Ass]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180932</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/win-the-draft-and-you-can-beat-everyones-ass"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T15:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Philadelphia Eagles are your decisive Super Bowl champions, and I could interpret their victory through a whole host of choices on the narrative play sheet. Jalen Hurts, the most serious person who has ever lived, finally getting the recognition he deserves as a fully-rounded quarterback. Eagles defensive coordinator Vic Fangio ruining Patrick Mahomes’s shit without having to call a single blitz. Kansas City’s atrocious pass protection finally catching up with them, same as in 2020. GOAT coronations withheld. Cooper DeJean’s pick-six. Saquon. The power of Italian thinking. Whatever take greases your pole, you can have at it.
So here’s mine: the Eagles won this title because they draft out of their fucking minds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Winter storm watch in effect (MON-2/10)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3820188</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-winter-storm-watch-in-effect-tue-2-10/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T14:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More winter weather is hitting the metro this week with high snow totals and a winter storm watch issued for the region.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick Mahomes Was In Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180909</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/patrick-mahomes-hell-eagles-chiefs-superbowl"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T14:02:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick Mahomes, the best quarterback in the world, spent Super Bowl Sunday being ground into a fine paste by the Eagles' pass rush, and then for good measure, jarred and preserved. Pressured on 38 percent of his snaps, Mahomes was hit 11 times, sacked six times, forced into a pair of picks, and fumbled the ball away once. In one of the more stunning stats in NFL history, the Eagles did all that without blitzing a single time. That trickles down—because they never had to send help, Philadelphia was able to stay in Cover 4 all game long, cutting off deep balls and quickly smothering anything underneath. "In order to make a team blitz, you have to be able to beat what they're showing." Mahomes said." And that's what we didn't do." 
Patrick Smith/Getty Images]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ExTiX – Ubuntu-based Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141010</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/extix-ubuntu-based-linux-distro/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T11:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ExTiX is a Linux distribution based on Ubuntu. 
The post ExTiX – Ubuntu-based Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Apple AirDrop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142236</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-apple-airdrop/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T11:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple AirDrop is a proprietary wireless ad hoc service. We recommend the best free and open source alternatives for Linux.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Apple AirDrop appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blanket Swimming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/blanket-swimming</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/blanket-swimming"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T08:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Blanket Swimming, an American electronic musician based in Kansas City.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlsaPlayer – heavily multi-threaded PCM player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142147</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alsaplayer-heavily-multi-threaded-pcm-player/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T07:03:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AlsaPlayer is a type of PCM player. It is heavily multi-threaded and tries to excercise the ALSA library and driver quite a bit. 
The post AlsaPlayer – heavily multi-threaded PCM player appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incoming Asteroid]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3049/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3049/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Eagles So Humiliated The Chiefs That Even Philly Fans Have To Believe]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180894</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-eagles-so-humiliated-the-chiefs-that-even-philly-fans-have-to-believe"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T03:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kansas City Chiefs did the sensible, defensive, and very orthodox thing when they won the opening coin flip of Super Bowl 59—they deferred possession until the second half. It was the last thing they controlled the entire evening.
The team that rope-a-doped their way to almost incandescent glory in 2024 instead found out that, sometimes, you just can't slip the punch. It wasn't the third-time's-not-the-charm jinx that did them in, it was the Philadelphia Eagles. And more decisively, it was the Eagles with only some Saquon Barkley, an entirely different M.O. That meant the Chiefs weren't undone by a single player but a smothering collective impervious to even Patrick Mahomes's multileveled sorceries. The final score of 40-22 grossly flattered the Chiefs and barely explained Philadelphia's dominance. It's as if the "GAME OVER" legend at the end of Kendrick Lamar's halftime show had been frantically cobbled together after Zack Baun's second quarter interception.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slint – blind-friendly Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142111</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/slint-blind-friendly-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T23:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slint is an easy-to-use, versatile, blind-friendly Linux distribution for 64-bit computers. It's based on Slackware.
The post Slint – blind-friendly Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Could Only Be One Hubie Brown]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180865</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/there-could-only-be-one-hubie-brown"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T23:12:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be wrong to say that Hubie Brown deserved a better sendoff than Bucks 135, Sixers 127 on Super Bowl Sunday because Hubie Brown was perfect for Bucks 135, Sixers 127. He would have bunny-hopped across an eight-lane highway for Bucks 135, Sixers 127 because for him—the last true basketball lifer—it wasn't the 135 or the 127 that moved him. It was the Bucks and Sixers part, and it would have been the same had he been given Pistons 112, Hornets 102, or Rockets 94, Raptors 87, or even anything involving the freshly re-deadified Wizards. Hubie was there unapologetically for The Game before him and only The Game before him. If you would have preferred Rockets-Raptors because it featured 81 points of better defense, you would have been wrong because every games was equal in his eyes— a chance to explain what was before him to people wanting to learn.
Hubie Brown is 91, and he looked and sounded every day of it 20 years ago when his coaching career ended. He coached somewhere for 30-some-odd years (even Wikipedia doesn't have firm dates for two of his high school jobs) and broadcasted somewhere for 29. He coached forever the same way, and he told the stories of the game the same way. He knew what he believed to be important, and walked and talked with that central precept for the entirety of his public life. He did it for so long and so unabashedly his way that he managed, somehow, to never fall out of fashion while anyone who came after him trying it Hubie's way was out of fashion immediately. The closest anyone came to doing Hubie was the much younger but no less self-assured JJ Redick, and he got in two years and change before he was hired to Hubie-up the Los Angeles Lakers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers’s Jets Tenure Ended In True Jets Fashion]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180859</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/aaron-rodgerss-jets-tenure-ended-in-true-jets-fashion"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T21:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brick Johnson wields a sure, swift sword, and even if he didn't wield this one, it's nice to think he did without even looking up from his Fortnite screen. This might just be a sins-of-the-father vehicle, but when the New York Jets make news, his name will be invoked because they are the Jets constantly doing Jets things.
If we are to trust Jay Glazer, and let's face it, he's no less trustworthy than any of the other sneaks who pull news out of the NFL before it can type up a release, Rodgers flew to New York last week to learn about his future with the Jets only to discover that he'd already had it. The Jets were, as they say, moving on to their next stupid idea, and their 19th starting quarterback since 2010, the last time they played more than the minimum allotted games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Hip Stretch To Help You Stay Sane]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180833</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-hip-stretch-to-help-you-stay-sane"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T19:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news is all shit right now. Sure, there are more artful, creative, and writerly,  ways to say that, but time is precious and writing something like that would prove nothing more than ownership of a thesaurus. 
If you're like me and millions of others, you are absorbing all this and wondering, "What can I do?" You can subscribe to journalism (which you probably already do! Yay!), donate money, volunteer, show up for your family, friends, and neighbors, and then what? That's the thing about the battle for a real democracy—it is not won in flashy, Hollywood fight scenes, though those do make for excellent inspirational images for sharing amid said battle for democracy. It's won in federal workers showing up to do their jobs. It's won in reporters showing up to do their jobs. It's won in a lot of us, in our own ways, showing up, doing our jobs, and not being assholes, even to the person who irritates you—and they are so, so annoying—but dammit we'll deal with that after we make sure there's still a republic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Superb Owl Lead Up That Never Was]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180851</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-superb-owl-lead-up-that-never-was"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T19:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This has not been a terribly memorable walk up to the Superb Owl, not in New Orleans, not across America, not even in Australia, where the NFL is staging a regular season game in 2026 as a very belated punishment to the Los Angeles Rams for those uniforms. And if you can't be weird in Louisiana, well, what exactly is the point?
When your biggest moment of the week, after all, is Roger Goodell leaning hard into an 18th game, you have a serious cultural dud on your hands. The football will be the football, of course, and as matchups go Eagles-Chiefs is not far from the best you can do. But New Orleans might be the last bastion of the pre-corporate days when the town created the atmosphere and it was up to the visitors to keep up. This time, the weirdest thing we got will be something we have to conjure in our own minds—the big game with a sitting President (Uncle Dismal) and a potential rival in 2028 (Stephen A. Smith). Neither is qualified to do the job, as one has proven and the other certainly would if given the chance, but the moment Smith's name appeared on a poll listing potential Democratic candidates and garnering 2 percent, we took an irrevocable turn toward a world in which Prince Andrew seems leaderly. All that is left for the rest of us is to find a country without an extradition treaty out of the way of the nuclear winds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickgui – virtual machine manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142101</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/quickgui-virtual-machine-manager/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T18:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quickgui is a graphical user interface for the Quickemu virtual machine manager.
The post Quickgui – virtual machine manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Snowstorm(s?) likely in KC (SUN-2/9)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3819475</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-snowstorms-likely-in-kc-sun-2-9/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T17:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Super Bowl Sunday, and New Orleans yesterday hit a record 85° at the airport. Here in Kansas City, we've dumped back into the colder air today and this cold will be with us for a while it appears. It's one ingredient to the set-up for multiple snow chances into next weekend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Snowstorm(s?) likely in KC (SUN-2/9)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3819475</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-snowstorms-likely-in-kc-sun-2-9/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T17:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Super Bowl Sunday and while New Orleans yesterday hit a record 85° at the airport...here in KC we've dumped back into the colder air today and this cold will be with us for awhile it appears. It's one ingredient to the set-up for multiple snow chances into next weekend. There will be a more [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BinEd – binary / hex editor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142123</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/bined-binary-hex-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T16:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BinEd is an editor for binary data (hex viewer/editor). It's written in Java so runs under a wide range of platforms.
The post BinEd – binary / hex editor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart.Framework – PHP and JavaScript web framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142066</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/smart-framework-php-javascript-web-framework/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T16:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart.Framework is a practical, modern and high performance PHP / JavaScript Framework for Web featuring Middlewares and MVC.
The post Smart.Framework – PHP and JavaScript web framework appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[19 Best Free and Open Source Linux Astronomy Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=4452</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/astronomy/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T15:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article focuses on selecting the best free astronomy software available for Linux.
The post 19 Best Free and Open Source Linux Astronomy Apps appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TiMidity++ – MIDI to WAVE converter and player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142143</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/timidity-midi-wave-converter-player/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T13:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TiMidity++ is a software synthesizer. It can play MIDI files by converting them into PCM waveform data.
The post TiMidity++ – MIDI to WAVE converter and player appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Best Free and Open Source CLI Tools to Find and Delete Duplicate Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139565</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-cli-tools-find-delete-duplicate-files/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T13:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This roundup focuses on free and open source command-line tools that help you find and remove duplicate files.
The post 15 Best Free and Open Source CLI Tools to Find and Delete Duplicate Files appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kinship Cafe is leaving Kansas City, Kansas. But the coffee shop isn't closing for good]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-02-09/kinship-cafe-strawberry-hill-independence-overland-park</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-02-09/kinship-cafe-strawberry-hill-independence-overland-park"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TJ Roberts first opened Kinship Cafe in 2021 in Strawberry Hill. After a lease deal fell through with his property owner, Roberts is leaving his original location behind for new shops in Independence and Overland Park.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Wilmore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glow – render Markdown on the command-line]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142081</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/glow-render-markdown-command-line/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T08:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glow is a terminal based markdown reader designed from the ground up to bring out the beauty—and power—of the CLI.
The post Glow – render Markdown on the command-line appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tyler Beede Holds Showcase For Interested Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840977</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/tyler-beede-holds-showcase-for-interested-teams.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T03:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right-hander Tyler Beede threw for teams held a pro day for interested teams on Friday, per a report from Ari Alexander of KPRC2. Alexander adds that Beede’s fastball was in the range of 93-95mph and that the Astros and Royals both were represented at the righty’s showcase. Beede, 32 in May, was selected in the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terrapin Vulnerability Scanner for the Terrapin attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142076</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/terrapin-vulnerability-scanner-terrapin-attack/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T23:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terrapin Vulnerability Scanner  can be used to determine the vulnerability of an SSH client or server against the Terrapin Attack.
The post Terrapin Vulnerability Scanner for the Terrapin attack appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[J.J. Picollo Discusses Royals Offseason Pursuits, Outfield Mix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840961</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/j-j-picollo-discusses-royals-offseason-pursuits-outfield-mix.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T21:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A year ago, the Royals had just put the finishing touching on an extension with budding superstar Bobby Witt Jr. that served as a capstone on the busiest and most aggressive offseason the club had put together in years. That strong offseason effort led to an 86-win season and a trip to the NLDS, where…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pop PHP Framework – toolkit for rapid application development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142062</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pop-php-framework-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T21:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pop PHP Framework contains a group of core components and an additional 30+ components that serve as a toolkit.
The post Pop PHP Framework – toolkit for rapid application development appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bochs – IA-32 (x86) PC emulator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142094</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/bochs-ia-32-x86-pc-emulator/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T20:39:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bochs is a highly portable IA-32 (x86) PC emulato, that runs on most popular platforms. 
The post Bochs – IA-32 (x86) PC emulator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Melt – backup and restore SSH private keys using memorable seed phrases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142085</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/melt-backup-restore-ssh-private-keys/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T19:38:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Melt is a utility that lets you backup and restore SSH private keys using memorable seed phrases.
The post Melt – backup and restore SSH private keys using memorable seed phrases appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cassowary – run Windows virtual machine on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142098</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/cassowary-windows-virtual-machine-linux/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T16:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cassowary lets you run a Windows virtual machine and use Windows applications on Linux as if they were native applications.
The post Cassowary – run Windows virtual machine on Linux appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Best Free and Open Source Media Players]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=70925</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-media-players/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T16:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A media player is software that lets you watch video and listen to music on your computer. We cover the best free and open source options.
The post 16 Best Free and Open Source Media Players appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VX Linux – systemd-free Plasma desktop distro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142105</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/vx-linux-systemd-free-plasma-desktop-distro/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T11:04:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VX Linux is a pre-configured, secure systemd-free Plasma desktop with focus on convenience, performance and simplicity.
The post VX Linux – systemd-free Plasma desktop distro appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[qr-backup – paper backup of files using QR codes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142078</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/qr-backup-paper-backup-qr-codes/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T07:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[qr-backup takes file(s), and outputs a "paper backup": a printable black-and-white PDF full of QR codes.
The post qr-backup – paper backup of files using QR codes appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effectively Wild Episode 2281: Season Preview Series: Orioles and Royals]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=456586</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/effectively-wild-episode-2281-season-preview-series-orioles-and-royals/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T05:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Lindbergh and Meg Rowley banter about the Dodgers’ overstuffed 2025 bobblehead lineup, Ippei Mizuhara’s sentencing, and the Angels’ tireless pursuit of players who were good several seasons ago. Then they preview the 2025 Baltimore Orioles (35:55) with the Baltimore Banner’s Danielle Allentuck, and the 2025 Kansas City Royals (1:08:21) with the Kansas City Star’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Lindbergh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[flxvwr – simple, cross-platform image viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141993</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/flxvwr-simple-cross-platform-image-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T23:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[flxvwr is a simple, cross-platform image viewer which provides a minimal user interface, keyboard shortcuts, and smooth performance.
The post flxvwr – simple, cross-platform image viewer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poll: Who’s Winning The Offseason In The AL Central?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840772</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/poll-whos-winning-the-offseason-in-the-al-central.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T23:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The calendar has flipped to February and the start of spring is just a matter of days away. While some notable free agents (including seven of MLBTR’s Top 50) remain unsigned, most clubs have already done the heavy lifting in terms of preparing their roster for the 2025 season. In the coming days, we’ll be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[highlight.js – syntax highlighter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141989</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/highlight-js-syntax-highlighter/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T21:26:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[highlight.js is a syntax highlighter written in JavaScript. It works in the browser as well as on the server
The post highlight.js – syntax highlighter appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tennessee Tried Something New And Beat An Old Rival]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180778</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tennessee-tried-something-new-and-beat-an-old-rival"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T20:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a classic rivalry said to have lost its juice, Thursday night’s UConn-Tennessee game sure felt plenty juiceful. In front of a season-record crowd at home, the No. 19 Lady Vols took down the No. 5 Huskies, 80-76, to end an 18-year rivalry drought.
To be fair, that timespan does include a 13-year gap in the series, which the late Pat Summitt called off in 2007 at the height of her feud with UConn head coach Geno Auriemma. He looks back on that heyday with little fondness. “It just became stupid and became something I didn't want to be a part of anymore,” Auriemma told reporters before Thursday’s game. “I think our fans are stupid. I think their fans are stupid, and how they reacted to the whole thing, it just became something other than a basketball game, and after a while that just got old.” (If he’s referring to the rivalry’s hostility, it should be noted that he had some hand in it, too.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickemu – run Linux, macOS, and Windows virtual machines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142055</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/quickemu-run-linux-macos-windows-virtual-machines/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T19:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quickemu is a wrapper for QEMU that automatically "does the right thing" when creating virtual machines.
The post Quickemu – run Linux, macOS, and Windows virtual machines appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QR Scanner – QR scanner/generator app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142016</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/qr-scanner-code-generator/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T19:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[QR Scanner is a QR code scanner and generator built with Flutter.
The post QR Scanner – QR scanner/generator app appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: It Is Now Time To Chat With The Defector Staff]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180806</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/alert-it-is-now-time-to-chat-with-the-defector-staff"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T18:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Friday! The Super Bowl is almost here! Let's chat!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Time Does “What Time Does The Super Bowl Start?” Start?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180482</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-time-does-what-time-does-the-super-bowl-start-start-3"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T18:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have now done this gag across four websites for 10 years, a time period in which the sweaty behavior I sought to skewer has morphed from a cynical attempt to ride, remora-like, on the prodigious belly of Google search traffic into an almost quaint, bygone phenomenon. It's not so much that publications across digital and traditional media are any less determined to degrade themselves in search of traffic, as it is that "digital media" and "traffic" are themselves largely bygone relics. I am almost nostalgic!
But only almost! That belly remains surfable, and plenty of news outlets are still determined to surf it. Perhaps as media literacy declines and as social media's utility as a news scraper craters, the public's thirst for knowledge—at least about one specific thing: what time the Super Bowl starts—can only be quenched by conducting a Google search. The funniest thing here is that the first result for any such search is a Google-generated box with the start time and the team logos, negating the primary utility of these sorts of posts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foto – simple image viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142052</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/foto-simple-image-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T18:31:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foto is a simple image viewer. It simply shows an image either on a window or in the terminal. It is designed to be used in scripts.
The post Foto – simple image viewer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Best Free and Open Source Console Email Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=58883</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-console-email-clients/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T18:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are our recommended console email clients. All free and open source goodness.
The post 15 Best Free and Open Source Console Email Clients appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Warcraft III: Reforged’ Was A Greedy Debacle]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179030</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/warcraft-iii-reforged-was-a-greedy-debacle"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T18:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to The Backlog, a new series in which we will take a look back at 12 games from 2020 that, in one way or another, had a lasting impact on the video game industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dillon Brooks Will Continue Poking Bears Until He’s Left With Bloody Stumps]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180773</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dillon-brooks-will-continue-poking-bears-until-hes-left-with-but-bloody-stumps"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T17:33:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You think you want an active trade deadline. You want everyone down in the shit, firing players and draft picks back and forth at subatomic speeds. That's what you tell yourself! And then one February everyone goes crazy in the Deal Zone and there are one billion trades in one week, so many coming so rapidly that the league's preeminent scoopster isn't even waiting to learn both halves of trades before posting them and moving to the next one. Before you have time to fully wrap your head around one perplexing deal, 14 more have followed in its wake. All I wanted was a little action to pull me out of seasonal malaise, you sob, desperate to force the genie back into the bottle. Just like that, and too late, you remember that what you want from a basketball season, more than anything, is some by-God basketball. 
They played some by-God basketball in Minneapolis Thursday night. The two participating teams were among the least active at the deadline. The Timberwolves, sitting sixth in the Western Conference standings with one of the most expensive active rosters in the NBA, were severely restricted by the current CBA and made zero moves. The visiting Houston Rockets kept their roster intact but acquired 32-year-old Cody Zeller to fill the very last seat on their bench, and otherwise picked up a few future second-round draft picks. The teams are good enough and young enough to justify standing pat, and to feel reasonably confident headed into the closing stretch of the regular season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File Lock PEA – filesystem-level encryption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141861</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/file-lock-pea-filesystem-level-encryption/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File Lock PEA (PEA = Password Encrypting Archive) encrypts data at the filesystem level 
The post File Lock PEA – filesystem-level encryption appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Thomas Hatch To Minor League Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840784</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/royals-sign-thomas-hatch-minor-league-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T16:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced Friday that they’ve signed righty Thomas Hatch to a minor league deal. The Moye Sports client will be in major league camp as a non-roster invitee this spring. Hatch, 30, originally agreed to a one-year deal with the Korea Baseball Organization’s Doosan Bears back in November, but that deal fell through after…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce Is Using A Hallucination To Sell AI]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180677</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/salesforce-is-using-a-hallucination-to-sell-ai"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T16:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot is happening in the world of artificial intelligence, and not a lot of it makes sense. We're told that AI is the future of business, yet it is wildly unprofitable; investment in AI companies is ramping up even as AI-adjacent tech stocks tumble; the American Plagiarism Machine is accusing the Chinese Plagiarism Machine of plagiarism. But nothing—nothing—is as head-spinning, as bizarre, or as infuriating as this, the bafflingly ubiquitous ad where renowned actors Matthew McConaughey and Woody Harrelson hawk Salesforce's newest AI enterprise software product:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s4JNLL7U8H8]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Kluegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In 1988, Buddy Ryan Was Watchin’ The Eagles Rap]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180657</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/in-1988-buddy-ryan-was-watchin-the-eagles-rap"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T16:18:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was October of 1988, and the Philadelphia Eagles were headed to their first NFC East title since the 1980 season. It didn’t seem like it at the time, though. Philadelphia finished the month 4-5, and New York, Washington, and Phoenix were all ahead of them in the standings.
That did not stop the crew at West Coast Video. With the team in fourth place in the division, the Philadelphia-based video rental chain pitched Eagles players on an idea—a rap song performed by the team, similar to the Chicago Bears' “Super Bowl Shuffle” three years earlier. Those Bears won the Super Bowl, and the song was nominated for an R&B Grammy, so it inspired a lot of imitators. Most were similar group raps by the team, but things did get weird around the margins. Bears coach Mike Ditka himself put out two different songs on VHS. The Cleveland Browns made a sci-fi short, D.T. in Dawg Territory, among other mini-movies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: A very snowy look next week (FRI-2/7)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3818013</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-a-very-snowy-look-next-week-fri-2-7/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T15:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple rounds of snow and bitterly cold temperatures are expected next week beginning as early as Monday night, going through Thursday]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: A very snowy look next week (FRI-2/7)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3818013</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-a-very-snowy-look-next-week-fri-2-7/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T15:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I continue to remain bullish on accumulating snow prospects for next week...starting as early as Monday evening but more than likely by early Tuesday. This would be considered round one...then another system for Wednesday into early Thursday morning. With cold air being tapped, lift and moisture being present, and a powdery snow scenario shaping up, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doechii’s Old Vlogs Document Her Self-Invention]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180701</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/doechiis-old-vlogs-document-her-self-invention"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T15:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doechii’s YouTube channel has 1.85 million subscribers. Her most recent video, a new single called "Nosebleeds," was posted shortly after she became the third woman ever to win the Grammy for Best Rap Album on Sunday.
I keep replaying moments from her Grammy performance of "Catfish" and "Denial is a River" – the shapes she made with her body while standing on the platform above her throng of dancers, the moment her dancers split her Thom Browne suit to reveal a stark white underwear set, and her Fosse turn in the bright lights. Doechii's performances are crisp and deliberate; at 26 years old, her creative vision seems fully realized already, executed with a precision as tight as her signature face tape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City’s Outfield Is a Missed Opportunity]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=456406</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/kansas-citys-outfield-is-a-missed-opportunity/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T15:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals got nothing from their outfield corners in 2024, and they appear to be content with getting nothing from them again in 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Szymborski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Masai Ujiri Continues His Baffling Wing Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180756</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/masai-ujiri-continues-his-baffling-wing-collection"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T15:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To understand the mind of Masai Ujiri, the brilliant team president of the Toronto Raptors who chisels away at his reputation with each passing season, it helps to hear his story about five incredible long guys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[octoscan – static vulnerability scanner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141898</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/octoscan-static-vulnerability-scanner/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T14:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Octoscan is a static vulnerability scanner for GitHub action workflows.
The post octoscan – static vulnerability scanner appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chimpanzee Culture Is Disappearing Because Of Us]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180713</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/chimpanzee-culture-is-disappearing-because-of-us"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T14:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For millennia, the western chimpanzees of Taï National Park in Ivory Coast have communicated with each other in a dialect of their own. They do not speak in words, but rather through gestures. In one gesture called leaf clip, a chimpanzee will take a leaf off a branch and rip it apart in their mouth, creating a ripping sound that might invite play. In another gesture called knuckle knock, males knock repeatedly on the trunk of a small tree; knuckle knock is an invitation meant to attract female chimpanzees, who may respond to the knocking gesture with a sexual display.
Scientists have observed the four populations of chimps in the Taï forest—the North, Northeast, East, and South groups—since the 1970s, learning about each of their particular customs. Knuckle knock was a staple in the North group for generations; before 2004, every male in the group used knuckle knock to woo females. But in the ensuing eight years, the population never had more than one adult male. This eliminated the need for a male to distinguish himself among competitors, and also prevented any younger male chimps from seeing the gesture in use and learning it for the future. In 2008, the last adult male chimp in the North group, and perhaps the last of his population to use knuckle knock, was killed by a poacher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sight Below]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/the-sight-below</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/the-sight-below"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T08:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Friday so we’re listening to something slightly more upbeat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snal Linux – Arch based live distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141977</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/snal-linux-arch-based-live-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T07:33:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Snal Linux is an Arch-based distro intended to be used as a live image from portable media .It uses the i3 window manager and Firefox.
The post Snal Linux – Arch based live distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suspension Bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3048/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3048/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>