<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-10-27T20:17:04.239Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Lakers Already Feel Different]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171430</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/these-lakers-already-feel-different"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T17:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Lakers are off to a 3-0 start, with wins against three teams that finished ahead of them in the West last season. Each victory has allowed them an opportunity to flash different strengths.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hornets Are Under Construction, But LaMelo Ball Is Still Really Fun To Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171409</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-hornets-are-under-construction-but-lamelo-ball-is-still-really-fun-to-watch"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T15:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though he hasn't shown it much in the past couple seasons, a healthy LaMelo Ball is capable of producing some breathtaking moments and gaudy stat lines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL Week 8 Uniform Schedule: Buccaneers, 49ers Wearing Throwback Uniforms, Bengals Donning White Alternate Helmets]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83062</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/27/nfl-week-8-uniform-schedule-buccaneers-49ers-wearing-throwback-uniforms-bengals-donning-white-alternate-helmets/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T15:31:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our weekly series that looks at every uniform matchup across the NFL continues with the Tampa Bay Buccaneers and San Francisco 49ers wearing their throwback uniforms and the Cincinnati Bengals donning their white alternate helmets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ah Shit, Shohei Ohtani Messed Up His Shoulder]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171413</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ah-shit-shohei-ohtani-messed-up-his-shoulder"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T14:29:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Los Angeles Dodgers hold a 2-0 lead in the World Series after Saturday night's 4-2 win over the New York Yankees, but the biggest concern right now is the state of Shohei Ohtani's labrum. The Dodgers superstar exited the game in the seventh inning after a stolen-base attempt partially dislocated his shoulder.
With two outs in the bottom of the seventh, Ohtani took off for second base and caught his arm awkwardly in the slide. After he was tagged out to end the inning, he stayed on the ground in pain while Dodgers staff attended to him. He then left the field holding his arm and didn't return. After Los Angeles escaped a dicey ninth inning to seal the win, manager Dave Roberts shared an update: Ohtani had suffered a left shoulder subluxation, and he would undergo further tests including an MRI on Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKC Baseball Club rebrands as Comets in honor of Mickey Mantle]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83036</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/26/okc-baseball-club-rebrands-as-comets-in-honor-of-mickey-mantle/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T00:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Los Angeles Dodgers and New York Yankees took to the field in game 2 of the World Series, the Dodgers Triple-A affiliate in Oklahoma City announced a new identity that pays homage to a Yankee icon. The Oklahoma City Comets name and identity, just unveiled moments ago, are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Caputo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Bird Passes Away]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=828264</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/doug-bird-passes-away.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-26T23:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[11-year MLB veteran Doug Bird passed away late last month, according to an obituary from a North Carolina funeral home. The former Royals, Phillies, Yankees, Cubs, and Red Sox right-hander was 74 years old. A California native in his early years, Bird was drafted by the Royals in the summer of 1969. He spent the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrat candidate for Missouri AG says teen pregnancy argument in abortion pill lawsuit is ‘insane’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858207</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/democrat-says-missouri-ags-teen-pregnancy-argument-in-abortion-pill-lawsuit-is-insane/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-26T20:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic candidate for Missouri Attorney General Elad Gross after filing to run for office in February (Annelise Hanshaw/Missouri Independent) Missouri Attorney General Andrew Bailey’s contention that a decrease in teen pregnancy could hurt the state financially and politically is “an absolutely insane argument,” his Democratic rival on the Nov. 5 ballot said Thursday. “Apparently he believes we need more teen...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Hancock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AL Central Notes: Warren, White Sox, Manfred, Caglianone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=828254</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/al-central-notes-warren-white-sox-manfred-caglianone.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-26T19:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tigers had interest in right-hander Will Warren during their trade talks with the Yankees this past summer, the New York Post’s Jon Heyman reports.  The two clubs reportedly had a provisional agreement involving Jack Flaherty relatively close to being completed before New York backed out due to concerns over Flaherty’s medical records, though it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That’s How You Start A World Series]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171396</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/thats-how-you-start-a-world-series"/>
        <updated>2024-10-26T14:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you think about sports as a television show rather than some fit people running around and doing things, Game 1 of the World Series was a terrible idea. Yes, the series is well cast, and the production value is solid by contemporary standards, but you just cannot give away your best stuff in the pilot episode.
Fortunately, by the rules of our diminishing yet still shared reality, Game 1 was an extraordinary epic. Freddie Freeman pointing his bat toward the sky after hitting the first walk-off grand slam in World Series history—straight up, rather than in the direction of the game-winner he’d just vaporized—told everyone watching that whatever else happens in these next several days, a baseball event is coming from on high. On this night, and maybe for the next week, football could eat what we in the agricultural sciences call shit. Baseball is, for the moment, back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facts Don’t Care About Your Feelings — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076667</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/facts-dont-care-about-your-feelings-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T23:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being Honest Is A Huge Hurdle In A Defamation Case: Waste of time and money.
Come On Guys, He Just Likes Hitler!: Jonathan Turley is doing damage control for Trump.
Lyle And Erik Could Be Up For Parole: LA DA wants to resentence the Menendez brothers.
UChicago Makes It Harder For Students To Learn: There's no need for a policy this strict.
Now That's A Fancy Ticket!: Alito gifted festival tickets by a literal princess.
The post Facts Don’t Care About Your Feelings — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partners In This Practice Area Are Doing Exceptionally Well]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076663</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/partners-in-this-practice-area-are-doing-exceptionally-well/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T23:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They're having a helluva run.
The post Partners In This Practice Area Are Doing Exceptionally Well appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alito Discloses Gift From Far-Right European Princess]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076662</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/alito-discloses-gift-from-far-right-european-princess/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T22:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wonder if Justice Kagan ever wishes she just took the damned bagels. 
The post Alito Discloses Gift From Far-Right European Princess appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Something Else Goldman-For-The-People Didn’t Do Very Well]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076622</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/10/heres-something-else-goldman-for-the-people-didnt-do-very-well"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T21:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the Insult to Injury Department.
The post Here’s Something Else Goldman-For-The-People Didn’t Do Very Well appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conquering Conferences: Embracing New Conversations]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076642</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/conquering-conferences-embracing-new-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T20:46:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How you can bring vibrant energy to each new interaction.
The post Conquering Conferences: Embracing New Conversations appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEJAL PATEL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Says He’s Eager To Tell Jack Smith His Personal Catchphrase: ‘You’re Fired!’]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076651</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/donald-trump-says-hes-eager-to-tell-jack-smith-his-personal-catchphrase-youre-fired/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T20:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If reelected, Trump wants Jack Smith OUT as special prosecutor, ASAP.
The post Donald Trump Says He’s Eager To Tell Jack Smith His Personal Catchphrase: ‘You’re Fired!’ appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WHL’s Lethbridge Hurricanes Mark 50th Anniversary of Arena, Junior Hockey in City With Special Jerseys]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83027</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/25/whls-lethbridge-hurricanes-mark-50th-anniversary-of-arena-junior-hockey-in-city-with-special-jerseys/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T19:26:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hurricanes to wear special jerseys against Red Deer Rebels on Saturday to mark 50th anniversary of Sportsplex as well as 50th anniversary of junior hockey in Lethbridge]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Turley Wants Everyone To Chill Out And Just Trust The Guy Who Speaks Fondly Of Hitler]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076648</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/jonathan-turley-wants-everyone-to-chill-out-and-just-trust-the-guy-who-speaks-fondly-of-hitler/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T19:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Turley says the darnedest things.
The post Jonathan Turley Wants Everyone To Chill Out And Just Trust The Guy Who Speaks Fondly Of Hitler appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stat(s) Of The Week: Avatars And Mood Monitors]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076617</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/stats-of-the-week-avatars-and-mood-monitors/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T18:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts predict ways in which AI will alter workplaces in the future.
The post Stat(s) Of The Week: Avatars And Mood Monitors appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vera Djordjevich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri to launch new driver licensing system early next month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858147</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missouri-to-launch-new-driver-licensing-system-early-next-month/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T18:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wayne Wallingford, the director of the Missouri Department of Revenue, speaks to reporters in December 2021 (photo courtesy of Missouri Governor’s Office) Of the many annoyances in life, a trip to the local motor vehicle office can rank near the top. In early November, the Missouri Department of Revenue will activate new equipment intended to reduce the aggravation, speed up...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rudi Keller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Jim’s to Jennings: KC bartender competes on Jeopardy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858052</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/from-jims-to-jennings-kc-bartender-competes-on-jeopardy-next-week/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T18:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeopardy Host Ken Jennings with Sammy Sanchez // Courtesy Sammy Sanchez Sammy Sanchez knows his stuff. After almost a decade of attempts, Sanchez was finally called up to the big leagues. That’s right, Sanchez is a contestant on an upcoming episode of Jeopardy. The bespectacled face on your screen may be a familiar one. Sanchez is a bartender at Jim’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filling Time When Slow With Work As A Lawyer At A Small Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076421</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/filling-time-when-slow-with-work-as-a-lawyer-at-a-small-firm/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T17:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A slowdown can be put to far better use than playing Freecell or just staring into space waiting for the phone to ring.
The post Filling Time When Slow With Work As A Lawyer At A Small Firm appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Rothman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composer Jherek Bischoff on achieving fractured emotional weight when scoring new drama Exhibiting Forgiveness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858080</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/composer-jherek-bischoff-on-achieving-fractured-emotional-weight-when-scoring-new-drama-exhibiting-forgiveness/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T17:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jherek Bischoff. // photo courtesy of the artist Director Titus Kaphar’s debut feature film, Exhibiting Forgiveness, is currently receiving rave reviews. In it, “Tarrell (André Holland) is an admired American painter who lives with his wife, singer Aisha (Andra Day), and their young son, Jermaine. Tarrell’s artwork excavates beauty from the anguish of his youth, keeping past wounds at bay. His...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Los Angeles DA Asks That Menendez Brothers Be Resentenced — Which Could Free Them Immediately]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076623</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/los-angeles-da-asks-that-menendez-brothers-be-resentenced-which-could-free-them-immediately/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T16:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Menendez brothers have been behind bars for decades -- and the DA believes they've 'paid their debt to society.'
The post Los Angeles DA Asks That Menendez Brothers Be Resentenced — Which Could Free Them Immediately appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unrivaled Women’s 3-on-3 Basketball League Launches Identities for Inaugural Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83018</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/25/unrivaled-womens-3-on-3-basketball-logo-launches-identities-for-6-inaugural-teams/basketball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T16:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Team identities currently have no geographic ties to accommodate possible future sales and relocations; use of Basketball Club in names aims to build sense of community and fan loyalty similar to European soccer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In A Game Of Risk, The Frustration Is The Point]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170439</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/in-a-game-of-risk-the-frustration-is-the-point"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T16:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it is time for the Defector staff to go into seclusion for our annual company meetings and fall frolic. This year we are gathering in Atlantic City, America's abandoned playground. We decided to hold a mini theme week to keep the site robust and full of blogs while we're in meetings. This year's theme: Risk!
I consider myself a risk-averse person in almost every fashion. It's not something I'm particularly proud of, but I will overthink every move I make, whether professional or personal, and either pass on anything that might go badly or wait until every other option has been eliminated. (One notable exception led to the website you're reading right now, but that's been talked about a lot at this point.) So when Justin asked me if I wanted to write something for Risk Week, I froze. We batted around a few ideas—if you wanted to read me writing about the 2009 Patriots-Colts 4th-and-2 game, sorry—but every idea I had was either boring or stretching the theme of "risk" to beyond its limit. Then I remembered, well, Risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Communion With MJ Lenderman]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171360</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/in-communion-with-mj-lenderman"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T16:12:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s something cathartic about a room full of strangers singing the words, “You don’t know the shape I’m in.” It’s not that the crowd wasn’t singing along to most every other song MJ Lenderman played at Montreal’s Fairmount Theatre, but it’s those lyrics – “What else can you say to help/A friend with a broken heart/You don’t know the shape I’m in” – sung not long after a hurricane devastated Lenderman’s home state of North Carolina, that seemed to encompass the questionable shape we are all in. 
Lenderman, 25, is currently on tour with his five-piece backup band (MJ Lenderman And The Wind) to promote his fifth album, Manning Fireworks. I had meant to see this show in Toronto, but it sold out almost immediately. I guess fewer people know Lenderman in Montreal, even though there’s something about him that fits in better there. I saw him on the street a couple of hours before his set, while getting dinner with a friend – a tall guy with a small entourage, he is hard to miss, but he looked like any university student in the city, with his T-shirt and shaggy curls. “That’s him,” I told my friend, who wasn’t familiar with him or his music. I felt silly immediately—Lenderman is so unassuming in person that just pointing him out somehow felt intrusive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elite Law School Called Out By Students Over Draconian Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076643</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/elite-law-school-called-out-by-students-over-draconian-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T16:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This doesn't seem like an outrageous demand.
The post Elite Law School Called Out By Students Over Draconian Policy appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acclaimed hip-hop/indie rock trio Blackstarkids say goodbye with today’s release of HEAVEN ON URF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857717</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/exploring-blackstarkids-visual-legacy-as-they-say-goodbye-with-heaven-on-urf/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T16:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackstarkids live. // Photo by Daniel Ruiz It boggles the mind to realize that Kansas City trio Blackstarkids has only been together for a little over five years. Thanks to an impressive discography—which began with self-releasing Let’s Play Sports and SURF on their own Bedroom Records, continued with a pair of mixtapes and two LPs on Dirty Hit, and ends...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Appealing Weekly Roundup]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076641</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/how-appealing-weekly-roundup-92/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T15:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The week in appellate news.
The post How Appealing Weekly Roundup appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Public Stadiums Keep Some Profits Private]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170967</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-public-stadiums-keep-some-profits-private"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T14:37:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April, the Chicago Bears unveiled a nearly $5 billion proposal for a new stadium. According to the headline of the press release, this new property would be publicly owned. It was a polite way of describing an arrangement in which taxpayers would put more than $2 billion into the construction costs—two decades after they footed more than $400 million in the renovation bill for Soldier Field—and in return would get a vague $8 billion in "regional economic impact."
"An enclosed stadium is essential for Chicago to attract year-round events like the Super Bowl and major concerts—unlocking billions in tourism revenue," the release read. But is it?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Gardner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If You Don’t Play, You Can’t Win]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170251</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/if-you-dont-play-you-cant-win"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T14:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within the storied canon of lesbian period romances between the two different types of women—blonde and brunette, both white—Desert Hearts is my favorite of the genre. The premise is as sleek as its approximately 90-minute runtime. Vivian (Helen Shaver), a buttoned-up English professor at Columbia, moves to Reno, Nevada, also known as the divorce capital of the world, to stay the six weeks required to get a quick, no-fault divorce. Enter Cay (Patricia Charbonneau), a younger, free-spirited (read: lesbian) woman, who pursues Vivian about as openly as a queer woman could in 1959. Tumbleweeds roll, nipples touch, and soon Vivian's world unravels.
Vivian first encounters Cay on the road to Reno, in the passenger seat of a car driven by a woman named Frances, who owns the all-inclusive divorce ranch where Vivian intends to spend the next six weeks reading and writing presumably stodgy literature. After Frances and Vivian's sensible car passes Cay, who is driving a glimmering convertible in the opposite direction, Cay reverses the convertible to say "hi" and start laying it on thick: "Can I call you professor?" she teases, dark hair whipping in the wind. When an oncoming car emerges behind her, Cay waits until the absolute last second to shift her car into drive and avoid a crash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Court Tells Lawyer Something He Already Should Know: Facts Aren’t Defamation]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076640</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/federal-court-tells-lawyer-something-he-already-should-know-facts-arent-defamation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T14:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the real-estate-firm-GC-acting-like-it's-his-1st-day-on-the-job dept
The post Federal Court Tells Lawyer Something He Already Should Know: Facts Aren’t Defamation appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Techdirt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Rap World’ Remembers The Truth About Suburban Malaise]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171357</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rap-world-remembers-the-truth-about-suburban-malaise"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T13:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Samsung Intensity was released in September 2009, when I was 13. I try to avoid dating myself too specifically when writing, but it feels important here to delineate the contours of a memory via time and place. The Intensity was a slide phone, with a full QWERTY keyboard on the inside panel. You could take pictures, but not videos. You could send texts and emails, the latter a function I never used because I could never figure it out and I didn’t have anyone to email anyway. My Intensity came in the most popular color, flamingo red, and I often feel that this particular phone in this particular color not only signifies the design and fashion of the era but also the anxieties of suburban kids, like me, who did not know what technology meant to them. 
By 2009, three generations of the iPhone had already cemented a new kind of envy amongst the most status-obsessed people—namely, teenagers. Touchscreens on mobile devices represented if not wealth then access. I remember feeling that to be faced with the prospect of using a glorified flip phone released the same year as the iPhone 3GS, which reoriented the word “sleek” in the global lexicon, was a kind of cosmic slap in the face. The common reassurance that Apple’s cutting-edge technology would soon be democratized, that everyone would eventually be able to afford something like an iPhone, was hollow comfort. The point, for me, wasn’t about some hazy day in the future when I too could have it. I wanted to be one of the first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.25.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076635</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-25-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T13:03:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* "Would you like e. Coli with that?" McDonald's lawsuits begin. [Law360]
* Trump says that if elected he'd fire Jack Smith in least surprising news dump. [ABA Journal]
* Despite progress, convincing lawyers to buy in to technology remains a challenge. Never mind, that might actually be the least surprising news dump. [Law.com International]
* Court blocks acquisition that would've further consolidated the handbag market. [Reuters]
* Judgment insurance market suffers another loss... which will happen when insurance companies just start gambling. [Bloomberg Law News]
* "Constitutional sheriffs" -- local officials who claim their office grants them the power to unilaterally override all the rest of the federalist system described in the Constitution have spent the last four years building ties with the election denial movement. [WIRED]
* Company charges big bucks for paralegal training and some students aren't impressed. [Roll on Friday]
The post Morning Docket: 10.25.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bird: The Life and Music of Charlie Parker author Chuck Haddix deep-dives the jazz album that put KC on the map]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855595</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/bird-the-life-and-music-of-charlie-parker-author-chuck-haddix-deep-dives-the-jazz-album-that-put-kc-on-the-map/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Parker in KC // Photo Courtesy of Library of Congress Jazz saxophonist Charlie “Bird” Parker has long been lauded here in Kansas City, but until last month’s release of Bird in Kansas City from Verve Records, listeners hadn’t had much of an opportunity to hear hometown performances from the legendary artist. The 13-track album collects rare recordings spanning the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Victor Wembanyama’s Hands Missed Opening Night]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171352</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/victor-wembanyamas-hands-missed-opening-night"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T12:59:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The official box score only credits Victor Wembanyama with four turnovers in San Antonio's 109-120 Thursday night loss to the hosting Dallas Mavericks. I suppose it's not a turnover when a rebound slips right through your fingers, or else I am confident that number would have zeroes after it. Wembanyama is one of the most gifted and extraordinary athletes alive; he can do just about everything; and against the Mavs his hands seemed to belong to someone else entirely. Possibly Pazuzu.
You can't revolutionize the sport every night. Up to 81 times in this regular season, Wembanyama will warp the game in amazing, breathtaking ways; he will do things nobody his size has ever done before, and which shame the agility and coordination of world-class athletes a foot shorter. Thursday night, it was as if he'd accidentally left one of his spatial dimensions—depth, assuredly—in the locker room. The Mavericks would miss a shot, and the rebound would be there and Wembanyama would be there to get it, and the ball would pass through (what should have been) his grip as though he was a green-screen artifact. A Spurs teammate would throw a lob in his direction, and he would leap and stretch out those incredible arms ... and interact with the ball in the manner of a slight breeze, scarcely even altering its trajectory.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Anyone Know How To Spell It? — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076620</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/does-anyone-know-how-to-spell-it-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T23:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State Supreme Court Typo Goes Viral: The Pelican State has a red squiggly under their seal.
Green Light For The Golden State!: California Bar gets the go ahead for new testing strategy.
Prepare Your Costumes!: It's ATL's 15th LEGALLY THEMED Costume Contest!
Furrball, Esq.: Check out this cat's legal background.
More Of A Bad Thing: Former head of state gets interesting appointing advice.
The post Does Anyone Know How To Spell It? — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re Big Fans Of Our Advertisers On ATL]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076592</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/were-big-fans-of-our-advertisers-on-atl/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T23:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We really enjoy working with you!
The post We’re Big Fans Of Our Advertisers On ATL appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Bar Exam Hits Obama-Era High]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076613</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/new-york-bar-exam-hits-obama-era-high/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T23:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been a long time coming.
The post New York Bar Exam Hits Obama-Era High appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pocket Watching Trump Judge Wants To Control Law School Donations]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076610</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/pocket-watching-trump-judge-wants-to-control-law-school-donations/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T22:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Love seeing "Originalism" used as a cudgel. 
The post Pocket Watching Trump Judge Wants To Control Law School Donations appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musical Theater Heritage’s Sweeney Todd leaves rough edges on a bloodless Sondheim staging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=854441</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/musical-theater-heritages-sweeney-todd-leaves-rough-edges-on-a-bloodless-sondheim-staging/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T21:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Tim Scott Stephen Sondheim’s Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street is not singular in its arc of rediscovery and reinvention in the auteur’s repertoire. First staged on Broadway in 1979, the grotesque and maudlin deep dive into nihilism finds regular resurgence with each new generation. Unlike much of Sondheim’s other works—especially noticeable locally in White Theater’s Into...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Psychedelic Furs and co-headliners The Jesus & Mary Chain revived ’80s darkness at Uptown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857822</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/the-psychedelic-furs-and-co-headliners-the-jesus-mary-chain-revived-80s-darkness-at-uptown/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T21:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Psychedelic Furs. // photo by Nick Spacek The Psychedelic Furs with the Jesus & Mary Chain and Frankie Rose Uptown Theater Wednesday, October 23 On paper, the Psychedelic Furs headlining their tour with the Jesus & Mary Chain makes sense. They have the bigger selection of hits and arguably the more popular name recognition, but in practice, they ended...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest Future Ready Lawyer Survey From Wolters Kluwer Finds Broad Adoption Of Gen AI By Legal Professionals]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076594</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/10/latest-future-ready-lawyer-survey-from-wolters-kluwer-finds-broad-adoption-of-gen-ai-by-legal-professionals.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T21:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Latest Future Ready Lawyer Survey From Wolters Kluwer Finds Broad Adoption Of Gen AI By Legal Professionals appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Korn proved they’ve still got the life at T-Mobile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857817</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-korn-proved-theyve-got-the-life-at-t-mobile/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T21:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Korn. // photo by Allison Scavo Korn with Gojira and Spiritbox T-Mobile Center Friday, October 18 Photos by Allison Scavo and Zyonn Scavo Korn Allison’s photos Zyonn’s photos Korn setlist Here to Stay Dead Bodies Everywhere Got the Life A.D.I.D.A.S. It’s On! Good God Start the Healing Blind Ball Tongue Clown Shoots and Ladders Twist Make Me Bad Y’All Want...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Scavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Firms May Not Be Ready To Offer The Mental Health Accommodations Young Lawyers Want]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076596</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/biglaw-firms-may-not-be-ready-to-offer-the-mental-health-accommodations-young-lawyers-want/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T20:44:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a very big problem for Biglaw. Law firms need to adapt -- and fast.
The post Biglaw Firms May Not Be Ready To Offer The Mental Health Accommodations Young Lawyers Want appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California Bar Gets Their Supreme Court’s Go Ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076608</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/california-bar-gets-their-supreme-courts-go-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T20:03:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just in time to stay on schedule!
The post California Bar Gets Their Supreme Court’s Go Ahead appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disgraced Former Trump Attorney Has Some Interesting Advice For The Ex-President]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076607</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/disgraced-former-trump-attorney-has-some-interesting-advice-for-the-ex-president/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T19:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making federal courts even more conservative isn't a popular idea.
The post Disgraced Former Trump Attorney Has Some Interesting Advice For The Ex-President appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything I Expect From Atlantic City, Based On The ‘Rugrats’ Vacation Episode]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170524</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/everything-i-expect-from-atlantic-city-based-on-the-rugrats-vacation-episode"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T19:14:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it is time for the Defector staff to go into seclusion for our annual company meetings and fall frolic. This year we are gathering in Atlantic City, America's abandoned playground. We decided to hold a mini theme week to keep the site robust and full of blogs while we're in meetings. This year's theme: Risk!
Unless you count Chuck E. Cheese birthday parties when you were a kid (and I kinda do), I haven't spent any time in casinos. So when I heard we were trading the peaceful Poconos for glitzy Atlantic City for this year's company meeting, I wasn't sure what to expect. I scoured my long term memory for a previous experience or cultural touch point to ground my expectations and then I remembered the 1997 Rugrats episode, "Vacation."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good news! KC-area movie theatres offer early-release screenings of Wicked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857783</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/good-news-kc-area-movie-theatres-offer-early-release-screenings-of-wicked/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T19:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wicked // Courtesy Universal Pictures Fans of Wicked who are eager to see the new film don’t need a magic spell to get early access. Kansas City area B&B Theatres and AMC Theatres are offering early access screenings on November 20. The film opens in theatres across the country on November 22, 2024, but Universal Pictures has released some early...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emirates NBA Cup Courts Unveiled For All 30 Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82906</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/24/emirates-nba-cup-courts-unveiled-for-all-30-teams/basketball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:36:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courts across the league include NBA Cup trophy at center court and in lanes along with gradient concentric circles and tonal graphics covering entire floor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NetDocuments Moves To Bring Generative AI To Content… Not The Other Way Around]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076591</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/netdocuments-moves-to-bring-generative-ai-to-content-not-the-other-way-around/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's soon going to be less about having AI than where your AI lives.
The post NetDocuments Moves To Bring Generative AI To Content… Not The Other Way Around appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keyboard Cat Becomes Courtroom Star During Zoom Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076605</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/keyboard-cat-becomes-courtroom-star-during-zoom-trial/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T17:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You never know when your furry 'legal assistant' will come in handy during trial.
The post Keyboard Cat Becomes Courtroom Star During Zoom Trial appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOP Harasses Nuns In Hunt For THE FRAUDS]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076599</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/gop-harasses-nuns-in-hunt-for-the-frauds/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who picks a fight with nuns? 
The post GOP Harasses Nuns In Hunt For THE FRAUDS appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Remember Our Cars]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171234</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lets-remember-our-cars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
My first car was a Jeep. Two-door Cherokee. Black. It had a working tape deck and an eager gas pedal, which was all I required. I drove that car to college and back a hundred times. I drove it to work. I drove it to my best friend’s house. I drove it to Boston. I drove it to New York City. I drove it to see girls. I drove it to parties, houses, stadiums, and ski resorts. I almost always drove alone, and preferred it that way. If I had a trip coming up and I knew it would be just me and my car, I was content. I’d load up on shitty food, plunge a cassette into the stereo, jack the volume up to the point of pain, and tear ass up and down I-95. I loved that car.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Viral Embarrassing State Supreme Court Mistake]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076598</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-viral-embarrassing-state-supreme-court-mistake/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The typo is making the rounds on social media.
The post The Viral Embarrassing State Supreme Court Mistake appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s No Rutgers Football In The Champagne Room]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171273</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/theres-no-rutgers-football-in-the-champagne-room"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is still a mostly dead mall I have to visit and another day of meetings and such, but I'm prepared to call the Defector offsite in Atlantic City a qualified success. This is mostly because my criteria for assessing this kind of thing are kind of a mess. Seeing some dolphins horsing around more or less cancels out a hotel-wide internet outage that postponed the recording of this episode; some of the most critically dire bar vibes I have ever encountered at 10 p.m. anywhere in the world are counteracted by seeing a security guard happily dancing to Kool & The Gang's "She's Fresh" on the casino floor the next morning. None of this is reasonable, really, but that is not the kind of thing a person (or flourishing media company) comes to a place like this for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: Your curated list of what and where to eat this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857802</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-your-curated-list-of-what-and-where-to-eat-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T16:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Life in KC is decisively delicious. In fact, there is often so much going on that it can be difficult to decide where to go and what to try. That’s where I come in. By day, I am the Food & Drink Editor of The Pitch, and by night, the good food and fun overflow into...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling Hidden Deal Insights: GenAI For Powerful Negotiation And Exceptional Client Service [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076369</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/unveiling-hidden-deal-insights-genai-for-powerful-negotiation-and-exceptional-client-service/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T15:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new GenAI-powered deal point extraction tool provides big advantages in the negotiation process and beyond. 
The post Unveiling Hidden Deal Insights: GenAI For Powerful Negotiation And Exceptional Client Service appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[National Museum of Toys and Miniatures unveils new exhibit featuring dozens of regional mixed-media masterminds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858033</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/national-museum-of-toys-and-miniatures-unveils-new-exhibit-featuring-dozens-of-regional-mixed-media-masterminds/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T15:18:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of sculptor Cesar Lopez’s submissions to the Local Artists Go Miniature exhibition. // Provided by Cesar Lopez. This Friday, local artists will display their latest small-scale projects for the newest exhibition at the National Museum of Toys and Miniatures .  The Local Artists Go Miniature exhibit will feature a variety of 2D and 3D artworks of any media from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Quick hitting storms (THU-10/24)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3706544</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-quick-hitting-storms-thu-10-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T14:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have noticed a subtle change to the weather this morning... clouds. Shocking, I know but important because those clouds are a sign of moisture in the atmosphere, something that has been lacking for weeks around these parts. That moisture will help fuel a couple of opportunities for storms. One during the day, which [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ATL’s 15th Annual Legally Themed Halloween Costume Contest]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076597</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/atls-15th-annual-legally-themed-halloween-costume-contest/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T14:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you got what it takes to top the winners of years past?
The post ATL’s 15th Annual Legally Themed Halloween Costume Contest appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia Got What It Wanted From The Six Kings Slam]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171311</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/saudi-arabia-got-what-it-wanted-from-the-six-kings-slam"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T14:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I couldn’t even go a week without Turki Alalshikh, the chairman of Saudi Arabia’s General Entertainment Authority, popping up on my laptop during a live sporting event. On Oct. 12, he was in the front row for the undisputed light heavyweight championship fight between Artur Beterbiev and Dmitry Bivol, a long-awaited bout he was instrumental in putting together. (He was the third-most important character of the night, getting name-checked by the ring announcer and both fighters and promptly calling for a rematch when he disagreed with the judges’ scorecards.) Not seven days later, there Alalshikh was on the glowing rectangle again, front and center at the Six Kings Slam—an exhibition he spearheaded that featured five of the best and most famous male tennis players on the planet, and also Hogler Rune. 
Alalshikh’s place within a murderous, deeply discriminatory regime has not dissuaded boxing from working in lockstep with him, catching the money he throws in order to stage high-demand fights that would not have happened without the unlimited wealth at his disposal. But there was nothing high-demand about the Six Kings Slam. It was an exhibition event whose headlining match-ups, like Carlos Alcaraz-Jannik Sinner, were ongoing rivalries that have grown without intervention from Alalshikh or anybody else. This event happened simply because it could, and because Saudi Arabia’s sportswashing efforts are now so ubiquitous, it felt immunized from any loud complaints.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Owen Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check Out This Mind-Blowing, Highly Secretive Trading Strategy (But Don’t Adopt It Unless You Want To Get Sued)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076582</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/10/check-out-this-mind-blowing-highly-secretive-trading-strategy-but-dont-adopt-it-unless-you-want-to-get-sued"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T14:05:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you heard of a country called ‘Venezuela’? Oh, you have…
The post Check Out This Mind-Blowing, Highly Secretive Trading Strategy (But Don’t Adopt It Unless You Want To Get Sued) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Would sports betting boost Missouri school funding? There’s no guarantee, experts say.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858070</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/would-sports-betting-boost-missouri-school-funding-theres-no-guarantee-experts-say/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T13:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Students attend class year-round at Ingels Elementary School in Kansas City, part of the Hickman Mills School District. Political scientists and experts on the state budget say Missouri classrooms aren’t guaranteed more funding if voters legalize sports betting. (Vaughn Wheat/The Beacon) Missourians are being bombarded with ads promoting Amendment 2, a constitutional amendment to legalize sports betting. The betting operators...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meg Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Matter What Happens In This Election, Nobody Is Allowed To Get Mad At Me]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171282</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/no-matter-what-happens-in-this-election-nobody-is-allowed-to-get-mad-at-me"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T13:41:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are less than two weeks out from the 2024 presidential election, and it's time to take stock of the race. 
As regular readers of Defector are certainly aware, I have spent the last few months using my proprietary prediction model, which was first created to project Tom Brady's weekly levels of crud, to forecast the outcome of the upcoming election. The model has told a clear story for the last few weeks: This election is a tossup. The current state of play poses a clear problem, however. If the election is a tossup, and the model can't offer any insight other than to forecast the race with a 50-50 chance to break in either direction, then how do I get people to pay attention to me?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nate Crudster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Do You Risk In Revisiting A Piece of Culture You Once Loved?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171283</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-do-you-risk-in-revisiting-a-piece-of-culture-you-once-loved"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T13:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it is time for the Defector staff to go into seclusion for our annual company meetings and fall frolic. This year we are gathering in Atlantic City, America's abandoned playground. We decided to hold a mini theme week to keep the site robust and full of blogs while we're in meetings. This year's theme: Risk!
I never would have seen the paintings that probably changed the trajectory of my life if it hadn’t been for a ridiculous, almost unbelievable, amount of luck. In the Fall of 2007, I went to a Dallas Stars hockey game. It was early in the season. My hair was still stained pink from a Manic Panic decision you can only make at 16, and when we walked in the arena an older woman made eye contact with me. They were handing out the kind of gimmicky give-away that is mainly an advertisement: novelty airplane tickets. I would probably have misplaced mine but the woman was so focused and insisted that I keep track of it, that this ticket would be important. And it was. At some point in the game, I won: my ticket flashed on the screen, and was magically transformed from a piece of shiny garbage into two free tickets to anywhere American Airlines flew in the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: All the snow data for KC! (THU-10/24)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3706201</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-all-the-snow-data-for-kc-thu-10-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T13:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'll get another blog out later this morning regarding the storm threats for this evening...but in the meantime... Today I'm presenting a power point about snow climatology for Kansas City to our Integrated Warning Team (IWT) seminar and it's all about one of my favorite topics...snow! The IWT is comprised of my colleagues from the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.24.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076585</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-24-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T13:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Former OpenAI employee says the company "broke copyright law." Except he's not a lawyer and what he's describing doesn't really sound like a copyright violation. But the NY Times is suing OpenAI so... here's a splashy profile about how OpenAI broke copyright law.  [NY Times]
* Disciplinary authorities recommend suspending Montana Attorney General's law license. Which would be significant if Montana's AG dutifully acted as the state's top lawyer as opposed to wasting taxpayer dollars filing frivolous lawsuits about how voter registration is unconstitutional. [Montana Free Press]
* Law firm leadership FOMO. [American Lawyer]
* Michael Avenatti may be out of prison sooner than expected. [Reuters]
* Elite firms cooling on California hiring. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Commission accuses judge of abusing contempt power to bully courtroom. Seems like a lot of that going around these days. [ABA Journal]
* Goldman and Apple to pay for CFPB violations. [Law360]
The post Morning Docket: 10.24.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Johnson County Republicans backtrack after years of attacking abortion rights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858053</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/johnson-county-republicans-backtrack-after-years-of-attacking-abortion-rights/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T11:44:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attendees of the Kansans for Constitutional Freedom watch party celebrate after primary election results verify Kansans voted to keep abortion a constitutional right. (Lily O’Shea Becker/Kansas Reflector) TOPEKA — Johnson County voters would never know by reading campaign websites that Republicans who are seeking reelection there were among the most zealous opponents of abortion rights. Legislators who championed the anti-abortion...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sherman Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Electric Poe spotlights R.H. Wilhoit’s sinister signature in latest cemetery staging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857740</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/electric-poe-spotlights-r-h-wilhoits-sinister-signature-in-latest-cemetery-staging/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T03:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Coterie Theatre The Coterie’s annual Halloween production of Electric Poe is back this year, and once again we’ve got a review that boils down to “Stop reading this and just go see it.” For newbies, Electric Poe is a one man show that runs under an hour, where an adaptation of a few of Edgar Allen Poe’s works are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye Logic Games, Hello Law Students! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076579</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/goodbye-logic-games-hello-law-students-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T23:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More People Are Taking The LSAT After Getting Rid Of The Logic Games Section: So long, and welcome!
Prepare For The Fall: States rush to amend their Constitutions before the Supreme Court overturns gay marriage.
Put Her Back On!: Litigant petitions Supreme Court to get Pauline Newman back.
The Funding Fell From A Biglaw Tree: Attorneys are just throwing money at Kamala's campaign.
Made In Italy: Will surrogacy be targeted in the US too?
The post Goodbye Logic Games, Hello Law Students! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Wachtell Slipping?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076572</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/is-wachtell-slipping/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T22:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Biglaw firm is no longer at the top of the M&A world.
The post Is Wachtell Slipping? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venom: The Last Dance forgets its signature moves and drunkenly stumbles through the grand finale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857744</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/venom-the-last-dance-forgets-its-signature-moves-and-drunkenly-stumbles-through-the-grand-finale/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T21:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Venom: The Last Dance. // Courtesy Columbia Pictures I want to start, dear reader, by letting you know that I’m coming from a place of love. I thought 2018’s Venom was a delightfully shaggy and bizarre affair, restaurant lobster tank bathtub and all. 2021’s Venom: Let There Be Carnage was kind of all over the place, but had its charms....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patent Owner Petitions Supreme Court For Pauline Newman To Hear His Case]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076566</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/patent-owner-petitions-supreme-court-for-pauline-newman-to-hear-his-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T21:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty big praise. 
The post Patent Owner Petitions Supreme Court For Pauline Newman To Hear His Case appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Merge Or Not To Merge, That Is The Question That’s Making Law Firm Leaders Anxious]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076549</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/to-merge-or-not-to-merge-that-is-the-question-thats-making-law-firm-leaders-anxious/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:42:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing partners don't want to get 'left out' of the rush on mergers.
The post To Merge Or Not To Merge, That Is The Question That’s Making Law Firm Leaders Anxious appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America’s 250th Birthday Celebration: Will Voters Choose Genuine Joyous Patriotism Or A Sad Missile Parade?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076504</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/americas-250th-birthday-celebration-will-voters-choose-genuine-joyous-patriotism-or-a-sad-missile-parade/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T20:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of directional velocity will come from the top based on whoever wins this presidential election.
The post America’s 250th Birthday Celebration: Will Voters Choose Genuine Joyous Patriotism Or A Sad Missile Parade? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Wolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AHL’s Providence Bruins Pay Tribute to First Responders With Special Edition Jerseys]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82896</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/23/ahls-providence-bruins-pay-tribute-to-first-responders-with-special-edition-jerseys/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T19:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Front of jersey features crest with colored stripes representing different branches of first responders and stars to pay respects to those who died in the line of duty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepping For The Supreme Court To Overturn <em>Obergefell</em>]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076560</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/prepping-for-the-supreme-court-to-overturn-obergefell/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T19:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conservatives are coming for same-sex marriage. These states want to be ready.
The post Prepping For The Supreme Court To Overturn <em>Obergefell</em> appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boise State Will Always Be The Greatest Underdogs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170735</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/boise-state-will-always-be-the-greatest-underdogs"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T18:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, it is time for the Defector staff to go into seclusion for our annual company meetings and fall frolic. This year we are gathering in Atlantic City, America's abandoned playground. We decided to hold a mini theme week to keep the site robust and full of blogs while we're in meetings. This year's theme: Risk!
The total number of "great games" that you witness as a sports fan can only increase. But in the growing mental pile of walk-offs, hail marys, buzzer beaters, and triple overtimes, I believe that there is a solid, unchanging foundation of formative instant-classics—games that literally shaped your concept of what sports drama should be. In the same way that, per Sam Sifton, a person's first source of pizza becomes the standard against which they judge all pizza for the rest of their lives, the first time you find yourself dazzled by a seemingly impossible outcome remains a permanent reference point. When I trouble myself for a list of "great games," the memories that immediately surface aren't fresh experiences but set impressions from a decade ago or longer. I think about David Freese's Game 6 in 2011, or Landon Donovan's goal against Algeria, or Trey Burke's shot against Kansas, or Boise State beating Oklahoma with a bag of tricks in the Fiesta Bowl.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In 2024, The GOP Is A Big Fan Of Teen Pregnancy]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076563</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/in-2024-the-gop-is-a-big-fan-of-teen-pregnancy/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T18:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus the skinny on Biglaw partner compensation and a Texas court's romantic scandal gets even more wild.
The post In 2024, The GOP Is A Big Fan Of Teen Pregnancy appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Give Up A Lot To Work For The Federal Judiciary]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076550</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/you-give-up-a-lot-to-work-for-the-federal-judiciary/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T17:43:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You shouldn’t have to give up your civil rights.
The post You Give Up A Lot To Work For The Federal Judiciary appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aliza Shatzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off Scrambles To Survive Caramel Week]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171162</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-not-so-great-defector-bake-off-scrambles-to-survive-caramel-week"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T17:21:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off, where Kelsey and Chris attempt to complete the technical challenges from the newest season of The Great British Bake Off in their own home kitchens, with the same time parameters as the professional-grade bakers competing on the show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looks Like Logic Games Really Did Gatekeep The LSAT]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076556</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/looks-like-logic-games-really-did-gatekeep-the-lsat/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T17:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yay! No more sketches!
The post Looks Like Logic Games Really Did Gatekeep The LSAT appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ABC Casts Aileen Cannon As Attorney General In Trump White House 2: Nightmare On Pennsylvania Ave]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076558</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/abc-casts-aileen-cannon-as-attorney-general-in-trump-white-house-2-nightmare-on-pennsylvania-ave/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T16:15:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spooky!
The post ABC Casts Aileen Cannon As Attorney General In Trump White House 2: Nightmare On Pennsylvania Ave appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pop, fizz, and celebrate as Blanc Champagne Bar brings bubbly vibes to Kansas City]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856489</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/pop-fizz-and-celebrate-as-blanc-champagne-bar-brings-bubbly-vibes-to-kansas-city/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T16:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blanc Champagne Bar // Photo By Tiffany Watts Raise your glasses, Kansas City—Blanc Champagne Bar is popping into town, ready to make a splash! Founded by Jordin Johnson, Blanc Champagne Bar, is located at 3835 Main Street in KCMO. This multi-level spot is set to bring a bubbly experience like no other, with a focus on champagne, community, and good...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers Stand Behind Kamala Harris When It Comes To Lining Her Campaign Coffers With Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076553</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/lawyers-stand-behind-kamala-harris-when-it-comes-to-lining-her-campaign-coffers-with-cash/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T15:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers strongly favor Kamala Harris in the presidential race -- and it's obvious from the millions upon millions of dollars she's received from them.
The post Lawyers Stand Behind Kamala Harris When It Comes To Lining Her Campaign Coffers With Cash appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Always Garbage Man Appreciation Week In Our Hearts]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171243</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-always-garbage-man-appreciation-week-in-our-hearts"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T15:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a little two-question quiz for your Wednesday: What would you borrow? What would you lend? I think I’ll borrow tools. Maybe something big and unwieldy, but only if there is an established social protocol for making the inconvenience up to the owner, like using a pickup truck for the afternoon and filling the tank before I bring it back. I’ll lend books, but only if I care more about getting the other person to read the book than I do about getting my copy back. I don’t want to second-guess any of my relationships due to debt on either side. Basically, I avoid mess at all costs. So this week’s story—which involves a coworker forcing our friend-of-a-friend to borrow an heirloom Halloween costume—is a true nightmare wrapped in an obligation.
Our guest this week is none other than Alex Sujong Laughlin, Defector’s Supervising Producer and Normal Gossip’s co-creator! Kelsey finally coaxed Alex to the other side of the mic for a tale of two civic-minded girlbosses in the Department of Sanitation, a stolen cannoli and a Halloween costume.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get the Red Out: Chicago NWSL Club Rebrands to Chicago Stars FC for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82866</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/23/get-the-red-out-chicago-nwsl-club-rebrands-to-chicago-stars-fc-for-2025/soccer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T15:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New name and crest officially take effect in 2025 NWSL season, but team will "celebrate our new era" during their final regular season game of 2024 on Sunday, November 3 against Kansas City]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italy’s Historically Horrific New Surrogacy Law Is Also A Threat To U.S. Attorneys]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076300</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/italys-historically-horrific-new-surrogacy-law-is-also-a-threat-to-u-s-attorneys/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T14:46:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Italian citizenship through ancestry could, in theory, cause some problems. 
The post Italy’s Historically Horrific New Surrogacy Law Is Also A Threat To U.S. Attorneys appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ellen Trachman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Music Club Blows Up The Chicken Man]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170923</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-music-club-blows-up-the-chicken-man-bruce-springsteen-nebraska-discussion"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T14:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Defector Music Club, where a number of our writers get together to dish about an album. Today, Dave McKenna, Luis Paez-Pumar, David Roth, and Lauren Theisen explore Bruce Springsteen's 1982 cult favorite Nebraska.
David: Friends, we are gathered here today to discuss a grim, spare, old album by the foremost living New Jerseyan. The record is Nebraska, the New Jerseyan in question is Bruce Springsteen, and the whole thing is kind of haunted and half-depressed. I do not know why everyone thought I should be the first person to say something about such an album, but as the oldest and saddest New Jerseyan on the staff I was delighted that Lauren picked this record, which has fascinated me since I was a teenager. I love it but find it kind of difficult to talk about. Not because I don’t think it’s great, but because it feels somehow too on the nose for me, being who and how I am, to be like “Oh you like Bruce Springsteen’s anthems? You should really check out his Mood Disorder Album, which has virtually no instrumentation, was recorded on a four-track, and seems to have been co-produced by a ghost.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Better rain potential ahead (WED-10/23)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3705444</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-better-rain-potential-ahead-wed-10-23/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T14:21:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday it looked like Autumn, but it sort of felt like summer with temperatures in the low to mid-80s in the region ahead of a cold front that moved through last night. This front is ushering in cooler, and somewhat more seasonable, air into the region. That's why temperatures will be in the 60s today [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Every NBA Uniform, Logo Change For 2024-25 Season]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82816</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/23/every-nba-uniform-logo-change-for-2024-25-season/basketball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T14:18:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A comprehensive list of every uniform, logo and court change that has taken place across the NBA for the 2024-25 season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hedge Fund Accused Of Acting Like Typical Australian On South Korean Vacation]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076527</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/10/hedge-fund-accused-of-acting-like-typical-australian-on-south-korean-vacation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T14:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Loud, brash and allegedly unafraid of breaking a few rules.
The post Hedge Fund Accused Of Acting Like Typical Australian On South Korean Vacation appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animals, Ranked By How Magical They Are To See]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171202</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/animals-ranked-by-how-magical-they-are-to-see"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T13:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First there was a dolphin, a brief glimpse of its sleek, slate-gray trunk arcing across the surface, and then, before you knew it, there were so many dolphins. More dolphins than you could count. So many dolphins that as soon as one crested the waves and the cluster of Defector staffers oohed and ahhed and hollered to their comrades It's over there!, the hollering would come from another part of the boat, for another pod of dolphins. They were playing—chasing each other, leaping, flipping their flukes skyward against the setting sun. Breasting the waves for no other reason because they could, and because their bodies were designed to do it, and because their brains are designed to enjoy doing it. At one point three dolphins, side by side, so close as to be touching, emerged from the water …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Preview Of The 2024-25 NBA Season, Accurately Enumerating Everything That Will Happen In It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171095</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-preview-of-the-2024-25-nba-season-accurately-enumerating-everything-that-will-happen-in-it"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wow! They're bringing the NBA back again! Who could have imagined this would happen? No one. There was no reason to expect, nor even to theorize, that it would or could ever happen. Kind of a jerk move when you think about it.
Here at Defector, we do not let the caprice of various sports leagues give us an excuse for failing in our blog duty. If the NBA is going to have a 2024-25 season—if the powers that be are going to announce this many hours after the first games, with no warning—then we will have to "pre-view" it, for the sake of our beloved public, who can learn nothing about any of this except what we provide. From our own loins!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Fresh Donuts and Friendly Bean Coffee prove to be accurate monikers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857607</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-fresh-donuts-and-friendly-bean-coffee-prove-to-be-accurate-monikers/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T13:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh Donuts // Photo By Tiffany Watts Fresh Donuts Tucked away in the corner of a small, unassuming strip mall just off Barry Road, Fresh Donuts is the kind of place you might miss if you’re not looking for it—but trust me, you’ll want to look.  Step inside, and you’re instantly greeted by the warm, comforting aroma of freshly baked...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.23.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076541</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-23-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T12:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Law school applications are up and some suggest it might be due to the end of the logic games section. Look, logic games were dumb but if the thing holding you back from applying to law school was not wanting to deal with one LSAT section then maybe law school isn't your bag. [Reuters]
* Wait, the former CEO of a company that marketed itself with shirtless teenagers might be involved in sex trafficking? [Law360]
* Firms need to tell the truth about which partners are on salary. [Law.com]
* Law professor files ethics complaint against former legal counsel. [Columbia Daily Spectator]
* Georgia Supreme Court tosses contempt ruling against Young Thug attorney. [AJC]
* UK firms have upped billable rates by 40 percent over the last five years. [LegalCheek]
* Lawyers donate $27 million to Harris over the last two months. Sadly it did not stop the fundraising emails in their inboxes. [Bloomberg Law News]
The post Morning Docket: 10.23.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri AG in abortion pill lawsuit argues fewer teen pregnancies hurt state financially]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857700</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missouri-ag-in-abortion-pill-lawsuit-argues-fewer-teen-pregnancies-hurt-state-financially/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-23T12:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri’s attorney general has renewed a push to restrict access to the abortion pill mifepristone, arguing in a lawsuit filed this month that its availability hurt the state by decreasing teenage pregnancy. The revised lawsuit was filed by Missouri Attorney General Andrew Bailey, alongside GOP attorneys general in Kansas and Idaho. It asks a judge in Texas to order the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Spoerre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>