<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-02-09T22:14:34.984Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers’s Jets Tenure Ended In True Jets Fashion]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180859</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/aaron-rodgerss-jets-tenure-ended-in-true-jets-fashion"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T21:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brick Johnson wields a sure, swift sword, and even if he didn't wield this one, it's nice to think he did without even looking up from his Fortnite screen. This might just be a sins-of-the-father vehicle, but when the New York Jets make news, his name will be invoked because they are the Jets constantly doing Jets things.
If we are to trust Jay Glazer, and let's face it, he's no less trustworthy than any of the other sneaks who pull news out of the NFL before it can type up a release, Rodgers flew to New York last week to learn about his future with the Jets only to discover that he'd already had it. The Jets were, as they say, moving on to their next stupid idea, and their 19th starting quarterback since 2010, the last time they played more than the minimum allotted games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Hip Stretch To Help You Stay Sane]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180833</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-hip-stretch-to-help-you-stay-sane"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T19:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news is all shit right now. Sure, there are more artful, creative, and writerly,  ways to say that, but time is precious and writing something like that would prove nothing more than ownership of a thesaurus. 
If you're like me and millions of others, you are absorbing all this and wondering, "What can I do?" You can subscribe to journalism (which you probably already do! Yay!), donate money, volunteer, show up for your family, friends, and neighbors, and then what? That's the thing about the battle for a real democracy—it is not won in flashy, Hollywood fight scenes, though those do make for excellent inspirational images for sharing amid said battle for democracy. It's won in federal workers showing up to do their jobs. It's won in reporters showing up to do their jobs. It's won in a lot of us, in our own ways, showing up, doing our jobs, and not being assholes, even to the person who irritates you—and they are so, so annoying—but dammit we'll deal with that after we make sure there's still a republic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Superb Owl Lead Up That Never Was]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180851</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-superb-owl-lead-up-that-never-was"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T19:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This has not been a terribly memorable walk up to the Superb Owl, not in New Orleans, not across America, not even in Australia, where the NFL is staging a regular season game in 2026 as a very belated punishment to the Los Angeles Rams for those uniforms. And if you can't be weird in Louisiana, well, what exactly is the point?
When your biggest moment of the week, after all, is Roger Goodell leaning hard into an 18th game, you have a serious cultural dud on your hands. The football will be the football, of course, and as matchups go Eagles-Chiefs is not far from the best you can do. But New Orleans might be the last bastion of the pre-corporate days when the town created the atmosphere and it was up to the visitors to keep up. This time, the weirdest thing we got will be something we have to conjure in our own minds—the big game with a sitting President (Uncle Dismal) and a potential rival in 2028 (Stephen A. Smith). Neither is qualified to do the job, as one has proven and the other certainly would if given the chance, but the moment Smith's name appeared on a poll listing potential Democratic candidates and garnering 2 percent, we took an irrevocable turn toward a world in which Prince Andrew seems leaderly. All that is left for the rest of us is to find a country without an extradition treaty out of the way of the nuclear winds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickgui – virtual machine manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142101</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/quickgui-virtual-machine-manager/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T18:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quickgui is a graphical user interface for the Quickemu virtual machine manager.
The post Quickgui – virtual machine manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Snowstorm(s?) likely in KC (SUN-2/9)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3819475</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-snowstorms-likely-in-kc-sun-2-9/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T17:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Super Bowl Sunday, and New Orleans yesterday hit a record 85° at the airport. Here in Kansas City, we've dumped back into the colder air today and this cold will be with us for a while it appears. It's one ingredient to the set-up for multiple snow chances into next weekend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Snowstorm(s?) likely in KC (SUN-2/9)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3819475</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-snowstorms-likely-in-kc-sun-2-9/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T17:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Super Bowl Sunday and while New Orleans yesterday hit a record 85° at the airport...here in KC we've dumped back into the colder air today and this cold will be with us for awhile it appears. It's one ingredient to the set-up for multiple snow chances into next weekend. There will be a more [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BinEd – binary / hex editor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142123</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/bined-binary-hex-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T16:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BinEd is an editor for binary data (hex viewer/editor). It's written in Java so runs under a wide range of platforms.
The post BinEd – binary / hex editor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart.Framework – PHP and JavaScript web framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142066</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/smart-framework-php-javascript-web-framework/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T16:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart.Framework is a practical, modern and high performance PHP / JavaScript Framework for Web featuring Middlewares and MVC.
The post Smart.Framework – PHP and JavaScript web framework appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[19 Best Free and Open Source Linux Astronomy Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=4452</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/astronomy/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T15:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article focuses on selecting the best free astronomy software available for Linux.
The post 19 Best Free and Open Source Linux Astronomy Apps appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TiMidity++ – MIDI to WAVE converter and player]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142143</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/timidity-midi-wave-converter-player/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T13:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TiMidity++ is a software synthesizer. It can play MIDI files by converting them into PCM waveform data.
The post TiMidity++ – MIDI to WAVE converter and player appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Best Free and Open Source CLI Tools to Find and Delete Duplicate Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139565</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-cli-tools-find-delete-duplicate-files/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T13:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This roundup focuses on free and open source command-line tools that help you find and remove duplicate files.
The post 15 Best Free and Open Source CLI Tools to Find and Delete Duplicate Files appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kinship Cafe is leaving Kansas City, Kansas. But the coffee shop isn't closing for good]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-02-09/kinship-cafe-strawberry-hill-independence-overland-park</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-02-09/kinship-cafe-strawberry-hill-independence-overland-park"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TJ Roberts first opened Kinship Cafe in 2021 in Strawberry Hill. After a lease deal fell through with his property owner, Roberts is leaving his original location behind for new shops in Independence and Overland Park.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Wilmore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glow – render Markdown on the command-line]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142081</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/glow-render-markdown-command-line/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T08:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glow is a terminal based markdown reader designed from the ground up to bring out the beauty—and power—of the CLI.
The post Glow – render Markdown on the command-line appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tyler Beede Holds Showcase For Interested Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840977</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/tyler-beede-holds-showcase-for-interested-teams.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-09T03:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right-hander Tyler Beede threw for teams held a pro day for interested teams on Friday, per a report from Ari Alexander of KPRC2. Alexander adds that Beede’s fastball was in the range of 93-95mph and that the Astros and Royals both were represented at the righty’s showcase. Beede, 32 in May, was selected in the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terrapin Vulnerability Scanner for the Terrapin attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142076</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/terrapin-vulnerability-scanner-terrapin-attack/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T23:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Terrapin Vulnerability Scanner  can be used to determine the vulnerability of an SSH client or server against the Terrapin Attack.
The post Terrapin Vulnerability Scanner for the Terrapin attack appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[J.J. Picollo Discusses Royals Offseason Pursuits, Outfield Mix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840961</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/j-j-picollo-discusses-royals-offseason-pursuits-outfield-mix.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T21:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A year ago, the Royals had just put the finishing touching on an extension with budding superstar Bobby Witt Jr. that served as a capstone on the busiest and most aggressive offseason the club had put together in years. That strong offseason effort led to an 86-win season and a trip to the NLDS, where…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pop PHP Framework – toolkit for rapid application development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142062</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pop-php-framework-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T21:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pop PHP Framework contains a group of core components and an additional 30+ components that serve as a toolkit.
The post Pop PHP Framework – toolkit for rapid application development appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bochs – IA-32 (x86) PC emulator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142094</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/bochs-ia-32-x86-pc-emulator/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T20:39:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bochs is a highly portable IA-32 (x86) PC emulato, that runs on most popular platforms. 
The post Bochs – IA-32 (x86) PC emulator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Melt – backup and restore SSH private keys using memorable seed phrases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142085</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/melt-backup-restore-ssh-private-keys/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T19:38:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Melt is a utility that lets you backup and restore SSH private keys using memorable seed phrases.
The post Melt – backup and restore SSH private keys using memorable seed phrases appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cassowary – run Windows virtual machine on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142098</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/cassowary-windows-virtual-machine-linux/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T16:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cassowary lets you run a Windows virtual machine and use Windows applications on Linux as if they were native applications.
The post Cassowary – run Windows virtual machine on Linux appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Best Free and Open Source Media Players]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=70925</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-media-players/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T16:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A media player is software that lets you watch video and listen to music on your computer. We cover the best free and open source options.
The post 16 Best Free and Open Source Media Players appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VX Linux – systemd-free Plasma desktop distro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142105</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/vx-linux-systemd-free-plasma-desktop-distro/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T11:04:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VX Linux is a pre-configured, secure systemd-free Plasma desktop with focus on convenience, performance and simplicity.
The post VX Linux – systemd-free Plasma desktop distro appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[qr-backup – paper backup of files using QR codes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142078</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/qr-backup-paper-backup-qr-codes/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T07:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[qr-backup takes file(s), and outputs a "paper backup": a printable black-and-white PDF full of QR codes.
The post qr-backup – paper backup of files using QR codes appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effectively Wild Episode 2281: Season Preview Series: Orioles and Royals]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=456586</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/effectively-wild-episode-2281-season-preview-series-orioles-and-royals/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-08T05:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Lindbergh and Meg Rowley banter about the Dodgers’ overstuffed 2025 bobblehead lineup, Ippei Mizuhara’s sentencing, and the Angels’ tireless pursuit of players who were good several seasons ago. Then they preview the 2025 Baltimore Orioles (35:55) with the Baltimore Banner’s Danielle Allentuck, and the 2025 Kansas City Royals (1:08:21) with the Kansas City Star’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Lindbergh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[flxvwr – simple, cross-platform image viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141993</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/flxvwr-simple-cross-platform-image-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T23:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[flxvwr is a simple, cross-platform image viewer which provides a minimal user interface, keyboard shortcuts, and smooth performance.
The post flxvwr – simple, cross-platform image viewer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poll: Who’s Winning The Offseason In The AL Central?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840772</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/poll-whos-winning-the-offseason-in-the-al-central.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T23:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The calendar has flipped to February and the start of spring is just a matter of days away. While some notable free agents (including seven of MLBTR’s Top 50) remain unsigned, most clubs have already done the heavy lifting in terms of preparing their roster for the 2025 season. In the coming days, we’ll be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[highlight.js – syntax highlighter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141989</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/highlight-js-syntax-highlighter/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T21:26:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[highlight.js is a syntax highlighter written in JavaScript. It works in the browser as well as on the server
The post highlight.js – syntax highlighter appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tennessee Tried Something New And Beat An Old Rival]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180778</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tennessee-tried-something-new-and-beat-an-old-rival"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T20:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a classic rivalry said to have lost its juice, Thursday night’s UConn-Tennessee game sure felt plenty juiceful. In front of a season-record crowd at home, the No. 19 Lady Vols took down the No. 5 Huskies, 80-76, to end an 18-year rivalry drought.
To be fair, that timespan does include a 13-year gap in the series, which the late Pat Summitt called off in 2007 at the height of her feud with UConn head coach Geno Auriemma. He looks back on that heyday with little fondness. “It just became stupid and became something I didn't want to be a part of anymore,” Auriemma told reporters before Thursday’s game. “I think our fans are stupid. I think their fans are stupid, and how they reacted to the whole thing, it just became something other than a basketball game, and after a while that just got old.” (If he’s referring to the rivalry’s hostility, it should be noted that he had some hand in it, too.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickemu – run Linux, macOS, and Windows virtual machines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142055</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/quickemu-run-linux-macos-windows-virtual-machines/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T19:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quickemu is a wrapper for QEMU that automatically "does the right thing" when creating virtual machines.
The post Quickemu – run Linux, macOS, and Windows virtual machines appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QR Scanner – QR scanner/generator app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142016</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/qr-scanner-code-generator/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T19:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[QR Scanner is a QR code scanner and generator built with Flutter.
The post QR Scanner – QR scanner/generator app appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: It Is Now Time To Chat With The Defector Staff]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180806</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/alert-it-is-now-time-to-chat-with-the-defector-staff"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T18:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Friday! The Super Bowl is almost here! Let's chat!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Time Does “What Time Does The Super Bowl Start?” Start?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180482</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-time-does-what-time-does-the-super-bowl-start-start-3"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T18:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have now done this gag across four websites for 10 years, a time period in which the sweaty behavior I sought to skewer has morphed from a cynical attempt to ride, remora-like, on the prodigious belly of Google search traffic into an almost quaint, bygone phenomenon. It's not so much that publications across digital and traditional media are any less determined to degrade themselves in search of traffic, as it is that "digital media" and "traffic" are themselves largely bygone relics. I am almost nostalgic!
But only almost! That belly remains surfable, and plenty of news outlets are still determined to surf it. Perhaps as media literacy declines and as social media's utility as a news scraper craters, the public's thirst for knowledge—at least about one specific thing: what time the Super Bowl starts—can only be quenched by conducting a Google search. The funniest thing here is that the first result for any such search is a Google-generated box with the start time and the team logos, negating the primary utility of these sorts of posts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foto – simple image viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142052</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/foto-simple-image-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T18:31:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foto is a simple image viewer. It simply shows an image either on a window or in the terminal. It is designed to be used in scripts.
The post Foto – simple image viewer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Best Free and Open Source Console Email Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=58883</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-console-email-clients/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T18:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are our recommended console email clients. All free and open source goodness.
The post 15 Best Free and Open Source Console Email Clients appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Warcraft III: Reforged’ Was A Greedy Debacle]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179030</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/warcraft-iii-reforged-was-a-greedy-debacle"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T18:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to The Backlog, a new series in which we will take a look back at 12 games from 2020 that, in one way or another, had a lasting impact on the video game industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dillon Brooks Will Continue Poking Bears Until He’s Left With Bloody Stumps]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180773</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dillon-brooks-will-continue-poking-bears-until-hes-left-with-but-bloody-stumps"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T17:33:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You think you want an active trade deadline. You want everyone down in the shit, firing players and draft picks back and forth at subatomic speeds. That's what you tell yourself! And then one February everyone goes crazy in the Deal Zone and there are one billion trades in one week, so many coming so rapidly that the league's preeminent scoopster isn't even waiting to learn both halves of trades before posting them and moving to the next one. Before you have time to fully wrap your head around one perplexing deal, 14 more have followed in its wake. All I wanted was a little action to pull me out of seasonal malaise, you sob, desperate to force the genie back into the bottle. Just like that, and too late, you remember that what you want from a basketball season, more than anything, is some by-God basketball. 
They played some by-God basketball in Minneapolis Thursday night. The two participating teams were among the least active at the deadline. The Timberwolves, sitting sixth in the Western Conference standings with one of the most expensive active rosters in the NBA, were severely restricted by the current CBA and made zero moves. The visiting Houston Rockets kept their roster intact but acquired 32-year-old Cody Zeller to fill the very last seat on their bench, and otherwise picked up a few future second-round draft picks. The teams are good enough and young enough to justify standing pat, and to feel reasonably confident headed into the closing stretch of the regular season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File Lock PEA – filesystem-level encryption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141861</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/file-lock-pea-filesystem-level-encryption/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File Lock PEA (PEA = Password Encrypting Archive) encrypts data at the filesystem level 
The post File Lock PEA – filesystem-level encryption appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Thomas Hatch To Minor League Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840784</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/royals-sign-thomas-hatch-minor-league-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T16:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced Friday that they’ve signed righty Thomas Hatch to a minor league deal. The Moye Sports client will be in major league camp as a non-roster invitee this spring. Hatch, 30, originally agreed to a one-year deal with the Korea Baseball Organization’s Doosan Bears back in November, but that deal fell through after…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce Is Using A Hallucination To Sell AI]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180677</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/salesforce-is-using-a-hallucination-to-sell-ai"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T16:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot is happening in the world of artificial intelligence, and not a lot of it makes sense. We're told that AI is the future of business, yet it is wildly unprofitable; investment in AI companies is ramping up even as AI-adjacent tech stocks tumble; the American Plagiarism Machine is accusing the Chinese Plagiarism Machine of plagiarism. But nothing—nothing—is as head-spinning, as bizarre, or as infuriating as this, the bafflingly ubiquitous ad where renowned actors Matthew McConaughey and Woody Harrelson hawk Salesforce's newest AI enterprise software product:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s4JNLL7U8H8]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Kluegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In 1988, Buddy Ryan Was Watchin’ The Eagles Rap]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180657</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/in-1988-buddy-ryan-was-watchin-the-eagles-rap"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T16:18:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was October of 1988, and the Philadelphia Eagles were headed to their first NFC East title since the 1980 season. It didn’t seem like it at the time, though. Philadelphia finished the month 4-5, and New York, Washington, and Phoenix were all ahead of them in the standings.
That did not stop the crew at West Coast Video. With the team in fourth place in the division, the Philadelphia-based video rental chain pitched Eagles players on an idea—a rap song performed by the team, similar to the Chicago Bears' “Super Bowl Shuffle” three years earlier. Those Bears won the Super Bowl, and the song was nominated for an R&B Grammy, so it inspired a lot of imitators. Most were similar group raps by the team, but things did get weird around the margins. Bears coach Mike Ditka himself put out two different songs on VHS. The Cleveland Browns made a sci-fi short, D.T. in Dawg Territory, among other mini-movies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: A very snowy look next week (FRI-2/7)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3818013</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-a-very-snowy-look-next-week-fri-2-7/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T15:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple rounds of snow and bitterly cold temperatures are expected next week beginning as early as Monday night, going through Thursday]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: A very snowy look next week (FRI-2/7)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3818013</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-a-very-snowy-look-next-week-fri-2-7/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T15:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I continue to remain bullish on accumulating snow prospects for next week...starting as early as Monday evening but more than likely by early Tuesday. This would be considered round one...then another system for Wednesday into early Thursday morning. With cold air being tapped, lift and moisture being present, and a powdery snow scenario shaping up, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doechii’s Old Vlogs Document Her Self-Invention]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180701</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/doechiis-old-vlogs-document-her-self-invention"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T15:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doechii’s YouTube channel has 1.85 million subscribers. Her most recent video, a new single called "Nosebleeds," was posted shortly after she became the third woman ever to win the Grammy for Best Rap Album on Sunday.
I keep replaying moments from her Grammy performance of "Catfish" and "Denial is a River" – the shapes she made with her body while standing on the platform above her throng of dancers, the moment her dancers split her Thom Browne suit to reveal a stark white underwear set, and her Fosse turn in the bright lights. Doechii's performances are crisp and deliberate; at 26 years old, her creative vision seems fully realized already, executed with a precision as tight as her signature face tape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City’s Outfield Is a Missed Opportunity]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=456406</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/kansas-citys-outfield-is-a-missed-opportunity/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T15:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals got nothing from their outfield corners in 2024, and they appear to be content with getting nothing from them again in 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Szymborski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Masai Ujiri Continues His Baffling Wing Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180756</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/masai-ujiri-continues-his-baffling-wing-collection"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T15:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To understand the mind of Masai Ujiri, the brilliant team president of the Toronto Raptors who chisels away at his reputation with each passing season, it helps to hear his story about five incredible long guys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[octoscan – static vulnerability scanner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141898</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/octoscan-static-vulnerability-scanner/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T14:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Octoscan is a static vulnerability scanner for GitHub action workflows.
The post octoscan – static vulnerability scanner appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chimpanzee Culture Is Disappearing Because Of Us]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180713</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/chimpanzee-culture-is-disappearing-because-of-us"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T14:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For millennia, the western chimpanzees of Taï National Park in Ivory Coast have communicated with each other in a dialect of their own. They do not speak in words, but rather through gestures. In one gesture called leaf clip, a chimpanzee will take a leaf off a branch and rip it apart in their mouth, creating a ripping sound that might invite play. In another gesture called knuckle knock, males knock repeatedly on the trunk of a small tree; knuckle knock is an invitation meant to attract female chimpanzees, who may respond to the knocking gesture with a sexual display.
Scientists have observed the four populations of chimps in the Taï forest—the North, Northeast, East, and South groups—since the 1970s, learning about each of their particular customs. Knuckle knock was a staple in the North group for generations; before 2004, every male in the group used knuckle knock to woo females. But in the ensuing eight years, the population never had more than one adult male. This eliminated the need for a male to distinguish himself among competitors, and also prevented any younger male chimps from seeing the gesture in use and learning it for the future. In 2008, the last adult male chimp in the North group, and perhaps the last of his population to use knuckle knock, was killed by a poacher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sight Below]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/the-sight-below</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/the-sight-below"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T08:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Friday so we’re listening to something slightly more upbeat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snal Linux – Arch based live distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141977</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/snal-linux-arch-based-live-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T07:33:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Snal Linux is an Arch-based distro intended to be used as a live image from portable media .It uses the i3 window manager and Firefox.
The post Snal Linux – Arch based live distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suspension Bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3048/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3048/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encpipe – encryption tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141838</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/encpipe-encryption-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T21:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Encpipe is billed as the simplest encryption tool in the world. 
The post Encpipe – encryption tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Eagles Fan Version Of Personal Growth, With Dan McQuade]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180646</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-eagles-fan-version-of-personal-growth-with-dan-mcquade"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T21:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have other stuff to talk to my therapist about, luckily, but there is a part of me that feels churlish and a little silly about not appreciating Sunday's upcoming Super Bowl matchup. Yes, we've gotten somewhere between plenty and more than enough of both these teams in the monitors over recent years; yes, some of this grumpiness is surely due to the fact that there were more novel and compelling options than these two very good but very familiar teams. I didn't write that I felt wrong in my churlishness, though. I felt, and still feel, faintly silly about it—about my inability to get especially excited about a game between these two extremely good and evenly matched teams, each of which dominated their respective conferences throughout the season and both of which make for pretty fascinating counterpoints to the other. I think the game will be good, but I can't quite feel what I probably should be feeling about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rouge – elegant, extendable code highlighter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141760</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/rouge-elegant-extendable-code-highlighter/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T21:02:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rouge is a pure Ruby syntax highlighter. It can highlight over 200 different languages, and output HTML or ANSI 256-color text. 
The post Rouge – elegant, extendable code highlighter appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone Thinks They Have A Shot]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180707</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/everyone-thinks-they-have-a-shot"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T20:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My first thought upon seeing that the Lakers had traded a haul for Hornets center Mark Williams was that Rob Pelinka had never bothered to tab over to the "games played" section of Williams's permanently mangled Basketball-Reference page. The second was that the Western Conference playoffs are going to be incredible this year.
The majority of the eight teams in the bottom half of the playoff race made win-now trades ahead of Thursday afternoon's trade deadline. The talent scramble somehow gets fiercer the further you go down the standings; four of the five teams between eighth and 12th, at least two of which will not even make the play-in field, pushed their chips in. Why would this many ailing teams further over-leverage themselves for a chance to fight their way into the playoffs? I'd argue that this is proof that the play-in is working as intended and keeping more teams than ever before from tanking, but more to the point, the teams at the bottom of the race are battle-tested while the teams at the top are not. They're not just pushing for a playoff spot due to some clever incentives or because it's the right thing to do. They're doing it because they think they've got a shot at taking out one of the variously green teams currently atop the standings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoBang – QR code and barcode snanner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141892</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/cobang-qr-code-barcode-scanner/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T18:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CoBang is a native QR Code and barcode scanner application for the Linux desktop.
The post CoBang – QR code and barcode snanner appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Last Living Bedwardite]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180481</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-last-living-bedwardite"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T18:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AUGUST TOWN, Jamaica — It's not simple to get to August Town, but it is easy. Anyone can take the road into this Kingston suburb, founded as a haven for freedmen. Its name refers to Emancipation Day of Aug. 1, 1838, which is celebrated as a national holiday. On the way in, one can see a beautifully preserved mural of two 20th-century men who capture the ethos of Caribbean black liberation: Marcus Garvey and Haile Selassie. Selassie's legacy is more contentious—the Rastafari people who venerate the late Ethiopian emperor are not universally loved, even here—but there's little controversy about Garvey, whose likeness appears on the $20 coin.
At the time, I had no idea that Garvey would soon be pardoned by Joe Biden in one of his last acts as president, plastering Garvey's name in American headlines for the first time in decades. He was convicted on trumped-up mail fraud charges in 1923, a prosecution less about any crime than it was about Garvey's towering stature as an activist who founded the Universal Negro Improvement Association and advocated for black people's rights in the U.S., Jamaica, and around the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casey Taylor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Wizards Have Forgotten How To Lose]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180650</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-washington-wizards-have-forgotten-how-to-lose"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T18:01:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A week ago when we explained the historical badness of the Washington Wizards, we were on solid mathematical and historical ground. The team was on pace to become one of the very worst teams ever; if you squinted into the police cruiser spotlight, as you no doubt have done at least once in the last year, they had an outside chance at being the very worst; if you watched them play, the case only became more convincing.
But because these are the Wizards, they couldn't even get the stink right. And because we want to be fair (this is a lie; we never want to be fair), we must now note that the Wiz are on a rare-for-them three-game winning streak during which they have lowered their margin of defeat to a terrible but not hideous 13.8 points per game, and now cannot finish with the worst record in NBA history. In fact, their 119-102 win over Brooklyn last night was their second most decisive victory of the season, a celebration of sorts after the already completely forgotten deal that sent Kyle Kuzma to Milwaukee for Khris Middleton, an athletic rookie, and a pick swap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YunoHost – Linux distribution simplifying server administration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141939</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/yunohost-linux-distribution-simplifying-server-administration/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T17:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YunoHost is a Debian-based Linux distribution which aims simplify server administration and democratize self-hosting.
The post YunoHost – Linux distribution simplifying server administration appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Want To Focus On My Salad]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180673</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-want-to-focus-on-my-salad"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T17:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
It’s the early 2000s and lifestyle magnate Martha Stewart has done a very bad thing. The Securities And Exchange Commission just opened a far-ranging investigation into biotech firm ImClone after its founder, Sam Waksal, divested himself of company stock right before the FDA announced that it had rejected ImClone’s application for a drug called Erbitux. Ever considerate, Waksal tipped off a number of fellow investors to dump their shares before the news hit. Stewart was one of those investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PixelViewer – cross-platform image viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141972</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pixelviewer-image-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T16:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PixelViewer is a cross-platform image viewer supports reading raw Luminance/YUV/RGB/ARGB/Bayer pixels data from file and rendering it.
The post PixelViewer – cross-platform image viewer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vv – image viewer for sixel terminals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142024</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/vv-image-viewer-sixel-terminals/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T16:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vv is different from the vast majority of image viewers. It's a small command-line program to view images from the terminal.
The post vv – image viewer for sixel terminals appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Think River Dolphins Don’t Piss On Each Other? Urine For A Surprise]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180604</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/think-river-dolphins-dont-piss-on-each-other-urine-for-a-surprise"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T15:58:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most majestic water shows in the world cannot be found in front of the grand casinos of Las Vegas or Macao. Instead, it can be seen, sporadically, in the brown waters of the Amazon and other South American rivers occupied by the river dolphins also called botos. As the botos grow, their bodies blush a pale pink, a color that is particularly evident in males. When the male dolphins need to defecate, they do so without any fuss:emptying their bowels directly into the river. But when the males pee, they sometimes get a little fancy with it.
In such cases, a male boto will slowly roll onto his back, exposing his belly to the surface. Then, like a hoisted flag, his penis will gradually emerge from its usually sheathed position. And finally, the boto will begin to pee in one mighty stream that reaches as high as three feet in the air. The powerful arc of the boto's pee sails over his own head and eventually plummets into the water several feet beyond the tip of the dolphin's long snout, or rostrum. Once the boto has peed all its pee, he will slowly roll over once again and resume swimming. With a show like this, who wouldn't want a front-row seat?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Setting up for multiple snows (THU-2/6)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3816695</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-setting-up-for-multiple-snows-thu-2-6/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T15:43:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is the potential for at least four inches of snow early next week with multiple rounds of snow expected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boxes – view, access, and manage remote and virtual systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141969</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/boxes-view-access-manage-remote-virtual-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T15:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boxes is a simple GNOME application to view, access, and manage remote and virtual systems.
The post Boxes – view, access, and manage remote and virtual systems appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Warriors And Jimmy Butler Are Trying To Stop The Clock]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180661</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-warriors-and-jimmy-butler-are-trying-to-stop-the-clock"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T14:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is almost sad that this week will likely be remembered as the Luka Doncic trade deadline, if only because the single weirdest trade of the week and maybe the decade happened four days later. That one involved more teams, players, personalities, and wrecked preconceptions than the one that saw the Mavericks bail on their generational star. Which is why the gods in their infinite chicaneries came up with this four-torsoed, five-headed beauty that centers around the skull-melting notion of Jimmy Butler, Stephen Curry, and Draymond Green as teammates for what might be their last serious run at incandescence.
The Doncic-Anthony Davis deal, which nobody saw coming on Saturday and still inspires conspiracy theories about who screwed whom and for what reasons this long after the deal, has the advantage both of happening first and involving the Los Angeles Lakers. But before there was Luka—before anyone other than Miriam Adelson even imagined that there could be a deal involving Luka—there was Jimmy. Good lord,  was there Jimmy. There was Jimmy staging a month-long one-man palace revolt that he surely could not win against septuagenarian strongman Pat Riley, which played out through a series of suspensions and recriminations long past the point of caring. But credit where due: Butler’s monomaniacal persistence in the face of the oddest NBA trade deadline in memory finally got him both the escape route and the raise that he wanted, even if the team he went to is actually further behind in the standings than the one he left.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlie Baker And The NCAA Roll Over For Donald Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180664</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/charlie-baker-and-the-ncaa-roll-over-for-donald-trump"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T14:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, Donald Trump signed an executive order seeking to ban trans athletes from competing in girls and women's sports. A few hours later, NCAA president Charlie Baker showed everyone just how little moral courage he has.
Like all of Trump's executive orders, the one he signed yesterday does not actually change the law of the land, nor does it create a clear path for enforcement. The executive order relies on a new and perverse interpretation of Title IX—the federal law that prevents schools that receive federal funding from discriminating on the basis of sex—arguing that schools that allow trans people equal opportunities to participate in sports are actually in violation of Title IX. The Trump administration is now threatening to pull federal funding from schools that protect the rights of trans people. The administration's interpretation of Title IX will certainly be challenged in court, and it's not clear how the administration plans to identify schools that are running afoul of this executive order.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sesdiff – generates a shortest edit script]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141822</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/sesdiff-generates-shortest-edit-script/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T13:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sesdiff is a shortest edit script diff that's written in the Rust programming language.
The post sesdiff – generates a shortest edit script appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XEphem – Serious Interactive Astronomical Software Ephemeris]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141944</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/xephem-serious-interactive-astronomical-software-ephemeris/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T10:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XEphem is a Motif based ephemeris and planetarium program for Unix-like operating systems including Linux.
The post XEphem – Serious Interactive Astronomical Software Ephemeris appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chloe Lula]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/chloe-lula-caa</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/chloe-lula-caa"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T08:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Chloe Lula, a Berlin-based cellist and electronic musician.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ONLYOFFICE Docs 8.3 released: stamps and multi-page selection in PDF files, enhanced collaboration in sheets, Shape Merge and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141998</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/onlyoffice-docs-8-3-released-stamps-multi-page-selection-enhanced-collaboration/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T07:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The developers of ONLYOFFICE Docs have released version 8.3, bringing a fresh wave of enhancements.
The post ONLYOFFICE Docs 8.3 released: stamps and multi-page selection in PDF files, enhanced collaboration in sheets, Shape Merge and more appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliShell – like IntelliSense, but for shells]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141738</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/intellishell-like-intellisense-but-for-shells/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T23:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IntelliShell acts like a bookmark store for commands. No need to have a clean history to find something useful with CTRL + R.
The post IntelliShell – like IntelliSense, but for shells appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snip – simple snippet manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141778</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/snip-simple-snippet-manager/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T20:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Snip is a simple snippet manager for your predefined Ultisnips Snippet Directory.
The post Snip – simple snippet manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Dipshit And His Strike Team Of Greasy Beavises Are Stripping The Wires From The Federal Government]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180358</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/billionaire-dipshit-and-his-strike-team-of-greasy-beavises-are-stripping-the-wires-from-the-federal-government"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T19:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most important thing to know about both the chittering Renfields gnawing through the ductwork of the American administrative state and the billionaire sociopath they serve is that they don't care. Every bit of damage they have done and will do springs from and follows this fundamental fact. They don't know anything about what they're wrecking, naturally—these are creatures that do and eat and shit on things, not ones that know—but it is more salient that they don't care enough even to try to know anything about it. They are busy and stupid in a way that mirrors their rancid imago—hardcore in a way that is mostly just erratic and impatient, secretive but grandiose, prissily paranoid, conducting their nasty business on an amphetamized and whimsical timetable—but they are also not really doing anything for the reasons that people or institutions do things.
They do not care about or understand the state because they do not acknowledge that it is valid; they do not care about or understand public service or public servants because they refuse the premise that such things could even exist. This goes beyond the private sector's familiar and self-flattering disdain for the public sector, which amounts to the load-bearing assumption that everything and everyone operating outside of the free market is somehow the minor leagues. There is another opposition at work here, a crabbed and curdled worldview that reflects libertarianism's signature balance of ideological resentment and pure childish certitude, and which is defined by the smash-and-grab anti-ethos of the vandal, but which is finally simpler and stupider than either.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yankees Claim Braden Shewmake]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840551</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/yankees-claim-braden-shewmake-waivers-royals.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T19:17:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Yankees announced Wednesday that they’ve claimed infielder Braden Shewmake off waivers from the Royals. He’ll bring their 40-man roster to capacity, meaning New York will now need to make a roster move once lefty Tim Hill’s deal is finalized. Kansas City designated Shewmake for assignment last week. They’d claimed him off waivers from the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NWSL To Pay $5 Million To Abused Players As Part Of Settlement]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180615</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nwsl-to-pay-5-million-to-abused-players-as-part-of-settlement"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T18:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NWSL will have to pay $5 million to players who were abused and submit regular accounts detailing how it is addressing reports of harassment and discrimination following a joint investigation by the attorney generals of New York, Illinois, and Washington D.C., the offices announced Wednesday. 
The news followed an investigation by all three attorneys general that found—like the other investigations before it—that the league failed to prevent or adequately respond to player reports of harassment and sexual misconduct. From the purview of the attorneys general, this also put the league in violation of Title VII of the Civil Rights Act, which prohibits employment discrimination based on race, color, religion, or national origin, as well as in violation of each state’s human rights act.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lesley Ryder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nets Sabotage Their Own Tank With Thrilling Upset Of Rockets]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180590</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nets-sabotage-their-own-tank-with-thrilling-upset-of-rockets"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T18:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday night's game between the Houston Rockets and Brooklyn Nets had the spirit of March Madness, and I'm not sure whether I intend that in a complimentary or derogatory way. Both teams were struggling to make free throws, finish layups, or just hold onto the ball long enough for an actual shot to go up. It was, at times, a very rough watch. But the finish made up for all of it.
The sloppiness was a key factor in how Brooklyn, a team that likely won't make the play-in, snatched a 99-97 win away from Houston. Walking out of the arena afterward, one fan within earshot compared it to Reggie Miller's eight points in nine seconds against the Knicks. That comparison felt a bit too ambitious, but "six points in six seconds from two players" is tough to capture eloquently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Would Think Nothing Of Being Shot In The Chest With This Plasma Cannon]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180584</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-would-think-nothing-of-being-shot-in-the-chest-with-this-plasma-cannon"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T17:29:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Leyh likes to screw around with voltage and electric fields and plasma. In his time he's built some of the world's biggest Tesla coils, huge towering transformers that throw off terrifying webs of crackling electricity. Working for a decade out of the since redeveloped American Steel Studios space in West Oakland, and now just plying his plasma skills wherever there's an empty tarmac, Leyh has imagined and tested and fabricated and tinkered with many a device that you or I might reasonably mistake for a doomsday weapon. One of these projects, which Leyh has been working on for 30 years, is a by-God plasma cannon, a huge gun that fires a 180,000-volt blast of hell-fire a distance of about 35 feet. 
Plasma, as you know, is at the extreme bitchin' end of all science. You can make it in your microwave if you don't mind blowing up your microwave, and possibly your home, but it is also the stuff they brew up inside of tokamak reactors. Plasma is what kerplodes out of a fuel-stuffed diamond-lined hohlraum after it's been bombarded by 192 freakin' lasers. It's what forks out of a thunderstorm with annihilating fury and chases every living thing for miles around under cover. In China last month researchers at the EAST nuclear fusion reactor fired up a plasma hotter than the interior of the Sun and held it in a steady state for just shy of 18 minutes, making that plasma more than twice as old as the second-oldest human-made plasma of this kind ever to have existed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-Highlight – powerful syntax highlighter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141867</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/re-highlight-powerful-syntax-highlighter/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T17:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Re-Highlight is a powerful syntax highlighter, which is a sub-module of the Reqable project. 
The post Re-Highlight – powerful syntax highlighter appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLB Loses Its Best Umpire To Sports Gambling]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180523</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mlb-loses-its-best-umpire-to-sports-gambling"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T17:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major League Baseball announced on Monday that umpire Pat Hoberg, who is famous for calling a perfect game in the 2022 World Series, was officially fired for violating the league's gambling policy. The news that Hoberg would be disciplined broke in June last year, though he appealed the decision then, denying that he bet on baseball.
According to MLB's investigation, Hoberg had shared a legal sports betting account with a friend he met at a poker tournament in 2014, and, after sports betting was legalized in Iowa in 2019, asked his friend to place non-baseball bets for him. His friend, a professional poker player, did bet on baseball, and later shared his account log-in with Hoberg. (Communication was done over Telegram; both Hoberg and his friend deleted their conversation logs after MLB's investigation began, because, according to Hoberg, he was embarrassed by the volume of his bets.) When Hoberg opened a sports betting account in his own name, the operator flagged that Hoberg's device was also associated with another account that had bet on baseball, and MLB opened an investigation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freeze – generate images of code and terminal output]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141872</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/freeze-generate-images-code-terminal-output/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T16:15:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freeze generates PNGs, SVGs, and WebPs of code and terminal output alike.
The post Freeze – generate images of code and terminal output appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Of Negative Thinking]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180529</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/erik-baker-make-your-own-job-interview"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T16:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Self-help literature is ubiquitous in American culture: A staple of airport bookstores, grocery magazine aisles, as well as its own separate category on the New York Times Nonfiction bestseller list (under Advice, How-To & Miscellaneous). The lifestyle trade, which props up actual scientists, amateur life coaches, and shameless grifters alike, thrives and shifts with each new social fad. Think Robert Greene. Think Malcolm Gladwell, Peggy Orenstein, Brene Brown, Thich Nhat Hanh, Eckhart Tolle. Atomic Habits. How To Win Friends & Influence People. The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People. 
Perennial topics include: body positivity, mental health, relationship advice, why gender essentialism is or isn’t true, pseduo-scientific/spiritual explanations for a bad or good personality, and, since the very beginning, guides to navigating the workplace. Books about how to make money are so popular they could constitute a separate genre. It might seem as if this appetite for self-improvement and creative enlightenment is baked into America itself. Moreover, one could be tricked into believing that the self-help industry’s constant focus on managerial expertise, adversarial competition, and a phrenology-like fixation on types of people is a reflection of objective truth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: An icy start (WED-2/5)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3815314</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-an-icy-start/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T14:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not the prettiest of mornings out there. The precipitation, which is so fine and light that it has barely shown up on the radar, has created a mess on bridges and overpasses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: An icy start]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3815314</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-an-icy-start/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T14:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not the prettiest of mornings out there, the precipitation, so fine and light that it's barely showing up on radar, has created a mess on bridges and overpasses. I didn't notice any pre-treatment on any of the overpasses last night on the way home on the major roads...so we start this morning with a mess [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On The Road With The Monte Carlo Ice Crews, Who Keep Disaster At Bay]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180528</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rally-monte-carlo-ice-crews"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T14:02:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The race, which starts in Monaco and loops 1,012 miles into the Alps and back over the finish line in the Principality, presents its drivers with the most treacherous stages of any rally on Earth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raphael Orlove</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Wing Café’s saucy wings & Exclusive Jerk’s bold Caribbean bites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=869556</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-wing-cafes-saucy-wings-exclusive-jerks-bold-caribbean-bites/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T14:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wing Cafe Northland // Photo By Tiffany Watts Wing Cafe As a dedicated wing enthusiast and firm believer that the saucier the wing, the better, I recently found myself at Wing Cafe’s Northland location on a quick lunch break with my mom. I went all in, ordering a 12-piece wing combo ($23.00): six Cajun Buffalo and six Durango, because, let’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Best Free and Open Source Linux Photo Management Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=3818</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/photomanagement/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T13:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo management software is a type of computer application that helps users to organize their digital image collection.
The post 8 Best Free and Open Source Linux Photo Management Software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qreator – create your own QR codes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141888</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/qreator-create-qr-codes/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T11:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qreator enables you to easily create your own QR codes to encode different types of information in an efficient and compact way.
The post Qreator – create your own QR codes appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>