<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-12-29T10:14:50.810Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[18 Best Free and Open Source Personal Finance Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=83790</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-personal-finance-software/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T08:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We focus on the best personal finance software for Linux. We only feature open source goodness.
The post 18 Best Free and Open Source Personal Finance Software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[stagen – wlroots-based wayland compositor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140193</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/stagen-wlroots-based-wayland-compositor/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T08:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[stagen is a simple experimental wlroots-based wayland compositor.
The post stagen – wlroots-based wayland compositor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Free and Open Source non-GTK non-Qt File Managers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=127276</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-non-gtk-non-qt-file-managers/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T06:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many graphical non-Qt and non-Gtk file managers available. This article examines 11 such file managers.
The post 11 Best Free and Open Source non-GTK non-Qt File Managers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[tere – terminal file explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140106</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tere-terminal-file-explorer/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T23:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tere is a terminal file explorer. It is a faster alternative to using cd and ls to browse folders in your terminal.
The post tere – terminal file explorer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12 Best Free and Open Source Terminal String Styling Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140124</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-terminal-string-styling-tools/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T16:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend developers appreciate the importance of UI design as it’s a critical part of developing an app. With terminal-based tools, visual design might not be foremost in a developer’s mind. While the design is constrained, it’s still important to communicate
The post 12 Best Free and Open Source Terminal String Styling Tools appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TreeTag – personal data manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140118</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/treetag-personal-data-manager/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T12:39:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TreeTag is a personal data manager. It stores information in a hierarchy and automatically positions items in the tree based on field values
The post TreeTag – personal data manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ansi-colors – add ANSI colors to terminal text]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140112</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ansi-colors-add-ansi-colors-terminal-text/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T07:15:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ansi-colors is a fast Node.js library for terminal styling. It's billed as a more performant drop-in replacement for chalk, with no dependencies.
The post ansi-colors – add ANSI colors to terminal text appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treemacs – tree layout file explorer for Emacs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140102</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/treemacs-tree-layout-file-explorer-emacs/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T05:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Treemacs is a file and project explorer similar to NeoTree or vim’s NerdTree, but largely inspired by the Project Explorer in Eclipse. 
The post Treemacs – tree layout file explorer for Emacs appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five KC places to ring in the New Year that aren’t focused on alcohol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866258</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/five-kc-places-to-ring-in-the-new-year-that-arent-focused-on-alcohol/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T22:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Uptown Theater Cheers to surviving 2024! Raise a glass of champagne or sparkling white grape juice. Everything goes here in KC, but some places are better than others for those who are looking to avoid an alcohol-focused party scene. Here are our top picks (that aren’t sold out) for ringing in the New Year with more entertainment or food...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Feels So Over In Sacramento]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177287</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/it-feels-so-over-in-sacramento"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T20:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sacramento Kings played and lost what threatens to be the last meaningful basketball game of their season on Thursday night. There is plenty of evidence to suggest that it may also have been the last meaningful basketball game they play in the years to come.
As franchise-breaking losses go, this one was at least a bang, not a whimper. The Kings hosted a hot Pistons team in the midst of an undefeated West Coast road trip, and despite their lone functional big man Domantas Sabonis missing the game with an illness, they built a double-digit lead early in the second quarter and steadily managed it for two quarters. This is what theoretically superior teams do at home against theoretically inferior ones, a dynamic which De'Aaron Fox's poor first half underscored. Down 10 with 3:36 left, Detroit began to mount a fierce resistance, which was enough for the Kings to totally clam up and stop playing anything resembling team basketball.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deadbeat Club Scrambling To Keep Players It Never Should Have Acquired]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177293</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/deadbeat-club-scrambling-to-keep-players-it-never-should-have-acquired"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T17:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When F.C. Barcelona acquired Dani Olmo from RB Leipzig back in August, it did so despite clearly not being anywhere close to able to afford Olmo's salary under La Liga's Financial Fair Play rules, which regulate each club's spending relative to its earnings and debts each season, and which Barcelona has been wrestling with for years as a result of years upon years of hideous mismanagement. Olmo wound up missing Barça's first couple of 2024 La Liga matches because the club couldn't register his salary with the league.
Good—or anyway, "good"—fortune came in the form of an Achilles tendon injury to trusty center back Andreas Christensen: In the event of an injury that will keep a given player out for four months or longer, La Liga rules permit a team to spend (and register) up to 80 percent of that player's salary for the purpose of filling the hole in the squad. With Christensen out, Barça got the space it needed to register Olmo, plus young attacker Pau Víctor—but only through the end of December. The club would have until then to benefit from Olmo's and Víctor's services; if by then it hadn't drummed up the additional income or savings it would need in order to extend their registrations through the end of the season, the registrations would expire on Jan. 1, rendering the two players unable to participate in La Liga matches and giving the club until the end of the January transfer window to get them re-registered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revisiting a ritual: Absente absinthe leans in on showmanship]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866226</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/revisiting-a-ritual-absente-absinthe-leans-in-on-showmanship/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T17:34:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grande Absente absinthe // Photo by Jordan Baranowski In the world of spirits, absinthe tends to sit in a bit of a mythical spot. It conjures images of tortured European artists like Vincent Van Gogh and Oscar Wilde, sipping hallucinogenic alcohol while creating their artistic masterpieces. For some, their only exposure to the uniquely-colored spirit is Nicole Kidman and Ewan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Baranowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Nosferatu’ Keeps You Waiting And Waiting]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177303</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nosferatu-keeps-you-waiting-and-waiting"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T16:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By the time Bram Stoker died in 1912, Dracula remained his most successful and lucrative creation, a crude way of looking at a writer’s corpus but, in this case, informative of what financial circumstances his widow, Florence, was left in and how the property of Dracula was handled. As executor of Stoker’s estate, Florence had sole authorization over Dracula’s usage in any medium, whether stage plays or nascent motion pictures. In 1921, F. W. Murnau and Prana Films, cofounded by producer Albin Grau, had completed a complicated shoot of a German film titled Nosferatu (the production could only utilize one camera, which meant there was only a single negative to work with), a dramatically stark reinterpretation of Dracula released to little fanfare.
Neither Murnau nor Prana sought permission to use elements from Stoker’s most famous novel from Florence, a concern made less straightforward by the regional differences in copyright law but one that Stoker’s widow nonetheless viewed as flagrant plagiarism. Florence, along with the British Society of Authors, soon launched a legal campaign to sue Prana Films for damages. Ultimately, Prana filed for bankruptcy and, in lieu of being able to pay restitution to Florence, relinquished Nosferatu’s rights and all copies of the film to the Stoker estate. The fiasco took about three years and by 1925, Nosferatu’s market value had fallen so steeply that Florence set about trying to destroy as many existing prints of the film as possible. Five years later, Universal bought the rights to Dracula from Florence and reportedly also bought an existing American print of Nosferatu that they then studied for the 1931 adaptation of the novel starring Bela Lugosi. Of course, extant copies of Nosferatu survived in other countries, prominently in France and the U.S., these and other copies shown in revivals and eventually restored throughout the years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Worst Things We Bought In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177210</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-worst-things-we-bought-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T15:53:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These were the worst purchases by the Defector staff in 2024.
Two Subscriptions To Paramount Plus]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: At least it's mild out there! (FRI-12/27)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3773230</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-at-least-its-mild-out-there-fri-12-27/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T14:44:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're in a lather rinse repeat scenario again today as some areas are starting with some fog, while others have some light rain or heavy drizzle falling. All areas though are running about 30° above average to start the day which is rather remarkable for this time of the year. Our low this morning has [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Buy A Sweater That Doesn’t Suck]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176452</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-to-buy-a-sweater-that-doesnt-suck"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T14:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though neither of us were alive during Jimmy Carter’s presidency, when the weather gets cold, my partner and I love to recite to each other in cartoonish voices, “Do what I do: wear a sweater!” I’m not actually sure if Carter ever said these exact words (I’m not finding it in the transcript of his 1977 sweater speech), but they are a potent reminder: In the cold months, your clothes are meant to keep you warm. 
Last year, a piece by Amanda Mull set off weeks of discourse about why sweaters are such poor quality these days. For most of my life, I wore garbage sweaters that barely kept me warm. I’m sure you know this experience, too. The affordable, accessible options are generally so terrible that it’s possible that the majority of sweaters many of us have worn in our lives have been acrylic or some other synthetic material. It's likely many people don’t know how nice and warm it feels to wear a sweater made from materials that aren't garbage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vim-tree – use tree for quick navigation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140092</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/vim-tree-quick-navigation/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T13:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vim-tree integrates good old tree into Vim and Nvim for all common operating systems. 
The post vim-tree – use tree for quick navigation appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12 Best Free and Open Source TypeScript-Based Web Content Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=97150</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-typescript-based-web-content-management-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are our favorite TypeScript-based web content management systems. They are all free and open source software.
The post 12 Best Free and Open Source TypeScript-Based Web Content Management Systems appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lasering Incidents]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3030/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3030/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fellowship Of The Champagne Saber]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177161</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-fellowship-of-the-champagne-saber"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T19:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know how it is when you're starting a new job. There are new rules and systems to figure out, a new overall cadence and a bunch of new people, and some number of other, stranger, newer things specific to that workplace that you can't really know about going in. When I was hired at the old site back in 2017, I had been through a couple of previous staff writing jobs and a great many recurrent freelance jobs and more get-me-over bullshit office gigs than I care to remember, and while I believed that would prepare me somewhat for the new job—and it did, sort of—I knew there would be stuff that I did not know how to do. 
That was years ago, now, and I remember worrying at the time that I was too old for it. I don't know that I have ever felt it more acutely than I did during my first appearance on the old podcast, where I joined Drew and Tim Marchman for a spirited round of The Price Is Right: Williams-Sonoma Edition. All those jobs I'd had and lost, the content management systems and corporate cultures I'd sort of figured out, the various flavors of shitty media ownership I'd endured—none of that was any help to me when I was tasked with guessing the price of a champagne saber from that year's catalog. I don't remember how wrong I was with my guess, but I do remember that I have seldom been more wrong about anything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Victor Wembanyama Crafted A Fittingly Weird Christmas Masterpiece]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177235</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/victor-wembanyama-crafted-a-fittingly-weird-christmas-masterpiece"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T19:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Basketball fans and league officials who were wringing their hands about the NFL encroaching on Christmas woke up on Wednesday to quite the treat. Knicks-Spurs was an incredible opener to an altogether great showcase day of hoops, largely because Victor Wembanyama played one of his best games as an NBA player. In his second game in Madison Square Garden (his first was only his eighth game as a Spur), Wemby went for 42 points, 18 rebounds, six made three-pointers, and four assists. He also had four blocks, though there's no point in emphasizing those, as he's averaging four per game anyway and he had a 10-block game and a seven-block half in his two previous games.
My favorite thing about a Wembanyama highlight is picking out where he is when there's a cut in the video, as it's usually much further out or in a more compromising position than anyone ever is in a clip where they will soon be highlighted. There he is, two players away out near the perimeter as OG Anunoby winds up for a doomed layup attempt, only for him to scythe over and erase it; there he is, lurking near the logo as Tre Jones pulls a three, only to zip in and dunk back the rebound.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Things We Read In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177042</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-best-things-we-read-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T18:57:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is what the Defector staff enjoyed reading in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Draymond Green Is Still Innovating]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177219</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/draymond-green-is-still-innovating"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T18:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Draymond Green…we'll wait a moment while you readjust your underwear…is the last living pre-modern basketball player, a time-traveler from the era when "everyone is just collateral damage to the greater goal" was the predominant philosophy who has arrived in our moment to do the absolute most. Which is why his little tribute to the 1970s, and to a handful of defunct WWE finishing moves, hit the Christmas basketball crowd so intensely. In executing and selling his inspired and illegal double-takedown of two Los Angeles Lakers, Green managed to commit four callable fouls on the same play. It was remarkable, but also just part of a full evening's work on a full day of quality basketball. And he still managed to fit in his normal output—no discernible offense, 10 rebounds, and a technical foul for complaining to referees—in that purely Greenian way of his.
The “four callable fouls” thing is particularly instructive where Green’s eye to the past is concerned. You can almost see Dalton Knecht and Rui Hachimura sensing that something is about to go very amiss for both of them. They both can see that Green is between them, but their main attention is on the rebound they seek. You can definitely see Scott Foster, the referee you love to hate mostly because he's probably the only referee whose name you know, already putting his whistle in his mouth; he's seen this general dynamic since Green became a pro and has the requisite Pavlovian response. None of this really snuck up on anyone, and yet it arrived as a surprise all the same.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 76ers Are Showing Signs Of Life Amid Brushes With Death]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177197</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-76ers-are-showing-signs-of-life-amid-brushes-with-death"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T17:29:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Philadelphia 76ers began the season in the toilet, but appear now to have slithered out of the bowl. They have the best record in the NBA since Thanksgiving, in a tie with three teams whose bonafides are for the most part pretty well established. All it took was a run of schedule heavy on the league's bozos—the 76ers have played (and beaten) the Charlotte Hornets three times in 18 days—and a little bit of musculoskeletal good fortune, and today the 76ers find themselves just a game out of the Eastern Conference play-in. The cruddiness of the East makes this not too much of an accomplishment, but the 76ers still hope to make something of this season, and a grip on the back of a breathtakingly sad playoff pack at least gives them reason to keep struggling upward.
Wednesday's 118-114 road win over the festively clad Boston Celtics was a good one. This was just the sixth time all season that Philadelphia has had all of Joel Embiid, Paul George, and Tyrese Maxey in the lineup at the same time, and the 76ers are now a respectable 4–2 with their core intact. This is not yet the world-destroying Big Three anyone might've imagined, in part because George and Embiid are still working their way into rhythm and shape, but in 107 minutes of shared court-time the trio has eked out a narrow positive net rating, by holding opposing teams to a suffocated 99.6 points per 100 possessions. Eventually one or more of these very good basketball players will remember how to shoot, and then Philadelphia's important lineups will also thrive, or at least stink a lot less, on the offensive end. For now it's enough to tread water with hellacious defense.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix NFL Viewership Claims Threaten Several International Incidents]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177198</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/netflix-nfl-viewership-claims-threaten-several-international-incidents"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T16:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix viewer statistics are notorious lies. Not just in the Nielsen "we're doing a lot of extrapolating" sense, nor even generous but plausible exaggerations. The data is wholly private, the methods proprietary, and the numbers they do choose to leak are immediately laughed down as mathematically absurd. All streamers play fast and loose with this stuff, but Netflix is particularly egregious. They have their ways: When you watch five minutes of a movie and turn it off because it's ass, Netflix multiplies that five minutes by whatever it needs to achieve the total runtime, then by the 16 people who no doubt live in your household, and that's how we end up with things like Red Notice being the most-watched movie on Earth, ever.
The NFL likes to brag about its ratings. This is understandable, because live sports are the only thing that gets decent broadcast ratings anymore, and the NFL is a juggernaut even in that rare air. So when NFL games made their Netflix debut on Christmas Day with a pair of boring blowouts, you knew the bragging would reach new heights. And because there's no third party actually tracking or verifying the numbers, they could just make up some shit. That is presumably what they did, when NFL Media shared some impressive metrics not long after Chiefs-Steelers ended, but they flew a little too close to the sun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go For It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177177</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/go-for-it"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T15:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. This week's guest host is Victoria Zeller. Her debut novel, One of the Boys, is set to be released on May 13, 2025 by Levine Querido
About a year ago now, I decided I wanted to bake bread.
I certainly did not grow up a baker, or even a cook at all: my skills in the kitchen stayed at the young bachelor-standard Kraft Mac/frozen pizza capacity into my early 20s. While my younger sisters were pressed into service at a young age, churning out cookies and brownies and birthday cakes with my mother, I was never called to duty. I was a boy, my sisters were girls. I could try to turn this into a moment of Injustice, yet another example of Young Victoria having a girlhood she didn’t know she wanted preemptively withheld from her; in reality, I was extremely fucking lazy. If I had been invited to participate, I would’ve said “no” and retreated to my room to play Madden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Zeller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Stuck in the muck (THU-12/26)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3769598</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-stuck-in-the-muck-thu-12-26/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T15:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's another murky and damp start to the day after Christmas in Kansas City. Periods of mist, drizzle, showers and a general fog are hanging around the region, and it's not going to change a lot over the next 36 hours or so until a system moves through tomorrow night. The good news is the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Stuck in the muck (THU-12/26)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3769598</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-stuck-in-the-muck-thu-12-26/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T15:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's another murky and damp start to the day after Christmas in KC. Periods of mist, drizzle, showers and a general fog are hanging around the region and it's not going to change a lot over the next 36 hours or so until a system moves through tomorrow night. The good news is the weekend [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Things We Heard In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176916</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-best-things-we-heard-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T13:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is what the Defector staff enjoyed listening to this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burek and Cake, a Bosnian bakery in Kansas City's Northland, makes each customer feel special]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2024-12-26/burek-cake-bosnian-bakery-kansas-city-northland</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2024-12-26/burek-cake-bosnian-bakery-kansas-city-northland"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T10:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fatima Hodzic opened Burek and Cake just over two years ago. Since then, the tiny Bosnian bakery in the Northland has become a destination to gather over cakes, coffee, and bureks, a traditional Bosnian snack made with pastry dough and savory fillings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Claudia Brancart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logseq – privacy-first platform for knowledge management and collaboration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140063</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/logseq-privacy-first-platform-knowledge-management-collaboration/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T07:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[logseq is a privacy-first, open-source knowledge management and note-taking software designed to enhance productivity
The post Logseq – privacy-first platform for knowledge management and collaboration appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Can A Life Be Wonderful?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177081</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-can-a-life-be-wonderful"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T14:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was originally published on Flaming Hydra on Dec. 4. If you like it, we encourage you to visit their site and subscribe.
For so long I avoided It’s a Wonderful Life—it was too bruising, its redemptions too meager for the guy I was in my 20s, with all those grand plans of his own. I always found myself wishing for more for poor George Bailey, I guess is what I’m saying. Trampled by bad luck, by his own virtue and his begrudging loyalties, stalled out at every moment of departure and always left to clean up someone else’s mess. And worst of all, tormented by the horrible Mister Potter, who creaks through Bedford Falls threatening foreclosures and buyouts in that blubbery old whine of his. I saw Potter as a special kind of real-world doom—a man so powerful you cannot fight against him, only beg him for mercy, as George’s father had done before him and as his children almost certainly will after. The Potters won’t live forever, but there is always another one on their way, with the cops and the bank examiner all working for them too. They weren’t going anywhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Saward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Did We Get Stuck In Our Rectums Last Year?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=175016</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-did-we-get-stuck-in-our-rectums-last-year-5"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you realize that this is the 12th year we've run this series? Time really flies when you don't have something lodged up your butt. But for those of you who do, read on to see if you made this year's list of the weirdest stuff that entered America's orifices. If not, there's always next year.
All reports are taken from the U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission's database of emergency room visits, all descriptions are verbatim, and all the entries below involved some very poor decisions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Lunch meetings at Made In KC Cafe and Al’s Bar & Grill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866040</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-made-in-kc-cafe-taproom-and-als-bar-grill/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Made In Kc Cafe Taproom // Photo By Tiffany Watts Made In KC Cafe & Taproom In the heart of Downtown Kansas City, Made in KC Café & Taproom offers a little bit of everything—coffee, local craft drinks, and a welcoming space to gather. It’s a spot that brings together coffee lovers, craft beverage enthusiasts, and anyone looking for a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Season’s Greetings from LinuxLinks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139997</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/seasons-greetings-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T08:41:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year from everyone at LinuxLinks.
The post Season’s Greetings from LinuxLinks appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Off until Mon, 1/6]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/off-until-mon-16</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/off-until-mon-16"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T05:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flow State will be off for holiday break until Monday, 1/6/25.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sun Avoidance]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3029/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3029/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>