<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-02-22T22:13:22.706Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fibbo – web-based game engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142701</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/fibbo-web-based-game-engine/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T21:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fibbo is a web-based game engine that allows you to create interactive experiences using JavaScript, right in your browser.
The post Fibbo – web-based game engine appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shinken – flexible and scalable monitoring framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142896</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/shinken-flexible-scalable-monitoring-framework/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T19:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shinken is a modern, Nagios compatible monitoring framework, written in Python.
The post Shinken – flexible and scalable monitoring framework appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kickpad – experimental kick drum audio sample generator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142666</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/kickpad-kick-drum-audio-sample-generator/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T17:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kickpad is an experimental kick drum audio sample generator written in Go.
The post Kickpad – experimental kick drum audio sample generator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Google Files]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142534</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-google-files/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T16:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Files is a file management app developed by Google for file browsing, media consumption, storage clean-up and offline file transfer.  We recommend the best free and open source alternatives for Linux.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Google Files appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teable – manage your data and connect your team]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142878</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/teable-manage-data-connect-team/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T15:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teable uses a simple, spreadsheet-like interface to create powerful database applications without any coding skills.
The post Teable – manage your data and connect your team appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Equibop – snappy Discord app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142709</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/equibop-snappy-discord-app/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T14:35:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Equibop is a cross-platform Vesktop Fork desktop app aiming to give you extra plugins but still give you a snappier Discord experience
The post Equibop – snappy Discord app appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ccrypt –  tool for encrypting and decrypting files and streams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142836</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ccrypt-tool-encrypting-decrypting-files-streams/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T10:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ccrypt is a tool for encrypting and decrypting files and streams. It is based on the Rijndael block cipher.
The post ccrypt –  tool for encrypting and decrypting files and streams appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some of Kansas City's best barbecue is found at these Korean and Japanese restaurants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-02-22/kansas-city-barbecue-kbbq-korean-japanese-food</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-02-22/kansas-city-barbecue-kbbq-korean-japanese-food"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond burnt ends, Kansas City also has a scene for Korean barbecue (K-BBQ) and Japanese barbecue (J-BBQ) full of flavorful sauces, marinated meats and enormous portions. Here's a guide to local restaurants and how to cook at home.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Xiao daCunha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Best Free and Open Source Web Project Management Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=13845</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/excellent-web-project-management-software/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T09:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Project management is the application of processes, methods, knowledge, skills and experience to achieve the project objectives. We pick the finest free and open source web project management software.
The post 15 Best Free and Open Source Web Project Management Software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sxcs – minimal X11 color picker and magnifier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142594</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/sxcs-minimal-x11-color-picker-magnifier/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-22T07:23:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sxcs is a minimal X11 color picker and magnifier with mouse and keyboard support.
The post sxcs – minimal X11 color picker and magnifier appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YTSubConverter – create styled YouTube subtitles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142658</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ytsubconverter-create-styled-youtube-subtitles/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T23:50:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YTSubConverter is primarily an .ass to .ytt converter.
The post YTSubConverter – create styled YouTube subtitles appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Details On Nolan Arenado Trade Talks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=842553</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/details-on-nolan-arenado-trade-talks.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T22:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For much of the offseason, a Nolan Arenado trade seemed inevitable. But spring training is now rolling along and he’s still a Cardinal. Today, Katie Woo of The Athletic takes an extensive look at the twists and turns of the winter. Many of the details came out over the past few months but the piece…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[microStudio – game engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142786</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/microstudio-game-engine/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T21:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[microStudio is a free, open source game engine online. It is also a platform to learn and practise programming.
The post microStudio – game engine appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Kluwe Arrested At City Council Meeting For Calling Out Garish MAGA Plaque]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182150</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/chris-kluwe-arrested-at-city-council-meeting-for-calling-out-garish-maga-plaque"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T20:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former NFL punter Chris Kluwe was arrested Tuesday night after speaking out in protest at a Huntington Beach City Council meeting. The California resident had voiced his disgust against a proposal to mark the 50th anniversary of the Huntington Beach Central Library with a plaque adorned with Trumpist kitsch. He spent the rest of his allotted time detailing what the MAGA movement actually represents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gephi – Open Graph Viz Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142810</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gephi-open-graph-viz-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T18:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gephi is visualization and exploration software for all kinds of graphs and networks. Like Photoshop but for graph data.
The post Gephi – Open Graph Viz Platform appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glossy, Gunky And Ready In Minutes: AI Meal Recipes Are Overrunning The Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181831</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/glossy-gunky-and-ready-in-minutes-ai-meal-recipes-are-overrunning-the-internet"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T18:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It all started with a Messenger notification. In my inbox was a blurry image of a Tiramisu Cupcake sent by my grandpa, featuring a too-perfect frosting swirl with a thick coating of cocoa powder and a mysterious missing chunk from the cupcake liner that made me think: What kind of monster eats through the cupcake liner? 
Like so many times before, the picture that he sent accompanied a short note: "Can we make this next time you're home?" Usually, I jump at the chance to plan a menu with my grandpa (my grandparents owned a restaurant for over 30 years and in lieu of going to culinary school, I learned how to cook from them). This time though, there was a problem: The post was very obviously AI-generated. When I called to tell him that the cupcake was AI—or "made by a robot," as he said—he had no idea. He has since sent me dozens more AI recipes, despite our conversation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Domrongchai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Snowing Sea Cucumbers At The Bottom Of The Sea]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181797</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-snowing-sea-cucumbers-at-the-bottom-of-the-sea"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T17:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At first, the footage could pass for a swath of sky that has suddenly become host to a flock of birds. Doves, perhaps. But soon the camera adjusts to reveal two white stellate shapes. They are too big, too lumpy and organic to be stars in the sky. As the camera drifts closer, they reveal themselves as sea stars, one with arms that taper elegantly, and one with arms that end in rounder stubs: the Bert and Ernie of the seafloor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prospect Limbo: The Best of the 2025 Post-Prospects]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=456462</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/prospect-limbo-the-best-of-the-2025-post-prospects/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T17:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s run through the long-term scouting prognoses for some of the players who no longer fit the parameters of my prospect lists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Longenhagen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Yankees No Longer Have To Look Like That, Will Still Be Acting Like That]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182116</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-new-york-yankees-no-longer-have-to-look-like-that-will-still-be-acting-like-that"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T16:22:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Yankees have finally addressed the reason they lost last year's World Series and haven't won one since 2009. Or possibly they are tired of looking like enormous 12-year-olds. Either way, the team is taking action.

https://bsky.app/profile/riveraveblues.bsky.social/post/3lioyqsgjg22v]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do You Make Sex And Party Music For An Era Uninterested In Both?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181815</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-do-you-make-sex-and-party-music-for-an-era-uninterested-in-both"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T15:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Listening Habits, a new column where I share the music I’ve been fixated on recently.

https://youtu.be/cH_QusSap2I?feature=shared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: The turnaround begins! (FRI-2/21)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3831577</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-the-turnaround-begins-fri-2-21/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T14:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another day another record low temperature for KCI...many areas, especially from the Metro northwards tanked sub-zero again, but that's it for that. There won't be sub-zero lows tomorrow, nor the next day, nor next week. Conceivably not for the rest of the season either. The worst of the cold appears to be over and while [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe's Weather Blog | In-depth Kansas City forecasts | FOX4KC</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Game Always Speaks For Itself]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182103</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-game-always-tells-canada-4-nations"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T14:36:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The only thing wrong about Canada's 3-2 overtime triumph over the United States in Thursday's 4 Nations title game is that there was only one extra period, and that lasted under 500 seconds. By rights, it could have, nay, should have lasted past midnight in the east, with every subsequent overtime as high-octane as the first.
Other than that, it could not have been much better as entertainment, as long as you accept the fact that there was an annoying level of contrivance to it. The country that cares most about hockey won, the game's most recognizable player, Connor McDavid, scored the winning goal, the game's disputably best player, Nathan MacKinnon, was named the most valuable player, and the goaltender who stole the show, Jordan Binnington, fully resuscitated the reputation as a big-game player he last enjoyed six years ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Secure-K OS – Debian-based live operating system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142788</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/open-secure-k-os-debian-based-live-operating-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T14:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Secure-K OS is an operating system booting from a USB key in which you can safely create and store your personal and private data. 
The post Open Secure-K OS – Debian-based live operating system appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pitch’s Sandwich Week 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?post_type=gtx_link&amp;p=872597</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/gtx_link/the-pitchs-sandwich-week-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T14:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From March 24-30th, you get 1/2 off some of our favorite sandwiches in the city!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>THE PITCH STAFF</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pitch’s Sandwich Week 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?page_id=872498</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/the-pitchs-sandwich-week-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T14:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From March 24-30th, you get 1/2 off some of our favorite sandwiches in the city! 1930 Classic Kitchen BBQ Honey Sriracha Boneless Chicken Breast This sandwich is piled high on a brioche bun with kosher pickles, lettuce, and a side of homemade coleslaw. 1930 N 77th St, Kansas City, KS 66112 (913) 258-5556 Website Bar Central The Club Sandwich Jalapeño...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Advisory Position</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hockey Remains Canada’s]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=182080</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/hockey-remains-canadas-4-nations"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T14:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a long enough time scale and if the sport is widely popular, a country tends to lose its dominance in a sport it creates. England ceded soccer long ago. The U.S. is, perhaps, in the process of losing its unquestioned position as the supreme basketballing nation. Canada, not for the first time and certainly not the last, faces a reckoning with its place in the hockey world. Since the fall of the U.S.S.R., the top of the sport has become more European, increasingly global, and, above all else, creepingly American. A smaller percentage of NHL players are from Canada than ever before, and more of the best players are from the U.S., as the league has expanded below the border and contracted above it. It's a numbers game, and if it isn't reflected in relative culture cachet, it'll become apparent by who raises the trophies in international competition. Canada may well lose its iron grip on hockey—but not yet.
Team Canada re-expressed its dominion with a 3-2 overtime win over the U.S. in the final of the 4 Nations Face-Off, a totally made-up all-star replacement that almost accidentally stumbled its way into becoming a geopolitical referendum, and served as emphatic notice that the sport is still Canada's to lose. I won't drag out this blog before giving you the climactic goal, the one that'll be replayed for years and years. And because the champions wear red maple leaves, you get the Chris Cuthbert call:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genome Analysis Toolkit (GATK)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142634</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/genome-analysis-toolkit-gatk/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T12:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GATK is a genomic analysis toolkit focused on variant discovery.
The post Genome Analysis Toolkit (GATK) appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Best Free and Open Source Linux File Encryption Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142719</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-linux-file-encryption-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T11:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This roundup looks at the finest GUI-based file encryption tools. Only free and open source software is included.
The post 6 Best Free and Open Source Linux File Encryption Tools appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tangent – clean and powerful notes app]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142642</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tangent-clean-powerful-notes-app/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T08:10:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tangent is designed to let you write the way you think. Your thoughts are connected; Tangent lets you link to existing notes and make new ones with ease.
The post Tangent – clean and powerful notes app appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raven]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/raven</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/raven"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T08:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Friday so we’re listening to something more upbeat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Words! – word puzzle game]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142624</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/words-word-puzzle-game/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T06:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words! is a word puzzle game where you have 6 tries to guess a hidden word.  A simple and addictive game.
The post Words! – word puzzle game appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scream Cipher]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3054/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3054/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[abPOA – adaptive banded Partial Order Alignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142456</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/abpoa-adaptive-banded-partial-order-alignment/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T23:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[abPOA is an extended version of Partial Order Alignment (POA) that performs adaptive banded dynamic programming (DP) with an SIMD implementation. 
The post abPOA – adaptive banded Partial Order Alignment appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Bayern Munich, What Michael Olise Says Goes]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181838</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/at-bayern-munich-what-michael-olise-says-goes"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T21:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's hard to know whether or not Bayern Munich is particularly good this season. On one hand, they have the best stats in Europe. Die Roten score more domestic goals than anyone in the Old Continent's top-five leagues, and allow among the fewest. Even in the Champions League, where their underwhelming results consigned them to the funky but fun new format's purgatory round, the Germans could point to their competition-best expected goal difference as evidence that their performances have been better than the scoreboards might indicate. And just in terms of pure talent, Bayern doesn't have to look at any other team's roster with envy. By all accounts, this should be one of the best teams in the world.
On the other hand, Bayern's cumulative showings across the season give off a strong whiff of a flat-track bully. Though they consistently hammer their lessers, Bayern's record against more or less equals isn't very good: four draws and no wins against Bayer Leverkusen (twice), Eintracht Frankfurt, and Borussia Dortmund in league play, a loss to Leverkusen that bounced them from the German Cup, and three Champions League defeats to Aston Villa, Barcelona, and Feyenoord by a combined score of 8-1. A 1-0 win over almost-didn't-even-make-it-to-purgatory Paris Saint-Germain and a 5-1 Bundesliga win over FC Lawn Ball Sports are the closest Bayern has come to statement victories this season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oboete – simple flashcard application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142554</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/oboete-simple-flashcard-application/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T20:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oboete is a simple flashcards application for the COSMIC desktop.
The post Oboete – simple flashcard application appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marina Mabrey Does Not See Her Future In Connecticut]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181844</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/marina-mabrey-does-not-see-her-future-in-connecticut"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T20:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An athlete who makes two separate trade requests in six months will probably not have public opinion on her side. But it’s also true that to this point in Marina Mabrey's WNBA career, luck has not been on her side either.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Basketball, Some Sandwich, with Rohan Nadkarni]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181858</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/some-basketball-some-sandwich-with-rohan-nadkarni"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T20:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About halfway through this week's episode, returning champion guest Rohan Nadkarni asked a question I didn't really know how to answer. We'd spent the first half talking about the NBA, which I enjoyed, and per the pre-show rundown the idea was to get back to it for a while in the second half before things kind of inexorably move in the direction of "talking about fried appetizers" in the way they always do on Rohan episodes. But before we could do that, Rohan asked why it is that we still feel compelled to do the sports talk at all when we could very easily justify doing an entire hour on foods we have enjoyed, with a couple Funbag questions stuck on at the end. It wasn't a gag, or anyway it wasn't just a gag. It's a good question.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: New sandwich passport, free coffee Friday, and Ruby Jean’s expands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=872486</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-new-sandwich-passport-free-coffee-friday-and-ruby-jeans-expands/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T20:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Life in KC is pretty delicious. In fact, there is often so much going on that it can be hard to decide where to go and what to try. That’s where I come in.  I’ve curated this weekly list of events, openings, deals, and celebrations to keep you in-the-know. Cheers! *Author’s note: I’m relieved to be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bobby Portis’s Big Suspension Is Ruinous Bullshit]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181984</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bobby-portiss-big-suspension-is-ruinous-bullshit"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T19:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday morning, the NBA announced that Milwaukee Bucks forward Bobby Portis would be suspended for 25 games after testing positive for the pain medication tramadol. The Bucks have 29 games left in the regular season, so they will be without a critical player for an extremely important stretch run in which they will have to fight desperately to stay in front of, somehow, the Detroit Pistons. Portis, in turn, will lose $2.8 million in game checks, so everyone involved is screwed—all over what Portis's representatives are calling an accident involving a substance of questionable performance benefit.
As Portis's agent Mark Bartlestein detailed to ESPN's Shams Charania, Portis takes the very similarly named Toradol to manage pain and inflammation from an elbow contusion he picked up at the start of the season, which explains the mixup. "The tramadol pill he took came from an assistant of his, with a valid prescription for the painkiller, which he mistakenly told Bobby was Toradol," said Bartlestein. Portis does not plan to appeal the suspension.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Victor Wembanyama Is Done For The Season Due To A Blood Clot In His Shoulder]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181993</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/wemby-blood-clot-shoulder"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T19:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Victor Wembanyama will not play for the rest of the regular season due to a deep vein thrombosis in his left shoulder, the Spurs announced Thursday. The team believes that the blood clot is an "isolated condition," per Shams Charania of ESPN.
Wembanyama was on court as recently as Sunday's All-Star Game, where he tried pretty hard, at least within the context of that game. The team said that the condition was discovered upon his return to San Antonio. Wembanyama had been feeling "low energy," and that feeling persisted throughout the All-Star break, which prompted the tests that uncovered the blood clot, according to Sam Amick of The Athletic. The Spurs are optimistic he'll return for the 2025-26 season, Tim MacMahon of ESPN reported, citing a team source.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please Stop Liking My Sport]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181990</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/4-nations-please-stop-liking-my-sport"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T18:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm just trying to watch a hockey game, man. Just trying to do some (friendly!) trash-talking with my Canadian relatives and pals. Leaning in to a (friendly!!!) rivalry with our closest neighbor, and hopefully beating them at their own sport, and, maybe if we're lucky, making Brad Marchand cry. I didn't sign on for Team USA becoming the icebound avatar of Trumpism.
Blame Bill Guerin. On Monday the former NHLer and Team USA GM went on Fox News to plead with the president to attend Thursday's 4 Nations Face-Off final in Boston, a rematch of Saturday's game that saw the U.S. defeat Canada 3-1 in Montreal, before which the American anthem received moderate but notable boos. After that, a whole bunch of people who have never watched a hockey game in their life all of a sudden became huge, or at least loud, Team USA fans because their politics consist solely of supporting things that will upset the people they're told they should hate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Checkmk – IT monitoring platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142687</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/checkmk-it-monitoring-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T17:41:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Checkmk provides comprehensive and specialized solutions for dealing with the very diverse environments within IT infrastructures.
The post Checkmk – IT monitoring platform appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Gordon On Grief, Connection, And His Novel ‘See Friendship’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181840</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jeremy-gordon-on-grief-connection-and-his-novel-see-friendship"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T17:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, I was going through the thousand-odd people I follow on one social media site in an effort to ease my transition onto another, when I noticed that I was still following the accounts of several people who were dead. I tabbed over to their pages, knowing I would not see anything profound or overwhelming, merely the mundane thoughts they'd had in 2013, 2017, or 2024, preserved in amber as long as the platform clings to life. The contrast between ephemerality and permanence was jarring. I didn't know whether it felt more respectful to continue following them or let them go.
This precise, hypermodern dissonance is one of the subjects of Jeremy Gordon's forthcoming novel, See Friendship. Gordon's book tells the story of Jacob, a somewhat adrift digital-media drone who needs to create something substantial to keep his career going. Once he learns that a close high school friend named Seth did not die in his sleep as he was told, but under stranger and more tragic circumstances, he decides to create a narrative podcast investigating the death.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Rubiales Found Guilty Of Sexually Assaulting Jenni Hermoso]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181971</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/luis-rubiales-found-guilty-of-sexually-assaulting-jenni-hermoso"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T16:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The National Court of Spain delivered its verdict today in the trial of former national soccer federation (RFEF) president Luis Rubiales, charged with sexual assault over the unbidden, nonconsensual kiss he planted on the mouth of women's national team star Jenni Hermoso during the medal ceremony after Spain's victory in the 2023 World Cup. Judge José Manuel Fernández-Prieto found Rubiales guilty of the assault charge, but acquitted him of an accompanying charge of coercion concerning his subsequent efforts at pressuring Hermoso into supporting him and downplaying the incident.
Although the prosecution had asked for a prison sentence of one year for the sexual assault charge (and a further 18 months for the coercion), the court opted to impose a fine instead: €20 per day over 18 months, €10,800 in total. Rubiales is also forbidden from contacting Hermoso or coming within 200 meters of her for one year. Also acquitted of coercion were Rubiales's fellow defendants on that charge, former women's national team coach Jorge Vilda and former federation executives Albert Luque and Rubén Rivera.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Black Box Diaries’ Splits A Journalist In Two]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181970</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/black-box-diaries-splits-a-journalist-in-two"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T16:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “black box” in the title of Shiori Itō’s documentary Black Box Diaries, in which the journalist investigates her own sexual assault, essentially refers to the excuse Japan gives for not properly investigating rape cases. “Because it’s in a black box, we’ll never really know what happened,” is what Itō was told, and as she says in the film, “I think that tells everything about our justice system.” But the black box works as a loose metaphor for another kind of unknowability that permeates the documentary, which was recently nominated for an Academy Award and is made up largely of personal video diaries, sound recordings, and a fly-on-the wall footage of the filmmaker as she investigates her case and ultimately writes a memoir about it (Black Box, 2017). Itō explains a few times that her way of surviving is to wrap herself up in work, to treat her case as a journalist would. But in the midst of this singular focus, the filmmaker in a sense puts herself—that is, Itō the survivor—in a black box. In the midst of this grand investigation, she herself remains unexamined. “I realized I haven’t faced myself,” she says at one point. The tension between the two sides of her—Itō the journalist and Itō the survivor—makes Black Box Diaries a kind of stealth dual narrative, one in which it becomes clear that a guilty verdict is not the end, not even close.
The film starts with a trigger warning, and I will defer to it here. Itō’s documentary opens with cherry blossom petals floating along the water beneath a script warning of the content and offering up how she has dealt with triggers in the past: by closing her eyes, by taking a deep breath. The flowers seem like just a pretty aesthetic choice at first, but by the end of the film you learn that these petals themselves became a trigger for Itō, and only later did she realize it was because the crime took place during cherry blossom season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[14 Best Free and Open Source Terminal-Based Image Viewers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=91820</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-terminal-based-image-viewers/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T15:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to view 24-bit high definition images in your terminal? We recommend our favourite terminal-based image viewers.
The post 14 Best Free and Open Source Terminal-Based Image Viewers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Bitter cold will leave soon (THU-2/20)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3830320</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-bitter-cold-will-leave-soon-thu-2-20/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T14:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last night we managed to set two records within 5 minutes of each other. We tanked in the late evening to -4° to set a record low for yesterday's date. Then 5 minutes later, we set a record low for today's date. We kept on dropping to at least -9°, if not -10°, to bottom [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Bitter cold will leave soon (THU-2/20)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3830320</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-bitter-cold-will-leave-soon-thu-2-20/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T14:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today in Kansas City it will be bitterly cold and tonight we'll be sub-zero again, and tomorrow we should moderate back into the 20° range.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Picket – screen color picker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142589</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/picket-screen-color-picker/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T14:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Picket is a screen color picker for Linux with magnifier and custom/user defined formats.
The post Picket – screen color picker appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is Why You Spend So Much Money On Kylian Mbappé]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181934</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-is-why-you-spend-so-much-money-on-kylian-mbappe"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T14:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What do you get the club that has everything? Trophies provide a buzz, as does dominance over another of the so-called titans of European soccer, but nothing gets the juices flowing more than a brand-new superstar. Soccer is a team sport, but few things can tilt the favor in the direction of one team more than a world-beating attacker. Real Madrid already had one such superstar in Vinícius Junior, but Wednesday's second leg against Manchester City demonstrated why one is never enough for this club and its limitless ambition. These must-win games, in the competition Real Madrid has won more than anyone else, are why the club spent multiple summers courting and, eventually, landing Kylian Mbappé.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s1aQb1bgPdQ]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[multiClock – track the time around the world]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142578</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/multiclock-track-time-world/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T11:47:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[multiClock is software that lets you track the current time in major financial centres around the globe.
The post multiClock – track the time around the world appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SME Server – Linux Server distribution for small to medium sized enterprises]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142650</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/sme-server-linux-server-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T08:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SME Server is billed as a complete, secure, stable and versatile Linux Server distribution.
The post SME Server – Linux Server distribution for small to medium sized enterprises appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Muriel Grossmann]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/muriel-grossmann</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/muriel-grossmann"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T08:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Muriel Grossmann, an Austrian saxophonist and composer born in Paris and raised in Vienna.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eloquent – proofreading software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142693</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/eloquent-proofreading-software/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T07:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eloquent is a proofreading tool for English, Spanish, French, German, Portuguese, Polish, Dutch, and more than 20 other languages.
The post Eloquent – proofreading software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redot Engine – multi-platform 2D and 3D game engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142621</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/redot-engine-multi-platform-2d-3d/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T07:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redot Engine lets you create your 2D and 3D games, cross-platform projects, or explore innovative ideas in XR technology.
The post Redot Engine – multi-platform 2D and 3D game engine appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Ross Stripling To Minor League Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=842336</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/royals-sign-ross-stripling-to-minor-league-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T23:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that they have signed right-hander Ross Stripling to a minor league deal. The Excel Sports Management has also been invited to participate in major league spring training. Stripling, 35, is a veteran swingman with plenty of good seasons under his belt. However, he’s coming off two pretty rough campaigns. From 2016 to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AliView – alignment viewer and editor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142460</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/aliview-alignment-viewer-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T23:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AliView is an alignment viewer and editor for bioinformatics that aims to be one of the fastest and most intuitive to use.
The post AliView – alignment viewer and editor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Lydia Tár Of Mantids]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181887</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-lydia-tar-of-mantids"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T23:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a Pal-level subscriber at Defector, you get access to a premium weekday newsletter called The Cipher, which has a recap of the blog day, links to other sites, and extra takes and bits from staffers. You can change your newsletter preferences or upgrade your subscription at the My Account page. Here's a piece from the newsletter archives.
Last Friday, my partner T and I were lucky enough to visit an insect lab at the American Museum of Natural History. The room was hot, humid, and smelled faintly of roach, because, well, there were lots of roaches there. Some were familiar, like the cocktail-sausage shaped Madagascar hissing cockroaches, and others were strange, like some freshly molted cave cockroaches whose newly hardened bodies gleamed the ethereal yellow of a bamboo shoot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QRab – QR code reader]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142476</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/qrab-qr-code-reader/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T21:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[QRab is software that grabs text of QR code from a screen and copies it to the clipboard.
The post QRab – QR code reader appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is The Logical Endpoint Of Zionism]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181787</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-is-the-logical-endpoint-of-zionism"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T21:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you wrote a piece of satire about a Zionist who harmed another Zionist that ended with both parties finding a way to blame a Palestinian, it would feel too pat. Also, the Anti-Defamation League would browbeat you for writing it, in between administering back rubs for Elon Musk. But that's what happened this past weekend in Miami Beach.
Mordechai Brafman, 27, told police that he shot 17 times at a vehicle Saturday night because he thought the two occupants were Palestinian. He also thought he killed them. In reality, they were Israeli tourists and very much alive. Ari Rabi was shot in the shoulder; his father Yaron was grazed on his forearm. Both were taken to the hospital, but not seriously injured. Brafman was charged with two counts of second-degree attempted murder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gossiping With A Robot Is A Real Pain In The Ass]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181762</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/gossiping-with-a-robot-is-a-real-pain-in-the-ass"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T19:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following is adapted from You Didn't Hear This From Me: (Mostly) True Notes on Gossip, by Kelsey McKinney, published on February 11, 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheus – systems and service monitoring system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142684</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/prometheus-systems-service-monitoring-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T18:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheus is an open-source systems monitoring and alerting toolkit. Prometheus collects and stores its metrics as time series data.
The post Prometheus – systems and service monitoring system appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[22 Best Free and Open Source Linux System Profilers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=5639</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/systemprofilers/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T17:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A system profiler is a utility that presents information about the hardware attached to a computer. Here's our verdict.
The post 22 Best Free and Open Source Linux System Profilers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zint – barcode generating solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142472</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/zint-barcode-generating-solution/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T17:47:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Zint project aims to provide a complete cross-platform open source barcode generating solution.
The post Zint – barcode generating solution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s The Yukon Quest Without The Yukon River?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181357</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/whats-the-yukon-quest-without-the-yukon-river"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T17:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the dog teams competing in the 2014 Yukon Quest rested at the race’s halfway point in Dawson City, I drove my Jeep Grand Cherokee out onto the frozen Yukon River. In Dawson, the main townsite sits on one side of the water, but the teams take their mandatory midpoint layover in a public campground on the other. For many years, an ice bridge has been built to connect the two sides—the main town and its more remote west-side suburbs—robust enough for even heavy vehicle traffic. During my coverage of the 2012 and 2013 Quests, I had always driven onto the ice bridge from the sloping boat ramp where a ferry docks in summer. That night in 2014, I did the same. It was very dark, and very, very cold.
I’d befriended a photographer from New York who was in town to cover the race, and she was in my passenger seat as I rolled us out onto the ice. We were partway across when I spotted an irregularity, a patch of darkness that resisted the light of my headlights. There was, I realized, open water lurking not all that far ahead of me. I tried not to panic, tried not to let on that we were both possibly about to die. Holding my breath, I put the Jeep into reverse, and eased back along my own tire tracks until we were on solid ground again. The next day, I learned that the bridge had been rerouted to cross farther upriver.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eva Holland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Artist’s Way’ Week 6: Are We Feeling Abundant?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181691</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-artists-way-week-6-are-we-feeling-abundant"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T17:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining a connection to your creative side can feel idiotic at best and selfish at worst during times like these. We're officially halfway through The Artist's Way, and this week we're definitely negotiating the tension between nudging our creativity and the reality of the world right now.
It would be an understatement to say spirits aren't high right now. Julia Cameron's blithe, prosperity gospel-y point of view may come from a sincere place, but it feels especially grating and out of touch at the moment. Luckily for us having a common annoyance can also be a useful source of inspiration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silence Brings Us Together]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181824</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/silence-brings-us-together"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T16:34:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past month, I've had plenty of days where my brain insists that I need to get the hell off the computer. This command is an inconvenient one when all of your professional responsibilities are on the computer, but as far as mental health struggles go, it's actually one of the better ones, because it pushes me out of my apartment and into the world of friends and movies and art. I always feel better when I'm among more than just myself—trading an impersonal infinite bombardment for a more intentional communication borne of other people's creativity and love.
Tuesday was rough, but I was lucky to have a ticket to the New York Philharmonic that night—a performance conducted by Karina Canellakis and main evented by Claude Debussy's sweeping masterpiece La Mer. I have no education in classical music and rarely listen to it on my own, but I do have a sincere appreciation for the craft of playing an instrument, and beyond that respect I also look forward to engaging with these unfamiliar pieces of music, which force my ears to evaluate a brand new sensory experience without much assistance. Like a detective or an explorer, you get the stimulus, and then you have to decide what to make of it. It comes in a language all its own, and your emotional reaction to the message is yours alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Microsoft Magnifier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142522</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-microsoft-magnifier/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T16:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magnifier is a screen magnifier app intended for visually impaired people to use when running Microsoft Windows. We recommend the best FOSS alternatives.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Microsoft Magnifier appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Bitter cold the focus for now (WED-2/19)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3829237</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-bitter-cold-the-focus-for-now-wed-2-19/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T16:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We shattered the record cold HIGH for yesterday at only 4°. The previous record cold high was 11° set back in 1936]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Bitter cold the focus for now (WED-2/19)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3829237</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-bitter-cold-the-focus-for-now-wed-2-19/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T16:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a snowy day yesterday and sort of a rare day too. We shattered the record cold HIGH for yesterday, only 4°. The previous record cold high was 11° set back in 1936. What though made it more rare, perhaps not unique, but rare, was that through afternoon temperatures just below that, it was [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Weekend With Yoko]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181802</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/my-weekend-with-yoko"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T15:44:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This time last week, I had what I assume to be the average level of knowledge about Yoko Ono and her art: She screamed, she protested, she was a little too present in a project that wasn’t hers, and she continued creating art that advocated for peace even after watching her husband get shot right in front of her. 
But in terms of what that art actually was, I would have had trouble describing or naming any of it. This struck me as a cultural oversight on my part, so I did what anyone would do and signed up to attend a two-day academic and artistic symposium celebrating her work in honor of her 92nd birthday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lindsey Adler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LeBron And Luka Will Have To Make A Weird, Compromised Roster Work]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181766</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lebron-and-luka-will-have-to-make-a-weird-compromised-roster-work"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T14:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a dream scenario for every ESPN producer, basketball-adjacent yapper, and SpringHill Company stakeholder, the Los Angeles Lakers will be the most fascinating team to watch during the NBA's sprint to the playoffs. It's not even close: No other team in the league so dramatically rejiggered itself at the trade deadline, to the point that the Luka Doncic trade feels categorically incomparable to the De'Aaron Fox or Jimmy Butler trades. The Lakers are fifth in the Western Conference at the moment, uncomfortably equipoised between second and eighth, leaving them very little latitude in figuring out how to get their two superstars, who are 15 years apart in age, on the same page.
Most intriguing of all, they have to do it with a hilariously unbalanced team. Days after snagging Doncic, L.A. agreed to trade a cache of future assets for permanently mangled Charlotte Hornets center Mark Williams—only to get him in for a physical and learn that there was apparently a compelling medical reason that he had played only 85 games in three seasons. Whatever the Lakers braintrust saw was bad enough that it compelled them to rescind the trade, which is a huge bummer for Williams and will probably cost him millions of dollars, and leaves the Lakers with a half-formed roster, without a functional two-way big. This is what makes them so fascinating. They have to try and win big, capitalizing on what's turning into a great LeBron campaign, with a totally compromised squad. The Lakers did not intend to have their season serve as evidence in the ongoing trial of whether or not big men have a place in the NBA, though that's now their burden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Hojicha at Goat Hill and biriyani at Moti Mahal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=872106</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-hojicha-at-goat-hill-and-biriyani-at-moti-mahal/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T14:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goat Hill Coffee Soda // Photo By Tiffany Watts Some coffee shop visits are meticulously planned—checking menus, mapping the best seat in the house, and prepping for the perfect Instagram shot. This was not one of those visits. After a satisfying brunch in the Westside neighborhood, we found ourselves wandering with no particular destination in mind. Then, like a casual...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drum Machine – create and play drum beats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142663</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/drum-machine-create-play-drum-beats/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T10:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drum Machine is a modern and intuitive application for creating, playing, and managing drum patterns.
The post Drum Machine – create and play drum beats appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[hascard – minimal command-line utility for reviewing notes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142362</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/hascard-minimal-command-line-utility-reviewing-notes/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T08:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hascard is a minimal command-line utility for reviewing notes. 'Flashcards' can be written in markdown-like syntax.
The post hascard – minimal command-line utility for reviewing notes appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 Best Free and Open Source Terminal Session Recording]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=59276</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-terminal-session-recording/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T08:33:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Console screencast software (also known as terminal recorder) lets you capture your terminal. Here's our verdict.
The post 15 Best Free and Open Source Terminal Session Recording appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Longform Editions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/longform-editions</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/longform-editions"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T08:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Longform Editions, an Australian record label.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KM3NeT]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3053/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3053/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning in Linux: Software Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=102196</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/machine-learning-linux/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T04:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This series looks at practical applications of machine learning from a Linux perspective. We feature free and open source software.
The post Machine Learning in Linux: Software Apps appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[studyFlash – learn flashcards in your terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142365</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/studyflash-learn-flashcards-terminal/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T23:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[studyFlash is a Python application for learning flashcards inside your terminal (for language learning).
The post studyFlash – learn flashcards in your terminal appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mise en Place: Oluwatobi Temitope Oni of Teetasty Foods dishes on auditing, food waste, and crayfish]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=872089</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/mise-en-place-oluwatobi-temitope-oni-of-teetasty-foods-dishes-on-auditing-food-waste-and-crayfish/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T20:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oluwatobi Temitope Oni, or Chef Tee, of Teetasty Foods // Courtesy Oluwatobi Temitope Oni Oluwatobi Temitope Oni, or Chef Tee, opened Teetasty Foods in midtown to expand on her successful catering business. Being among the few to bring Nigerian food to the midwestern masses required a few compromises, like adding hand pies and fries to the menu, but Chef Tee...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[libqrencode – encoding data in a QR Code symbol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142400</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/libqrencode-encoding-data-qr-code-symbol/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T19:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[libqrencode is a fast and compact library for encoding data in a QR Code symbol,
The post libqrencode – encoding data in a QR Code symbol appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stand Down: Phillies Toilet Crisis Abates As Bryce Harper Returns To Spring Training]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181768</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/stand-down-phillies-toilet-crisis-abates-as-bryce-harper-returns-to-spring-training"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T19:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, the Philadelphia Phillies' spring training was dogged with absences, which, while relatively small in number, were significant in total WAR and name recognition value. While Shohei Ohtani was spiritually throwing fourteen pitches in a Dodgers uniform, the Phillies first full squad workout took place without Bryce Harper and Aaron Nola, who were out with food poisoning, and Trea Turner, who was out with a new baby.
The absence of Harper and, by extension, Nola, would not have been particularly notable if not for Harper's new TikTok content, in which he revealed, in an iced vanilla latte–making video, that he and his family preferred drinking raw milk—though in the video he used Maple Hill, which is not only pasteurized but ultra-pasteurized. Here is a series of possibly unrelated facts. Pasteurization is the simple process of treating food products to mild heat in order to neutralize microorganisms and enzymes that cause disease. Raw milk accordingly comes with an increased risk of carrying germs like E. coli and Salmonella. Aaron Nola, who is TikTok-less, has yet to go on record declaring his allegiance, or lack thereof, to raw milk. The actual cause of Harper and Nola's food poisoning is unknown. Harper's TikTok also revealed a knowledge of an involved matcha-making process complete with sieve and whisk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is It OK For Me To Drink Out Of A Cup I Once Pissed In?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181732</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/is-it-ok-for-me-to-drink-out-of-a-cup-i-once-pissed-in"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T17:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about directors ripping off one another, overcooked chicken wings, football, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Examine – system information viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142342</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/examine-system-information-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T17:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Examine is a system information viewer for the COSMIC Desktop. It runs on other desktops. 
The post Examine – system information viewer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gidget The Survivor]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181272</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/gidget-the-survivor"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T16:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kathy Kohner Zuckerman was at home in the Pacific Palisades, her husband Marvin working on the computer in his office, when a neighbor came pounding on their front door.
“Kathy, get out! Get out now!”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Davis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 4 Nations Face-Off Really Might Be The Solution For All-Star Malaise]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181753</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-4-nations-face-off-really-might-be-the-solution-for-all-star-malaise"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T15:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a lot of pressure on Canada and the United States to put on a sparkly, sparky show Thursday night in the 4 Nations Face-Off final. This has as much to do with nationalism as it does with the belief that hockey has figured out the all-star weekend conundrum that basketball has mangled, but you take it the way it hits you.
And let's downplay the nationalism part. Thursday's show almost has to begin with a line brawl during the Canadian national anthem, because that is precisely the bar the two teams set for themselves when they played on Saturday. Nothing sells these days quite like jingoism, the U.S. is back to treating Canada like the unnamed 14th colony, and well, there are going to be Tkachuks on the ice. The hockey could be brilliant on Thursday; it very well might be since most of the world's best players this time around are Canadians or Americans. But Saturday also gave us three serious fights in the game's first nine seconds, which got the attention of even hockey arrivistes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning in Linux: Serge – web interface for chatting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142561</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/machine-learning-linux-serge-web-interface-chatting/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T15:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serge is a chat interface crafted with LLaMA for running GGUF models.
The post Machine Learning in Linux: Serge – web interface for chatting appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[tui-deck – TUI frontend for Nextcloud Deck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142356</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tui-deck-tui-frontend-nextcloud-deck/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T14:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tui-deck is a TUI frontend for Nextcloud Deck app written in GO using the Rich Interactive Widgets for Terminal UIs.
The post tui-deck – TUI frontend for Nextcloud Deck appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is What We Came For]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181710</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/4-nations-usa-canada-this-is-what-we-came-for"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T14:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a good and strange time to be a hockey fan. It's a perfect storm: the 4 Nations Face-Off going far beyond expectations, the U.S. and Canada engaged in uncustomary and very stupid geopolitical beef, the NBA having existential conniptions over its disastrous all-star game. The numbers back up the anecdotal evidence that casual fans are paying attention to the tournament in a way they haven't acknowledged hockey in years; I've been hearing from non-fan friends about that bellicose USA-Canada game this weekend. With this wider attention inevitably comes getting caught up in the culture wars. Pick your poison—hockey can be used to support any pet take, no matter how deluded or xenophobic. It's enough to invert the classic plea: Please don't like my sport. 
But that's the price of popularity. And if Thursday night's U.S. vs. Canada winner-take-all final of the first best-on-best tournament in a decade attracts some of the "wrong" type of audience members, that's not my problem, or yours. We get to enjoy two incredible hockey teams who genuinely dislike each other settling things on the ice. Nothing but pride and bragging rights will actually be on the line, and that's more than enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Some extra snow + too much cold  (TUE-2/18)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3828002</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-some-extra-snow-too-much-cold-tue-2-18/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T14:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we're starting with generally cloudy conditions with some snow showers. The big story this morning is the -20° wind chills that have spread through the region.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WADA’s Doping Ban Settlement With Jannik Sinner Creates More Questions Than Answers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=181665</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/wadas-doping-ban-settlement-with-jannik-sinner-creates-more-questions-than-answers"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T14:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most puzzling part of the Jannik Sinner's doping saga might be its conclusion. The World Anti-Doping Agency (WADA) announced over the weekend that it had reached a settlement with the top-ranked player in men's tennis. WADA would no longer be moving forward with its appeal of a previous "no fault or negligence" ruling reached by a tennis-specific anti-doping authority, which, had it been successful, could have carried a ban of one to two years. Instead, WADA and Sinner agreed to a settlement: He would accept a three-month suspension, starting Feb. 9 to May 4, a span in which he would miss no major tournaments on the tour.
There has been a lot of conspiratorial chatter about this case, much of it from fellow players, much of it wildly ill-informed (with one exception). I had my own narrower misgivings. Sinner's story involved a somewhat convoluted series of mishaps: His trainer supplied a physiotherapist with an over-the-counter topical clostebol spray for a finger cut, then said spray got into Sinner's body when the physio massaged the player's sore-covered dermatitic skin. That was meant to explain how metabolites of clostebol were detected in two samples collected from Sinner eight days apart last March. But how could experienced staffers whose critical job function was to keep prohibited substances out of their employer's body do something this careless? Why would clostebol spray ever be in the vicinity of a work trip? Why were those staffers retained for months after this catastrophic error?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GSConnect – complete implementation of KDE Connect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=142494</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gsconnect-complete-implementation-kde-connect/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T10:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GSConnect is a complete implementation of KDE Connect, especially for GNOME Shell with Nautilus, Chrome, and Firefox integration. 
The post GSConnect – complete implementation of KDE Connect appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>