<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-12-31T14:13:50.075Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible-Coconut – Linux distro dedicated to accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140288</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/accessible-coconut-linux-distro-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T11:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible-Coconut (AC) is a community driven Linux distribution which is completely accessible for persons with visual impairments.
The post Accessible-Coconut – Linux distro dedicated to accessibility appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[transgender – minimalistic terminal file explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140268</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/transgender-minimalistic-terminal-file-explorer/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T08:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[transgender is a minimalistic TUI file explorer with minimal dependencies, written by a Ranger hater.
The post transgender – minimalistic terminal file explorer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[zpotify – CLI for controlling Spotify playback]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140275</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/zpotify-cli-spotify/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T06:41:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[zpotify is a CLI for controlling Spotify playback and much more.
The post zpotify – CLI for controlling Spotify playback appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SrTemplate – string template system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140264</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/srtemplate-string-template-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T05:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mr. strings template (SrTemplate) is a library that allows you to render just text templates. It's written in Rust.
The post SrTemplate – string template system appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Things We Ate In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177408</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-best-things-we-ate-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T18:36:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is what the Defector staff enjoyed eating in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Defector Pals Attempt ‘The Artist’s Way’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176828</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/your-defector-pals-attempt-the-artists-way"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T18:10:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you harbor secret creative dreams for the new year? Do you miss the way it felt to make things just for the sake of it, without any care for how good or commercially viable it was? Maybe you’ve never considered yourself an artist, but there’s a tinge of discontent you can’t escape in your daily life.
I have great news for you: Some Defector staffers are going to do The Artist’s Way together, and we’d love for you to join us.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Microsoft Disk Cleanup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140137</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-microsoft-disk-cleanup/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T18:06:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Disk Cleanup is a computer maintenance utility designed to free up disk space. We recommend the best free and open source alternatives.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Microsoft Disk Cleanup appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Wrestling Matches I Liked In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=175972</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/some-wrestling-matches-i-liked-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T17:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a concerning year. WWE continued to enlarge and enrich itself even as it failed to honestly reckon with the legacy of Vince McMahon. AEW—once an avatar of hope and change—took a creative and cultural nosedive. The Japanese scene is economically hamstrung and can't keep its top talents from moving to the States. It all combined for perhaps the worst non-COVID year for a wrestling fan since the widespread adoption of internet streaming. I look around and I crave a spark—an inspiring rivalry like Kobashi-Misawa, Punk-Joe, or Omega-Okada that lights a better path forward.
With that pessimism in mind, I picked 10 matches from 10 promotions this year, instead of the 15 I struggled to narrow down in 2022 and 2023. But I liked them, and I think you should check them out, because I got out of them what I still get out of great wrestling: excitement, astonishment, joy. Here they are, in chronological order:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Dec. 30: Out Of Office (Themeless)]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177258</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-dec-30-out-of-office-themeless"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T16:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time to to wrap up the month with a challenging themeless. Keep an eye out for tricky clues and fun wordplay. This puzzle was constructed by Evan Mulvihill, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Evan is a cruciverbalist living in San Francisco. His crosswords have been published by the Wall Street Journal and Los Angeles Times, and will be appearing in the New York Times sometime in the next year or two. When he's not working as a pharmacist at Zuckerberg San Francisco General Hospital, he enjoys attending gay ski weeks, "doing it live," and creating Spotify playlists with titles like "Extra Chill Vibes ✨ONLY✨." He puts out crosswords that attempt to slap, chew, tear, and eat, on his blog FlossWords. Collab? 
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Fancy Little Mocktail Was Missing More Than Booze]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=175821</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/my-fancy-little-mocktail-was-missing-more-than-booze"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T15:19:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I stopped drinking alcohol in June 2023, a decision that was long overdue and has since improved my life unconditionally—congratulations to me! And yet stopping drinking did in no way quench my urge to drink, because that's not how addiction works. In fact, I felt thirstier than ever and fiending for something to glug at a bar or a house party and pretend I was still a younger, more foolish version of myself. So I turned to mocktails, because that's what was increasingly advertised on the menus and on the subways and in a slew of articles and books. People were paying $14 for a Phony Negroni® at the shadowy pizza place down the street, so why shouldn't I?
My first foray in mocktails happened in 2016, during a six-month dry spell when I was on a course of the acne drug Accutane. The dive bars I went to with friends didn't yet have a trendy fleet of non-alcoholic drinks, and I was mostly too scared to make a bartender feel put upon by asking for an off-the-menu mocktail. (I did try this once in an attempt to flirt with the bartender and promptly received a Shirley Temple, which I didn't not enjoy but also made me feel like a child with no game.) Sodas were a no-go because of the caffeine, and plain seltzer made me wonder if bubbles were worth paying up to $3 for water. After some trial and error, I settled on a DIY mocktail I called spicy drink: I'd order seltzer with pineapple juice and douse it with hot sauce that I carried in my bag. The resulting concoction was sweet and sizzly, vaguely reminiscent of some of my favorite tequila drinks, although I would never serve it to anyone else. I made it work with spicy drink because I knew in a few months I'd be back in the saddle, reunited with my beloved tequila soda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Cold...colder...coldest (MON-12/30)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3774971</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-cold-colder-coldest-mon-12-30/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T15:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today will likely be the last mildish day for the next couple of weeks at least (although Thursday may not be too bad) as a significant pattern shift will be starting and ushering in likely the cold air we've seen around these parts since last January. With the cold, chances of snow with be showing [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Best Free and Open Source JavaScript-Based Web Content Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=91754</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-javascript-web-content-management-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T06:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are our favorite JavaScript-based web content management systems. They are all free and open source software.
The post 6 Best Free and Open Source JavaScript-Based Web Content Management Systems appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gg – TUI for small offline games]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140252</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gg-tui-small-offline-games/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T06:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[gg is a small collection of games that you can play in your terminal.
The post gg – TUI for small offline games appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Capsule Instructions]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3031/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3031/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers Incapable Of Throwing Even One Touchdown Pass]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177374</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/aaron-rodgers-incapable-of-throwing-even-one-touchdown-pass"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T23:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been said many times before, across many different eras, but that doesn't make it any less true: The New York Jets always find new ways to humiliate themselves. Regardless of the circumstances, they really can take any setup and provide it with a proper punchline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Gumbel Kept It All In Perspective]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177365</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/greg-gumbel-kept-it-all-in-perspective"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T23:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Greg Gumbel was named host of the CBS NFL pregame show in 1990, he was viewed as a departure for the network. Brent Musberger had been host of The NFL Today for the past 15 years, and a lot of people were tired of his shtick. He dominated the show, and much of the network's sports coverage. Reporters wondered whether Gumbel, who had previously called NFL games and hosted NCAA men’s basketball tournament coverage for CBS, would be another preempting pregame personality.
He wasn’t, instead guiding the show in a lower key. Gumbel hosted in the studio with Terry Bradshaw, while Lesley Visser and Pat O’Brien handled features. The new host wanted to be the conductor, not the star. “If Terry stars on that show,” Gumbel told the AP right before starting, “then I’ll have done my job.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL Schedule Creep Is Getting Out Of Control]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177346</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nfl-schedule-creep-is-getting-out-of-control"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T20:02:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Christmas showcase, the Black Friday game, the doubled-up Monday Night Football experience, the possibility of RedZone introducing commercials—the NFL realized that it didn't have to stick to three days per week, and it could be as ubiquitous and greedy as it wants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[screenFetch – Bash information tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140247</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/screenfetch-bash-information-tool/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T19:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[screenFetch is a handy Bash script that can be used to generate one of those nifty terminal theme information and ASCII distribution logos.
The post screenFetch – Bash information tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PakOS – Debian-based Linux distribution from Pakistan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140222</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pakos-debian-based-linux-distribution-pakistan/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T18:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PakOS is a Debian-based Linux distribution which bills itself as reasonably secure. It's designed to be light on resources. 
The post PakOS – Debian-based Linux distribution from Pakistan appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to popular CLI tools: tar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=105947</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alternatives-popular-cli-tools-tar/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T17:56:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We showcase free and open source alternatives to tar, the most widely used archiving utility in Linux systems.
The post Alternatives to popular CLI tools: tar appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magnus Carlsen Quits Chess Tournament Over Jeans Violation]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177351</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/magnus-carlsen-quits-chess-tournament-over-jeans-violation"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T17:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This past Friday, Magnus Carlsen left his lunch meeting and headed to the second day of the World Rapid Chess Championship. He said he changed beforehand, putting on a blazer over a button-front shirt. He changed his shoes, too. Crucially, he didn’t change out of the jeans he was wearing.
Carlsen told the Chess YouTube show Take Take Take that he was in a rush to make it to the tournament. He got there in time, but his pants got him into trouble: Jeans are not allowed, per the International Chess Federation's dress code. FIDE said in a statement later that jeans are “explicitly prohibited under long-standing regulations for this event,” adding that the rules are “designed to ensure professionalism and fairness for all participants.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cam Ward Tarnishes The Sanctity Of Bowl Game Sponsored By Toaster Pastry]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177334</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cam-ward-tarnishes-the-sanctity-of-bowl-game-sponsored-by-toaster-pastry"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T14:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Select portions of the college football world were outraged—big shock there—by Miami quarterback Cam Ward's decision to play only the first half of Saturday's bowl game sponsored by a toaster pastry. In this exhibition, the Hurricanes ended up losing to Iowa State, 42-41.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fex – command-line file explorer prioritizing quick navigation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140108</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/fex-command-line-file-explorer-prioritizing-quick-navigation/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T10:22:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[fex is a command-line file explorer inspired by Vim, exa and fzf, built with quick exploration and navigation in mind.
The post fex – command-line file explorer prioritizing quick navigation appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[18 Best Free and Open Source Personal Finance Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=83790</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-personal-finance-software/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T08:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We focus on the best personal finance software for Linux. We only feature open source goodness.
The post 18 Best Free and Open Source Personal Finance Software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[stagen – wlroots-based wayland compositor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140193</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/stagen-wlroots-based-wayland-compositor/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T08:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[stagen is a simple experimental wlroots-based wayland compositor.
The post stagen – wlroots-based wayland compositor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Free and Open Source non-GTK non-Qt File Managers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=127276</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-non-gtk-non-qt-file-managers/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T06:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many graphical non-Qt and non-Gtk file managers available. This article examines 11 such file managers.
The post 11 Best Free and Open Source non-GTK non-Qt File Managers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[tere – terminal file explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140106</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tere-terminal-file-explorer/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T23:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tere is a terminal file explorer. It is a faster alternative to using cd and ls to browse folders in your terminal.
The post tere – terminal file explorer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12 Best Free and Open Source Terminal String Styling Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140124</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-terminal-string-styling-tools/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T16:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend developers appreciate the importance of UI design as it’s a critical part of developing an app. With terminal-based tools, visual design might not be foremost in a developer’s mind. While the design is constrained, it’s still important to communicate
The post 12 Best Free and Open Source Terminal String Styling Tools appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TreeTag – personal data manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140118</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/treetag-personal-data-manager/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T12:39:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TreeTag is a personal data manager. It stores information in a hierarchy and automatically positions items in the tree based on field values
The post TreeTag – personal data manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ansi-colors – add ANSI colors to terminal text]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140112</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ansi-colors-add-ansi-colors-terminal-text/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T07:15:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ansi-colors is a fast Node.js library for terminal styling. It's billed as a more performant drop-in replacement for chalk, with no dependencies.
The post ansi-colors – add ANSI colors to terminal text appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treemacs – tree layout file explorer for Emacs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140102</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/treemacs-tree-layout-file-explorer-emacs/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T05:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Treemacs is a file and project explorer similar to NeoTree or vim’s NerdTree, but largely inspired by the Project Explorer in Eclipse. 
The post Treemacs – tree layout file explorer for Emacs appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five KC places to ring in the New Year that aren’t focused on alcohol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866258</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/five-kc-places-to-ring-in-the-new-year-that-arent-focused-on-alcohol/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T22:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Uptown Theater Cheers to surviving 2024! Raise a glass of champagne or sparkling white grape juice. Everything goes here in KC, but some places are better than others for those who are looking to avoid an alcohol-focused party scene. Here are our top picks (that aren’t sold out) for ringing in the New Year with more entertainment or food...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Feels So Over In Sacramento]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177287</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/it-feels-so-over-in-sacramento"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T20:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sacramento Kings played and lost what threatens to be the last meaningful basketball game of their season on Thursday night. There is plenty of evidence to suggest that it may also have been the last meaningful basketball game they play in the years to come.
As franchise-breaking losses go, this one was at least a bang, not a whimper. The Kings hosted a hot Pistons team in the midst of an undefeated West Coast road trip, and despite their lone functional big man Domantas Sabonis missing the game with an illness, they built a double-digit lead early in the second quarter and steadily managed it for two quarters. This is what theoretically superior teams do at home against theoretically inferior ones, a dynamic which De'Aaron Fox's poor first half underscored. Down 10 with 3:36 left, Detroit began to mount a fierce resistance, which was enough for the Kings to totally clam up and stop playing anything resembling team basketball.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deadbeat Club Scrambling To Keep Players It Never Should Have Acquired]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177293</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/deadbeat-club-scrambling-to-keep-players-it-never-should-have-acquired"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T17:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When F.C. Barcelona acquired Dani Olmo from RB Leipzig back in August, it did so despite clearly not being anywhere close to able to afford Olmo's salary under La Liga's Financial Fair Play rules, which regulate each club's spending relative to its earnings and debts each season, and which Barcelona has been wrestling with for years as a result of years upon years of hideous mismanagement. Olmo wound up missing Barça's first couple of 2024 La Liga matches because the club couldn't register his salary with the league.
Good—or anyway, "good"—fortune came in the form of an Achilles tendon injury to trusty center back Andreas Christensen: In the event of an injury that will keep a given player out for four months or longer, La Liga rules permit a team to spend (and register) up to 80 percent of that player's salary for the purpose of filling the hole in the squad. With Christensen out, Barça got the space it needed to register Olmo, plus young attacker Pau Víctor—but only through the end of December. The club would have until then to benefit from Olmo's and Víctor's services; if by then it hadn't drummed up the additional income or savings it would need in order to extend their registrations through the end of the season, the registrations would expire on Jan. 1, rendering the two players unable to participate in La Liga matches and giving the club until the end of the January transfer window to get them re-registered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revisiting a ritual: Absente absinthe leans in on showmanship]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866226</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/revisiting-a-ritual-absente-absinthe-leans-in-on-showmanship/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T17:34:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grande Absente absinthe // Photo by Jordan Baranowski In the world of spirits, absinthe tends to sit in a bit of a mythical spot. It conjures images of tortured European artists like Vincent Van Gogh and Oscar Wilde, sipping hallucinogenic alcohol while creating their artistic masterpieces. For some, their only exposure to the uniquely-colored spirit is Nicole Kidman and Ewan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Baranowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Nosferatu’ Keeps You Waiting And Waiting]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177303</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nosferatu-keeps-you-waiting-and-waiting"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T16:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By the time Bram Stoker died in 1912, Dracula remained his most successful and lucrative creation, a crude way of looking at a writer’s corpus but, in this case, informative of what financial circumstances his widow, Florence, was left in and how the property of Dracula was handled. As executor of Stoker’s estate, Florence had sole authorization over Dracula’s usage in any medium, whether stage plays or nascent motion pictures. In 1921, F. W. Murnau and Prana Films, cofounded by producer Albin Grau, had completed a complicated shoot of a German film titled Nosferatu (the production could only utilize one camera, which meant there was only a single negative to work with), a dramatically stark reinterpretation of Dracula released to little fanfare.
Neither Murnau nor Prana sought permission to use elements from Stoker’s most famous novel from Florence, a concern made less straightforward by the regional differences in copyright law but one that Stoker’s widow nonetheless viewed as flagrant plagiarism. Florence, along with the British Society of Authors, soon launched a legal campaign to sue Prana Films for damages. Ultimately, Prana filed for bankruptcy and, in lieu of being able to pay restitution to Florence, relinquished Nosferatu’s rights and all copies of the film to the Stoker estate. The fiasco took about three years and by 1925, Nosferatu’s market value had fallen so steeply that Florence set about trying to destroy as many existing prints of the film as possible. Five years later, Universal bought the rights to Dracula from Florence and reportedly also bought an existing American print of Nosferatu that they then studied for the 1931 adaptation of the novel starring Bela Lugosi. Of course, extant copies of Nosferatu survived in other countries, prominently in France and the U.S., these and other copies shown in revivals and eventually restored throughout the years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Worst Things We Bought In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177210</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-worst-things-we-bought-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T15:53:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These were the worst purchases by the Defector staff in 2024.
Two Subscriptions To Paramount Plus]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: At least it's mild out there! (FRI-12/27)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3773230</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-at-least-its-mild-out-there-fri-12-27/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T14:44:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're in a lather rinse repeat scenario again today as some areas are starting with some fog, while others have some light rain or heavy drizzle falling. All areas though are running about 30° above average to start the day which is rather remarkable for this time of the year. Our low this morning has [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Buy A Sweater That Doesn’t Suck]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176452</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-to-buy-a-sweater-that-doesnt-suck"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T14:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though neither of us were alive during Jimmy Carter’s presidency, when the weather gets cold, my partner and I love to recite to each other in cartoonish voices, “Do what I do: wear a sweater!” I’m not actually sure if Carter ever said these exact words (I’m not finding it in the transcript of his 1977 sweater speech), but they are a potent reminder: In the cold months, your clothes are meant to keep you warm. 
Last year, a piece by Amanda Mull set off weeks of discourse about why sweaters are such poor quality these days. For most of my life, I wore garbage sweaters that barely kept me warm. I’m sure you know this experience, too. The affordable, accessible options are generally so terrible that it’s possible that the majority of sweaters many of us have worn in our lives have been acrylic or some other synthetic material. It's likely many people don’t know how nice and warm it feels to wear a sweater made from materials that aren't garbage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vim-tree – use tree for quick navigation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140092</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/vim-tree-quick-navigation/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T13:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vim-tree integrates good old tree into Vim and Nvim for all common operating systems. 
The post vim-tree – use tree for quick navigation appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12 Best Free and Open Source TypeScript-Based Web Content Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=97150</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-typescript-based-web-content-management-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are our favorite TypeScript-based web content management systems. They are all free and open source software.
The post 12 Best Free and Open Source TypeScript-Based Web Content Management Systems appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lasering Incidents]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3030/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3030/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>