<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-01-11T10:14:43.308Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fast Reader – read text quickly and effectively]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140777</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/fast-reader-read-text-quickly-effectively/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-11T08:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fast Reader is a versatile application designed to assist users in reading text swiftly and effectively.
The post Fast Reader – read text quickly and effectively appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Free and Open Source Graphical Download Managers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=124412</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-graphical-download-managers/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-11T06:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A download manager is a type of software that manages the downloading of files from the Internet.
The post 11 Best Free and Open Source Graphical Download Managers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File Shredder – file deletion software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140796</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/file-shredder-file-deletion-software/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T20:33:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File Shredder is a file deletion program designed to permanently remove sensitive files from your computer.
The post File Shredder – file deletion software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Injury Luck Is All About Timing]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178270</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/injury-luck-is-all-about-timing"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T18:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Watching the Orlando Magic lose to the Minnesota Timberwolves on Thursday, in the Magic's final game without their best player, I was reminded of the spring of 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AnduinOS – Debian-based Linux operating system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140751</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/anduinos-debian-based-linux-operating-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T18:40:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AnduinOS is a custom Debian-based Linux distribution that aims to facilitate developers transitioning from Windows to Ubuntu.
The post AnduinOS – Debian-based Linux operating system appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Puzzling Time]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178254</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-puzzling-time"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T18:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A part of being home for the holidays is trying to find something to do in the New Jersey suburbs, especially as someone who despises driving but, to be very clear, has developed much more confidence in driving alone. After a couple of weeks of on-the-town reporting and extensive testing of all available entertainment options, I can officially confirm: The best form of entertainment is solving jigsaw puzzles at the municipal library.
I have visited two local libraries, and this is enough of a sample size to conclude that all suburban libraries must have a communal puzzling–type situation. One (my town's library) had a communal puzzle table with the pieces laid down flat, and another (the neighboring town's library) had a sort of inclined board covered in felt that wooden puzzle pieces stuck to—kinder on the neck but more difficult to slide large chunks of puzzle about. Anyone can work on the puzzle. Once the puzzle is completed, it is swapped out with a new one, which means a theoretically infinite supply of free puzzles. Sounds like a bargain to me!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week In Maligned Little Fish]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178218</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-week-in-maligned-little-fish"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T17:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two species of tiny, drab, and otherwise forgettable fish—the blotchy brown snail darter and the pale, silvery delta smelt—will never meet in real life. The snail darter swims in rivers and streams in America's South and the delta smelt can only be found in a single estuary in California. But the fish have more in common than you might think. Both snail darters and delta smelt are freshwater fish that are native to the U.S. Both species have been listed as endangered at some point and subsequently become the lodestar of a controversial conservation battle. And both fish are in the news this week.
These two species collided in the news for seemingly different reasons—the darter starred in a new paper arguing it is actually not a distinct species, and the smelt was unlucky enough to become the subject of a tenuously coherent response from Donald Trump to a question about the L.A. wildfires. Two odd little fish making national headlines in one week might seem like a coincidence, but these fish are more entangled than they'll ever know. (How could they know? They're fish.) They tell a story about the process of science and conservation, and how blameless species become scapegoats for quagmires of our own making.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Does The NFL Hate London So Much?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178257</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-does-the-nfl-hate-london-so-much"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T16:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no news in England that does not have some microscopic yet tangential link to Prince Harry and Meghan Markle, and while America has helped fuel that machine by taking the poor semi-orphaned waifs in to see how much Netflix money they could steal, it had not yet occurred to anyone that we might be just as sick of their story as the Brits are.
Well, shots fired back, kids. Roger Goodell, in his ancillary role as international agent-provocateur, has delivered unto London its 2025 football ambassadors, and he could not have chosen them with a more malicious eye. They are the Jacksonville Jaguars, the perennial colonial finger in the eye, the New York Jets, who may be trying to set up Brick Johnson for a future peerage but otherwise have no business being exported anywhere beyond Moonachie, and the Cleveland Browns, the most unpleasant team the league can offer. Jags, Jets, and Brownies are the buzzkill of this century, and they will all be ordered to infect Tottenham and Wembley Stadiums this coming fall in what under normal circumstances would be considered an act of war.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Of MLB Is Chasing Roki Sasaki]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178188</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/all-of-mlb-is-chasing-roki-sasaki"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T15:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DALLAS — I’m a punk who’s been in many mosh pits in my lifetime. Never have I experienced a media scrum that felt more like a mosh pit than the one surrounding Roki Sasaki’s agent Joel Wolfe at MLB’s Winter Meetings. The presser moved quickly, not just in terms of the brisk cadence of questions and answers but physically moved—from a corner in the Hilton Anatole’s Grand Ballroom, which acted as the media workroom, onto the stage with the podium and the MLB logo backdrop. Journalists followed Wolfe until they were crowding around the stage like they were at a basement show.
Wolfe addressed the scrum with a microphone that didn’t always work—adding to the DIY show feel, come to think of it—while fielding but not quite answering questions about where the most interesting international free agent in years would be likely to sign. That, honestly, is where the comparison to a punk show ends. Everything else is pure transactional offseason baseball, with a generous side order of rules—all of it just about the least punk thing imaginable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jen Ramos Eisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: One more system over the weekend (FRI-1/10)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3786114</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-one-more-system-over-the-weekend-fri-1-10/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T15:23:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is another snow system coming Kansas City's way Saturday night. It's a cold front that will create a line of snow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[wxDownload Fast – download manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140764</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/wxdownload-fast-download-manager/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T15:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[wxDownload Fast is a multithreaded download manager written using wxWidgets and Aria2. This is written in C++.
The post wxDownload Fast – download manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raise your glass: Kansas City’s ultimate zero-proof celebration is happening this weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866881</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/raise-your-glass-kansas-citys-ultimate-zero-proof-celebration-is-happening-this-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T15:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pitch archive photo of Dry Vibes 2023 // photo by Samantha Levi Sip Steady, a zero-proof creative agency, aims to redefine the way we celebrate. Dry Vibes: A Zero Proof Experience will be held on January 12 at The Station by 28 Event Space. For the third year, this event will showcase the art socializing without a single drop of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notre Dame Derangement Syndrome Is Real]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178245</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/notre-dame-derangement-syndrome-is-real"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T14:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are now assured of 10 more days of Notre Dame in our faces, and ridiculously, that means another 10 days of hearing how the Irish not being tied to a conference like all the poor schools is an unfair advantage. I mean, what other program has a kicker with a chiropractor on call to come in every week and keep his bones aligned?
The kicker in question, Mitch Jeter, hit a 41-yard field goal with 12 seconds left to give the Irish a 27-24 victory in a highly disjointed game that for three quarters looked like it should have been played in a rainstorm. The chiropractor in question, Andrew Jeter, is his dad, who flew in each week to work on his son's directionally challenged leg after a hip injury. The conferences that Notre Dame are not in, the story goes, mean they don't have to share their playoff payoff with anyone else, giving them a leg up to keep Jeter's leg up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Tracker – simple time-tracker program for GNOME]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140757</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/time-tracker-simple-time-tracker-program-gnome/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T12:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time Tracker is a simple time-tracker program for GNOME. This software is written in JavaScript.
The post Time Tracker – simple time-tracker program for GNOME appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to popular CLI tools: Wget]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=113934</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alternatives-popular-cli-tools-wget/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T10:09:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We spotlight alternatives tools to Wget, a non-interactive network downloader.
The post Alternatives to popular CLI tools: Wget appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new and exciting for KC Restaurant Week 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2025-01-10/kc-restaurant-week-2025-deals-where-to-eat-kansas-city</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2025-01-10/kc-restaurant-week-2025-deals-where-to-eat-kansas-city"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City Restaurant Week, which runs this year from Jan. 10-19, will give local diners a chance to get out of the house after the blizzard and explore the city's diverse eateries — with special menus and deals. A portion of Restaurant Week proceeds will also support local charity House of Hope.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kraske, Josh Marvine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bosnian bakery hidden in Kansas City's Northland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/podcast/kansas-city-today/2025-01-10/a-bosnian-bakery-hidden-in-kansas-citys-northland</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/podcast/kansas-city-today/2025-01-10/a-bosnian-bakery-hidden-in-kansas-citys-northland"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Step inside the tiny A-frame cottage where local bakery Burek and Cake makes fresh Bosnian baked goods on the daily — and always with love. Owner Fatina Hodzic opened it two years ago and already has a slate of regulars, whom she greets by name.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nomin Ujiyediin, Olivia Hewitt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shy One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/shy-one</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/shy-one"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T08:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Friday so we’re listening to something more upbeat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Free and Open Source Web Hosting Control Panels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=5309</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/webhostingcontrolpanels/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T07:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web hosting control panels offer an attractive solution to developers and designers that host multiple web sites on virtual private servers and dedicated servers.
The post 11 Best Free and Open Source Web Hosting Control Panels appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TUXEDO OS – Ubuntu-based Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140740</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tuxedo-os-ubuntu-based-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T07:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TUXEDO OS is a Linux distribution that's based on Ubuntu / Kubuntu.
The post TUXEDO OS – Ubuntu-based Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Free and Open Source Replacements for ls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=70404</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-replacements-ls/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T06:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When invoked without any arguments, ls lists the files in the current working directory. We recommend some great replacements.
The post 11 Best Free and Open Source Replacements for ls appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chess Zoo]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3036/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3036/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elive – Debian-based desktop Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140674</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/elive-debian-based-desktop-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T23:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elive is a Debian-based distribution featuring the Enlightenment window manager.
The post Elive – Debian-based desktop Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nolan Arenado Reportedly Less Likely To Be Traded]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=837434</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/01/nolan-arenado-trade-rumors-red-sox-royals-cardinals.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T22:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nolan Arenado saga has been perhaps the main storyline of the Cardinals’ offseason. As the club looks to scale back payroll and open up playing time for younger players (Nolan Gorman, in particular), Arenado has become one of the most prominent trade candidates in the sport. His full no-trade clause, downturn at the plate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Los Angeles Is A Football Town, With Diana Moskovitz]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178039</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/los-angeles-is-a-football-town-with-diana-moskovitz"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T20:12:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While The Distraction is allowed to get as heavy as we want, the idea is mostly to do something goofy or stupid. I reminded myself of that while listening to this week's episode, in which our own Diana Moskovitz breaks down the first weekend of the NFL playoff slate from her home in Los Angeles. We recorded it Tuesday morning, in what turned out to be the last remotely normal-seeming moments of the week in that region. It's a fun episode, but because things have gotten very bad in Los Angeles in the days since we recorded, and because of the extent to which that reality is absent from the episode ... well, this was a good opportunity for me to remind myself that the name of the podcast is The Distraction, and then to say it until I believed it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: Restaurant closures and openings, local Dry January options, and more food news]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866865</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-restaurant-closures-and-openings-local-dry-january-options-and-more-food-news/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T20:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Life in KC is pretty delicious. In fact, there is often so much going on that it can be hard to decide where to go and what to try. That’s where I come in.  I’ve curated this weekly list of events, openings, deals, and celebrations to keep you in-the-know. Cheers! Something New Kansas City Restaurant Week:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ECT – fast and effective C++ file optimizer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140642</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ect-fast-effective-file-optimizer/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T19:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient Compression Tool (or ECT) is a C++ file optimizer. It supports PNG, JPEG, GZIP and ZIP files.
The post ECT – fast and effective C++ file optimizer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evan Mobley Is The Real Thing]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178172</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/evan-mobley-is-the-real-thing"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T18:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any time you get Cleveland and Oklahoma City into the first sentence of your blog, you can be reasonably sure that no one from either coast of North America will read it all the way to the end. The pressure's off! I can fill this blog with anything I like! Therefore I am choosing to spend the next several paragraphs sermonizing about the divine skills of Cleveland big man Evan Mobley. Mobley and the Cavaliers prevailed Wednesday night over the visiting Thunder, in a matchup of teams carrying combined 25-game active win streaks. This was a great game, from beginning to end, and if you ignored it because you consider these to be flyover teams, you deserve to feel bad this morning.
Mobley was incredible. Cavaliers head coach Kenny Atkinson is putting him everywhere on the floor and using him in as many ways as possible. The Cavaliers run normal-ish stuff to get the ball moving toward the basket, but Mobley's particular gifts make all the actions a tick or two more dangerous than they'd be if you replaced him with a normal-ish NBA big man. Consider the dribble handoff, or DHO. It's a staple of the modern game, but NBA defenses are getting better at defending it, so that it often feels less like a powerful go-to and more like some shit your team does by lazy habit, or from lack of any better ideas. In a DHO, the ball is passed to a big man up the floor, near the free-throw line. Guards and shooters whir around the arc; the big man takes a hard dribble or two parallel to the free-throw line and hands the ball off to one of his buds, who pulls a sprinting defender into a collision with the big man, and is thus freed to slice down the middle of the floor. All the quick-moving action around the perimeter creates secondary opportunities, but this is the basic action: a big guy lumbering sideways and punching the ball into the tummy of a teammate while absorbing into his own tummy his teammate's defender.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dahliaOS – intuitive Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140717</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/dahliaos-intuitive-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T17:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dahliaOS is a Linux distribution with a modern user interface, multitasking, advanced networking, security features and respectful privacy.
The post dahliaOS – intuitive Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Must Free Joe Burrow]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178155</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/we-must-free-joe-burrow"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T17:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
The advent of a 14-team playoff field in the NFL has forever neutered the possibility that a deserving team might not make it into the bracket. Not that you could make such arguments convincingly before; it’s not like I’m shedding tears for Matt Cassel and the 2008 Patriots. But a smaller field made the idea of bubble teams just plausible enough for Stephen A. Smith to make his best “Excuse me?!” face whenever a boring-ass 10-win team somehow got excluded. Any team that misses the playoffs now is one that indisputably deserves to, regardless of its preseason expectations or standout individual performances. You thought you could get in with style points, but you can’t. You are scum. Garbage. Dogshit. The Raiders by another name.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to popular CLI tools: curl]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=106327</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alternatives-popular-cli-tools-curl/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T16:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We spotlight alternatives tools to curl, a utility for transferring data from or to a server, supporting many protocols.
The post Alternatives to popular CLI tools: curl appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CuerdOS Linux – distribution of Spanish origin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140706</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/cuerdos-linux-distribution-spanish-origin/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T16:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CuerdOS is a Debian-based Linux distribution of Spanish origin focused on stability and constant performance.
The post CuerdOS Linux – distribution of Spanish origin appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Accumulating snows likely (THU-1/9)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3784679</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-accumulating-snows-likely-thu-1-9/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T15:41:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City weather will change later Thursday afternoon as clouds increase, some light snow moves up the I-35 corridor from the southwest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Topgrade – system specific update tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140698</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/topgrade-system-specific-update-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T15:32:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Topgrade detects which tools you use and runs the appropriate commands to update them.
The post Topgrade – system specific update tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NHL Has Given Up On New Year’s Day]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178149</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-nhl-has-given-up-on-new-years-day"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T14:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I didn't watch the Winter Classic. I can't even blame that fact on the teams involved, shit-ass as they may have been, because the draw of an outdoor game is almost entirely the venue: the visuals, the pageantry, the novelty of a hockey game in a non-hockey building under the open sky. The reason I didn't watch was that I hadn't realized until the morning of the game that it was being held on Dec. 31 instead of the usual New Year's Day, and by that point I already had plans, and canceling plans to watch Blues–Blackhawks is a great way to lose friends and gain regrets.
I liked it when it was New Year's Day. It's a perfect day for sports: I'm almost certainly not leaving the house, and I'd like something pretty and low-stakes to watch. I also liked that the NHL had its day. Every other league has its day. The NBA has Christmas. The NFL, which greedily wants Christmas for itself but will never truly own it, has the Super Bowl, which is basically a holiday already. MLB has its summer holidays, days off work being ideal for afternoon first pitches. And New Year's Day was for hockey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has The Tennis Ball Gotten Worse?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173112</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/has-the-tennis-ball-gotten-worse"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T14:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best way to snap an athlete out of platitude autopilot in a press conference is to get them to vent about some technical complaint. Like everyone else, they have esoteric gripes about their workplace, and are happy to explain them in full when given the chance. During my time at the ATP Finals, a year-end tournament in Italy for the top of the men’s tour, I asked several players to reflect on the object they clobber all day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sentora – web hosting control panel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140629</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/sentora-web-hosting-control-panel/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T12:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sentora is a complete open-source web hosting control panel. Sentora is designed to be installed on a minimal OS.
The post Sentora – web hosting control panel appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lilidog Linux – optimized Openbox desktop from a Debian base]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140668</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/lilidog-linux-optimized-openbox-desktop-debian/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T12:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lilidog Linux is a Debian-based distribution sporting an optimized Openbox desktop
The post Lilidog Linux – optimized Openbox desktop from a Debian base appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vim-fern – asynchronous tree viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140632</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/vim-fern-asynchronous-tree-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T10:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[vim-fern is a general purpose asynchronous tree viewer written in VimL.
The post vim-fern – asynchronous tree viewer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mischa Blanos (Interview)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/mischa-blanos-interview</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/mischa-blanos-interview"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T08:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Mischa Blanos, a Romanian pianist and composer from Bucharest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[lsv – Vlang implementation of ls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140665</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/lsv-vlang-implementation-ls/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T07:16:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[lsv is a modern alternative to ls in the spirit of exa, eza, lsd, pls, natls, ls-go and others.
The post lsv – Vlang implementation of ls appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best Free and Open Source Command-Line HTTP Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=8735</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/good-command-line-http-clients/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T06:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These clients let you download files over the internet from the command line. But they can also be used for many more interesting purposes.
The post 10 Best Free and Open Source Command-Line HTTP Clients appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inviska Rename – batch rename utility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140655</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/inviska-rename-batch-rename-utility/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T22:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inviska Rename is a batch file rename utility that allows you to give meaningful names to groups of files.
The post Inviska Rename – batch rename utility appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Growing Pains Are Over For UCLA]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178088</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-growing-pains-are-over-for-ucla"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T22:44:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, the team sending me into wistful aunt mode most often is No. 1 UCLA, whom I last blogged two seasons ago, back when I was still figuring out how to cover regular-season college basketball here and back when their young players were still figuring out how to play college basketball.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future Of Fire Cannot Look Like Its Present]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178091</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-future-of-fire-cannot-look-like-its-present"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T22:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Los Angeles is burning. 
At least two people are dead and more than 80,000 people have evacuated their homes. The images and videos of the Palisades, Eaton, and Hurst Fires, each of which is currently at zero-percent containment, show a wave of destruction: a vast swath of Pacific Palisades reduced from three dimensions to two; a long line of freeway-side Malibu homes ablaze mere feet away from the indifferent Pacific Ocean; overhead views from airplane window of what looks more like a roiling caldera than the second-most populous city in the U.S.; palm trees atilt at 45-degree angles in the fierce wind; a bulldozer clearing a thicket of Teslas and Mercedes-Benzes, abandoned because the people fleeing in them realized they would have to run for it to survive; power lines snapping like fireworks; two people and a dog in a gorgeous, well-appointed kitchen framed by generous windows offering 270-degree views, views currently showing a ferocious tornado of fire whipping at inhuman speeds right outside. Their voices are soft, in deference to the force of the blaze and to its suddenness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loc-OS – Linux distribution based on Debian]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140626</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/loc-os-linux-distribution-debian/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T21:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Loc-OS is a Debian-based distribution focused on low resource consumption which makes it useful for older hardware.
The post Loc-OS – Linux distribution based on Debian appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Claim Braden Shewmake]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=837140</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/01/royals-claim-braden-shewmake.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T19:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that they have claimed Braden Shewmake off waivers from the White Sox. The infielder had been designated for assignment by Chicago a week ago when they acquired left-hander Tyler Gilbert. Shewmake, 27, was the 21st overall pick of the 2019 draft, selected by the Braves out of Texas A&M. He’s appeared in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bradley Beal And The Suns Are Stuck Heavin’ In Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178085</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bradley-beal-and-the-suns-are-stuck-heavin-in-hell"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T19:02:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hell is always a little bit nearer at hand in the Western Conference. In the East you can want to be bad, and try to be bad, and in fact be quite bad, and still host a playoff series. Not so in the West: In the West it's possible to want to be good, to try to be good, and to be very close to good, and to wake up every morning in hell. The Phoenix Suns are in hell. They're not even the only ones. The Warriors are in hell. The Kings are in hell. Each of these teams, if they were in the East, might make the Finals. Well, probably not the Kings.
The Suns opened the season in great form, winning eight of nine against a reasonably diverse set of opponents. None of the wins were particularly convincing, but a strength of a veteran roster, like Phoenix's, is that it should reliably out-execute and outperform opponents in the clutch. You would expect a team led by Kevin Durant, Devin Booker, and Bradley Beal to win a majority of its close games, if for no other reason than by pure shot-making brilliance. With game-to-game load management, with reasonable (read: non-Thibs-ian) minutes limits, and with Phoenix's stars' own wisely calibrated distributions of effort, you would not bat an eyelash at the Suns posting the modest net rating of an also-ran while winning 70 percent of their games. What I am getting at is the Suns don't necessarily need to dominate every night in order to convince themselves or anyone else that they are a serious contender. Their form to start the season was more or less exactly what you'd expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tess – hackable, simple, rapid and beautiful terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140648</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tess-hackable-simple-rapid-beautiful-terminal/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T18:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tess is a hackable, simple, rapid and beautiful terminal for the new era of technology. It's written in JavaScript.
The post Tess – hackable, simple, rapid and beautiful terminal appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s No Magic To Be Found In Golden State]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178094</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/theres-no-magic-to-be-found-in-golden-state"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T18:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Golden State Warriors fans come by their belief in the occult honestly. They have been mesmerized by the varied and bewildering sorceries of Stephen Curry and all within his purview for more than a decade now, and no bad moment or game cannot be scrubbed clean within the time it takes for his next 37-foot jumper with one second left on the shot clock to go from fingertip to net. His most strident critics, both of them, believe he should have to play while wearing a spangly black-and-purple caftan with crescent moons and stars and a pointy hat. That's his deal, pure and simple.
Thus, it is a bafflement to them that he and the team he enchants are suddenly trafficking with the Washington Wizards, who we know from our reading are the very antithesis of magic. In the last 21 games, or one fourth of a season, the Warriors with Curry are 6-15, with the latest example being last night's 114-98 hammering at the hands of the Jimmy-Butler-free Miami Heat. The game was a slow-cold build from the beginning to the point where the Warriors fell behind by 20 with two minutes left; they led for four minutes and never after the first quarter. They are not only 6-15, they are 5-9 at home in that stretch, which means they are 1-6 on the road and about to embark on a four-game roadie against the Pistons, Pacers, Raptors and Timberwolves. This would have been a 3-1 trip at worse in the good old days; now, 1-3 seems like it would be satisfactory given the circumstances.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pearl Linux OS – Ubuntu-based distro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140591</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pearl-linux-os-ubuntu-based-distro/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T17:57:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pearl Linux is an Ubuntu-based distribution with various desktop environments including MATE and its own PearlDE.
The post Pearl Linux OS – Ubuntu-based distro appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Becoming A Penn State Fan Again Means Remembering How To Hate Notre Dame]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178054</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/becoming-a-penn-state-fan-again-means-remembering-how-to-hate-notre-dame"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T17:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I didn’t know that her parents were Penn State fans until I saw it. It was the summer before senior year of high school. A bunch of us went to hang out in a friend’s basement. The poster on the wall was an homage to Washington Crossing the Delaware. Instead of George Washington leading the Continental Army across the river, however, Joe Paterno stood in the prow of the boat with the Penn State Nittany Lions. Perhaps they were away at Rutgers that week.
It is possibly the kitschiest Penn State product I have ever seen. It was made by George LaVanish, a talented artist who worked for the school and still lives in the state, and is dated 1986. In my memory there was a lot of Penn State wall art in that basement, and that was not unusual. I knew plenty of people in Philadelphia with full Penn State rooms, some of whom hadn’t even attended the school. But they liked college football, and Penn State was the best team that could conceivably be considered local. There remain a lot of Penn State fans in Philadelphia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Sneaky snow system ahead (WED-1/8)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3783327</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-sneaky-snow-system-ahead-wed-1-8/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T15:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As fires spread in neighborhoods across Los Angeles county, winter storms and weather are continuing to hit other parts of the United States]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Sneaky snow system ahead (WED-1/8)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3783327</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-sneaky-snow-system-ahead-wed-1-8/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T15:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the winter season when arctic air masses move through the area, one always has t watch for clouds to affect the temperatures, especially at night. One of the golden rules for forecasting sub-zero temperatures is cloud cover. IF there are clouds for any length of time, it will keep temperatures in many areas above [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPEG Archive – utilities for archive JPEGs for long term storage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140635</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/jpeg-archive-utilities-jpegs-long-term-storage/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T15:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JPEG Archive is a small collection of utilities for archiving photos for saving to long term storage or serving over the web.
The post JPEG Archive – utilities for archive JPEGs for long term storage appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antonio Pierce Got What Every Raiders Coach Gets]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178041</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/antonio-pierce-got-what-every-raiders-coach-gets"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T14:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a sport that’s constantly morphing into strange new shapes as its decision-makers try and try to find the next big thing, the Las Vegas Raiders know what they like and they like what they know. This doesn’t work, but it works for us—it’s why we can do a simple cut-and-paste on them and pass it off as fresh analysis. They make it that easy for us all.
Yep, the Raiders struck again, in the conservatory with the lead weight around their own ankles, just as they always do. There is one area and one area only in which they are the class of the NFL, and they do that work with such remarkable precision that nobody with any dignity takes pride in predicting what they'll do. It's not calling your shot when it happens every year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DraftKings Determined To See How Much It Can Squeeze Out Of Problem Bettors]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178011</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/draftkings-determined-to-see-how-much-it-can-squeeze-out-of-problem-bettors"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T14:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the price of $20 per month, select DraftKings customers in New York can now enroll in a program that the company is calling DraftKings Sportsbook+. What does a subscription to this stupidly named product get you? It seems to be a way for eager sports bettors to pay DraftKings an extra fee for the opportunity to lose more money.
People who pay the monthly fee will have access to boosted payouts on parlay bets, which are already the most profitable type of bets (for DraftKings). These boosts will only apply to parlays where odds on the individual legs are -500 or shorter, and will scale up with the size of the parlay: A two-leg parlay comes with a 10-percent profit boost, a six-leg parlay gets 50 percent, and so on up to an 11-leg parlay, which can qualify for a 100 percent boost. The maximum eligible bet is $25.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vesta – Hosting Control Panel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140606</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/vesta-hosting-control-panel/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T12:16:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vesta provides an easy to use control panel that allows the management of websites, DNS, mail, backups, and more.
The post Vesta – Hosting Control Panel appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CutefishOS – Linux distribution with its own desktop environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140617</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/cutefishos-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T11:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CutefishOS is a Debian- or Ubuntu-based with its own Cutefish Desktop Environment.
The post CutefishOS – Linux distribution with its own desktop environment appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[StygianSift – terminal file explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140610</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/stygiansift-terminal-file-explorer/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T10:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[StygianSift will navigate you through the rivers of data and forests of directories with unparalleled ease. 
The post StygianSift – terminal file explorer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zasper – IDE for Data Science]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140599</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/zasper-ide-data-science/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T08:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zasper is an IDE designed from the ground up to support massive concurrency.
The post Zasper – IDE for Data Science appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jon Batiste]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/jon-batiste</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/jon-batiste"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T08:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Jon Batiste, an American pianist, bandleader, and composer from Louisiana.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trimix]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3035/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3035/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Restaurant Week 2025 is back and bigger than ever: Our staff picks can help narrow down the options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866790</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-restaurant-week-2025-is-back-and-bigger-than-ever-our-staff-picks-can-help-narrow-down-the-options/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T22:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Sarah Sipple KC Restaruant Week begins this weekend, and runs from January 10-19. Over 240 restaurants in the Kansas City metro are participating by offering specially priced set menus. The annual event put on by Visit KC and the Greater KC Restaurant Association serves severeal purposes.  First and foremost, KC Restaurant Week (KCRW) invites diners to celebrate our...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[rlxOS – independent, safely mutable and privacy oriented Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140580</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/rlxos-independent-safely-mutable-privacy-oriented-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T21:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[rlxOS is a Linux distribution that's built from scratch to offer better control over the core and working.
The post rlxOS – independent, safely mutable and privacy oriented Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Seidler’s Padres Are A Family Business]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177925</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/peter-seidlers-padres-are-a-family-business"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T20:36:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Monday, Sheel Seidler, the widow of former Padres chairman Peter Seidler, filed a complaint against two of the latter's brothers over control of the team. The complaint alleges that Matthew and Robert Seidler, as successor trustees to Peter Seidler's trust, failed to comply with their fiduciary duties to Sheel Seidler, the sole beneficiary of the trust, including by withholding funds and using the trust as a "piggybank" to enrich themselves. It also states that Peter Seidler wished for his wife to become the control person of the team, including a handwritten ranking with his wife and children at the top. After Peter Seidler's death, his eldest brother John was instead submitted to MLB as the Padres' next control person.
A spokesman for the Seidler Trusts released a statement calling Sheel Seidler's complaint "entirely without merit." According to the statement, the trustee of Seidler's trust was solely responsible for appointing the next control person, and in 2020, when Peter Seidler took control of the team, Sheel Seidler had agreed that she "had no right to be or to designate the Control Person and that she would not interfere with the designated Control Person." It also alleged that Sheel Seidler had agreed in May 2024 that John Seidler would be the best control person for the team. The statement did not address the issue of whether or not Matthew and Robert Seidler had mismanaged the trust, which, while likely being a more salient moral-legal issue at the crux of the complaint, is less relevant to the general public.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Weird And Unusual Trick To Deciphering And Decoding A Josina Anderson Report Or News Item]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177984</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/one-weird-and-unusual-trick-to-deciphering-and-decoding-a-josina-anderson-report-or-news-item"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T19:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As writers and bloggers, we all develop crutches or supports that we overrely on or use too often. One such tic or tendency is the use of two synonyms or words that mean the same thing in sequence or next to each other to underscore or emphasize a point or insight. The redundant style or mode can be a difficult and hard practice to shake or move past, as two words can punch-up or add some much needed pop or pizzazz to an otherwise staid or simple-seeming sentence. That's the theory or idea anyway, though it only works and functions if the two words or clauses are actually different or divergent from each other; more often and usually, the effect or result is a sentence and unit of writing that is obscurant and hazy. 
This brings and delivers us to Josina Anderson, a perpetual mainstay in the candidate field of the Shams Charania Award For Excellence In Divulging Of Information Through Syntax Comprehended By Many. Anderson's written text work output is an infinite joy forever, and she was awarded the 2023 win for her news updates. The Defector staff was enjoying and liking Anderson's latest and newest unique news when Dave McKenna observationally noticed that she's the leading foremost practitioner and specialist of this way of writing and disseminating information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1Panel – modern web-based control panel for Linux server management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140585</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/1panel-modern-web-based-control-panel-linux-server-management/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T19:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1Panel enables users to effortlessly manage their Linux servers.
The post 1Panel – modern web-based control panel for Linux server management appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s In A Knockoff?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177972</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/whats-in-a-knockoff"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T18:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In that gray purgatory that was the week between Christmas and New Year's, a debate arose on my feeds: When is a luxury fashion knockoff a populist victory, and when is it sinister duplicity?
The debate about how class is expressed in conspicuous consumption took form most recently in twining debates about a Walmart knockoff purse and a pair of sisters showing off their Christmas gifts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Learned It By Watching You]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177964</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ai-learned-it-by-watching-you"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T17:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about football, bags, car buttons, meowing on an airplane, and more.
Well now, here we are. Happy first bag of 2025 everyone, and let’s all thank the great Rachelle Hampton for braving the sonororotomotorolavirus and hosting this column so brilliantly just last week. Now let’s get to your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OptiImage – GUI image compressor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140562</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/optiimage-gui-image-compressor/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T17:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Optimize your images with OptiImage, a useful image compressor that supports PNG, JPEG, WebP and SVG file types.
The post OptiImage – GUI image compressor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Lorenzen Is a Royal Again, This Time by Choice]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=454145</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/michael-lorenzen-is-a-royal-again-this-time-by-choice/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T17:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The right-hander returns to Kansas City on a one-year deal, and he might finally have time to unpack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davy Andrews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobian – Debian derivative for mobile devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140556</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/mobian-debian-derivative-mobile-devices/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T15:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobian is a Debian-based distro intended for smartphones and other mobile devices.
The post Mobian – Debian derivative for mobile devices appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democracy Dies As Awful Man No Longer Able To Freely Drive 18 Blocks In Manhattan]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177892</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/democracy-dies-as-awful-man-no-longer-able-to-freely-drive-18-blocks-in-manhattan"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T15:52:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is not very difficult to learn true and useful things about the new congestion pricing toll system that New York City switched on last weekend, but it is much easier to learn untrue things about it. The program itself is easy to understand; this post at Gothamist, to pick one of many, lays out both the broad strokes and the particulars in a lucid way, as does the city's website. While New York's is the first congestion pricing gambit of its kind in the United States, previous examples in London (which implemented it in 2003) and Stockholm (which did so in 2006) offer some sense of how it might work both in practice and in terms of how quickly people will get used to it. Congestion pricing has been coming into existence, fitfully and fretfully and in public, since 2007; there's a site where you can track the differences in traffic delays since the program finally went into effect just after midnight on Saturday.
The program could and probably should be simpler, and it is nice if also a little sad to imagine a different and more readily governable world in which it would be. In this one there are ins and outs and what-have-you's as there are with any bit of ambitious public policy, and carve-outs and compromises and concessions as there will be in any bit of public policy that inconveniences noisy and powerful constituencies, and hanging over it all there is the familiar element of lurid furious grievance inherent to every policy debate concerned with how people use cars. Given how atrophied and sclerotic and abstracted and plainly corrupt state and local government is, and not to put too fine a point on it but further given how absolutely fucking insane people become whenever they feel that their natural right to Do Car Stuff is being infringed upon, even this sort of tenuous and robustly caveated neoliberal intervention both feels and mostly is revolutionary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's blog: Rare (for us) optical phenomena seen (TUE-1/7)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3781914</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-rare-for-us-optical-phenomena-seen-tue-1-7/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T15:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a weekend of winter storms, more extreme cold and below freezing temperatures are expected, including snow chances on Friday in the KC metro]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's blog: Rare (for us) optical phenomena seen (TUE-1/7)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3781914</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-rare-for-us-optical-phenomena-seen-tue-1-7/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T15:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a sub-zero start to the day for many areas, especially north of the I-70 corridor. So far KCI has tanked to -3° as we've been expected for awhile and sure enough some areas were near, if not below, -10°. Both Lawrence and St Joseph airports, renowned for tanking in these conditions because of their [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Comprehensive And Maddening History Of Color Star, Would-Be Titans Of Just About Anything]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=168729</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-comprehensive-and-maddening-history-of-color-star-would-be-titans-of-just-about-anything"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T13:57:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The story starts with a signing ceremony. On Dec. 20, 2021, the Philadelphia 76ers staged a publicity event to announce a new marketing partnership with the Chinese company Color Star Technology Co., Ltd. This was an unglamorous affair—a team backdrop, some placards, dreary fluorescent lighting—but it was certainly given more ceremony and publicity than the typical mid-tier sponsorship deal. The 76ers published a brief video of the event to their website, and a couple of photos on Twitter. Then-team president Chris Heck emphasized the cross-cultural significance of the deal; the contract between the two parties reflected the visibility boost flowing from the very popular American basketball team to the unheard-of new international sponsor.
The partnership was supposed to last for most of three NBA seasons. It was aborted after less than one month, with the 76ers alleging a breach of contract but declining to elaborate, and sweeping the whole mess into an unattributed statement made to a local reporter on a Friday afternoon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Best Free and Open Source Linux Network Simulators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140494</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-linux-network-simulators/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T12:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Network simulation is a technique whereby a software program replicates the behavior of a real network. We make our picks.
The post 5 Best Free and Open Source Linux Network Simulators appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TileOS – Debian based Linux distribution using tiling window managers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140527</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tileos-debian-based-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T12:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TileOS is a Debian-based distro using tiling window managers as its user interface. 
The post TileOS – Debian based Linux distribution using tiling window managers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flow State Episode 259]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-episode-259</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-episode-259"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T08:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s episode opens with a Harold Budd track and then moves into new ambient music by Mark Barrott, Seefeel, Bibio, More Eaze, Florian T M Zeisig, and Fennesz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TerminusDM – cross platform terminal download manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140439</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/terminusdm-cross-platform-terminal-download-manager/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T07:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TerminusDM is a powerful cross-platform terminal application download manager built with Rust.
The post TerminusDM – cross platform terminal download manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals To Re-Sign Michael Lorenzen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=836874</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/01/royals-to-re-sign-michael-lorenzen.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T23:20:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals are re-signing Michael Lorenzen on a one-year, $7MM deal, reports Jeff Passan of ESPN. There’s a $12MM mutual option for 2026. Lorenzen heads back to Kansas City after finishing the ’24 campaign with the Royals. Kansas City acquired him from the Ranges in a deadline deal that sent reliever Walter Pennington to Texas. Lorenzen made…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>