<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-10-17T02:48:25.864Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pittsburgh Steelers To Celebrate 50th Anniversary Of Super Bowl IX With Throwback Uniforms]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82649</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/16/pittsburgh-steelers-to-celebrate-50th-anniversary-of-super-bowl-ix-with-throwback-uniforms/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T01:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pittsburgh Steelers will celebrate the 50th anniversary of their victory over the Minnesota Vikings in Super Bowl IX by wearing throwback uniforms during Sunday's game against the New York Jets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cheers To Brick And Mortar! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076268</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/cheers-to-brick-and-mortar-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T23:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A New, Physical Law School Is On The Way!: Good news for Alaska!
Close Reading Must Not Be His Forte: If Joe Deters doesn't understand "Boneless," you think he gets statutes?
Tax Crimes Come To Roost: Ex-Biglaw partner sentenced to prison time.
The Part Of Partnering No One Likes: It isn't all just easy money.
Cheers To Second Chances: New Jersey Supreme Court extends olive branch to some former attorneys.
The post Cheers To Brick And Mortar! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Some Point, Even Judges *Need* To Retire]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076264</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/at-some-point-even-judges-need-to-retire/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T21:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hope for the judges' sake most of them retire before then.
The post At Some Point, Even Judges *Need* To Retire appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Biglaw Firm Names Its First Black Firmwide Managing Partner]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076240</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/top-biglaw-firm-names-its-first-black-firmwide-managing-partner/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T20:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He joins a handful of other Black lawyers who are successfully leading Am Law 200 firms.
The post Top Biglaw Firm Names Its First Black Firmwide Managing Partner appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[National WWI Museum cracks open 100 year old time capsule after KCPD bomb squad inspection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856220</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/national-wwi-museum-cracks-open-100-year-old-time-capsule-after-kcpd-bomb-squad-inspection/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T20:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twelve items were featured on stage at the National WWI Museum on Oct. 16, displaying photos, newspapers articles, and more that were hidden inside of the 100 year old time capsule. This morning, a century-old time capsule was opened for the first time at the National WWI Museum and Memorial. The ceremony was led by members of the museum, memorial...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Were You Disbarred In New Jersey? You May Be Eligible To Practice Again.]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076254</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/were-you-disbarred-in-new-jersey-you-may-be-eligible-to-practice-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T20:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Garden State believes in second chances. 
The post Were You Disbarred In New Jersey? You May Be Eligible To Practice Again. appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Partner Isn’t The Constant Money Party You Think It Is]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076184</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/biglaw-partner-isnt-the-constant-money-party-you-think-it-is/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T19:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even partners can have their salary slashed.
The post Biglaw Partner Isn’t The Constant Money Party You Think It Is appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Country singer MaRynn Taylor walks us through her seasons of life ahead of PBR show]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856009</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/country-singer-marynn-taylor-walks-us-through-her-seasons-of-life-ahead-of-pbr-show/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T19:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of MaRynn Taylor Over the past few years, country singer MaRynn Taylor’s career has grown by leaps and bounds. Thanks to some very excellent singles, including “Dads and Daughters” and “Shakin’ in My Boots,” along with this spring’s Get to Know Me EP, Taylor knows how to craft a song sure to get you lifting your cup whenever...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOS Nation Apologizes For Ill-Advised Rollout, Not For Being Named BOS Nation]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170630</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bos-nation-apologizes-for-ill-advised-rollout-not-for-being-named-bos-nation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good news: It's been more than 24 hours since the NWSL announced its latest expansion team, and everyone is still talking about it. Bad news: Everyone is still talking about it because they are making fun of it, to the extent that the team has been forced to issue an apology for how it handled its media rollout. 
The people charged with introducing BOS Nation to the world ran into a problem that many organizations do these days, which is that at some point they found themselves in a room with an advertising exec or brand consultant who said something along the lines of, "Why should we be scared to be bold?" These things tend to happen when you hire an advertising agency with an About page that looks like this. As a result, BOS Nation announced itself with a promotional video built around a strained joke about testicles, which included the phrase "goat balls."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Biglaw Partner Sentenced To Time Behind Bars After Pleading Guilty To Tax Crimes]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076243</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/ex-biglaw-partner-sentenced-to-time-behind-bars-after-pleading-guilty-to-tax-crimes/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In addition to prison time, this former partner owes the government more than $3.9 million in taxes.
The post Ex-Biglaw Partner Sentenced To Time Behind Bars After Pleading Guilty To Tax Crimes appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Owner Or Broadcaster, All Tom Brady Has To Do Is Show Up]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170626</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/as-owner-or-broadcaster-all-tom-brady-has-to-do-is-show-up"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing about Tom Brady's entrance into the Las Vegas Raiders' ownership group is funnier than the handwringing about how this new conflict might affect his broadcasting duties with Fox. That one’s simple—it won't. Being an owner means he’s forbidden from doing some of the basic stuff that broadcasters do, from being critical of officiating to attending to basic pre-production duties, but Brady’s booth work always seemed like a lucrative way to kill time until this thing came along. If it means that Fox is on the hook for $37.5 million a year of Brady half-arseing his way through Falcons-Broncos, well, Fox hired Brady to be Brady. Breaking down Bo Nix for the Sunday proles was surely never the hook for him. For one thing, the cash was too good for him not to do it. For two, the appeal of the gig was surely diminished by the fact that there’s no way to prove beyond a doubt that you’re the best at it when you're stuck musing about why Bo Nix isn't.
But there's more—much, much more. Brady is not going to rest on his freshly approved ownership percentage (five percent), not by any means. He is coming in to have, according to the Las Vegas Review Journal's Vincent Bonsignore, “a much bigger role than people think in the direction of the franchise in all areas on the football side.” That's according to the ubiquitous "league source," which as we know could mean anything from Antonio Brown up to but not including Roger Goodell. It only makes sense that Brady isn't just making a passive investment here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supreme Court Candidate Calls Out Opponent’s Busted Textualism]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076242</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/supreme-court-candidate-calls-out-opponents-busted-textualism/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T17:44:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For Ohio voters, there's only one choice here.
The post Supreme Court Candidate Calls Out Opponent’s Busted Textualism appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Going On With Bama?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170579</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/whats-going-on-with-bama"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T17:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Alabama Crimson Tide are currently 5-1 and ranked No. 7 in the AP poll in Kalen DeBoer's first season as head coach, so it's hard to say that anything is necessarily "wrong" with this team. On paper, things are just fine, even with the one loss. It's not like Bama never lost any games under Nick Saban. And yet, if you spend enough time in their corner of the internet, you'd think the sky is falling. After a big, tenure-defining win against Kirby Smart's Georgia, DeBoer's Tide blew it against Vanderbilt, the punching bag of the SEC. How bad was the loss? Beyond the fact that it was Vandy's first win against a top-five team in their history, there was the added bonus that it was a top-to-bottom beating in which the Tide never held a lead all game.
It was a bad loss for a program of Alabama's stature, made worse by the fact that it was followed up with another stinker in South Carolina. Alabama edged an unranked Gamecocks team by just two points, and looked vulnerable the whole game. In fact, the Tide have spent a lot of time looking vulnerable this year: They spent three quarters struggling against USF before finally pulling away late in the fourth, and even their big win against Georgia featured a heroic second-half comeback by the Bulldogs that turned what should have been a triumphant blowout into an escape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Short History Of The Goalie Goal]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170583</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/filip-gustavsson-adds-himself-to-the-short-history-of-the-goalie-goal"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T17:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The goalie goal is the holy grail. More than three times as rare in the history of the NHL as a five-goal game, there have been just 18 instances of a goalie scoring, by 15 different goalies. An intentional goalie goal—one where the goalie shoots the puck into an empty net, rather than being credited for being the last player to touch the puck before the other team scores an own goal—has happened just 11 times.
Welcome to the club, Filip Gustavsson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NC Lt. Gov. Sues CNN For $50M: I’m Not A Perv, I’m The Hapless Pizza Guy!]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076231</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/nc-lt-gov-sues-cnn-for-50m-im-not-a-perv-im-the-hapless-pizza-guy/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T17:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not porny at all, dude.
The post NC Lt. Gov. Sues CNN For $50M: I’m Not A Perv, I’m The Hapless Pizza Guy! appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Emerging AI Use Cases For Law Firms [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076221</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-emerging-ai-use-cases-for-law-firms/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sign up for this CLE-eligible webinar from our friends at iManage and learn best practices on how your firm can leverage AI to achieve faster results.
The post The Emerging AI Use Cases For Law Firms appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>IManage and Above The Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Illegal Casino Night Is For The Children]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170580</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/illegal-casino-night-is-for-the-children"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all have dreams. We all want to smell good. We all want the best for our children. We all want our children to get scouted and land full-ride athletic scholarships and smell good. We all want to fundraise for the team. We all want to gamble. We all know that the rules don’t apply to us if we’re doing it for the kids. When did I lose you? 
The tough thing about doing crimes with others is that everyone has leverage on everyone else. (As a Scorpio, this is a nightmare scenario for me. I work alone.) And while sometimes the scarcity mindset is a scam, sometimes it’s a fact of life: there is a fixed number of people who can host a single bingo game. Within any suburban enclave there is only so many people who want to buy essential oils. There is a limit to how much petty lawbreaking one cop can pretend not to see without having his palms greased. But where exactly are these limits? We must go to casino night to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Only State In America Without A Physical Law School Will Be Getting One Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076241</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-only-state-in-america-without-a-physical-law-school-will-be-getting-one-soon/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T15:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to prospective law students in Alaska, who will soon be able to study law in their home state.
The post The Only State In America Without A Physical Law School Will Be Getting One Soon appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Young Associates Should Contribute To 401(k) Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076182</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/more-young-associates-should-contribute-to-401k-plans/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T14:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When planning for retirement, you have to consider the long game.
The post More Young Associates Should Contribute To 401(k) Plans appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Rothman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: A rain chance showing up (WED-10/16)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3698480</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-a-rain-chance-showing-up-wed-10-16/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T14:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a frosty morning out there with temperatures down to 25-30° in the region, perhaps lower in some areas as well. I saw a lot of frost out there as well. So it's a cold start but temperatures will recover somewhat this afternoon with bright sunshine and lighter winds as high pressure settles on top [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Midland gig, Underoath prove they’re still not chasing safety after 20 years on the grind]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856202</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/at-midland-gig-underoath-prove-theyre-still-not-chasing-safety-after-20-years-on-the-grind/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T14:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They’re Only Chasing Safety remains one of the most iconic post-hardcore albums of the 2000s from one of the most iconic post-hardcore bands, Underoath. Underoath’s sound has generally verged on metalcore with more unclean vocals—featuring more clean vocals from drummer Aaron Gillespie, They’re Only Chasing Safety has had the ability to attract a wider fanbase. For me, the album served...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Madrid gig, Underoath prove they’re still not chasing safety after 20 years on the grind]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856202</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/at-madrid-gig-underoath-prove-theyre-still-not-chasing-safety-after-20-years-on-the-grind/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T14:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They’re Only Chasing Safety remains one of the most iconic post-hardcore albums of the 2000s from one of the most iconic post-hardcore bands, Underoath. Underoath’s sound has generally verged on metalcore with more unclean vocals—featuring more clean vocals from drummer Aaron Gillespie, They’re Only Chasing Safety has had the ability to attract a wider fanbase. For me, the album served...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CMMC 2.0 Final Rule Released: New Compliance Standards Set To Begin Next Year]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076232</id>
        <link href="http://breakingdefense.com/2024/10/cmmc-2-0-final-rule-released-new-compliance-standards-set-to-begin-next-year/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T14:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CMMC 2.0 introduced a third-party assessment dependent on contractor's CUI capacity.
The post CMMC 2.0 Final Rule Released: New Compliance Standards Set To Begin Next Year appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CARLEY WELCH - BREAKING DEFENSE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Columbus’s Johnny Gaudreau Tribute Was A Thank You, Not A Goodbye]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170536</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/columbuss-johnny-gaudreau-tribute-was-a-thank-you-not-a-goodbye"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T13:45:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is difficult to grasp, from the outside, what Johnny Gaudreau meant to fans of the Columbus Blue Jackets, even in the two short seasons he spent there before he and his brother Matthew were struck and killed by a suspected drunk driver on Aug. 29. Columbus fans are used to their stars leaving: for more money, bigger cities, more competitive franchises. If Gaudreau shocked the rest of the world when he signed with the Blue Jackets, he didn't shock Columbusites—he merely became one of them. He embraced them, and they embraced him in return. He wanted to be there. He always will be, in memory, because memory lasts longer than a life.
Tuesday marked the home opener for the Blue Jackets, and the night belonged to Gaudreau. The team revealed a memorial to Gaudreau on the concourse, featuring his used equipment and signs left by fans after his death, which will be there all season. All players on the Blue Jackets and the visiting Panthers wore his No. 13 in warmups. A video package was played on the jumbotron honoring his life. His wife Meredith and their two young kids were invited onto the ice as Gaudreau's banner was raised to the rafters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Feeling fresh at Nekter Juice Bar and Taco Tuesday at Jalapeño Tacos KC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856172</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-feeling-fresh-at-nekter-juice-bar-and-taco-tuesday-at-jalapeno-tacos-kc/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T13:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nekter Juice Bar // Photo by Tiffany Watts Nekter Juice Bar When it comes to food and drink in Kansas City, I usually find myself diving into the rich, hearty world of local restaurants, breweries, and lounges. But every now and then, I like to hit pause on comfort food and explore something a little lighter; something that still leaves...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Judge Finally Woke Up]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170520</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/aaron-judge-finally-woke-up"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T12:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Judge got back to being Aaron Judge and gave an ass playoff game its one shining moment. Judge's slump-busting and majestic two-run moonshot over the center-field wall in the bottom of the seventh inning highlighted his New York Yankees' 6-3 win over the Cleveland Guardians in Game 2 of the ALCS. 
Judge came into Tuesday night’s home game hitting just .133 with only one run batted in, one extra-base hit and zero homers this postseason. “Did he get it?” TBS play-by-play guy Brian Anderson asked as Judge sent a letter-high, 95-mph fastball from Guardians hurler Hunter Gaddis skyward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.16.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076236</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-16-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T12:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Gorsuch's new book presents factually inaccurate record to advance political agenda. Not really a shocker -- in Bremerton v. Kennedy the dissent explicitly calls him out for his propensity for making up facts. [Politico]
* Biglaw firms are increasingly suing clients over unpaid bills. [New York Law Journal]
* Judge Reed O'Connor is overseeing the DOJ-Boeing settlement that raises real questions over the government offering a sweetheart deal to protect a company from a damaging trial over the deadly results of its greedy cost-cutting measures. So obviously O'Connor's biggest concern is if the DOJ's proposed independent monitor was chosen by DEI policies. [Reuters]
* Judge in trouble for ordering restitution that went to himself in case involving damage to his truck. Judges can't preside over cases where they have a personal financial interest! Who does this guy think he is, a Supreme Court justice? [ABA Journal]
* Uncle Luke testifies that 2 Live Crew songs weren't works for hire... unlike Miami football in the 90s, amirite? [Law360]
* Everything we learn about the RFK Jr-Olivia Nuzzi-Ryan Lizza situation is against our will. [Daily Beast]
* Fortress becomes big player in litigation finance. [Bloomberg Law News]
The post Morning Docket: 10.16.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Atmosphere at VooDoo Lounge with Reverie and NOFUN!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856100</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-atmosphere-at-voodoo-lounge-with-reverie-and-nofun/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T12:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Atmosphere. // photo by Allison Scavo Atmosphere with Reverie and NOFUN! VooDoo Lounge Saturday, October 12 Touring in support of last year’s Talk Talk EP, Minneapolis rappers Ant and Slug, better known as Atmosphere took to the stage at Harrah’s VooDoo Lounge on Saturday for a career-spanning set. Los Angeles-based rapper, singer, and songwriter Reverie — known for her raw...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Scavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight Players Elect Free Agency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=827342</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/eight-players-elect-free-agency.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T03:53:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the offseason nears, a number of players elect minor league free agency each week. These players are separate from six-year MLB free agents, who’ll reach the open market five days after the conclusion of the World Series. Eligible minor leaguers can begin electing free agency as soon as the regular season wraps up. These…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hastened Departure — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076228</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/hastened-departure-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T23:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law Firm Founder Speeds Up Retirement Date: More time to spend with the family!
Don't Doubt Our Client!: Lawyers drop an experiment to counter an opposing expert. Unfortunately, they forgot the consent forms.
Protecting Kids? Not On My Watch!: Yes, this involves the 5th Circuit.
The People Want To Know About Bonuses!: Keep us informed so we can share!
The post Hastened Departure — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Are Women Lawyers Doing When It Comes To Making It Rain?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076224</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/how-are-women-lawyers-doing-when-it-comes-to-making-it-rain/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T23:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The data is disheartening for women in the legal profession, but hopefully things will improve in the future.
The post How Are Women Lawyers Doing When It Comes To Making It Rain? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UnitedLex CEO’s Sudden Departure Appears To Be Due To Personal Allegations Unrelated To Work]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076210</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/10/unitedlex-ceos-sudden-departure-appears-to-be-due-to-personal-allegations-unrelated-to-work.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T22:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A source inside UnitedLex with knowledge of the situation said that its CEO’s departure had nothing to do with his work there or any sort of corporate or employment-related malfeasance.
The post UnitedLex CEO’s Sudden Departure Appears To Be Due To Personal Allegations Unrelated To Work appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s BOS Nation]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170512</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-bos-nation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T22:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good news! The NWSL is getting a franchise in Boston. Bad news: The name of the team is BOS Nation FC.

https://twitter.com/NWSLBoston/status/1846193497855938956]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Questions For A Court Access Crusader (Part I)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075923</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/3-questions-for-a-court-access-crusader-part-i/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T21:28:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Lissner's work with FLP has led to well-deserved public recognition.
The post 3 Questions For A Court Access Crusader (Part I) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaston Kroub</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hembree and friends turned The Bottleneck into a Saturday night pizza party]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855796</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/hembree-and-friends-turned-the-bottleneck-into-a-saturday-night-pizza-party/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T21:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hembree // Photo by Nick Spacek Hembree w/ The Creature Comforts and Flash Floods The Bottleneck Saturday, Oct. 12 Saturday’s night’s Hembree show was one for the books. On one hand, the band was playing sans Garrett Childers, but on the other, they ordered Pizza Shuttle from the stage during their show. That’s like, the wildest thing I’ve seen in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marketing Roundup: Free Research Tools, Cross-Selling Plans, AI Tips]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076121</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/marketing-roundup-free-research-tools-cross-selling-plans-ai-tips/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T20:46:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What you missed this month from the Legal Marketing Association. 
The post Marketing Roundup: Free Research Tools, Cross-Selling Plans, AI Tips appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KATHERINE HOLLAR BARNARD</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Network Analysis To Gauge The Justices’ Relative Importance In Oral Arguments]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076212</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/using-network-analysis-to-gauge-the-justices-relative-importance-in-oral-arguments/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T20:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This analysis underscores that influence within judicial discourse is more multifaceted than meets the eye.
The post Using Network Analysis To Gauge The Justices’ Relative Importance In Oral Arguments appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Adam Feldman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Judge Seems Skeptical About Birkin Bag Antitrust Suit]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076157</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/federal-judge-seems-skeptical-about-birkin-bag-antitrust-suit/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T19:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this high fashion case, antitrust law may be out of style, according to this judge.
The post Federal Judge Seems Skeptical About Birkin Bag Antitrust Suit appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the Bottle: Concluding our cinephile meets whiskey connoisseur series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855735</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/inside-the-bottle-concluding-our-cinephile-meets-whiskey-connoisseur-series/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T19:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filmland’s Quadraforce packaging // Courtesy Filmland So, first things first, let’s address the elephant in the room. For the whiskey nerd, these offerings scream “marketing gimmick,” but that is to the unlearned whiskey nerd. It is only a gimmick if you can’t back it up or if the final product is different from the spirit of its creator. On both...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Dahlor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Lawyers Shake What Their Mommas Gave ‘Em At Second Circuit In Effort To Fend Off NY Criminal Sentencing]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076219</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/trump-lawyers-shake-what-their-mommas-gave-em-at-second-circuit-in-effort-to-fend-off-ny-criminal-sentencing/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And if the facts and law aren't on your side, pound the table.
The post Trump Lawyers Shake What Their Mommas Gave ‘Em At Second Circuit In Effort To Fend Off NY Criminal Sentencing appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jerry Jones Doesn’t Appreciate Your Tone]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170491</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jerry-jones-doesnt-appreciate-your-tone"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:28:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerry Jones turns down publicity with the same steely firmness of a seven-year-old confronted with a vat of Froot Loops. He is addicted to the blank stares of people listening to his gale-force bloviations, and as a result he may be the most powerful person in America, non-politics division, who most aggressively and devotedly seeks out people with cameras and microphones to record his outermost thoughts.
So when Jones snapped at the hosts of his weekly radio show—a brief aside: HE STILL DOES A WEEKLY RADIO SHOW!—on Tuesday morning for the impertinence of asking him not very pointed questions about Sunday's game, in which his Cowboys were edged by Detroit, 47-9, people snapped to attention, or what passes for attention in this cultural moment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC staple counterculture shop 7th Heaven set to close after 50 years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=856023</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-staple-counterculture-shop-7th-heaven-set-to-close-after-50-years/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[7th Heaven, a record store located at 7621 Troost Avenue, is set to close after 50 years of serving the Kansas City community. // Photo by Lane Rozin After serving the Kansas City community for half a century, record store 7th Heaven has announced that it will be closing its doors by the end of the year.  On Sept. 30,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What We Talk About When We Talk About Our Toilet Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170476</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-we-talk-about-when-we-talk-about-our-toilet-apps"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about farts, mashed potatoes, playfully threatening your besties with violence, and more.
Before I get started, I just wanted to thank all of the readers, friends, and coworkers for their condolences last week. Everywhere I looked, social media included, I saw nothing but kind words for my family. The internet is a better place than it’s often reported to be, and you people stand as proof of that. So thank you. It’s been a pleasure writing for you all, and it always will be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fifth Circuit Rules Judge Can’t Micromanage Government Because Irony Is Dead]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076214</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/fifth-circuit-rules-judge-cant-micromanage-government-because-irony-is-dead/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:43:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most activist court in the nation wants you to know they will not suffer anyone questioning the constitutionality of Republican policies.
The post Fifth Circuit Rules Judge Can’t Micromanage Government Because Irony Is Dead appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calling All Biglaw Associates: 2024 Bonus Season Awaits]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076160</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/calling-all-biglaw-associates-2024-bonus-season-awaits/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Make your predictions and share your thoughts in our annual bonus season survey.
The post Calling All Biglaw Associates: 2024 Bonus Season Awaits appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New NWSL Team in Boston to Be Known As ‘BOS Nation FC’]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82633</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/15/new-nwsl-team-in-boston-to-be-known-as-bos-nation-fc/soccer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T16:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Massachusetts-based team will become 15th franchise in National Women's Soccer League when it takes to the pitch for the 2026 season]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clio Cloud Conference Continues To Understand The Power Of Community]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076207</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/clio-cloud-conference-continues-to-understand-the-power-of-community/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T16:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clio's conference keeps on growing.
The post Clio Cloud Conference Continues To Understand The Power Of Community appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Briston Maroney proves that he is worth keeping an eye on at Truman show last Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855792</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/briston-maroney-proves-that-he-is-worth-keeping-an-eye-on-at-truman-show-last-wednesday/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T16:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Briston Maroney // Photo by Haley Mullenix Briston Maroney w/ Annie DiRusso The Truman Wednesday, Oct. 9 Briston Maroney played his first Kansas City show ever with Wednesday night’s stop of the Ultrapure Part 2 Tour at The Truman. The Knoxville alt-rocker showed us what we’ve been missing and left us craving more. Fellow Tennessee based rocker Annie DiRusso joined Maroney,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zoe Strohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Vientos Blew The Dodgers Away]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170441</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mark-vientos-blew-the-dodgers-away"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T15:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dodgers pitching beast that had looked so invulnerable for the last two games of its series with the Padres and its first nine innings against the Mets suddenly toppled in the beginning of NLCS Game 2. Such are the momentum swings of the postseason, and such is the damage that sophomore third baseman Mark Vientos can do when he locks onto a ball from the batter's box.
After a glum 9-0 loss on Sunday night, it was Mr. Smile himself, Francisco Lindor, who gave the Mets a pick-me-up with a lead-off dinger to right against Dodger opener Ryan Brasier. That longball not only punctured L.A.'s lengthy scoreless streak, it also helped set up the key moment of the ballgame as Landon Knack labored through the second inning. Scooping up a couple of outs while allowing a single, a walk, and an RBI double, Knack was set to face the 1-for-1 Lindor with men on second and third and the score already 2-0. Dodgers manager Dave Roberts directed his man toward the correct strategic decision, sending Lindor to first on an imaginary quartet of balls. But the choice to face the next man in the order over Lindor only steamed up the Mets' two-spot hitter, who's no slouch himself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers Face Consequences For Countering Trial Expert’s Test]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076209</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/lawyers-face-consequences-for-countering-trial-experts-test/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T15:34:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worth it. 
The post Lawyers Face Consequences For Countering Trial Expert’s Test appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Criminy! King Conker Charged With Cheeky Cheating At Conkers Contest]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170446</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/criminy-king-conker-charged-with-cheeky-cheating-at-conkers-contest"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T15:28:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strap yourself in for this one: There are allegations of cheating at the annual World Conker Championships. It gets worse: The man accused of breaking the rules is King Conker himself. While being searched after the event, a steel conker painted brown was found in King Conker's pocket. I will give you a minute to compose yourself.
For the one or two of you unfamiliar with the sport, conkers is a traditional childhood game in the U.K. Players put a string through a horse chestnut seed and crash their conkers together. The player with the conker that breaks first loses the match and, presumably, their pride for losing at such an important sport. Here’s the entry from the Encyclopedia of Traditional British Sports, right after cock throwing. (I am not looking that one up.) The game was first written about in an 1821 memoir, but it appears other nuts and snail shells were used too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QMJHL’s Moncton Wildcats Debut Latest Version of ‘Blackout’ Jerseys]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82624</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/15/qmjhls-moncton-wildcats-debut-latest-version-of-blackout-jerseys/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T15:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Brunswick-based team has long history of black alternate jerseys, but this one gets bold with red claw marks diagonally across front of sweater]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nick Sirianni Has Had It Up To Here With The Fans Of The Team He Coaches]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170422</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nick-sirianni-has-had-it-up-to-here-with-the-fans-of-the-team-he-coaches"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eagles fans love to complain about the team. Eagles fans love to complain about the head coach. This week they’re getting a chance to do both after the team won, which perhaps raises the bar on what can be considered a perfect Eagles game. On Sunday the Eagles pretty much played like shit against a team they were expected to beat by more than a touchdown. Fans seemed pissed the whole game. Like, more than usual, and for more obvious reasons than usual.
Much of that ire went toward Nick Sirianni. He heard it during Sunday’s 20-16 win over the lowly Browns, a game in which the Eagles never trailed and never really seemed to get going. Philadelphia fans are rarely happy, but they had a right to complain in this one. The Eagles got wide receivers A.J. Brown and Devonta Smith back from injury. Lane Johnson returned to anchor the offensive line. The team was coming off a bye and playing at home one of the worst teams in the league. And while they got the job done, booing was a pretty reasonable response to the experience of watching them do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Am Law 100 Firm’s Founder Retires Early, Leaving Biglaw Behind]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076158</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/am-law-100-firms-founder-retires-early-leaving-biglaw-behind/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:48:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He took two family member employees with him upon his exit from the firm.
The post Am Law 100 Firm’s Founder Retires Early, Leaving Biglaw Behind appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Jets Remain Allergic To Competence]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170436</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-jets-remain-allergic-to-competence"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:32:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Jets are a team that specializes in unfulfilled promise. The promise of the 2023 season was Aaron Rodgers's arrival, and was dashed the moment his Achilles tendon rolled up the back of his leg in the season opener. The start of this season brought even more promise: While Rodgers was out last year, the rest of the Jets' roster cohered into one of the league's more talent-rich outfits, and it wasn't hard to imagine a team that went 7-10 with Zach Wilson starting most of the games suddenly becoming a force after Rodgers reclaimed his position. A 2-3 start put a damper on things, but also opened the door for promises to be made. It was a coaching problem! With Robert Saleh shitcanned and Nathaniel Hackett stripped of his play-calling duties, the Jets would finally—finally!—be ready to transform into the great team their roster says they are supposed to be. Monday night's game against the Bills was a great opportunity for the Jets to finally start making good on some of those promises.
Did we see a transformed and re-energized Jets team on Monday night? Well, the offense looked better than it had. Todd Downing's play-calling opened some running lanes for Breece Hall that were previously hard to come by, and Rodgers had his best game as a Jet, throwing for 294 yards and two touchdowns. But is a team that is about to turn the corner one that loses 23-20 to a sputtering division rival at home? Is a team that has ironed out its inefficiencies one that nets one touchdown from four red-zone drives, gets repeatedly run over by Ray Davis and Ty Johnson, misses two field goals, and commits 11 penalties? The Jets under Saleh were a team that dropped way too many passes, drew way too many flags, and routinely undid itself with mistakes of all varieties. Our first look at the post-Saleh Jets indicates that this is still a team that drops way too many passes, draws way too many flags, and knows just how to undo itself with stupid mistakes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Besides, Pharma and PBMs, Who Drives Up Drug Costs?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076156</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/10/video-besides-pharma-and-pbms-who-drives-up-drug-costs/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you thought that Big Pharma and the PBMs were the only bad guys in the saga of unreasonably high prescription drug prices in the United States, you would be wrong. Hear who else is to blame from the CEO of Blue Shield of California.
The post Video: Besides, Pharma and PBMs, Who Drives Up Drug Costs? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arundhati Parmar - Medcity News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TBS’s Score Bug Is Dreadful]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170414</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tbss-score-bug-is-dreadful"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T13:56:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let us say—just as an example—that you were switching back and forth on your TV Monday night, between the ALCS and your favorite hockey team during commercials. Let us pretend, in this scenario, that you did not always switch back to the baseball game in time for the start of each inning, and sometimes missed a few pitches. Let us also imagine that at the start of the bottom of the third, you tuned in just in time to see Juan Soto crank a ball just over the wall in right-center. As he rounded the bases, you would naturally have turned your eyes to the score bug in the top-right of your screen. There, at first glance, and also second and third glances, you would notice the little bases graphic has second base a different color than the other two—lighter, filled in. You have been conditioned by a lifetime of score bugs to know what this means: There was a guy on second! Soto's was a two-run home run!
But no. It was a solo shot. The TBS graphic is just like that. It makes it look like there's always a runner a second.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newhouse KC is an ‘innovative, empathetic disrupter’ combatting local domestic violence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855647</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/newhouse-kc-is-an-innovative-empathetic-disrupter-combatting-local-domestic-violence/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T13:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Newhouse KC’s Website The building that holds Newhouse KC—the area’s longest-serving domestic violence shelter—is ordinary. It’s brown, square, and melts into the background. Its nondescript features turn no heads. The building doesn’t even show up on Google Maps, so most of the public wouldn’t be able to find it. This is how you know that the people...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shannon Carpenter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Go See What’s Swimming Around On Europa]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169530</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/europa-clipper-jupiter-moon-launch-all-these-worlds-are-ours"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T13:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything about the Europa Clipper mission is huge. Sent to investigate the ice-covered and perhaps habitable second moon of Jupiter, it is qualified by NASA as a Large Strategic Science Mission, conveying with that designation its outsized cost, the peak technical capabilities of its instruments, and the importance of the science it expects to undertake. It is just the seventh planetary science mission to receive the LSSM designation, an elite group that includes landmark missions like Voyager probes and Mars rovers.
The spacecraft itself is massive: the largest NASA's ever built. Twenty feet tall, 72 feet wide when its panels are deployed—about the length of an 18-wheeler—more than 13,000 pounds, nearly half of that propellant, the rest the lightest-weight tech there is. Look at this beast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.15.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076201</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-15-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T12:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Partners wonder "who moved my imported, artisanal White Stilton cheese?" [American Lawyer]
* Running a 5:30 am, 122-decibel looped recording of a woman screaming to prove a point ends in lawyers ordered to make door-to-door apologies. [ABA Journal]
* Trump makes another bid to move his NY criminal case to federal court. If at first you don't succeed yadda yadda definition of psychosis. [Reuters]
* DOJ says its Boeing plea deal is the best it could get. Imagine what "trying" could accomplish? [Law360]
* Lewis Brisbois now with considerably less "Lewis." [Bloomberg Law News]
* James Carville gives a shout out to Above the Law around the 48 minute mark of his latest podcast. [Politics War Room]
* Lilly Ledbetter dies at 86. [NY Times]
The post Morning Docket: 10.15.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Notes: Lineup Needs, Outfield, Wacha, Frazier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=827265</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/royals-notes-lineup-needs-outfield-wacha-frazier.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T04:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Royals brass held their end-of-season press conference today, with general manager J.J. Picollo and manager Matt Quatraro fielding questions from MLB.com’s Anne Rogers (two links) and other reporters about the club’s successful 2024 campaign and some of their plans for the coming offseason. While Picollo described the Royals’ offense as “acceptable” overall, the team is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Cole Ragans Built On His Breakout Season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=827257</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/how-cole-ragans-built-on-his-breakout-season.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T02:38:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After losing 106 games in 2023, the Royals responded to the embarrassing result by going on a relative spending spree last winter.  Bobby Witt Jr.’s 11-year, $288.78MM extension naturally drew most of the attention, but Kansas City spent $110.5MM on free agent contracts, most notably bringing Seth Lugo and Michael Wacha to bolster the pitching…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orrin Grey’s Glowing in the Dark collects a decade of critical writing about eerie, uncanny cinema]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855692</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/orrin-greys-glowing-in-the-dark-collects-a-decade-of-critical-writing-about-eerie-uncanny-cinema/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T23:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orrin Grey lives for horror. Not just the horror of modern existence, but the horror of life itself. It’s easy to be the kind of person who appreciates big jumpscares or killer clowns, but there’s a real talent in the mind that chooses to derive joy from the terror of the minutiae. This eye for detail has helped Grey become...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josh Hawley draws rebuke over use of private jets for Missouri Senate campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855711</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/josh-hawley-draws-rebuke-over-use-of-private-jets-for-missouri-senate-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T18:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senator Josh Hawley speaks to reporters aat the governor’s ham breakfast at the Missouri State Fair in Sedalia on Aug. 15 (Annelise Hanshaw/Missouri Independent) One of Josh Hawley’s favorite lines of attack during his first run for U.S. Senate in 2018 was to lambaste his Democratic opponent for using a private jet to travel the state. “I say, ‘Look,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Hancock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Not The Weather Machine That Is Making Life Shittier]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170247</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-not-the-weather-machine-that-is-making-life-shittier"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T17:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you find yourself on FEMA's website, odds are you are already in a worst-case scenario. No one thinks of the Federal Emergency Management Agency except when their house has been reduced to a pile of debris and all the roads leading in and out of your city have been washed off the map. Or, for instance, when you see something on TikTok about the government corralling people in Florida and preventing them from evacuating ahead of catastrophic hurricanes. FEMA works almost exclusively in natural disasters, so there is a bleak logic to devoting pages on its website to fact-check a growing list of hurricane-related conspiracy theories.
"FEMA is not blockading people in Florida and preventing evacuations," one of the entries reads. "FEMA does not control traffic flow or conduct traffic stops, which are handled by local authorities. This is a harmful rumor that can put lives in danger."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with The Boulet Brothers’ Dragula contestant Jaharia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855549</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-the-boulet-brothers-dragula-contestant-jaharia/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T16:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Evening Star Photography When the new season of The Boulet Brothers’ Dragula was announced in September, the Kansas City drag community was shaken. Turns out, one of the creepy-kooky, spooky-kooky contestants hails from the metro. Introducing Jaharia, who’s been turning some ghoulish looks week after week as she battles for the title of World’s Next Drag Supermonster. The horror-themed drag...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Oct. 14: Flower Arrangement]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170288</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-oct-14-flower-arrangement"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smile: It's time to do the crossword! This week's puzzle was constructed by Erik Agard and Kelsey Dixon, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Kelsey is a crossword editor for The Atlantic (magazine). Erik is a crossword editor who has been in the Atlantic (ocean). The tallest person whose hand Erik has ever shaken is Ralph Nader, who is 6-foot-4, but he was sitting down. Kelsey has shaken hands with Artis Gilmore, who is 7-foot-2, and he was standing up! They hope you enjoy this puzzle however you feel most comfortable! 
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nelson-Atkins Museum unveils podcast Art Bytes to deep dive history, context, and conversation behind featured works]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855697</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/nelson-atkins-museum-unveils-podcast-art-bytes-to-deep-dive-history-context-and-conversation-behind-featured-works/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T14:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samantha Koslow chats alongside Kathleen Leighton, host of the podcast Art Bytes, in the fifth episode of the audio series. A new podcast, Art Bytes, has launched at the Nelson-Atkins Museum of Art in Kansas City. Art Bytes is a series geared towards listeners who are interested in art and want to learn more.  Hosted by Kathleen Leighton, Media Relations...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Liberty Too-Smalled The Lynx]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170344</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-liberty-too-smalled-the-lynx"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T14:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BROOKLYN, N.Y. — I chuckled when I saw the words printed on the giveaway T-shirts at Finals Game 2 in New York on Sunday afternoon: “NOT DONE YET.” A kinder reading goes that all contenders think like this, no matter their situation. In the shadow of a Game 1 win, those words might have projected a noble kind of focus. We won’t rest on our regular-season laurels. Job’s not finished. Eyes on the prize. Giveaway shirt production lead times are probably not such that the Liberty ordered thousands of these to cope, anyway. But the shirts took on a slightly grimmer, funnier meaning in light of what actually happened in Game 1: an awful New York collapse. Now, methought the shirt doth protest too much. The “Our Season Is Definitely Not Over” T-shirt had people asking a lot of questions already answered by the shirt.
In a technical sense, it was true, though. The Liberty were not done yet. They still had a split to salvage in New York. And their home crowd, if volume was any sign, loved them no less for their choking. Fans might have felt a sense of déjà vu as the Liberty went up 17 points early, gutted through the second and third quarters, and then let the Lynx make it a one-possession game late in the fourth. But Breanna Stewart, she said afterward, was determined not to let “history repeat itself.” A determined Stewart is an awesome sight, and her arms made possible an alternate ending. Minnesota tried running back the small lineup that had worked for them in Game 1, but Stewart reminded them why it had always been a risky idea. She timed jumps like a defensive back to grab Minnesota lobs out of the air; she hung low to wreck entry passes and dribbles. After Courtney Williams skated past Jonquel Jones to make it a 68-66 game with 3:40 left to play, the Liberty ended the game on a 12-0 run. Stewart would finish with eight rebounds and a Finals-record seven steals, three of them in the fourth quarter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: I'm back and so is fall (MON-10/14)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3696321</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-im-back-and-so-is-fall-mon-10-14/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T14:21:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So let's see, in my absence, you guys have had a ton of summer weather, another huge northern lights experience, a comet in the early evening in the western sky, and yet, still no rain. With the assumption that there is no rain through Sunday, this will be the driest start to October on record. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the disrupter who is about to become Missouri’s next lieutenant governor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855702</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/meet-the-disrupter-who-is-about-to-become-missouris-next-lieutenant-governor/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T13:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Wasinger (photo submitted) For more evidence of Missouri’s drift to the far side of MAGA madness, look no further than the race for lieutenant governor. In the primary election, Republican voters turned aside Lincoln Hough, the veteran senator and state budget expert. They rejected Holly Thompson Rehder, a state senator with a compelling biography and rock-solid conservative values. They...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barbara Shelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The View From The Way, Way Back Of The Berlin Inline Skating Marathon]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170153</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-view-from-the-way-way-back-of-the-berlin-inline-skating-marathon"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T13:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BERLIN — My toenail ripped five miles ago and the pain is overwhelming. The looming dark skies make good on their threat as rain begins to sprinkle. The wind picks up. My heart quickens. I am in the middle of every rollerblader’s nightmare. All around, skaters skid and slow for fear of falling or colliding.
A few feet ahead of me, a far-too chipper man in a white helmet races up to a woman as she cautiously makes her way down the road, her legs shaking harder with every glide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Bice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abby Olcese’s essay collection Films for All Seasons syncs cinematic blockbusters and deep-cuts to explorations of belief]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=849021</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/abby-olceses-essay-collection-films-for-all-seasons-syncs-cinematic-blockbusters-and-deep-cuts-to-explorations-of-belief/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T13:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s your favorite Christmas movie? Easter movie? Pentecost movie? Casual viewers and movie buffs alike have favorite movies to watch at certain times of the year. But for film critic Abby Olcese, movies with spiritual themes aren’t just limited to the holiday season. As our Film Editor at The Pitch, we can attest to that firsthand. The way she’ll program...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Jaguars Are On The Cusp Of The Slope]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170343</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-jaguars-are-on-the-cusp-of-the-slope"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T00:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Jacksonville Jaguars are on a precipice. Or maybe some sort of bluff or enlarged dune. Definitely not a cliff of any kind. The Greatest Show in Teal continued in London on Sunday and the Jaguars were decimated by the Bears to the tune of 35-16. Afterwards head coach Doug Pederson said his 1-5 team was on the verge of something. Greatness? Doom? 
"We're on a slippery slope, or right on the cusp of that slope," Pederson said. "At some point we've got to [say] enough is enough, and you've got to have enough pride and figure out a way."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert DeLong, Atlas Genius co-headline Madrid for rock rave in unfortunately intimate show]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855076</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/robert-delong-atlas-genius-co-headline-madrid-for-rock-rave-in-unfortunately-intimate-show/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T21:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Madrid gig Monday Oct. 7, 2024 with co-headliners Robert DeLong and Atlas Genius. // Photo by Brock Wilbur Monday night saw one of the season’s best rock shows his Midtown KC. Unfortunately, a tremendous trifecta of circumstances aligned to result in The Pitch’s staff being some of the only people in attendance. A Chiefs game against New Orleans, a surprise Royals...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Recover An Onside Kick]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170311</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-to-recover-an-onside-kick"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T20:33:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Saturday, in three separate college football games, I saw a personal record three onside kicks recovered by the kicking team. Our once-beautiful and vibrant (OK, maybe it was never beautiful or vibrant) onside kick culture has suffered some real blows in the last year. The NFL effectively banned surprise onside kicks with its new kickoff rule, which allows onside kicks only in the fourth quarter and also requires the kicking team to declare they are onside kicking. But yesterday, these guys kept the culture alive. Let's consider their onside kick strategies:
1. Rocket It Right Off The Other Guy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lane Thomas Put Detroit’s Ace In A Hole]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170301</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lane-thomas-put-detroits-ace-in-a-hole"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T17:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The challenge of pitching is to stay unknowable—to keep hitters guessing, to never be timed up or figured out. By the end of the Tigers-Guardians American League Divisional Series, which featured a considerable number of relief innings even by the standards of postseason baseball, it did feel like these teams, who had met 13 times already in the regular season, were each becoming quite familiar with the other. The resulting sights could be something unfamiliar to fans: Detroit’s Beau Brieske, who hadn’t given up a home run off his fastball all season, serving up a go-ahead meatball to David Fry in Game 4; unhittable Guardians closer Emmanuel Clase allowing one less earned run in this series than he had all year. The threat of overexposure made each game feel extra tense. “It was such a fun series,” Cleveland manager Stephen Vogt said after Game 5 on Saturday, a 7-3 Guardians win. “Two very evenly matched teams going at it, and it was a lot of fun.” 
Though Cleveland’s path to the postseason wasn’t as bizarre as Detroit’s—the Guardians took first place in the division in mid-April and never relinquished it, despite scares from the Twins and Royals—they were both teams depending on run prevention. The Guardians offense cooled off in the second half, but the team stayed afloat thanks to an elite homegrown bullpen. An early-season injury to ace Shane Bieber, plus some underperformance from young arms, left the Guardians rotation in roughly the same [shrug emoji] shape as the Tigers’ heading into the postseason.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday Notes: Zyhir Hope Has Baseball in His Blood (and Impressive Pop)]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=448768</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/sunday-notes-zyhir-hope-has-baseball-in-his-blood-and-impressive-pop/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T11:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus Xavier Isaac on Noah Schultz, Ryan Pepiot's worst two pitches, Luis Tiant facts, Matt Bowman on sweepers, Carter Jensen on Justin Verlander, facts and stats galore, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Laurila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL Week 6 Uniform Schedule: Panthers Debuting New Combination While Patriots, Jets Wearing Throwback Threads]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82613</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/13/nfl-week-6-uniform-schedule-panthers-debuting-new-combination-while-patriots-jets-wearing-throwback-threads/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T07:21:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our weekly series that looks at every uniform matchup across the NFL continues with the Carolina Panthers debuting a new uniform combination and the New England Patriots and New York Jets wearing throwback uniforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>