<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-10-30T08:22:46.822Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Green Bay Packers To Wear 1950s Throwback Uniforms On Sunday]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83106</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/30/green-bay-packers-to-wear-1950s-throwback-uniforms-on-sunday/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T06:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Green Bay Packers announced they'll wear their 1950s throwback uniforms during Sunday's game against the Detroit Lions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Hope The Work Pays Off — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076770</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/lets-hope-the-work-pays-off-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T23:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billing For A Special Treat: Bonus season is around the corner and associates are working hard!
Everything Comes Up On The Campaign Trail: Judge faces ethics complaint for her stance on reproductive rights.
Layoffs Are Headed To The ACLU: The Northern California office is expected to hit by mid-November.
Pay Now Or Pay Later: Moody's former general counsel sentenced over tax evasion.
Judge Prevents Troop Ballots From Being Thrown Away: Remember when voting was simple?
The post Let’s Hope The Work Pays Off — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Associates Are Getting Ready For A Big Payday]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076760</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/biglaw-associates-are-getting-ready-for-a-big-payday/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T23:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four months later is better than not at all.
The post Biglaw Associates Are Getting Ready For A Big Payday appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Three Principles Of Responsible AI Development, And Other Takeaways From The Everlaw Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076725</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/10/the-three-principles-of-responsible-ai-development-and-other-takeaways-from-the-everlaw-summit.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T22:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO AJ Shankar detailed the core principles that guide the company’s AI development – principles that he said are 'table stakes' to ensuring responsible AI development and the best long-term outcomes for customers.
The post The Three Principles Of Responsible AI Development, And Other Takeaways From The Everlaw Summit appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Of Course Kamala Harris Could Do A Joe Rogan Interview…]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076742</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/of-course-kamala-harris-could-do-a-joe-rogan-interview/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T21:28:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the wife of an entertainment lawyer, the VP *really* knows how to make 'charming small talk.'
The post Of Course Kamala Harris Could Do A Joe Rogan Interview… appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PA Judge Tosses Effort By GOP Congressmen To Throw Out Military And Overseas Ballots]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076758</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/pa-judge-tosses-effort-by-gop-congressmen-to-throw-out-military-and-overseas-ballots/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T20:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For America!
The post PA Judge Tosses Effort By GOP Congressmen To Throw Out Military And Overseas Ballots appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sadly, Jerrod Mustaf Was More Than A Basketball Player]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171730</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/sadly-jerrod-mustaf-was-more-than-a-basketball-player"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T20:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I interviewed Jerrod Mustaf in 2003. At the time, he was launching a basketball minor league called the Street Basketball Association. I asked Mustaf, a former first-round pick of the New York Knicks whose own playing career ended years earlier after he was tied to an Arizona homicide, if he thought his past would hamper his chances at getting back into the game in any meaningful way.
“The jury’s still out,” he told me.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Moody’s General Counsel Gets Prison Time For Tax Evasion]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076762</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/former-moodys-general-counsel-gets-prison-time-for-tax-evasion/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T20:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don't forget the government's cut!
The post Former Moody’s General Counsel Gets Prison Time For Tax Evasion appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Questions For A Court Access Crusader (Part II)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076439</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/3-questions-for-a-court-access-crusader-part-ii/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T19:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can all hope that AI can be a boon to the challenging task of assimilating an ever-growing set of data generated by the legal industry.
The post 3 Questions For A Court Access Crusader (Part II) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaston Kroub</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dan And Dave Visit A Mall Over The Ocean]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171485</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dan-and-dave-visit-a-mall-over-the-ocean"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T19:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John L. Young called it the Million Dollar Pier, because he said it cost a million dollars to build. That was a lot of money at the time, and so very much something that John L. Young would say. The former lifeguard had been a showman on the Atlantic City boardwalk at various locations, and in 1906 opened his showpiece amusement pier in what was then an up-and-coming New Jersey resort city.
“His twice-daily, deep-sea net hauls were famous, attracting thousands of wide-eyed tourists,” Nelson Johnson writes in Boardwalk Empire: The Birth, High Times And Corruption of Atlantic City. “Wearing knickers, an old sweater and cap, he was a wiry and weathered, red-faced man with sparkling blue eyes, reminiscent of a leprechaun. As he lowered the net to the floor of the pier, Young went into his routine of identifying the sea animals he had caught. It was an animated performance that mesmerized his customers.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new queer matchmaking experience Where To Find Us allows friends to show off single besties]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858836</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/a-new-queer-matchmaking-experience-where-to-find-us-allows-friends-to-show-off-single-besties/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T19:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Where To Find Us Find your next connection with Where To Find Us, a new queer-centric matchmaking event that brings singles together for a night of love and laughter on Nov. 21.  Located at the Parlor KC , the event gives friends a chance to pitch their single bestie to a room of potential matches. Lo Cowan and Tiffany...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s NBL Brings Back Indigenous Round for Another Season]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83089</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/29/australias-nbl-brings-back-indigenous-round-for-another-season/basketball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T18:44:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teams across Australia and New Zealand will wear jerseys designed by local Indigenous artists for games between November 7 and 10]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Pre-Election Dog Story For You, The Dog Fan]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171657</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-pre-election-dog-story-for-you-the-dog-fan"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T18:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about cool stadiums, Danny DeVito, cancelled puddings, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building CoPilot’s CoPilot (For Lawyers)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076751</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/building-copilots-copilot-for-lawyers/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T18:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's CoPilot could become the default AI for business... who will make it work for legal?
The post Building CoPilot’s CoPilot (For Lawyers) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Misterwives at the Truman]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858591</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-misterwives-at-the-truman/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T17:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Misterwives. // photo by Daniel Fuchs Misterwives with Joan and Moody Joody The Truman Sunday, October 27 Touring in support of Nosebleeds: Encore, the deluxe one-year anniversary edition of their 2023 album, New York indie pop act Misterwives took to the Truman stage on Sunday to play a set drawing from their nearly decade-long catalog. In fact, Misterwives’ set was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Fuchs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans Are Politicizing Judicial Ethics Complaints]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076754</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/republicans-are-politicizing-judicial-ethics-complaints/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T17:47:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at what's happening in North Carolina.
The post Republicans Are Politicizing Judicial Ethics Complaints appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Porches at recordBar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858596</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-porches-at-recordbar/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Porches. // photo by Whitney Young Porches with sweet93 RecordBar Friday, October 25 Friday night, Aaron Maine’s synth-pop project Porches took to the stage of RecordBar in support of his recent album, Shirt. sweet93, also known as Chloe Kohanski, the winner of The Voice season 13, opened, and our photographer Whitney Young was there to cpature it all. Porches sweet93...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Whitney Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barcelona Has Put It All Together]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171660</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/barcelona-has-put-it-all-together"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T17:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the long and storied history of Barcelona, this past week hardly rates as one of its best. This is a club that has won 27 La Liga trophies, five Champions Leagues, a sextuple, you name it. Two wins in four days is great, and doubly so when considering the opposition, but it's still only October, and there are no ticker-tape parades under the Arc de Triomf in October. Nevertheless, Barcelona really needed this exact week, with these exact results, in its efforts to shake off the doldrums that have haunted it in its post–Lionel Messi haze, and at last inaugurate a new era worthy of the best of the old ones.
The week from heaven started in the Champions League on Oct. 23. Barcelona had started this newly formatted tournament with a wet fart, losing 2-1 to Monaco in the opener after Eric García got himself sent off in the 10th minute. Though a 5-0 drubbing of Swiss side Young Boys followed, the level of the opposition meant the match was more or less useless in determining what the ceiling of first-year manager Hansi Flick's new-look, refreshed, but still unproven side was going to be. The first serious test came last Wednesday at the hands of Bayern Munich, and it's safe to say Barcelona aced it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Associates Are Billing Hours In Bulk, Hoping For Special Bonuses On Top Of Regular Bonuses]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076743</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/biglaw-associates-are-billing-hours-in-bulk-hoping-for-special-bonuses-on-top-of-regular-bonuses/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T16:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw associates definitely didn't forget about the Milbank summer bonuses, and they're expecting to make BANK come bonus season.
The post Biglaw Associates Are Billing Hours In Bulk, Hoping For Special Bonuses On Top Of Regular Bonuses appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dream Of The 1980s Is Alive And Unwell On Atlantic City Playlists]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171524</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-dream-of-the-1980s-is-alive-and-unwell-on-atlantic-city-playlists"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T16:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before last week, I had a grand total of two gambling/casino experiences to my name, and they were both embarrassing and terrible. There was the time when I completely screwed up a free-money loophole on a betting app and had to sweat out a bunch of stupid college basketball games, and there was the time I went to a wedding in Aurora, Ill. and smashed a beer bottle during a too-enthusiastic swing on a Golden Tee machine.
So when I first heard that Defector was going to Atlantic City for its fall meetings, I was nervous and determined to spend my leisure money only on candy and pinball. I had confidence that I wouldn't be tempted to gamble, but I knew casinos and their ilk were dens of trickery, structured to trap you into semi-consciously giving them whole wads of cash. I didn't love our odds as a company of surviving the week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solos & Small Firm Lawyers: Have You Taken Our Compensation Survey Yet?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076727</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/solos-small-firm-lawyers-compensation-survey/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T16:19:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tell us how much you make and help us benchmark small firm pay.
The post Solos & Small Firm Lawyers: Have You Taken Our Compensation Survey Yet? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeff Bezos Made Someone Else’s Business Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171640</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jeff-bezos-made-someone-elses-business-decision"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T15:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Friday, Washington Post publisher and CEO Will Lewis announced in an editorial published on the paper's website that the Post's editorial board would not be endorsing a candidate in the 2024 presidential election, as it has traditionally done. 
The backlash to this decision arrived swiftly and from all directions, thanks largely to reporting from NPR's David Folkenflik, who revealed that the editorial board had in fact drafted an endorsement of Democratic candidate Kamala Harris earlier this month. According to Folkenflik's reporting, the paper's billionaire owner, Jeff Bezos, reviewed a draft of the endorsement before Lewis announced that the Post would not be endorsing a candidate this year. Some Post staffers, faced with their publication's owner meddling in editorial decisions, revolted. A few published articles criticizing management's decision to nix the endorsement, while others submitted letters of resignation. A much bigger and more damaging reaction came from outside the paper: According to Folkenflik, at least 200,000 people have cancelled their digital subscriptions to the Post since the publication of Lewis's editorial, a number that represents roughly eight percent of the paper's paid circulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Firms Do Lawyers Love? More Than 700 Readers Weigh In [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076745</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/ranking-the-law-firms-lawyers-love/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T15:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing our inaugural ranking of Most Desirable Firms, along with other lateral market insights.
The post Which Firms Do Lawyers Love? More Than 700 Readers Weigh In appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ABOVE THE LAW AND LATERAL LINK</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They’re Saying It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170499</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/theyre-saying-it"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T15:07:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is not quite right to say that you never know what you're going to get from a Donald Trump campaign event. You might see some things, up to and including the richest man alive showing up and capering about behind Trump like a weird child, but fundamentally people go to these events for the same reason that people stand around in Times Square on New Year's Eve, which is to wait for and then witness the one big thing that they know will happen. Taken on its own, there's nothing much to the jerky descent of a bedazzled ball at midnight, and probably even less to a peevish former president pivoting disconcertingly from side to side before horking up some undigested chunk of reactionary cable-news gristle at mid-size convention center, but also there doesn't really have to be. There isn't re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Layoffs Are Headed For Public Interest Attorneys In Northern California]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076741</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/layoffs-are-headed-for-public-interest-attorneys-in-northern-california/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T14:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ACLU NorCal is gearing up for some cuts.
The post Layoffs Are Headed For Public Interest Attorneys In Northern California appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Lives At The Rainforest Cafe?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171338</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/who-lives-at-the-rainforest-cafe"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T14:29:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A RAINFOREST, New Jersey — Last week in Atlantic City, amid discussions of business, enterprise, and strategy, nearly half of the Defector staff convened for fine dining at the exclusive, Michelin-snubbed establishment that is the Rainforest Cafe. Sean, Justin, and I had the unique privilege of shepherding Ray into his first-ever Rainforest Cafe experience, which quickly catapulted him into an abyssal state of misery that persisted despite a glass of the Rainforest Cafe house red. But that is not what I am here to discuss. I am here to discuss the creatures.
As soon as I glimpsed the dark tunnel of vines that connects the Rainforest Cafe gift shop to the Rainforest Cafe restaurant, a threshold I had not crossed since my halcyon days, a question began buzzing in my mind: Which rainforest is the Rainforest Cafe supposed to be? Of course, the most obvious candidate would be the Amazon, the world's only A-List rainforest. But I also suspected that Rainforest Cafe may be a product of its time and represent not one particular biome, but rather a melange of all rainforests—the high-concept restaurant equivalent of a Coexist decal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Stronger storm risk tomorrow (TUE-10/29)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3711055</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-stronger-storm-risk-tomorrow-tue-10-29/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T14:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Storm risks increase mid-afternoon but especially Wednesday evening in Kansas City. Some storms may have stronger winds, some smaller hail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strict Abortion Laws Are Likely Already Having An Economic Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076724</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/10/strict-abortion-laws-is-likely-already-having-an-economic-impact/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T14:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A panel of experts at the HLTH conference agreed that states with strict abortion measures are likely to see negative economic impact as medical residents decline to train there and physicians move out.
The post Strict Abortion Laws Are Likely Already Having An Economic Impact appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ARUNDHATI PARMAR - MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.29.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076739</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-29-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T13:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Ready and rested Steve Bannon is out of prison. Check to see if he has any new tattoos! [NBC]
* Pay guarantees are back at firms unwilling to lose out on lateral partners thinking the grass may not be greener. [American Lawyer]
* Second Circuit upholds New York concealed carry law after Supreme Court showed Bruen buyer's remorse. [ABA Journal]
* Subway sandwiches may no longer be footlongs or $5 and now a lawsuit claims they might be short of meat. [Reuters]
* New bid from Pennsylvania Republicans sets the stage for the Supreme Court to seize control of the election... if justices want to take it. [Vox]
* Ninth Circuit delivers victory to opponents of forced arbitration. [Law360]
* In unsurprising news, there's a hefty statistical uptick in infant mortality following the Supreme Court's Dobbs decision. [Balls and Strikes]
The post Morning Docket: 10.29.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If This World Series Ends In A Sweep I Will Launch The Yankees Into The Sun]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171642</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/if-this-world-series-ends-in-a-sweep-i-will-launch-the-yankees-into-the-sun"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T13:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No team karmically deserves a championship, though that sentiment is especially true this year. Neither the Dodgers nor the Yankees chalk up kindly on the moral scale of historic suffering, but, on paper, they can make up for it by promising entertainment for the masses: a powerhouse vs. powerhouse match-up laden with stars. What, then, to make of the fact that one of the purported powerhouses not only currently resembles an ant, but one of those types of ant whose primary defense mechanism is literally exploding?
After falling to a 2-0 series deficit to the Dodgers to open the World Series, the Yankees spent their first game at home making their eventual 4-2 loss feel like a blowout. Now, as per the laws of arithmetic, the Yankees are down 3-0. The sweep alarms are going off! The spaceship is steering itself directly into the sun! The Dodgers have continued getting their postseason success from relatively unexpected corners. The "Three Batters Away"-style FOX chyrons for Shohei Ohtani (though also used for other stars, such as Juan Soto and Bryce Harper) weren't paying off even before people started making slow-motion videos of Ohtani's backpack-wearing range of motion. Then again, the Dodgers haven't needed them to. After all: Freddie Freeman.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lockstep Revamp Means Big Money! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076716</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/lockstep-revamp-means-big-money-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T23:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clifford Chance Is Switching Things Up: Being a partner really pays!
Crossing The Pond: Magic Circle firm wants to open offices in Texas and Boston.
No Thoughts In The Study Room: Harvard punishes faculty for protesting by reading quietly in the library.
Timing Issues: Judges ignore history to get textual about what the "Day" in "Election Day" means.
Current Events Aren't The Only Things That Are Spooky!: Prepare for ATL's 15th annual Legally Themed Halloween Costume Contest!
The post Lockstep Revamp Means Big Money! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tracking The Moves Of The Supreme Court]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076722</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/tracking-the-moves-of-the-supreme-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T23:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like physical moves, not the jurisprudence of the Court.
The post Tracking The Moves Of The Supreme Court appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Biglaw Attorney Tells Trump To Eliminate FBI Background Checks For Security Clearance]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076714</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/former-biglaw-attorney-tells-trump-to-eliminate-fbi-background-checks-for-security-clearance/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T22:18:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Background check? Don't know her.
The post Former Biglaw Attorney Tells Trump To Eliminate FBI Background Checks For Security Clearance appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where The Candidates Stand On Police Accountability And Reform]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076708</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/where-the-candidates-stand-on-police-accountability-and-reform/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T21:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[National Police Accountability Project breaks down the records of both candidates.
The post Where The Candidates Stand On Police Accountability And Reform appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nick Bosa Wants The Attention Without The Culpability]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171573</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nick-bosa-wants-the-attention-without-the-culpability"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T20:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shortly after the San Francisco 49ers' 30-24 win over the Dallas Cowboys, Sunday Night Football's Melissa Stark interviewed a couple of players from the winning team. George Kittle, Brock Purdy, and Isaac Guerendo were in the middle of answering questions when their teammate Nick Bosa briefly popped into the background, pointing at the Make America Great Again hat on his head. "All right, Nick Bosa with a message there," Stark said before continuing her interview.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Knew What When? The Latest In The Judge/Partner Romantic Scandal Rocking The Legal World]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076693</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/who-knew-what-when-the-latest-in-the-judge-partner-romantic-scandal-rocking-the-legal-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T20:46:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Soap opera or legal ethics lapse? Feels like both.
The post Who Knew What When? The Latest In The Judge/Partner Romantic Scandal Rocking The Legal World appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Judges Pen ‘Election Day’ Fan Fiction That Tosses Bunches Of Ballots]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076698</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/trump-judges-pen-election-day-fan-fiction-that-tosses-bunches-of-ballots/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T20:02:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone knows the definition of 'Election Day' is about casting ballots. What these Trump judges suppose is, 'What if it isn't?'
The post Trump Judges Pen ‘Election Day’ Fan Fiction That Tosses Bunches Of Ballots appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Max Verstappen Finally Punished For Driving Like Max Verstappen]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171505</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/max-verstappen-finally-punished-for-driving-like-max-verstappen"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T19:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has rarely been a shortage of drama in this topsy-turvy Formula 1 season, with no truly boring weekends to speak of since the weather turned warm, but Sunday's Mexico City Grand Prix stood out, thanks to chaos up and down the grid. It seemed that every lap had a different combination of drivers trying to ram each other off the road, all while sending aggrieved radio messages like they were going out of style. By the end of the 71 laps, almost every driver had a bone to pick with someone, whether that was an opponent, a teammate, or a pit wall.
The 20th race of the season started with Yuki Tsunoda and Alex Albon making contact before the first turn, landing both drivers with a Did Not Finish, and only got sillier from there. Sergio Pérez continued to be down real bad in what surely has to be his last home race on a top team—it has to be, right? Right?—drawing more notice for calling Liam Lawson an idiot after a scuffle on the track. (Lawson also flipped off Pérez on track; the Australian has been really good at pissing off the old guard, following last week's entanglement with Fernando Alonso.) Teammates Carlos Sainz and Charles Leclerc had a frosty post-race moment, as Ferrari had Leclerc hang back during the race in order to not slow Sainz down, only for Lando Norris to take advantage of the reduced pace and pass the Monegasque driver. Ferrari's plan worked, but only for Sainz, who won the day, followed by Norris in second. Leclerc couldn't fight back against the McLaren and finished third, although with the fastest lap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk Sued By PA District Attorney For Running Illegal Election Lottery]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076701</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/musk-sued-by-pa-district-attorney-for-running-illegal-election-lottery/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T19:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But what if we call the winners subcontractors? Is that cool?
The post Musk Sued By PA District Attorney For Running Illegal Election Lottery appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Like Erik Done Hag]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171491</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/more-like-erik-done-hag"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T19:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester United lost at West Ham 2-1 on Sunday. After equalizing in the 81st minute, the visitors conceded a penalty in the second minute of stoppage time, which Jarrod Bowen converted for the winner. The loss dropped the miserable Red Devils to 14th in the Premier League table, with 11 points in nine matches. Only two clubs in the league have scored fewer goals than United's measly eight. On Monday the club announced the dismissal of manager Erik ten Hag, which, well, that makes sense.
In 2022-23, his first full season with the club, Ten Hag led the Red Devils to a League Cup title and a return to Champions League qualification; perhaps just as impressively, he ran off Cristiano Ronaldo and seemed to rejuvenate a moribund Marcus Rashford, who scored 30 goals in all competitions. It's been a steep and largely uninterrupted fall since then. Last season United plunged to an eighth-place finish, its lowest since the advent of the Premier League, and squandered that UCL berth, finishing dead last in Group A with four points from six matches and even missing out on the Europa League fallback spot. Rashford regressed; Ten Hag picked a stupid fight with winger Jadon Sancho and banished him from the squad; the Brazilian winger Antony, one of Ten Hag's flagship additions, performed abysmally on the field while also facing horrifying domestic violence accusations from an ex-girlfriend and two others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard Doubles Down On ‘Protest’ Retaliation & Punishes Teachers For Studying In Library]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076695</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/harvard-doubles-down-on-protest-retaliation-punishes-teachers-for-studying-in-library/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T18:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a bad look for the school.
The post Harvard Doubles Down On ‘Protest’ Retaliation & Punishes Teachers For Studying In Library appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Origins and Oddities of World Series Patches and Uniforms]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83075</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/28/the-origins-and-oddities-of-world-series-patches-and-uniforms/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T18:21:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look back at the history of teams wearing World Series patches on their uniforms and some of the oddities that have happened along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Creamer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Partners Are Making Bank, ‘Very Satisfied’ With Their Pay]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076697</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/biglaw-partners-are-making-bank-very-satisfied-with-their-pay/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T17:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw partners seem to be pretty pleased with their financials.
The post Biglaw Partners Are Making Bank, ‘Very Satisfied’ With Their Pay appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Browns Win Because Of, Despite Jameis Winston]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171503</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/browns-win-because-of-despite-jameis-winston"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T17:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cleveland Browns snapped their five-game losing streak on Sunday, upsetting the Baltimore Ravens 29-24 in their first game since quarterback Deshaun Watson tore his Achilles tendon. Beating the best team in the division immediately after losing the quarterback they're paying $46 million per season—a mega-contract with two more years on it to which the Browns signed Watson after 22 massage therapists had already filed sexual assault lawsuits against him—is a funny result for a rotten organization, although, as befits the Browns, even the triumph was weird and off-putting. They got the full-strength Jameis Winston experience, as the vet threw his team into and nearly out of a big win.
One week ago, Winston seemed unlikely to see the field this season. The Browns demoted him to emergency QB and listed him as inactive before their Week 7 game against the Cincinnati Bengals, only for emergency to strike. Not only did Watson tear his Achilles in that game, but backup Dorian Thompson-Robinson hurt a finger on his throwing hand after playing two godawful quarters in Watson's stead. So the Browns activated Winston and became the first team in 16 years to have three different players attempt double-digit passes in the same game. Winston earned the start this week and instantly cut a weird promo before the game, looking directly into the broadcast camera as he touted his "unwavering faith, ultimate belief, depending on the lord." He echoed similar sentiments in a signature lacrimal pregame hype speech to his team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Real Friends at the Granada]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858261</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-real-friends-at-the-granada/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T17:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Real Friends. // photo by Daniel Fuchs Real Friends with Can’t Swim, Carly Cosgrove, and Slow Joy The Granada Friday, October 25 Touring in support of their recently-released fourth album, Blue Hour, Illinois emo pop punkers Real Friends took to the Granada stage on Friday night. On hand for support were New Jersey rockers Can’t Swim, indie emo trio Carly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Fuchs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Sofi Tukker at the Midland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858257</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-sofi-tukker-at-the-midland/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T17:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sofi Tukker. // photo by Kylee Gregg Sofi Tukker with Shermanology The Midland Tuesday, October 22 Indie dance duo Sofi Tukker brought the BREAD Tour to the Midland on Tuesday, October 22, with Dutch electronic duo Shermanology opening. Our photographer Kylee Gregg was there to capture it all. Sofi Tukker Shermanology Categories: Music Tags: photo gallery, shermanology, sofi tukker, The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kylee Gregg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International Biglaw Firm’s Expansion Plan Comes To U.S. Cities]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076694</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/international-biglaw-firms-expansion-plan-comes-to-u-s-cities/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T17:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freshfields is looking to grow here.
The post International Biglaw Firm’s Expansion Plan Comes To U.S. Cities appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike McCarthy Is Still Sitting In The Hottest Seat In Sports]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171538</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mike-mccarthy-is-still-sitting-in-the-hottest-seat-in-sports"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T16:54:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that Manchester United's latest ex-coach Erik ten Hag has been finally been deposed as the world's meest verslagen piñata (that's "most beaten piñata" for our non-Dutch readership), the new leader in the field of hanging from the rafters and swinging tortuously from side to side is Dallas Cowboys coach Mike McCarthy. There is nobody else even close.
It wasn’t so long ago that we had Robert Saleh, Sheldon Keefe, Christie Sides, and Pedro Grifol. All had high-profile jobs and higher-profile stars—Saleh had the New York Jets and Aaron Rodgers, Keefe had the Toronto Maple Leafs and Auston Matthews, Sides had the Indiana Fever and Caitlin Clark, and Grifol had the Chicago White Sox and, uh, Corey Julks, but also this year’s White Sox were an outlier’s outlier, and so deserve mention all the same.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Firm Revamps Its Lockstep Partner Comp System To Offer Huge Paydays To Top Talent]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076691</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/biglaw-firm-revamps-its-lockstep-partner-comp-system-to-offer-huge-paydays-to-top-talent/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T16:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wow! The top UK-based firm really wants to make it rain on its partners.
The post Biglaw Firm Revamps Its Lockstep Partner Comp System To Offer Huge Paydays To Top Talent appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former RePaul’s Drag Race contestants pay homage to KC with ‘Queens of Oz’ tribute show]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858175</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/former-repauls-drag-race-contestants-pay-homage-to-kansas-city-with-queens-of-oz-tribute-show/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T16:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drag queens Widow Von’Du, Mo Heart and Q present the Queens of Oz tribute show on Nov. 8. // Provided by The Truman Theatre Something wicked is making its way to the Truman Theatre, located at 601 E Truman Rd, on Nov. 8. Drag artists Widow Von’Du, Q, and Mo Heart will share the stage at the Queens of Oz...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Oct. 28: A Cryptic!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171506</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-oct-28-a-cryptic"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T15:05:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re celebrating our first full year of Defector crosswords with a slightly different kind of puzzle than you’re used to, a cryptic by Hoang-Kim Vu. Kim works in global public health in Washington, D.C., and is a member of the crossword editing team at Defector and AVCX. His puzzles have appeared in numerous outlets, including the New York Times, Los Angeles Times, and USA Today. We’ll be back to our regularly scheduled programming next week, but thanks for solving along. It’s been a fun year of puzzles.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. Launched 16 years ago as the house crossword of The Onion, the AVCX not only offers weekly standard crosswords, but also midi puzzles, a cryptic, a themeless offering, and a trivia contest. Like Defector, AVCX is an independent venture with a fresher sensibility than mainstream outlets, and is committed to diversity in its masthead, fair pay to our contributors, and a fiercely progressive streak. And like Defector, the AVCX relies on subscriptions from solvers like you. If you like Defector's puzzles, please consider a subscription with the AVCX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Past 2 Weeks, Without The Candidates’ Names]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076689</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-past-2-weeks-without-the-candidates-names/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T14:51:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How would you react to some of the recent statements and events if neither candidate's name was attached?
The post The Past 2 Weeks, Without The Candidates’ Names appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Herrmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Commanders Pulled Off The Perfect Hail Mary]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171465</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-commanders-pulled-off-the-perfect-hail-mary"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T14:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A good Hail Mary looks like chaos, and isn't. It's not just a matter of having every receiver sprint to the end zone, chucking the ball up, and hoping for the best. A good Hail Mary is a designed play. Everyone has their spot to be in, their role to play. If it still requires a mini-miracle to complete, well, a good Hail Mary is about shaving off the odds by controlling what you can control. And Washington's 52-yard touchdown to beat Chicago 18-15 at the buzzer on Sunday was not merely a good Hail Mary; it was flawless. This [football man voice] is how you draw it up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Singer Settles For Torturing Southwest CEO Rather Than Firing Him]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076677</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/10/paul-singer-settles-for-torturing-southwest-ceo-rather-than-firing-him"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T14:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bob Jordan may live to regret this ‘victory.’
The post Paul Singer Settles For Torturing Southwest CEO Rather Than Firing Him appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Winds, heat, and drought easing rains ahead (MON-10/28)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3709898</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-winds-heat-and-drought-easing-rains-ahead-mon-10-28/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T14:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heading into Halloween and the weather is going to be very variable over the next week or so as things are changing now in the jet stream. Gone will be the persistent dryness that plagued the area for the late summer into mid fall time period. Rain chances will become more frequent and the drought [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe's Weather Blog | In-depth Kansas City forecasts | FOX4KC</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Jets Are All Out Of Scapegoats And Need A Quarterback]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171459</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-jets-are-all-out-of-scapegoats-and-need-a-quarterback"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T13:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Jets were supposed to be a Super Bowl contender with a healthy Aaron Rodgers; they are 2-6 and at this point would be extraordinarily lucky to reach the playoffs. Through eight games last year, they were 4-4 with Zach Wilson. How many excuses are left for Rodgers to deploy?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.28.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076688</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-28-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T13:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Freshfields eyes expansion. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Fifth Circuit rules union busting to be protected speech. [Reuters]
* Also, a Fifth Circuit panel of three guys trying to be Trump's next Supreme Court nominee redefined how absentee voting works a week before the election. And even if it doesn't go into effect right away, the confusion it causes might just be enough. [Slate]
* The task of training young lawyers in the AI era. [Artificial Lawyer]
* Delta going after Crowdstrike over global IT collapse. [Law360]
* Did not have "foreign aristocracy" on my Bingo card of people funding the lives of Supreme Court justices but here we are. [ABA Journal]
* Things aren't getting better for Jackson Walker in wake of judge scandal. [Texas Lawyer]
The post Morning Docket: 10.28.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Just One Day Travel Tours’ Sherrie Ortiz]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=857676</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-just-one-day-travel-tours-sherrie-ortiz/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T13:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Sherrie Ortiz Sherrie Ortiz is omnipresent—figuratively and literally. After decades of owning a bakery, Ortiz wanted to spread her wings a bit. So, she started Just One Day Travel Tours, where she curates personalized walking and bus tours for conferences, family events, team bonding, reunions, and more. “I love it when someone calls me and says, ‘I have this crazy idea for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Lakers Already Feel Different]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171430</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/these-lakers-already-feel-different"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T17:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Lakers are off to a 3-0 start, with wins against three teams that finished ahead of them in the West last season. Each victory has allowed them an opportunity to flash different strengths.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hornets Are Under Construction, But LaMelo Ball Is Still Really Fun To Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171409</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-hornets-are-under-construction-but-lamelo-ball-is-still-really-fun-to-watch"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T15:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though he hasn't shown it much in the past couple seasons, a healthy LaMelo Ball is capable of producing some breathtaking moments and gaudy stat lines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL Week 8 Uniform Schedule: Buccaneers, 49ers Wearing Throwback Uniforms, Bengals Donning White Alternate Helmets]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83062</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/27/nfl-week-8-uniform-schedule-buccaneers-49ers-wearing-throwback-uniforms-bengals-donning-white-alternate-helmets/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T15:31:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our weekly series that looks at every uniform matchup across the NFL continues with the Tampa Bay Buccaneers and San Francisco 49ers wearing their throwback uniforms and the Cincinnati Bengals donning their white alternate helmets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ah Shit, Shohei Ohtani Messed Up His Shoulder]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171413</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ah-shit-shohei-ohtani-messed-up-his-shoulder"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T14:29:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Los Angeles Dodgers hold a 2-0 lead in the World Series after Saturday night's 4-2 win over the New York Yankees, but the biggest concern right now is the state of Shohei Ohtani's labrum. The Dodgers superstar exited the game in the seventh inning after a stolen-base attempt partially dislocated his shoulder.
With two outs in the bottom of the seventh, Ohtani took off for second base and caught his arm awkwardly in the slide. After he was tagged out to end the inning, he stayed on the ground in pain while Dodgers staff attended to him. He then left the field holding his arm and didn't return. After Los Angeles escaped a dicey ninth inning to seal the win, manager Dave Roberts shared an update: Ohtani had suffered a left shoulder subluxation, and he would undergo further tests including an MRI on Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKC Baseball Club rebrands as Comets in honor of Mickey Mantle]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83036</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/26/okc-baseball-club-rebrands-as-comets-in-honor-of-mickey-mantle/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T00:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Los Angeles Dodgers and New York Yankees took to the field in game 2 of the World Series, the Dodgers Triple-A affiliate in Oklahoma City announced a new identity that pays homage to a Yankee icon. The Oklahoma City Comets name and identity, just unveiled moments ago, are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Caputo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Bird Passes Away]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=828264</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/doug-bird-passes-away.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-26T23:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[11-year MLB veteran Doug Bird passed away late last month, according to an obituary from a North Carolina funeral home. The former Royals, Phillies, Yankees, Cubs, and Red Sox right-hander was 74 years old. A California native in his early years, Bird was drafted by the Royals in the summer of 1969. He spent the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrat candidate for Missouri AG says teen pregnancy argument in abortion pill lawsuit is ‘insane’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858207</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/democrat-says-missouri-ags-teen-pregnancy-argument-in-abortion-pill-lawsuit-is-insane/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-26T20:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic candidate for Missouri Attorney General Elad Gross after filing to run for office in February (Annelise Hanshaw/Missouri Independent) Missouri Attorney General Andrew Bailey’s contention that a decrease in teen pregnancy could hurt the state financially and politically is “an absolutely insane argument,” his Democratic rival on the Nov. 5 ballot said Thursday. “Apparently he believes we need more teen...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Hancock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AL Central Notes: Warren, White Sox, Manfred, Caglianone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=828254</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/al-central-notes-warren-white-sox-manfred-caglianone.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-26T19:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tigers had interest in right-hander Will Warren during their trade talks with the Yankees this past summer, the New York Post’s Jon Heyman reports.  The two clubs reportedly had a provisional agreement involving Jack Flaherty relatively close to being completed before New York backed out due to concerns over Flaherty’s medical records, though it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That’s How You Start A World Series]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171396</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/thats-how-you-start-a-world-series"/>
        <updated>2024-10-26T14:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you think about sports as a television show rather than some fit people running around and doing things, Game 1 of the World Series was a terrible idea. Yes, the series is well cast, and the production value is solid by contemporary standards, but you just cannot give away your best stuff in the pilot episode.
Fortunately, by the rules of our diminishing yet still shared reality, Game 1 was an extraordinary epic. Freddie Freeman pointing his bat toward the sky after hitting the first walk-off grand slam in World Series history—straight up, rather than in the direction of the game-winner he’d just vaporized—told everyone watching that whatever else happens in these next several days, a baseball event is coming from on high. On this night, and maybe for the next week, football could eat what we in the agricultural sciences call shit. Baseball is, for the moment, back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facts Don’t Care About Your Feelings — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076667</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/facts-dont-care-about-your-feelings-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T23:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being Honest Is A Huge Hurdle In A Defamation Case: Waste of time and money.
Come On Guys, He Just Likes Hitler!: Jonathan Turley is doing damage control for Trump.
Lyle And Erik Could Be Up For Parole: LA DA wants to resentence the Menendez brothers.
UChicago Makes It Harder For Students To Learn: There's no need for a policy this strict.
Now That's A Fancy Ticket!: Alito gifted festival tickets by a literal princess.
The post Facts Don’t Care About Your Feelings — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partners In This Practice Area Are Doing Exceptionally Well]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076663</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/partners-in-this-practice-area-are-doing-exceptionally-well/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T23:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They're having a helluva run.
The post Partners In This Practice Area Are Doing Exceptionally Well appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alito Discloses Gift From Far-Right European Princess]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076662</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/alito-discloses-gift-from-far-right-european-princess/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T22:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wonder if Justice Kagan ever wishes she just took the damned bagels. 
The post Alito Discloses Gift From Far-Right European Princess appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Something Else Goldman-For-The-People Didn’t Do Very Well]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076622</id>
        <link href="https://dealbreaker.com/2024/10/heres-something-else-goldman-for-the-people-didnt-do-very-well"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T21:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the Insult to Injury Department.
The post Here’s Something Else Goldman-For-The-People Didn’t Do Very Well appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Shazar - Dealbreaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conquering Conferences: Embracing New Conversations]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076642</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/conquering-conferences-embracing-new-conversations/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T20:46:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How you can bring vibrant energy to each new interaction.
The post Conquering Conferences: Embracing New Conversations appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEJAL PATEL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>