<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-10-12T14:12:42.059Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Tech Red Raiders Unveil Alternate Uniforms Featuring Patrick Mahomes’ “Gladiator” Logo]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82600</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/12/texas-tech-red-raiders-unveil-alternate-uniforms-featuring-patrick-mahomes-gladiator-logo/college/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T14:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Tech unveiled new alternate uniforms that feature former quarterback Patrick Mahomes' "Gladiator" logo and will be worn against Colorado on Nov. 9.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Food recs: Kansas City’s best soups and stews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2024-10-12/kansas-city-best-soups-stews-restaurants</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2024-10-12/kansas-city-best-soups-stews-restaurants"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Soup is maybe the quintessential comfort food, especially when the weather gets colder. At these Kansas City restaurants, you’ll find hearty pozole, flavor-packed ramen, creamy New England clam chowder and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Ellison, Claudia Brancart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Do I Recognize That Black Couch From?! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076123</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/where-do-i-recognize-that-black-couch-from-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T23:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You're Telling On Yourself: Partner accused of using office for adult videos without sharing profits.
Year In The Making: The Feds have been trying to crack Eric Adams’s phone for a while now.
California Dubs The Portfolio: Nice try, no dice.
High-Flying Tricks!: Law student leads helicopter flyover.
The post Where Do I Recognize That Black Couch From?! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serving Articles Of Impeachment To A Supreme Court Justice]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076115</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/serving-articles-of-impeachment-to-a-supreme-court-justice/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T22:18:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It *can* happen...
The post Serving Articles Of Impeachment To A Supreme Court Justice appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conquering Conferences: Making Every Conversation Count]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076048</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/conquering-conferences-making-every-conversation-count/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T21:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each interaction is an opportunity to engage in a meaningful and enjoyable dialogue.
The post Conquering Conferences: Making Every Conversation Count appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEJAL PATEL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stat(s) Of The Week: Gen AI Versus Outside Counsel]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076110</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/stats-of-the-week-gen-ai-versus-outside-counsel/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T20:46:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will tech-savvy law departments need less outside help?  
The post Stat(s) Of The Week: Gen AI Versus Outside Counsel appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Barker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘Cost Plus’ Boondoggle That Hobbles US Defense]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076095</id>
        <link href="http://breakingdefense.com/2024/10/the-cost-plus-boondoggle-that-hobbles-us-defense/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T20:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Army policy on ‘enabling modern software development’ actually doubles down on some of DoD’s worst dysfunctions, argues Warren Katz, chairman of the Alliance for Commercial Technology in Government, violating the spirit – and perhaps the letter – of the law.
The post The ‘Cost Plus’ Boondoggle That Hobbles US Defense appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WARREN KATZ - BREAKING DEFENSE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Can Be Difficult To Estimate The Cost Of Legal Services]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075885</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/it-can-be-difficult-to-estimate-the-cost-of-legal-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T19:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As with eating, clients are less likely to choke on the bill if it's broken up into smaller pieces.
The post It Can Be Difficult To Estimate The Cost Of Legal Services appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Rothman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No More ‘Three-Course Meals’: Diddy’s Lawyer Says Jail Food Has Been ‘Rough’ On Client’s Gourmet Palate]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076114</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/no-more-three-course-meals-diddys-lawyer-says-jail-food-has-been-rough-on-clients-gourmet-palate/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T18:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry, Diddy, but there's no 'spaghetti, fettucini, and veal' behind bars.
The post No More ‘Three-Course Meals’: Diddy’s Lawyer Says Jail Food Has Been ‘Rough’ On Client’s Gourmet Palate appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Was That The Greatest WNBA Finals Game Ever?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170117</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/was-that-the-greatest-wnba-finals-game-ever"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T18:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Lynx were down 15 points with five minutes left to play, a deficit from which no team had ever overcome in the Finals. But a blend of tactical changes and clutch plays erased the Liberty's lead—and my memories of it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Totally Cool That I Didn’t Get To See The Northern Lights. Seriously! I Promise!!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170189</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-totally-cool-that-i-didnt-get-to-see-the-northern-lights-seriously-i-promise"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T18:04:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this week, the sun did its big one, producing the largest solar flare in nearly two decades. In its aftermath, the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration issued a severe geomagnetic storm watch for Thursday and Friday. This storm could not only temporarily disrupt power and radio signals, but also trigger stellar spectacles across the world known as aurora borealis.
Last night, as I traversed the streets of Brooklyn, photographers worldwide turned their eyes to sky.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Appealing Weekly Roundup]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076105</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/how-appealing-weekly-roundup-90/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T17:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The week in appellate news.
The post How Appealing Weekly Roundup appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I Own An Unremarkable 1990 Mark Jackson Basketball Card]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170085</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-i-own-an-unremarkable-1990-mark-jackson-basketball-card"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T17:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I bought the card in May of 2022. It was one of my many low-dollar purchases on eBay, made during one of my manic buying phrases; those tend to happen when I’m in a particularly good or particularly bad mood. “Stop buying things,” my wife will say when, say, a UK demo cassette of the song “Your Woman” by White Town arrives at the house. And I will reply, “But I’m in one of my manic buying phases when I am in a particularly good or particularly bad mood!” Eventually I toss the item in a box and forget about it, and then I try to remember to work on things in therapy and maybe ask for a medication tweak.
Anyway, this particular purchase was her fault for once. She was the one who told me about the card. Jan usually experiences sports vicariously through me, but she is a baseball fan. Our third date featured a long discussion about Bobby Estalella and whether he was the worst player named in the Mitchell Report. (Feel free to discuss in the comments.) So she knows a bit about sports cards. And one of the reasons we love each other so much is that she, like me, has a brain full of esoteric knowledge that could never, ever be useful in any scenario. Sometimes she tells me something wonderful and I just kiss her.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sixpence None the Richer’s Leigh Nash on the band’s reformation, upcoming Knuckleheads gig]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855590</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/sixpence-none-the-richers-leigh-nash-on-the-bands-reformation-upcoming-knuckleheads-gig/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T17:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sixpence None The Richer. // photo credit Ben Pearson While not quite reaching the heights of fellow crossover artists DC Talk, alternative music act Sixpence None the Richer came out of the Christian music scene to secular success. Thanks to the still imminently popular single “Kiss Me,” alongside covers of The La’s “There She Goes” and “Don’t Dream it’s Over”...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join The Conversation On In-House Careers!]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076118</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/join-the-conversation-on-in-house-careers/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T17:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Above the Law’s Olga V. Mack will be hosting focus groups as part of our annual In-House Compensation Report. Here’s how you can join. 
The post Join The Conversation On In-House Careers! appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AHL’s Hershey Bears to Wear Special Jerseys Marking Back-to-Back Calder Cups]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82593</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/11/ahls-hershey-bears-to-wear-special-jerseys-marking-back-to-back-calder-cups/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T16:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 and 2024 American Hockey League champions will wear special edition jerseys for both games of 2024-25 regular season opening weekend on October 12 and 13 vs. Cleveland Monsters]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attorney Says Law Firm Filmed Pornos In His Office]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076111</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/attorney-says-law-firm-filmed-pornos-in-his-office/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T16:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some... interesting allegations.
The post Attorney Says Law Firm Filmed Pornos In His Office appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Owns An Idea?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170108</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/who-owns-an-idea"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T16:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standing in front of Sol LeWitt’s Wall Drawings, I felt my body go all fuzzy. My eyes followed the precise lines that crossed each other again and again, each on its own predetermined path but also existing as a component of the whole. Humble straight lines drawn in pencil or crayon, multiplied to such a dizzying degree that when you stand back, they blend together into a wiggling mass that comes into and out of focus like an optical illusion. I wanted to run my fingers over the lines; I imagined I would be able to feel the ridges they made in the wall, the way my handwriting does in my notebooks. 
It was the last day of summer, and I was visiting Mass MoCA for the first time with a group of my former coworkers. It’s been seven years since we all worked together, and in that time our relationships have cohered more into a family. There were 10 of us there that day, plus two babies, so once we started looking at the art, we broke up into groups based on our pace, interests, and whether we had a toddler to chase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with paranormal investigator and Kindred Spirits star Amy Bruni]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=852612</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-paranormal-investigator-and-kindred-spirits-star-amy-bruni/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T16:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amy Bruni // Photo Courtesy of Kauffman Center for the Performing Arts Given that spooky season has officially kicked off, it only makes sense we’d want to touch base with renowned paranormal investigator Amy Bruni. The star of Kindred Spirits and Ghost Hunters will appear later this month at the Kauffman Center for the Performing Arts. If you’re into otherworldly apparitions, hauntings, and demonic activity...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law Student To Lead Helicopter Flyover At Big SEC Football Game]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076103</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/law-student-to-lead-helicopter-flyover-at-big-sec-football-game/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T15:27:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This veteran is being granted a rare opportunity as a law student -- leading a game flyover as a pilot.
The post Law Student To Lead Helicopter Flyover At Big SEC Football Game appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yankees Advance to ALCS Behind Dominant Gerrit Cole Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=448673</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/yankees-advance-to-alcs-behind-dominant-gerrit-cole-performance/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T15:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an postseason era marked by aggressive bullpen usage and pitching staff chaos, Gerrit Cole delivered a fantastic seven-inning performance on Thursday night to lead the Yankees past the Royals and into the ALCS. The final score of 3-1 makes the game appear closer than it actually felt; the Royals really only threatened once or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Mailhot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City Chiefs owners fund radio ad campaign opposing Missouri abortion amendment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855629</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kansas-city-chiefs-owners-fund-radio-ad-campaign-opposing-missouri-abortion-amendment/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T14:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A handful of people opposed to Amendment 3 protested outside the Missouri Supreme Court on Tuesday, Sept. 10, 2024, following a ruling to keep the abortion amendment on the Nov. 5 ballot (Anna Spoerre/Missouri Independent) The family business that owns the Kansas City Chiefs is one of the biggest funders of a political action committee opposing a proposed amendment to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Spoerre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California Holds On Tight To Its Notoriously Difficult Bar Exam]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076106</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/california-holds-on-tight-to-its-notoriously-difficult-bar-exam/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T14:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[California's Big Plan For Alternative Bar Admission Gets Nixed.
The post California Holds On Tight To Its Notoriously Difficult Bar Exam appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom-Tom C’est Moi]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169140</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tom-tom-cest-moi"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T14:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To concretize these ideas and actually train my ear to listen for certain key details—how hard a drummer hits, what part of the stick they use, where they cheat a beat on one limb to steal a beat on another—took a good teacher, and I unknowingly had one of the best.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FBI Has Apparently Spent A Year Trying To Crack NYC Mayor Eric Adams’s Personal Phone]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076104</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-fbi-has-apparently-spent-a-year-trying-to-crack-nyc-mayor-eric-adamss-personal-phone/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T14:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the MAYOR-BEATS-FEDS dept
The post The FBI Has Apparently Spent A Year Trying To Crack NYC Mayor Eric Adams’s Personal Phone appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Techdirt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLB’s Television Product Is Getting Shittier In Exciting New Ways]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170119</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mlbs-television-product-is-getting-shittier-in-exciting-new-ways"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T13:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major League Baseball has been broadcast regularly on television in North America for more than 70 years. By now, you figure it could be done pretty well. This is because humans tend to get better at things through repetition. You give me enough chances to learn and refine the doing of something, even something that involves wires and buttons and so forth, and I am going to be way better at the thing after a few decades at it. Recently I replaced my home's wireless router, all by myself! From the accumulated experience of having occasionally replaced routers over the years, now you can just hand to me a router and, buddy, I am gonna install that sucker without dying.
Something weird seems to be happening with baseball broadcasts, however. Despite the basic requirements having changed roughly not at all over the course of most of a century—the game is still played on a diamond, you point a camera at it and press the "on" button, etc.—the people who produce baseball broadcasts are suddenly worse at the job. Not just in the sense of assigning the utterly joyless duo of Bob Costas and Ron Darling to the Royals-Yankees divisional series. That certainly sucked, yes, but something worse was happening in the other ALDS, between the Detroit Tigers and the Cleveland Guardians, also produced by TNT Sports (formerly Turner Sports). Here is the normal view of the action at a Tigers home game, taken from moments before the Tigers clinched their postseason berth, on Sept. 27:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.11.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076101</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-11-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T12:47:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Uh oh... SpaghettiOs: Woman arrested after cops found a "suspicious substance" on a spoon in her purse during a routine traffic stop -- it was canned pasta sauce. [Lowering the Bar]
* Respect the LinkedIn hustle: FTX officer updates profile to reflect prison sentence. [CNN]
* What this tells me is that Roberts is still very, very annoyed with the Fifth Circuit's nonsense. [National Law Journal]
* Speaking of forum shopping: "US Appellate Judge Urges Caution on Judge-Shopping Rule." This is why, unfortunately, it's become necessary for journalists to clarify "TRUMP Appellate Judge Urges Caution on Judge-Shopping Rule." Without that context, this news story reads as though this isn't a wholly partisan stance.
* The thing about loser-pays is that the winners can rack up some epic mini-bar charges along the way. [Roll on Friday]
* Nixon Peabody sues personal injury firm. [ABA Journal]
* If only some Supreme Court justices cared about miscarriages of justice as much as they care about jailing women after a miscarriage. [Dorf on Law]
* Judge Kindred texted with former clerk/inappropriate relationship/prosecutor about a case as he presided over it. This is distinct from the senior prosecutor who sent the judge nude photographs. Get it together, Alaska! [Reuters]
The post Morning Docket: 10.11.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump origin biopic The Apprentice is a gorgeously made exposé that exposes nothing new]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=854463</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/trump-origin-biopic-the-apprentice-is-a-gorgeously-made-expose-that-exposes-nothing-new/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T03:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Apprentice, the new film from Ali Abbasi headed to theaters this weekend, is a shallow dive into the origins of Donald J. Trump. Set against the inciting incident of the Trump family being sued by the government for discrimination against Blacks in their apartment rentals, the 1973 case that could’ve sunk a real-estate slumlord instead created a branched and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bird Dawgs Replace Wood Ducks Down East]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82589</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/10/bird-dawgs-replace-wood-ducks-down-east/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T03:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kinston, North Carolina, won’t miss a beat when it comes to professional baseball in 2025. The town lost its Single-A team, the Down East Wood Ducks, at the end of the 2024 season, when that franchise headed south to become the Hub City Spartanburgers. Before residents could miss having a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Caputo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mississippi Mud Monsters join Frontier League]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82573</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/10/mississippi-mud-monsters-join-frontier-league/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:45:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just about a month after the Double-A Mississippi Braves recorded their final out before relocating to Georgia for the 2025 season, the town of Pearl, Mississippi, is welcoming a new baseball team to Trustmark Park. The Mississippi Mud Monsters joined the independent Frontier League, unveiling their name and logo this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Caputo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missourians to vote on paid sick leave and minimum wage hike next month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855576</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missourians-to-vote-on-paid-sick-leave-and-minimum-wage-hike-next-month/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Missourians for Healthy Families and Fair Wages prepare for a press conference in May, 2024 (Annelise Hanshaw/Missouri Independent). A measure that would guarantee paid sick leave for over 700,000 Missouri workers who currently lack it, as well as gradually raise the minimum wage to $15, will appear on voters’ ballots next month. The ballot initiative, called Proposition A, has been...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clara Bates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Nonequity Partnering — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076089</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/more-non-equity-partnering-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T23:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another Biglaw Firm Introduces VVS Salary Class: Let's call nonequity partnerships what they are.
You Better Catch Up!: Tech adoption is on the rise!
The Workplace Hasn't Adapted To Gen Z: Which side will give first?
Lip Syncing, Your Honor: Judge suspended over non-judicial TikToking.
The post More Nonequity Partnering — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks So Much To Our Advertisers]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076057</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/thanks-so-much-to-our-advertisers-18/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T23:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We love working with you!
The post Thanks So Much To Our Advertisers appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Your Calendars For The Sean Combs Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076087</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/mark-your-calendars-for-the-sean-combs-trial/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T22:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is gearing up to be a major media trial.
The post Mark Your Calendars For The Sean Combs Trial appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting The Most Value From Your Outside Counsel Hire]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076078</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/getting-the-most-value-from-your-outside-counsel-hire/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T21:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can sign up for the free beta now.
The post Getting The Most Value From Your Outside Counsel Hire appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tiffany Price plans to lean on motherhood experiences in addressing local education, crime, and more in District 26]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855310</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/tiffany-price-plans-to-lean-on-motherhood-experiences-in-addressing-local-education-crime-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T21:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of upballot.com The Missouri House of Representatives District 26 covers the Southeast side of Kansas City. Tiffany Price, in her first run for elected office, is the Democratic candidate up for the seat. Price is the founder and executive director of Hold Em Up 4 Care—an organization that provides clothing and mentorship to underserved youth. She graduated from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking Ahead To 2025: Reining In Partners’ Compensation Expectations]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076027</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/looking-ahead-to-2025-reining-in-partners-compensation-expectations/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T20:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things may look great financially, but law firm leaders still want to be cautious.
The post Looking Ahead To 2025: Reining In Partners’ Compensation Expectations appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Remember Some Dad]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170007</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lets-remember-some-dad"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T20:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you see me describing an episode of The Distraction as "a very special episode," I am almost certainly joking. It is the nature of the podcast, it is right there in the very title of the pod, that this is mostly goofy stuff. We can and do talk about serious and sad stuff but, as a general rule, Drew and I are both sufficiently people-pleasing, so we tend to wrap those particular pills in a healthy dollop of peanut butter before offering it to you, the listener, who I guess is a dog in this scenario. However, I am not joking when I say that this week's episode is a very special episode, and unlike any other we've done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Given 3-Month Unpaid Suspension Over Racy TikToks]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076079</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/judge-given-3-month-unpaid-suspension-over-racy-tiktoks/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T20:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We sentence you to being too lit fr. 
The post Judge Given 3-Month Unpaid Suspension Over Racy TikToks appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump, ‘Genetics’ Enthusiast, Demands FCC Investigation Of CBS For Criminal Video Editing]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076065</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/donald-trump-genetics-enthusiast-demands-fcc-investigation-of-cbs-for-criminal-video-editing/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T19:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is this a cancel culture?
The post Donald Trump, ‘Genetics’ Enthusiast, Demands FCC Investigation Of CBS For Criminal Video Editing appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: Two new standout menus, Kitty’s Cafe reopens, and 100 free meals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855479</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-two-new-standout-menus-kittys-cafe-reopens-and-100-free-meals/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T19:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Looking for delicious plans? Whether you want to impress a date, show your fam the best of KC, or just get out of the house, we’ve got you covered… all while supporting (mostly) local.  Here is your weekly roundup of the best food and drink offerings around Kansas City. Cheers! Something New Yoli Tortilleria: Yoli Tortilleria’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nominations Are Now Open For The Alli Gerkman Legal Visionary Award; Deadline is Nov. 1]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076062</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/10/nominations-are-now-open-for-the-alli-gerkman-legal-visionary-award-deadline-is-nov-1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T18:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The award recognizes an innovator who has made significant impacts early in their career toward making the American legal system work better for everyone.
The post Nominations Are Now Open For The Alli Gerkman Legal Visionary Award; Deadline is Nov. 1 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Headbangers to the front: Gatecreeper turns The Bottleneck into a continuous circle pit on Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855484</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/headbangers-to-the-front-gatecreeper-turns-the-bottleneck-into-a-continuous-circle-pit-on-wednesday/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T18:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatecreeper at The Bottleneck on Wednesday, Oct. 9, 2024. // Photo by Nick Spacek Gatecreeper w/ Frozen Soul and Worm The Bottleneck Wednesday, Oct. 9 May’s release of Arizona’s Gatecreeper latest, Dark Superstition, coincided with me needing to mow my lawn. The tracks paired with trimming the yard, resulted in me listening to Gatecreeper’s sun-bleached death metal at least once a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kitty's Cafe spent months waiting for a renovation. A hungry line of customers greeted its return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2024-10-10/kittys-cafe-kansas-city-pork-tenderloin-sandwich-best-restaurant</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2024-10-10/kittys-cafe-kansas-city-pork-tenderloin-sandwich-best-restaurant"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Famous for its triple-decker pork tenderloin sandwich, the Kansas City restaurant closed unexpectedly this spring when its planned renovation hit roadblocks with contractors and the city. Jinna Soulivong says she didn't expect to see so much community support — or a line down the block when they reopened.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabe Rosenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law Firm Tech Adoption More Important Than Ever When It Comes To AI]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076051</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/law-firm-tech-adoption-more-important-than-ever-when-it-comes-to-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don't sit around waiting for AI... get out there and help build it.
The post Law Firm Tech Adoption More Important Than Ever When It Comes To AI appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yankees Show It’s Better To Be Good Than Lucky in ALDS Game 3]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=448552</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/yankees-show-its-better-to-be-good-than-lucky-in-alds-game-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If anyone needs the Royals they'll be out shopping for a rabbit's foot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiri Oler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Got My Fill]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170043</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-got-my-fill"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:28:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
I was stressed. It was summer, and my dad was dying. On multiple occasions, I had to drop everything at a moment’s notice to go help my mom and siblings with him. I went back and forth so many times over the past few months, I genuinely lost count. I’d get a call or text, pack my shit, and then make the six-plus hour drive to Connecticut (one time I flew, just because I needed to conserve my energy) to do whatever was needed. Every trip could have been my last.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Real World Is Coming For Gen Z Lawyers]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076049</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-real-world-is-coming-for-gen-z-lawyers/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 'Gen Z gets fired' trend hits the legal space.
The post The Real World Is Coming For Gen Z Lawyers appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Takes A Village To Pitch A Shutout]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170077</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/it-takes-a-village-to-pitch-a-shutout"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is difficult, even the morning after, to know how to view the Los Angeles Dodgers' 8-0 shutout of San Diego in Game 4 of the National League Division Series. Was it an homage to the power of desperation? The triumph of an efficient system over individual excellence? Plain dumb luck replayed eight times in succession?
However you assign motive, let alone value, the Dodgers performed the rarest of feats on Wednesday night when they tied up their series on the strength of an eight-pitcher shutout. Rarer still, only one of those eight, Alex Vesia, faced more than five Padres hitters. Vesia was stretched out over the fourth and fifth innings in a 30-pitch marathon that had oldey-timey rememberers sighing over the recent death of Luis Tiant, the wonderfully idiosyncratic pitcher who threw a 155-pitch complete game in the 1975 World Series, three days after pitching a complete game shutout, all at age 34 and while celebrating every win with a cigar the length and girth of an adult spaniel. But that was then. This is the very opposite of that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Translating Between Contracts And Code: Bridging The Gap Between Legal And Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1074562</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/translating-between-contracts-and-code-bridging-the-gap-between-legal-and-tech/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technology can be a powerful ally for legal professionals.
The post Translating Between Contracts And Code: Bridging The Gap Between Legal And Tech appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga V. Mack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Original Seattle Seahawks Logo: Controversy in the 70s and a Surprising Discovery Decades Later]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82562</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/10/the-original-seattle-seahawks-logo-controversy-in-the-70s-and-a-surprising-discovery-decades-later/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Seattle Seahawks will once again wear their much-loved throwback uniforms tonight when they take on the San Francisco 49ers, but the logo wasn’t without its controversy when it was first unveiled nearly fifty years ago. Officially presented to the world on June 17, 1975, the Seahawks original logo and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Creamer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mise en Place: Jeff “Cheffrey” Workman on James Beard aftermath]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=854502</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/mise-en-place-jeff-cheffrey-workman-on-james-beard-aftermath/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeff Workman // Photo by Jenny Wheat Chef Jeff Workman–Cheffrey if you’re close–has honed his skills at several top Kansas City culinary destinations, such as Corvino, The Campground, and now, Tailleur. His Midwestern-leaning dishes and care for his team play no small role in his accomplishments, most recently as a 2024 James Beard Award semi-finalist for Emerging Chef while at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Questions To Make Fund Formation Your Competitive Advantage [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075988</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-questions-to-make-fund-formation-your-competitive-advantage/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:33:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A law firm success checklist from our friends at Thomson Reuters. 
The post The Questions To Make Fund Formation Your Competitive Advantage appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>THOMSON REUTERS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Argonaut Octopus Has Mastered The Free Ride]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169146</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-argonaut-octopus-has-mastered-the-free-ride"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:21:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2019, the photographer Harris Narainen had just wrapped up a night dive off Anilao in the Philippines and begun his staggered ascent to the surface when his dive leader pointed a flashlight at something bright and yellow. Narainen looked over and saw a tiny shelled octopus called an argonaut, or paper nautilus, clinging to the candy wrapper as if it were a magic carpet. "I was just too excited," Narainen wrote in an email. Earlier, the dive leader had mentioned they might see argonauts if they were lucky, and now here one was, sailing into the bright beam of light.
Although most octopuses live near the ocean floor and its ample hiding places, argonauts spend their entire lives sailing in the open ocean, just below the surface. This lifestyle has rendered the small cephalopods rather elusive to the scientists who wish to study them. "Most observations on argonauts are opportunistic," Roger Villanueva, a marine biologist at Spain's Institute of Marine Sciences, wrote in an email. In many of these serendipitous observations, argonauts are spotted clinging to some kind of substrate, such as a twig of driftwood or some gelatinous creature. But a traditional sampling net cannot capture these associations; the turbulence of retrieval will separate an argonaut from its trusty steed or entangle it randomly with another.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 50 Biglaw Firm Creates Nonequity Partnership Tier To Create More ‘Promotion And Development’ Opportunities For Attorney Talent]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076026</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/top-50-biglaw-firm-creates-nonequity-partnership-tier-to-create-more-promotion-and-development-opportunities-for-attorney-talent/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T14:43:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cleary Gottlieb had an all-equity partnership for all of its existence, but times have changed, and now the firm needs to change too.
The post Top 50 Biglaw Firm Creates Nonequity Partnership Tier To Create More ‘Promotion And Development’ Opportunities For Attorney Talent appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tropicana Field Shredded By Hurricane Milton]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170048</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tropicana-field-shredded-by-hurricane-milton"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T14:29:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Florida is digging out this morning after the arrival of Milton, the unconscionably powerful hurricane that slammed the Gulf Coast around Sarasota last night. Power is out for millions; it will take days and weeks to count the dead and tally the damage. But we already have the defining visual of the storm: Tropicana Field, home to the Rays, lost most of its roof overnight in high winds.
Here's some stunning drone footage from WXChasing:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Francisco Lindor Has Been Waiting Years For This]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170010</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/francisco-lindor-has-been-waiting-years-for-this"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T14:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wish that Major League Baseball gave out its MVP awards in the same way that high school movies dramatize the crowning of a Prom Queen—all the students watching rapt as an adult with an on-stage microphone calls the protagonist's name. It'd be obvious how the NL MVP would go in any coming-of-age movie worth its salt: Shohei Ohtani humbly breaks off a piece of his tiara to give to Francisco Lindor, because he can't bring himself to soak up the entirety of the recognition for himself.
Lindor's all-around success at the plate and at shortstop this season had earned him an undisputed spot as the National League's second-most valuable player well before Wednesday. And if it wasn't already, his place in the hearts of Mets fans was cemented by the skin-saving sockdolager he levitated in the ninth inning in Atlanta to deliver New York a playoff berth on the day after the so-called last day of the season. But I don't know if anything he's done in his career so far can match his cathartic triumph near the end of one of the most excruciating innings in recent playoff memory—one that allowed the Mets to knock out the Phillies and earn a trip to the NLCS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Things Healthcare Leaders Should Know About The 2024 Election]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076025</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/10/healthcare-election-trump-harris/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T14:03:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During a recent conference, Ceci Connolly, CEO of the Alliance of Community Health Plans, shared five things she thinks the healthcare industry should know about the upcoming election.
The post 5 Things Healthcare Leaders Should Know About The 2024 Election appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MARISSA PLESCIA - MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[God Appears To Have Given The Mets A Big Sloppy Kiss On The Mouth]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=170005</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/god-appears-to-have-given-the-mets-a-big-sloppy-kiss-on-the-mouth"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T13:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first two innings of what would prove the final Phillies-Mets NLDS game were aesthetically hideous, on all sides. Second-half Ranger Suárez, not to be confused with first-half Ranger Suárez, loaded the bases with one out in the first, and escaped without a scratch. One inning later, he did the same thing again. So it didn't feel like the Phillies' luck had run out in the sixth inning, when the bullpen loaded the bases with Francisco Lindor up, so much as it felt like inevitability. What did you honestly think was going to happen but a grand slam?

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BXNWDtE_V2Q]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overland Park non-profit ice cream parlor The Golden Scoop serves sweets and opportunities in equal measure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853613</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/overland-park-non-profit-ice-cream-parlor-the-golden-scoop-serves-sweets-and-opportunities-in-equal-measure/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T13:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Golden Scoop’s new location // Photo by Soffia Hernandez The Golden Scoop—a locally-owned nonprofit ice cream and coffee shop that employs adults with mental disabilities—is celebrating the grand opening of their second location on W 103 St. in Overland Park. One “super scooper” who has gained local notoriety as the “Mayor of Leawood,” better known to family as Jack,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soffia Hernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.10.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076043</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-10-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T12:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Lawyer suspended for slapping another attorney on courthouse steps. [ABA Journal]
* Clarence Thomas spent Glossip hearing making up stuff about the record despite being corrected multiple times. These are not serious people. [Slate]
* You've got to Hawk Tuah and hire some IP lawyers for that thing. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Biglaw learning that just because that they're not the answer to every hot market. [American Lawyer]
* Diddy accuses DHS of leaking grand jury materials. [Rolling Stone]
* Musk's zombie Twitter will avoid classification as a gatekeeper product under EU regulation. Which seems like a backhanded acknowledgement that the company isn't financially relevant any more. [Reuters]
* S&C dropped from FTX suit. [Law360]
The post Morning Docket: 10.10.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Greg Jackson brings live version of History That Doesn’t Suck! podcast to Liberty Hall this Friday night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855463</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dr-greg-jackson-brings-live-version-of-history-that-doesnt-suck-podcast-to-liberty-hall-this-friday-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T04:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Greg Jackson, host of the podcast History That Doesn’t Suck! performs on stage during the 2023-2024 tour season. Jackson will be kicking off the 2024-2024 tour in Lawrence, Kansas, on Oct. 11.   A musical history lesson with Dr. Greg Jackson, host of the podcast show, History That Doesn’t Suck!, will take place at Liberty Hall in Lawrence, Kansas,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planned Parenthood will close 3 Missouri clinics, expand telehealth services]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855452</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/planned-parenthood-will-close-3-missouri-clinics-expand-telehealth-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T01:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Planned Parenthood clinic in St. Louis on June 24, 2022 (Tessa Weinberg/Missouri Independent) Three Planned Parenthood clinics in eastern and southern Missouri will shut their doors next month, though the organization’s leaders insist the moves will ultimately expand access to reproductive health care. As part of the consolidation effort, Planned Parenthood Great Rivers will be expanding telehealth services and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Spoerre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Somebody Please Think Of Donald Trump! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076017</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/will-somebody-please-think-of-donald-trump-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T23:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Giuliani Wants His Case To Wait: Because he's the reason folks have a problem with Trump.
So Much For Standing Your Ground: Twitter caves to Brazil's demands.
Things Are About To Get SPOOKY: Prepare your costumes for ATL's Halloween Contest!
It Isn't Looking Good For The 5th Circuit: Seems like they're going to get reversed, again!
Now That's A Lot Of LSATs!: A world in crisis means more 1Ls!
The post Will Somebody Please Think Of Donald Trump! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These State Attorneys General Are Coming After TikTok]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076004</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/these-state-attorneys-general-are-coming-after-tiktok/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T23:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AGs say they're doing it for the children.
The post These State Attorneys General Are Coming After TikTok appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ABA Really Doesn’t Want To Get Sued By Blum & Co.]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076014</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-aba-really-doesnt-want-to-get-sued-by-blum-co/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T22:18:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When SFFA v. Harvard was first decided, we were flooded with what were effectively solidarity posts — Biglaw firms and universities sent out statements reaffirming their steadfast commitment to fostering diversity no matter what the Supreme Court decided. Then the lawsuits happened. Since then, big-name firms like Morrison Foerster skipped the courtroom and decided to […]
The post The ABA Really Doesn’t Want To Get Sued By Blum & Co. appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Courtney Williams Helps The Lynx Slide Their Way Into The Finals]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169903</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/courtney-williams-helps-the-lynx-slide-their-way-into-the-finals"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T21:39:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Minnesota Lynx blew out the Connecticut Sun in Game 5 of the WNBA semifinals Tuesday, they looked like they had spent years gelling together. They were the better team on both ends of the floor. Part of that can be chalked up to the simple existence of Napheesa Collier, who put up her third consecutive game of at least 25 points and 10 rebounds, a WNBA postseason record, and could probably turn a quartet of traffic cones into a sound basketball team.
But the Lynx have been a treat to watch precisely because they're not a one-woman show. Instead, they are insistent on a harmonious style of hoop, heavy on ball movement. Watching them skate past the Sun, 88-77, and rejoice with the traditional post-victory Electric Slide, it was hard to believe a team this cohesive was still so new: Only five players on this Lynx team returned from the roster last season, and of those five, only three have meaningfully figured in this playoff run. This team was assembled in free agency and on the trading block by Cheryl Reeve and her double-duty as head coach and president of basketball ops. Tuesday's elimination game was specifically a showcase for the Lynx's most critical offseason signing: veteran guard Courtney Williams, who had 24 points, seven assists, and five rebounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Biden Is NOT A Fan Of Merrick Garland, New Book Says]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075995</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/joe-biden-is-not-a-fan-of-merrick-garland-new-book-says/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T21:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As noted in Bob Woodward's new book, President Biden wasn't too thrilled with AG Garland over his son Hunter's prosecution.
The post Joe Biden Is NOT A Fan Of Merrick Garland, New Book Says appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Teacher’s debut supernatural thriller addresses slavery, compliance, and complex literary history]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855092</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-teachers-debut-supernatural-thriller-addresses-slavery-compliance-and-complex-literary-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T21:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teacher and Novelist Matthew Reed Williams with a copy of Somewhere. // Photo Courtesy of Matthew Reed Williams Local author Matthew Reed Williams’ debut novel Somewhere is hitting the shelves this week. The supernatural thriller is based in Missouri and explores complex themes such as slavery, different racial perspectives in literature, and compliance. The Kansas City-based writer and teacher knew...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soffia Hernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Judges Push Back On Self-Importance Of CEOs]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076003</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/federal-judges-push-back-on-self-importance-of-ceos/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T20:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No. You aren't too good to sit for a deposition.
The post Federal Judges Push Back On Self-Importance Of CEOs appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phil Vassar Is A State Fair Legend And I Hereby Demand His Induction Into The Nashville Songwriters Hall Of Fame]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075917</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/phil-vassar-is-a-state-fair-legend-and-i-hereby-demand-his-induction-into-the-nashville-songwriters-hall-of-fame/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T20:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['Thanks again for having us to the state fair,' Vassar purrs into the microphone. 'We appreciate this.'
The post Phil Vassar Is A State Fair Legend And I Hereby Demand His Induction Into The Nashville Songwriters Hall Of Fame appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Wolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spilling the tea on the restaurant industry from the 2024 Kansas City Restaurant Festival]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855028</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/2024-kansas-city-restaurant-festival/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T20:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City Restaurant Festival // Photo by Sarah Sipple Cocktails, hot chicken, a new neighborhood cafe, the latest ramen trend… these are fun and generally unifying topics. However, the things we consume don’t just poof out of thin air and onto our plates. Keeping the human element of food and drink in mind is crucial, and there’s no better way...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Ready: ATL’s Legally Themed Halloween Costume Contest Will Be Here Soon]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075999</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/get-ready-atl-legally-themed-halloween-costume-contest-will-be-here-soon-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T19:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use this time wisely to create a spectacular costume. We can't wait to see it!
The post Get Ready: ATL’s Legally Themed Halloween Costume Contest Will Be Here Soon appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opinion: Election season serves as a stark reminder of Missouri’s susceptibility to hateful ideologies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=854293</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/opinion-election-season-serves-as-a-stark-reminder-of-missouris-susceptibility-to-christian-nationalism/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T19:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senator Josh Hawley speaks to reporters after joining challenger Lucas Kunce in the middle of the floor of the governor’s ham breakfast at the Missouri State Fair in Sedalia Thursday morning (Annelise Hanshaw/Missouri Independent). It was 1996 when Missouri last voted for a Democratic U.S. president—Bill Clinton. Since then, voters in the Show Me state have witnessed the rise...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael McGrady Jr.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rudy Giuiliani Asks Court To Hold Off On Collecting Judgments Against Him Because It Might Embarrass Donald Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075986</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/rudy-giuiliani-asks-court-to-hold-off-on-collecting-judgments-against-him-because-it-might-embarrass-donald-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T18:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No, he's not representing himself. Why do you ask?
The post Rudy Giuiliani Asks Court To Hold Off On Collecting Judgments Against Him Because It Might Embarrass Donald Trump appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Underestimate The Power Of Spite]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169893</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dont-underestimate-the-power-of-spite"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T18:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As much as the MLB postseason is about which team can rack up the most consecutive series wins in a pressure-packed month, I can't help but also see it as a bit of a Baseball Pageant, in which each city indirectly competes to prove that they have the most charming and lovable and deserving group of boys. Most of the remaining franchises have a little flower they can offer to the neutrals, something that says Hey, wouldn't you like to see these sweeties succeed? As best I can tell, their claims are as follows:
The Mets are rallying behind absurdist lucky charms like a purple blob and a pumpkin
The "gritty Tigs" keep manufacturing clutch hits right when they need them
The Phillies are basically the Himbo Brigade
The Dodgers lead off with the best-liked man in the sport, making his playoff debut
The Guardians have exceeded all expectations with a rookie manager who's not afraid to cry
The Royals are playing against the Yankees]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Access Back In Brazil After Elon Caved And Paid $5M]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075990</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/twitter-access-back-in-brazil-after-elon-caved-and-paid-5m/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T17:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil: 1 Angry Billionaire With A Weird Jump: -$44B
The post Twitter Access Back In Brazil After Elon Caved And Paid $5M appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bear Wins Fat Bear Week By Defeating Bear That Killed Her Cub]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169899</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bear-wins-fat-bear-week-by-defeating-bear-that-killed-her-cub"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T17:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been an especially dramatic edition of Fat Bear Week, the annual fan-voted competition to crown the brown bear at Alaska's Katmai National Park who packed on the most poundage ahead of winter hibernation. You may remember last week's horrors, when the start of voting was delayed by the inexplicable killing of Bear 402 by "Digger." Neither of those bears had qualified for the knockout round of the competition, but if you read down in the story, you noticed one who has: "Chunk," last year's runner-up. Chunk was spotted stealing 402's carcass from Digger, presumably to cache it as food. Cannibalism is not, we understand, specifically prohibited in the Fat Bear Week rulebook.
But Chunk has his own history, and infamy. He is biggest bear on the river, clocking in at over 1,200 pounds. He fell in the finals in 2023 to "Grazer," a 19-year-old blonde female bear who pulled off the upset in fan voting. If only that were the only history between the two when they met for a finals rematch this year. This was a revenge game—for Grazer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Still Woozy brought Loveseat to the Midland Monday night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855316</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-still-woozy-brought-loveseat-to-the-midland-monday-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T17:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Still Woozy. // photo by Kylee Gregg Still Woozy with Paw Paw Rod and Gus Dapperton The Midland Monday, October 7 Touring in support of this summer’s Loveseat, Still Woozy (Sven Eric Gamsky’s solo project) took to the stage of the Midland Monday night for a spaced-out psyechedelic party. Funk/R&B/rapper Paw Paw Rod and hooky singer-songwriter Gus Dapperton opened. Our...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kylee Gregg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Decides To Just Make Up The Rules As She Goes Along]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075983</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/judge-decides-to-just-make-up-the-rules-as-she-goes-along/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T17:03:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why not?
The post Judge Decides To Just Make Up The Rules As She Goes Along appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Padres Keep Getting Louder]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169932</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-padres-keep-getting-louder"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T16:46:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The San Diego Padres have spent most of their 55 years of existence working to be inoffensive. That effort has been the franchise’s single greatest achievement, give or take the giddy heights of Benito Santiagomania. From their fashion (the too-often maligned and indisputably distinctive color palette) to their cramped geography (surrounded by the Dodgers, Angels, Diamondbacks, the Mexican border, and the Pacific Ocean) to their average finish (76-86, 19 games behind), the Padres have largely stayed out of everyone's way.
But not anymore, and here's some anecdotal proof:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[San Diego Wave, NWSL Sued For Team’s “Abusive And Hostile Work Environment”]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169636</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/san-diego-wave-nwsl-sued-for-teams-abusive-and-hostile-work-environment"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T16:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jill Ellis wore a smile in June of 2021 when she appeared in a press release photo announcing the new San Diego NWSL club, and her as its president. The former U.S. Women's National Team coach who led the team to back-to-back World Cup wins—making the United States one of just four countries in the competition’s men’s and women’s history to successfully defend a title—wore sunglasses and all black with a striking cream coat as she strolled along a sandy beach. Days later, the team posted a sit-down interview with Ellis in which she said the team’s ownership "really wanted to do something special on the female landscape and create an environment where it’s run by females." At a press event, Ellis said the Wave would stand as "not simply as a football club, but as a platform for those who dare to dream."
This week, five former Wave employees—all women—filed a lawsuit against both the Wave and the NWSL in San Diego Superior Court. The lawsuit asserts 15 claims, including disability discrimination, racial discrimination, sexual harassment, failure to investigate and prevent discrimination and harassment, retaliation, wrongful termination, and retaliating for engaging in protected activity. Overall, it portrays the Wave in stark contrast to the club’s marketing as a sports team that would be more than just a sports team and with a highly accomplished woman in charge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fifth Circuit’s Jurisprudence Is Too Far Right Even For This Supreme Court]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075979</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-fifth-circuits-jurisprudence-is-too-far-right-even-for-this-supreme-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T16:16:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SCOTUS predictions say the Fifth Circuit will be overturned in ghost guns case.
The post The Fifth Circuit’s Jurisprudence Is Too Far Right Even For This Supreme Court appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind The Bud: Show-Me Organics’ team of cannabis connoisseurs are your friends and neighbors reinventing the Missouri market]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850740</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/behind-the-bud-show-me-organics-team-of-cannabis-connoisseurs-are-your-friends-and-neighbors-reinventing-the-missouri-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Zach Bauman Most people remember their first time buying weed. Or, maybe not the first time, but that really sketchy time. Or perhaps a time when that one guy shorted that eighth. Whatever it may be, most average cannabis users would probably say that they’ve had a memorable experience when obtaining the substance. It’s no secret that a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Ellett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Golden Bachelorette’ Is Like A Wildlife Cam But For Old Dudes Who Rock]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169607</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-golden-bachelorette-is-like-a-wildlife-cam-but-for-old-dudes-who-rock"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the slow-motion car crash that was the end of the Golden Bachelor, I was prepared for the first season of its sister show to flop. I watched most of Gerry Turner's journey to find love with tears in my eyes, and as Alex Sujong Laughlin wrote at the time, the new entry into the Bachelor pantheon offered "a refreshing break from the onslaught of cheap trauma the franchise has been churning out the last few years." That joy was short-lived, as it tends to be in the Bachelor universe.
One day before the season finale, The Hollywood Reporter published a story titled "The Golden Bachelor's Not-So-Golden Past." In the grand scheme of Bachelor scandals, Turner's was rather tame; there were no allegations of antebellum cosplay or sexual abuse. The most dramatic revelations were about the two women Turner had dated since the death of his wife. As THR noted, "He was single and a widower, after all, not cheating. But his amorous activity certainly didn’t align with how he regularly yanked viewers’ heartstrings with on-air announcements about his lack of a love life since his wife died."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All’s Fair In Love And Fanfiction]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169835</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/alls-fair-in-love-and-fanfiction"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What you do with your first laptop is no one’s business. In fact, one might argue that getting your first laptop is what empowers you to have private business. It’s a strange and intoxicating revelation to be unshackled from the computer in the family room, the ever-present prying eyes of your parents, your siblings meddling with your budding online life. Where will you go? Who will you be? What, exactly, is the range of the WiFi router?
Welcome back to the new season of Normal Gossip! We’re beginning Season 7 with a tale of newfound freedom and literary discoveries, with just a dash of star crossed romance. The hero of today’s story, Victoria, is fresh out of high school and has decided to use her online liberation to join a community near to her heart and to participate in the creation of perhaps the most impassioned and maligned of all media: fanfiction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major ‘Surge’ In LSAT Demand May Lead To Intense Law School Application Cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075984</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/major-surge-in-lsat-demand-may-lead-to-intense-law-school-application-cycle/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone wants to be a lawyer right now, and the increase in LSAT registrations seems to prove it.
The post Major ‘Surge’ In LSAT Demand May Lead To Intense Law School Application Cycle appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Milwaukee Admirals swipe match against Coachella Valley Firebirds in 5-2 shootout]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855168</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-milwaukee-admirals-swipe-match-against-coachella-valley-firebirds-in-5-2-shootout/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Milwaukee Admirals versus Coachella Valley Firebirds on Friday, Oct 4 2024. // Photo by Eli Ralls Cable Dahmer Arena hosted another night of hockey—This time not the hometown Kansas City Mavericks. The American Hockey League’s Milwaukee Admirals and Coachella Valley Firebirds dueled it out on Friday, Oct. 4. It was a game full of lights and action as the Admirals...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Ralls</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solos & Small Firm Lawyers: Have You Taken Our Compensation Survey Yet?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075981</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/09/solos-small-firm-lawyers-compensation-survey/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T14:51:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tell us how much you make and help us benchmark small firm pay.
The post Solos & Small Firm Lawyers: Have You Taken Our Compensation Survey Yet? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Why The FTC’s Lawsuit Against PBMs May Have Some Legs]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075961</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/10/video-why-the-ftcs-lawsuit-against-pbms-may-have-some-legs/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T14:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Months before the FTC sued the three largest pharmacy benefit managers, the CEO of Blue Shield of California battled its PBM - CVS Caremark - to bring a lower cost prostate cancer drug to its members.
The post Video: Why The FTC’s Lawsuit Against PBMs May Have Some Legs appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arundhati Parmar - Medcity News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s Officially Hockey In Utah Now]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169865</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/theres-officially-hockey-in-utah-now"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T13:32:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the return of the NHL has felt like it's slipping under the radar a bit—not for you, of course; you've studied Lauren's preview like it's the Dead Sea Scrolls—blame it on the season's soft launch. Is it truly an Opening Day if there are five separate opening days depending on the team? Some clubs won't play their first meaningful hockey until Friday, a full week after the lads were getting after it in Prague. It doesn't help that many of the games so far, including those Czechia games and Tuesday night's tripleheader, have involved teams that still sound a little fake to me: the "Utah Hockey Club," the "Seattle Kraken," the "Buffalo Sabres."
But it is real, regular-season action, and I come bearing video to prove it. The Utah Hockey Fellas are, of course, the old Arizona Coyotes in everything but name. (It's all the same players, but the history and intellectual property still belong to Alex Meruelo, at least until 2029. Those Coyotes also own the history of the original Winnipeg Jets, not to be confused with the current Winnipeg Jets, who own the history of the Atlanta Thrashers. Aren't sports fun?) So this is not an expansion roster—despite the temporary lack of a name, and the tenancy in a building that after a hasty first round of renovations only holds about 11,000 for hockey—and won't be dogshit, or at least no more dogshit than the Coyotes were. This is a real, big-boy hockey team, and Salt Lake City fans, who turned out in strong numbers to buy season tickets, were ready to welcome them. In their first game, hosting the Blackhawks (who are dogshit), Dylan Guenther made sure the fans didn't have to wait longer than five minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Fall brunch flavors at Snooze and whiskey tastings at Barley & Vine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855060</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-snoozes-new-fall-menu-and-whiskey-tastings-at-barley-vine/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T13:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Snooze Am Eatery // Photo By Tiffany Watts A Delicious dive into Snooze’s new seasonal menu I recently dropped by Snooze, an A.M. Eatery to check out their fall menu, and let me tell you—it’s like fall wrapped up in pancake form.  With items like the Pumpkin Pecan Pancakes ($11.50), bursting with a vanilla cream cheese filling, drizzled with caramel,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off Conquers Biscuit Week Easily]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169723</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-not-so-great-defector-bake-off-conquers-biscuit-week-easily"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T12:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off, where Kelsey and Chris attempt to complete the technical challenges from the newest season of The Great British Bake Off in their own home kitchens, with the same time parameters as the professional-grade bakers competing on the show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.09.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075973</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-09-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T12:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Justice Jackson spends ghost guns argument trying to figure out post-Chevron rules. Spoiler alert, it's just Calvinball. [Law360]
* Confirming what we already knew... the FBI inquiry into Kavanaugh's background was a sham. [ABA Journal]
* Disbarred lawyers have a plan. [Slate]
* CVS and UnitedHealth want FTC commissioners to disqualify themselves because they displayed bias in suggesting that maybe it's bad to artificially inflate insulin prices.
* The Alex Jones reckoning is nigh. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Judges say social media amplifies personal risk. [Legaltech News]
* Davis Polk pushes UK trainee pay to new high. [LegalCheek]
The post Morning Docket: 10.09.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jacksonville Jaguars To Wear “Prowler” Throwback Uniforms Second Time This Season]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82549</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/09/jacksonville-jaguars-to-wear-prowler-throwbacks-second-time-this-season/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T06:37:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Jacksonville Jaguars announced they’ll wear their “Prowler” throwback uniforms for a second time this season when they host the New York Jets on Dec. 15.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Los Angeles Lakers Officially Unveil 2024-25 City Edition Uniforms, Court]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82538</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/09/los-angeles-lakers-officially-unveil-2024-25-city-edition-uniforms-court/basketball/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:40:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although they leaked on social media last month, the Los Angeles Lakers unveiled their 2024-25 City Edition uniforms – as well as the first City Edition court in franchise history – on Tuesday afternoon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poll: Who Will Win The AL Division Series?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=826877</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/10/poll-who-will-win-the-al-division-series.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T04:02:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last night, MLBTR readers weighed in on the National League Division Series. With both series knotted up 1-1 at the time, readers heavily favored the Padres to upset the Dodgers while giving a slight edge to the Phillies to take down the Mets. The lower seeds each prevailed at home tonight to put the NL’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roses de Montréal Aim To Be a Thorn in the Side of Fellow NSL Clubs]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82527</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/08/roses-de-montreal-aim-to-be-a-thorn-in-the-side-of-fellow-nsl-clubs/soccer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T03:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blue rose of primary crest inspired by Montreal city logo and coat of arms; typography inspired by iconic Montreal Farine Five Roses sign]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law Firms Are Ghosting Their Clients — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075956</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/law-firms-are-ghosting-their-clients-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T23:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do Y'all Not Want Money?: Start returning those phone calls!
What's Your Check Looking Like?: Tell us about those bonuses!
That's A Weird Way To Define A Fetus!: Florida tries to ban abortion referendum using odd reading of nuisance laws.
Looking To Do Good Work?: These schools specialize in racial justice.
AI May Change The Law School Application Process: Some changes will need to be made, but what do you do?
The post Law Firms Are Ghosting Their Clients — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Supreme Court Mentor To Colleague]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075949</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/from-supreme-court-mentor-to-colleague/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T23:01:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They already had a working rapport.
The post From Supreme Court Mentor To Colleague appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantastic Fest 2024: A locksmith is trapped by escalating tensions in Belgian thriller Night Call]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855102</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/fantastic-fest-2024-a-locksmith-is-trapped-by-escalating-tensions-in-belgian-thriller-night-call/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T22:29:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is part of our coverage from Fantastic Fest 2024 in Austin, TX where genre films are debuting before they get wider release. Check out all of our coverage here.  Europe has a grand tradition of ticking-clock thrillers from The 39 Steps to Das Boot to Run Lola Run. The latest entry into that storied subgenre (and heir apparent to the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Torres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CNN SCOTUS Scribe Says You Hurt The Chief Justice’s Feelings]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075950</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/cnn-scotus-scribe-says-you-hurt-the-chief-justices-feelings/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T22:18:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sigh more, asshole.
The post CNN SCOTUS Scribe Says You Hurt The Chief Justice’s Feelings appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All the New NHL Logos and Uniforms for 2024-25]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82519</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/08/all-the-new-nhl-logos-and-uniforms-for-2024-25/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T22:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024-25 NHL season is underway, and with it came a few surprisingly big changes to team logos and uniforms. But I must caution: If you were looking for anything other than a return to the ’90s, you might be disappointed. Before we hit up the what the teams did,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Creamer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yale Law’s Diversity Decreases After Affirmative Action’s Death Knell]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075925</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/yale-laws-diversity-decreases-after-affirmative-actions-death-knell/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:32:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are now fewer students of color at Yale Law. What does diversity look like at other leading law schools?
The post Yale Law’s Diversity Decreases After Affirmative Action’s Death Knell appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyer Conflicts Create More Delay In Murdered Law Professor Case]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075954</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/lawyer-conflicts-create-more-delay-in-murdered-law-professor-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:22:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Again? Really?
The post Lawyer Conflicts Create More Delay In Murdered Law Professor Case appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Kansas City Ballet’s Naomi Tanioka]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=854233</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-kansas-city-ballets-naomi-tanioka/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Kansas City Ballet Kansas City Ballet’s newest stage spectacular is a modern reimagining of a beloved classic—Septime Webre’s ALICE (in wonderland). If you’ve seen the ornate billboards around town promoting the performance, you get a sense of how visually stunning the show looks. The performance—opening Oct. 11 at Muriel Kauffman Theatre—promises to be an immersive experience for all...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maikel Garcia Has Earned the Favor of the BABIP Gods]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=448373</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/maikel-garcia-has-earned-the-favor-of-the-babip-gods/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T20:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t be a hero, just be on base when the hero comes up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Baumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frances Tiafoe Provides Postmatch Feedback To Umpire: “Fuck You”]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169767</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/frances-tiafoe-provides-postmatch-feedback-to-umpire-fuck-you"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T20:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frances Tiafoe always says exactly what he means. This is one of his great charms, winning him lots of attention and affection from fans. That candor will also likely wind up costing him thousands of dollars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida Tries To Ban Abortion Referendum Ads Under Public Health Law That Regulates Slaughterhouses And Septic Tanks]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075944</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/florida-tries-to-ban-abortion-referendum-ads-under-public-health-law-that-regulates-slaughterhouses-and-septic-tanks/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T20:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ron DeSantis is a free speech warrior!
The post Florida Tries To Ban Abortion Referendum Ads Under Public Health Law That Regulates Slaughterhouses And Septic Tanks appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clio Releases Clio Duo, Generative AI Built Directly Into Its Law Practice Management Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075926</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/10/clio-releases-clio-duo-generative-ai-built-directly-into-its-law-practice-management-platform.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T19:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Calling it a major first step in its wider AI product roadmap, the law practice management company Clio released Clio Duo, a generative AI product built directly into the Clio Manage law practice management platform.
The post Clio Releases Clio Duo, Generative AI Built Directly Into Its Law Practice Management Platform appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Author Paul Koudounaris explores the history of mourning pets in new book Faithful Unto Death]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=853618</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/author-paul-koudounaris-explores-the-history-of-mourning-pets-in-new-book-faithful-unto-death/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T19:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Faithful Unto Death // Photo by Paul Koudounaris Out this week from Thames & Hudson, author Paul Koudounaris’ new book, Faithful Unto Death, tells the history of “pet cemeteries, animal graves, and eternal devotion” with emotional heft and an eye for detail. From Mr. Winbridge’s burial of a dog named Cherry at London’s Hyde Park to the dusty desert...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October Surprises Are Bullshit]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169681</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/october-surprises-are-bullshit"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T18:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about golf, Houston, candy bars, wet shoulder pads, and more.
I had a family emergency to attend to last week, and we weren’t able to get a guest Funbag host lined up in time after I had to drop everything. As a result, this slot remained vacant. My apologies. I hope you didn’t use that empty space of time to, you know, do actual work. That would have been tragic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking The Door To Generating Success At Legal Conferences]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075657</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/unlocking-the-door-to-generating-success-at-legal-conferences/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T18:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The real value in attending conferences occurs when the participant is well prepared.
The post Unlocking The Door To Generating Success At Legal Conferences appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Fretzin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law Schools Are Burying Their Heads In The Sand About Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075934</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/law-schools-are-burying-their-heads-in-the-sand-about-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T17:48:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The majority of law schools are just ignoring the reality of modern technology.
The post Law Schools Are Burying Their Heads In The Sand About Generative AI appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You’re Stuck In A Time Loop. How Are You Helping Your Team Win A Game?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169699</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/youre-stuck-in-a-time-loop-how-are-you-helping-your-team-win-a-game"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T17:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because I have a normal inner life and a healthy relationship to sports, after watching the Yankees lose Game 2 of the ALDS Monday night, I went to sleep and immediately had a dream in which I was watching the Yankees lose Game 2 of the ALDS. But something was weird about this dream game: It was the exact same as the real game, and I knew the outcome of every pitch and every at-bat before it happened. What if I was cursed to forever watch the Royals bloop and dink their way to victory, over and over and over?
I woke up, thankfully, but the hypothetical stuck with me until there was only way to forget about it: turn it into a blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Top Law Schools For Racial Justice (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075931</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/the-top-law-schools-for-racial-justice-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T17:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Searching for a law school where you'll learn how to be a changemaker in society? Look no further.
The post The Top Law Schools For Racial Justice (2024) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers Fires Robert Saleh]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169701</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/aaron-rodgers-fires-robert-saleh"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a while there, the New York Jets were convinced that they were just one piece away from realizing their vision of divisional dominance. That'll have to happen under a new head coach: On Tuesday, the team fired Robert Saleh after a 2-3 start to the season; he was escorted out of the building by security.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: KALEO brought Icelandic blues rock to The Midland Sunday night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=854523</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-kaleo-brought-icelandic-blues-rock-to-the-midland-sunday-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T17:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KALEO. // Photo by Daniel Fuchs KALEO The Midland Sunday, Oct. 6 Icelandic blues rock band, KALEO, made their debut KC appearance at The Midland last Sunday night as part of their Payback Tour. Roots rockers Larkin Poe opened and our photographer Daniel Fuchs was there to capture it all. KALEO KALEO Setlist USA Today Break My Baby Broken Bones...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Fuchs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tarik Skubal Didn’t Need Much Help]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169679</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tarik-skubal-didnt-need-much-help"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T16:46:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the New Testament, a carpenter from Nazareth saved his followers from damnation and promised them eternal life in his kingdom. In the ALDS, a Carpenter from Florida saved the Tigers from a potential 0-2 series hole and promised them at least two more days of playoff baseball. The latter was more exciting; Jesus probably couldn't even make contact off Emmanuel Clase, while Kerry Carpenter uppercutted a two-strike slider deep into the right-field seats to break a scoreless tie in the ninth inning and deliver Detroit a 3-0 victory on Monday.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rMzV93VrZ08]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law Firms FAILING At The Single Most Basic Lawyering Task]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075935</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/law-firms-failing-at-the-single-most-basic-lawyering-task/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T16:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Come on people. Seriously?
The post Law Firms FAILING At The Single Most Basic Lawyering Task appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryce Harper Is A Bargain]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169538</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bryce-harper-is-a-bargain"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T16:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the nature of baseball economics that each offseason's record-breaking contract will wind up being surpassed; if it works out well enough, it might even come to seem like a deal. In this context, it maybe shouldn't register as a surprise that Bryce Harper, who made $26,050,000 in cash this season, seems like a bargain. His 13-year, $330 million contract, which contains no opt-outs, was the highlight of a 2019 offseason in which Phillies owner John Middleton said the team was prepared to “maybe even be a little bit stupid.” They weren’t; Harper is worth much more to the Phillies than they’re paying him.
The Phillies have been contenders in each of the last three years after almost a decade of being an afterthought. They won a pennant, with the deciding runs coming off a Harper homer in the bottom of the 8th of a clinching game. They won their first division title in 13 years this season. Harper won an MVP. There are other important players on the Phillies, but Harper is the one that has driven the team to its recent success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eat This Now: Slow Rise doughnuts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=854493</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/eat-this-now-slow-rise-doughnuts/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T16:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slow Rise doughnuts // Photo by Sarah Sipple If you’ve heard anything about Slow Rise, I guarantee that two topics were covered: how quickly they sell out with people lining up for them at 5 a.m., and,—to explain the former—how incredible they are.  So the question from some of you may be: are they worth it? Lining up at 5...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AHL’s Iowa Wild Hoping New Alternate Jersey Really Hits Home]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82505</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/08/ahls-iowa-wild-hoping-new-alternate-jersey-really-hits-home/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T15:38:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New white alternate features State Crest logo on front, which blend elements from NHL parent club's logo with outline of Iowa and Des Moines skyline]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Foreigner and Loverboy classic rocked Azura Saturday night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=854521</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-foreigner-and-loverboy-classic-rocked-azura-saturday-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T15:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foreigner. // Photo by Shannon Martens Foreigner w/ Loverboy Azura Amphitheater Saturday, Oct. 5 Fresh off a summer co-headlining tour with fellow classic rockers, Styx, Foreigner brought their slew of hits to Azura on Friday as part of The Historic Farewell Tour. With Canadians Loverboy in town, it was a night of songs to which you definitely know all the words....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shannon Martens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Biglaw Partner Writes Biting Novel Dishing On What’s Wrong With The Profession]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075928</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/former-biglaw-partner-writes-biting-novel-dishing-on-whats-wrong-with-the-profession/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T14:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This lawyer has lots of thoughts about the class action process.
The post Former Biglaw Partner Writes Biting Novel Dishing On What’s Wrong With The Profession appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Tall Guy’ Is Richard Curtis At His Pre-Hollywood Best]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=169035</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-tall-guy-is-richard-curtis-at-his-pre-hollywood-best"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T14:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About halfway through my millionth encounter with Elephant, the fictional, Andrew Lloyd Webber-spoofing musical that features in the 1989 film The Tall Guy, I thought it might be one of the most perfectly executed pieces of satire in the history of the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[J&J Backs Down From 340B Rebates, But Maintains They’re ‘Legally Permissible’ Per Statute]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075914</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/10/johnson-and-johnson-340b-rebates-duplicate-discounts-hrsa-jnj/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T14:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Johnson & Johnson stopped short of implementing its proposal to alter the way two drugs are paid for under the 340B drug discount program, but the drugmaker made it clear it still wants changes. In other recent regulatory news, we have drug approvals, clinical holds, and one product withdrawal.
The post J&J Backs Down From 340B Rebates, But Maintains They’re ‘Legally Permissible’ Per Statute appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FRANK VINLUAN - MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: The Steel Woods said final farewell to KC at Knuckleheads Friday night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=854516</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-the-steel-woods-said-final-farewell-to-kc-at-knuckleheads-friday-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T14:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Steel Woods // Photo by Mike Dotson The Steel Woods w/ Jean Jeansonne Knuckleheads Friday, Oct. 4 While country rockers the Steel Woods were just in Kansas City this past August, opening for outlaw country artist Cody Jinks at Starlight, they made another stop this past Friday night to headline Knuckleheads. It was a bittersweet show, as they are currently...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Dotson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Love, Hate, Clairvoyance: Your 2024–25 NHL Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=167442</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/love-hate-clairvoyance-your-2024-25-nhl-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T13:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's hockey time!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret Sauce: Burnt Ends takes readers on a Kansas City bbq-based Midwest mystery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=850679</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/secret-sauce-burnt-endstakes-readers-on-a-kansas-city-bbq-based-midwest-mystery/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T13:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illustration by Keegan Hudspeth Even though mystery author Laura Wetsel only lived in Kansas City for four years, the city’s energy followed her all the way to Washington, D.C. More specifically, cravings for our world-famous barbeque have proven to be unshakable. This September, her book, Burnt Ends, hit the stands and offered a delicious spin on whodunnits. The murder suspects...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kaylynn Mullins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 10.08.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1075922</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/morning-docket-10-08-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T12:56:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Supreme Court decides to keep R. Kelly trapped in a closet. [Reuters]
* Georgia Supreme Court reinstates 6-week abortion ban while it considers appeal. Dissent points out that the majority couldn't come up with any basis for this outside of the underlying merits arguments. [Washington Post]
* Quantum computing will require upping your cybersecurity game. [Bloomberg Law News]
* 2 Live Crew are trying to get back the rights to their music -- which other artists have had to do -- but the label is making the novel argument that the group was making works for hire and aren't eligible for the copyright clawback. [Law360]
* Most in-house counsel don't see AI as "transformative." Which is a weird word to survey because what does that even mean? [Corporate Counsel]
* Another Deshaun Watson lawsuit intercepted before trial. [The Athletic]
* Judge facing ethics inquiry for failing to be “patient, dignified or courteous.” [ABA Journal]
The post Morning Docket: 10.08.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantastic Fest 2024: Li Yang’s over-the-top action-adventure Escape from the 21st Century weaponizes nostalgia. Literally.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855101</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/fantastic-fest-2024-li-yangs-over-the-top-action-adventure-escape-from-the-21st-century-weaponizes-nostalgia-literally/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T06:24:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is part of our coverage from Fantastic Fest 2024 in Austin, TX where genre films are debuting before they get wider release. Check out all of our coverage here.  Escape From The 21st Century. The Chinese film is a crowd-pleasing action-adventure-comedy-time travel coming-of-age story that both traffics in 90s nostalgia and comments on escapism and the necessity of a childlike...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Torres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That Escalated Quickly: Royals Rally Against Rodón, Secure Split in the Bronx]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=448338</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/that-escalated-quickly-royals-rally-against-rodon-secure-split-in-the-bronx/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T06:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A big home run by Salvador Perez and a flurry of hits by his lesser-known teammates erased some impressive early innings by the Yankees starter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Jaffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Western Kentucky Hilltoppers Unveil Big Red-Inspired Helmets]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=82498</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/10/08/western-kentucky-hilltoppers-unveil-big-red-inspired-helmets/college/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T05:27:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Western Kentucky recently announced it will wear helmets inspired by its mascot, Big Red, during Thursday's game against UTEP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>