<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-01-05T12:29:00.985Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chordcat – chord naming program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140419</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/chordcat-chord-naming-program/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-05T10:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chordcat is a desktop app that helps you identify and name chords based on inputted notes.
The post Chordcat – chord naming program appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lock – process data with GnuPG]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140431</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/lock-process-data-gnupg/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-05T09:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lock is a graphical front-end for GnuPG (GPG) making use of an attractive LibAdwaita GUI.
The post Lock – process data with GnuPG appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[delicolour – lightweight colour finder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140425</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/delicolour-lightweight-colour-finder/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-05T08:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[delicolour is a lightweight colour finder written in Python.
The post delicolour – lightweight colour finder appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[nvim-tree – file explorer for Neovim]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140408</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/nvim-tree-file-explorer-neovim/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-05T06:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[nvim-tree.lua is a file explorer / filesystem tree view plugin for Neovim. It's written in Lua.
The post nvim-tree – file explorer for Neovim appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Intense winter storm moves in (SAT-1/4)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3779067</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-intense-winter-storm-moves-in-sat-1-4/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-04T16:14:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Winter Storm Blair is moving into the Kansas City metro with sleet, freezing rain and snow creating blizzard-like conditions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Intense winter storm moves in (SAT-1/4)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3779067</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-intense-winter-storm-moves-in-sat-1-4/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-04T16:14:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A rare Saturday blog for you today as the weather, as usual, dictates the blog update. We're starting the day with clouds and an atmosphere that is gradually saturating through the Plains. The scope of the storms impacts will be through a corridor along the I-70 region, roughly 100-200 miles on either side into the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to popular CLI tools: history]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=106586</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alternatives-popular-cli-tools-history/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-04T14:40:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[history is a command which displays or manipulates the history list. We recommend alternatives to this command.
The post Alternatives to popular CLI tools: history appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chess Clock – time games of over-the-board chess]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140397</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/chess-clock-time-games-board/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-04T14:25:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chess Clock is a simple application to provide time control for over-the-board chess games. It's written in Python.
The post Chess Clock – time games of over-the-board chess appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archey 4 – simple system information tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140382</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/archey-simple-system-information-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-04T11:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Archey is a simple system information tool written in Python.
The post Archey 4 – simple system information tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[hiSHtory – better shell history]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140342</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/hishtory-better-shell-history/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T23:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hiSHtory is a better shell history. It stores your shell history in context 
The post hiSHtory – better shell history appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vancouver’s Favorite Sport Isn’t Hockey, It’s Talking About Locker-Room Beefs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177526</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/vancouvers-favorite-sport-isnt-hockey-its-talking-about-locker-room-beefs"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T22:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps like their shooting percentage, the harmony and good vibes of the Vancouver Canucks were due for regression this year. Still clinging to the second Western Conference wild card spot but with a tough remaining schedule and a new batch of injuries, the Canucks are neither good enough to contend (as they were last year) nor bad enough to write off (as they were for several years before that). The on-ice product is such a slog that the only entertainment the team now provides is in the form of a purported rift between their two top centers, Elias Pettersson and J.T. Miller.
The simplest version of this story goes that Pettersson is passive and disengaged while Miller is intense and abrasive to the point of bullying, and because of this, they do not get along. “Petey and my relationship has come a long way. We're still working at it. We're completely different people, you know what I mean?” Miller told Sportsnet's Iain MacIntyre last February. If you’re at all familiar with hockey media’s latent Don Cherry mindset, you can guess that they tend to read the Swedish Pettersson as aloof and effete, while J.T. Miller, who gets caught swearing on the on-ice microphone roughly 15 times a season, plays his foil, the classic American red-ass who cares a lot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xplr –  hackable, minimal, fast TUI file explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140350</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/xplr-hackable-minimal-fast-tui-file-explorer/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T21:58:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xplr is a terminal UI based file explorer that aims to increase your terminal productivity. It's written in Rust.
The post xplr –  hackable, minimal, fast TUI file explorer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bean Counter: Second Best Coffee serves grounds for inclusion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866148</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/bean-counter-second-best-coffee-serves-grounds-for-inclusion/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T20:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Second Best Coffee For any small business, building a sense of community is a key factor for growth. There are plenty of places in Kansas City that have good coffee, good cocktails, or good barbecue, but it’s the spots where you feel a personal connection that keep you coming back—again and again. For Leia and Nathan Anderson,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Baranowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Jimmy Butler Fiasco Is Getting Ugly]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177623</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-jimmy-butler-fiasco-is-getting-ugly"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T18:18:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unsatisfied that the Miami Heat didn't get the hint the first or second times around, Jimmy Butler finally just said it on Thursday night: He wants a trade. The permanently aggrieved Heat forward has been especially aggrieved this season after the team didn't offer him an extension on his big honking contract this past summer, so despite the Heat actually playing some decent basketball, he's done with them.
The shape of this superstar trade demand mostly adheres to the standards of the form, but things could get weird in the month remaining between now and the trading deadline. These are the Miami Heat and Jimmy Butler we're talking about here, two forces whose stubbornness is only matched by their performance of obstinance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burying The SEC Feels Too Good To Be Wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177606</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/burying-the-sec-feels-too-good-to-be-wrong"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T17:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The South Eastern Conference has not had a good go of it in this year's bowl season. The conference reached a low point during last night's Sugar Bowl, in which Georgia was pantsed by Notre Dame. It was an odd thing, watching this Notre Dame team that lost to NIU cruise to a 23-10 victory while looking bigger and stronger than their SEC powerhouse opponents.
You can argue that Georgia played better than the score indicates, even while starting QB Gunner Stockton. Stockton was fine, throwing for 234 yards and one touchdown while outplaying his counterpart, Riley Leonard, who threw for just 90 yards a touchdown. The game was decided in the margins, with Georgia losing two fumbles at critical points and Notre Dame beginning the second half with a 98-yard kick return for a touchdown. Georgia was out-coached, out-schemed, and much of their season's sloppiness finally came back to bite them. Maybe their rookie QB was a deficit, but I would ask anyone making that argument to go watch some Carson Beck tape from this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Underexplained Predictions For 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177596</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/underexplained-predictions-for-2025"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T16:08:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is what's going to happen in 2025, according to the Defector staff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Only Catch Bob Dylan With Time]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177502</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/you-can-only-catch-bob-dylan-with-time"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T15:42:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who threw the glass in the street, man? That query has echoed in my head ever since I saw D.A. Pennebaker's 1967 documentary Don't Look Back, which captured in cinéma vérité the overwhelming attention that followed Bob Dylan to England in '65, while he was still a solo acoustic act on stage. The documentary crystallizes what is probably the most commonly shared cultural image we have of Dylan: a skinny dude with sunglasses and messy hair and disordered energy, speaking in snide riddles, beset by clueless questions from square reporters.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OP9ArKYGvD4]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Near blizzard conditions possible (FRI-1/3)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3778079</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-near-blizzard-conditions-possible-fri-1-3/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T15:25:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A winter storm this weekend in Kansas City will bring snow, sleet, ice and Arctic temperatures, with winds that may spur blizzard conditions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upsets Aside, The College Football Playoff Is Going According To Plan]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177580</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/upsets-aside-the-college-football-playoff-is-going-according-to-plan"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T14:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a weird but entirely satisfactory anomaly of the first true college football national tournament that the seeding mattered exactly not at all. The lowest seed in the field is going to end up as a touchdown favorite over the highest seed remaining, three of the four semifinalists are big, name-brand schools that can be found less than 500 miles from each other, and every remaining team is a traditional powerhouse. 
In other words, in its first attempt at a proper tournament, this most baronial of sports got the only things it ever wants, which is an emphatic reinforcement of its regional roots (plus those outworlders from Austin) and the return of Notre Dame. The rest of you can piss right off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warm up from the inside out with some of the best soups in Kansas City]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866102</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/warm-up-from-the-inside-out-with-some-of-the-best-soups-in-kansas-city/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T14:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blue Crab & Sweet Corn Bisque at Pierpont’s // Photo courtesy Pierpont’s at Union Station I am a year-round soup connoisseur. Give me a savory broth with a large spoon, and I’m happy. But a soup has to meet a few requirements for me to get excited about it. First, it has to evoke a feeling of “healing,” which is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Cisco Packet Tracer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140365</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-cisco-packet-tracer/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T13:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Packet Tracer is a networking simulation tool for teaching and learning how to create network topologies. We recommend the best free and open source alternatives.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Cisco Packet Tracer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bevel – command line history in an SQLite database]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140339</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/bevel-command-line-history-sqlite-database/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T12:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bevel is a tool which offers command line history in an SQLite database for effective re-use.
The post Bevel – command line history in an SQLite database appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[rtfetch – Neofetch but in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140378</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/rtfetch-neofetch-rust/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T11:44:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[rtfetch is a command-line system information tool. It's a clone of neofetch but written in Rust.
The post rtfetch – Neofetch but in Rust appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ditana – Arch-based Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140352</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ditana-arch-based-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T09:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ditana Linux is a rolling release distro based on Arch Linux with built-in AI.  Ditana prioritizes giving users full control over their system.
The post Ditana – Arch-based Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[browsr – file explorer in your terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140347</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/browsr-file-explorer-terminal/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T08:44:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[browsr is a a pleasant file explorer in your terminal supporting all filesystems.
The post browsr – file explorer in your terminal appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Origami Black Hole]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3033/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3033/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jay – Wayland compositor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140330</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/jay-wayland-compositor/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T22:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jay is a Wayland compositor which offers an i3 look and feel.
The post Jay – Wayland compositor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Re-Sign Austin Cox To Minors Contract]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=836513</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/01/royals-re-sign-austin-cox-to-minors-contract.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T22:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have signed Austin Cox to another minor league contract. After electing free agency in November, the left-hander will return to the only MLB organization he’s known throughout his seven-year pro career. The team announced the signing this afternoon. Cox, who turns 28 on Opening Day, first signed with the Royals as a fifth-round…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leo Morgenstern</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kathará – lightweight network emulation system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140325</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/kathara-lightweight-network-emulation-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T20:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kathará is a lightweight network emulation system based on Docker containers. It's written in Python.
The post Kathará – lightweight network emulation system appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tahlequah Grieves Again]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177544</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tahlequah-grieves-again"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T19:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2018, the orca Tahlequah, or J35, made headlines for her tour of grief, in which she carried the dead body of her calf for 17 days. The baby, which lived only for half an hour, was female. At the time, she marked the first successful birth in Tahlequah's pod, known as the J Pod, in three years. A baby orca can weigh as much as 300 pounds. But each time the body slid off her snout, Tahlequah dove to retrieve it. Tahlequah swam with her dead calf for at least 1,000 miles before she dropped her body, which had begun to decompose. Many people considered Tahlequah's behavior a display of grief, although some researchers had reservations. (Spoiler: I personally find the most logical explanation to be grief.) 
In late December 2024, Tahlequah gave birth to another calf, which would have been her third baby to survive, in addition to the 13-year-old Notch, or J47, and the 3-year-old Phoenix, or J57, both male. Tahlequah's new calf, J61, was female, which would have been a boon for the struggling population of southern residents, a culturally distinct population of orcas in the Pacific Northwest that includes J, K, and L pods. On Dec. 24, the Center for Whale Research expressed concern about the health of the calf, which was likely born prematurely. "J35 is an experienced mother, and we hope that she is able to keep J61 alive through these difficult early days," the Center posted on Facebook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Football Is The Way To Enlightenment]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177518</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/morning-football-is-the-way-to-enlightenment"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T18:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
No one plans on becoming a morning person. We all have morning people in our lives, and they tend to be an unappealing lot. They openly (proudly!) declare themselves to be morning people, almost as a warning to others. They can’t wait to start their day with an enthusiasm unknown to mankind, so that they get on with the process of 21st century self-optimization: Waking up at 3:00 a.m., doing 900 crunches before breakfast, updating multiple life goal spreadsheets, making every call while on speakerphone while on a Peloton, and drinking oddly colored protein shakes for “body fuel” every other hour. Real Marky Mark shit. Teenage you would vomit in horror at the idea of ever morphing into this sort of creature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust-Traverse – terminal based file explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140322</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/rust-traverse-terminal-based-file-explorer/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T17:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rust-Traverse is a terminal based file explorer. It is inspired by the NNN file manager. It uses Ratatui for the terminal UI.
The post Rust-Traverse – terminal based file explorer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Time The Bulls And Hornets Play Each Other, The Venue Must Be Hell Itself]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177503</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-next-time-the-bulls-and-hornets-play-each-other-the-venue-must-be-hell-itself"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T17:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Charlotte Hornets are puke. By win percentage they are one of the three or four worst teams in basketball, but unlike their fellow losers, the Hornets sincerely believe they have some significant part of their core of the future already in place, which is sad enough that if I think about it for very long I will cry. The Chicago Bulls aren't quite puke, but they'd be better off if they were. Instead, they are the very textbook case of NBA mediocrity, a dreary irrelevant also-ran made up of mismatched bozos hoping to play their ways individually into trades to anyplace else, except Charlotte. The six-win Washington Wizards are currently 3–1 against these two bumbling outfits; it's a real dog-food buffet down in the lower half of the Eastern Conference.
Both teams shoot a lot of three-pointers. My abacus tells me there are worse ways to lose a basketball game, but there are not many that are uglier. The Bulls have had a better time with bombing away: Per Cleaning the Glass, they've outperformed their expected record by about two wins, a taste of good fortune which accounts entirely for their hold on middling-hood despite being one of the handful of worst defensive teams out there. The Hornets are bad at shooting and even worse at picking their shots—you'd have to watch a couple of their games to appreciate how blindly and recklessly their "best" players chuck crap only vaguely basketward—and as a consequence they have the third worst offense by points per possession in the NBA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamips – emulate Cisco routers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140320</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/dynamips-emulate-cisco-routers/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T16:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamips is an emulator computer program that was written to emulate Cisco routers.
The post Dynamips – emulate Cisco routers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Didn’t Orchestra Musicians Choose To Learn Cooler Instruments?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177424</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-didnt-orchestra-musicians-choose-to-learn-cooler-instruments"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T16:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Drew's off. Today, we're talking about Jesus's farts, woodwinds, Monty Python, and more.
Hello Funbaggers (I'm assuming that's how y'all refer to yourselves), this is Rachelle Hampton, a non-Drew staff writer here at Defector. First: an apology, both for not being Drew and for being late with this week's Funbag. My household was felled by a plague that began with my cousin's adorable 8-month-old twins/disease vectors. But thanks to the wonders of modern medicine (shout-out to amoxicillin) I'm on my way back to fighting shape and ready to answer all your burning questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arizona State Showed Us How Good The 12-Team Playoff Can Be]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177488</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/arizona-state-showed-us-how-good-the-12-team-playoff-can-be"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T14:25:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Texas Longhorns defeated the Arizona State Sun Devils, 39-31, in a double-overtime thriller to advance to the semifinals of the 12-team college football playoff. After the Longhorns got out to a quick 14-0 lead in the first quarter, the Sun Devils clawed their way back, slowly but surely, before closing the fourth quarter with 16 straight points. A pair of missed field goals by Texas certainly helped the comeback.
ASU quarterback Sam Leavitt threw for 222 yards, completing 24-of-46 passes, along with an ill-timed interception to end the second OT. On the other side, Texas quarterback Quinn Ewers threw for 322 yards and accounted for three TDs and one interception. But the player of the game was easily ASU running back Cam Skattebo, whose toughness and gladiator effort nearly won the game. He rushed for 143 yards and two TDs, and caught eight passes for another 99 yards. He even threw a 42-yard touchdown pass for good measure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Major winter storm ahead (THU-1/2)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3777031</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-major-winter-storm-ahead-thu-1-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T14:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Temperatures Thursday won't be too bad, with highs in the lower to mid-40s; colder air comes in tonight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Major winter storm ahead (THU-1/2)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3777031</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-major-winter-storm-ahead-thu-1-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T14:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Temperatures Thursday won't be too bad, with highs in the lower to mid-40s; colder air comes in tonight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NerdFetch – fetch script using Nerdfonts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140199</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/nerdfetch-fetch-script-nerdfonts/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T07:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NerdFetch is a simple shell script which fetches information about your system.
The post NerdFetch – fetch script using Nerdfonts appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do You Win When You Compete With Yourself?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176544</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-do-you-win-when-you-compete-with-yourself"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T18:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The good thing about hinging some degree of your mental health on working out is that you can almost always exercise; the bad thing about hinging some degree of your mental health on working out is that you can almost always exercise. 
This story of hubris starts in January, when I was climbing in the gym and my finger—and this is not a medical term, but it is the most accurate way I can describe the process—exploded. Perched near the top of the wall, my left hand curled around a sloping hunk of white plastic and my right pulling hand on a wallet-thick crimp oriented sideways, I unmoored my left to swing it over to a larger white hold, bearing all my body weight for a long second or two on my tensed right hand. The tension violently and suddenly resolved itself; by which I mean a tendon in my right ring finger snapped.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Major winter storm potential increases (WED-2025)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3776402</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-major-winter-storm-potential-increases-wed-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T18:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Snow is expected this weekend in Kansas City. Here's how much you can expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Major winter storm potential increases (WED-2025)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3776402</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-major-winter-storm-potential-increases-wed-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T18:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year! 2024 will go down as the 16th warmest year in KC weather record history...records go back about 135 years...and the 58th driest year with 34.63" of moisture. It was memorable in some ways too...including the increase in severe weather and tornadoes in the region, some of the big ups and downs, and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Was Wrong About Diet Coke]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176331</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-was-wrong-about-diet-coke"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T16:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was in college, I declared Diet Coke my enemy. My reason was the only good reason to declare anything an enemy: someone wrote a bad blog about it. 
Some girl I didn’t know published an op-ed in the school newspaper counting all the reasons she was truly, deeply devoted to Diet Coke. It wasn’t serious, but it pissed me off so much I started fights with girls in my sorority kitchen over it. Couldn’t they see that she was making all of us look like idiots by publishing something like this?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Northland coziness at BC Bistro and Renegade Coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866069</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-northland-coziness-at-bc-bistro-and-renegade-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T14:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BC Bistro BC Bistro was the perfect spot for a casual lunch with my mom and daughter. The ambiance felt effortlessly festive, with a cozy, holiday-inspired touch that made the space warm and inviting without going overboard. The service was just as welcoming—attentive and efficient, with hot, fresh food arriving at our table right on time. We started with the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Horrible Things Did We Do To Our Penises Last Year?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=175085</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-horrible-things-did-we-do-to-our-penises-last-year-5"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T14:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy new year to one and all. Make a resolution never to do any of these things.
All descriptions are taken verbatim from the U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission’s database of emergency room visits:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNS3 – network simulator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140312</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gns3-network-simulator/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T09:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Graphical Network Simulator-3 (GNS3) is software that allows users to emulate, configure, test, and troubleshoot virtual and real networks.
The post GNS3 – network simulator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skew-T Log-P]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3032/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3032/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>