<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-11-13T12:31:02.448Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pokey LaFarge brought his protracted platter of hits to Knuckleheads last Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861304</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/pokey-lafarge-brought-his-protracted-platter-of-hits-to-knuckleheads-last-friday/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T21:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pokey LaFarge at Knuckleheads on Friday, Nov. 8, 2024. // Photo by Joe Ellett On Friday, Nov. 8, Pokey LaFarge brought his slicked-back hair and polished guitar skills to Knuckleheads.  Salt Lake City-based The Tailspins opened the night with their ‘50s style ragtime. The husband and wife duo of Oskar and Julia Buie filled Knuckleheads Garage with ancient-esque air, as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Ellett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steve-O continues to up the ante with The Super Dummy Tour and we are better for it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=860743</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/steve-o-continues-to-up-the-ante-with-the-super-dummy-tour-and-we-are-better-for-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T19:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Photo “Steve-O”—Even the sound of the name fascinates. It conjures the near-mythological gen x/millennial cultural-comedic zeitgeist. For those of us lucky enough to have come of age with Steve-O and the Jackass fellas, Steve-O’s persona and antics bring to the fore a reminder of the necessity of the edifying elixir of humor—perhaps when the world has needed it most...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexej Savreux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s The Worst Sport To Play With A Poopy Diaper?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173011</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/whats-the-worst-sport-to-play-with-a-poopy-diaper"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T18:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about Skittles, playing sports with a full diaper, college football, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big Pigeon Isn’t Scary Enough]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173031</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-big-pigeon-isnt-scary-enough"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T17:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first thing I thought when I saw the big pigeon was I wish I didn't know the big pigeon was here. Oh, I was plenty charmed. It's a hyperrealistic, 16-foot aluminum pigeon—like pizza, the basic idea is good enough that I'm not really sure there's any version of the execution that wouldn't have satisfied me. But I had come specifically to see the pigeon, and achieved that goal, and wished I had been surprised by it instead. Turned a corner and been gobsmacked by the pigeon, or been riding up 10th Avenue and seen the pigeon in the distance, getting ever-closer and -larger. What the hell? would have been my ideal reaction to seeing the big pigeon for the first time. Why is there a pigeon here?
Well, why not? It's Manhattan. There are pigeons everywhere. Anywhere from half a million to nine million, depending on who you ask. Iván Argote, a Colombian artist living in Paris, has added one more with his sculpture which perches atop the High Line, an unused rail trestle turned linear park, and stares somewhat menacingly down on passing traffic. The sculpture is called Dinosaur (on display through spring 2026), and it does look more than a little saurian at this scale—the claws look like they could properly gut you, perhaps as revenge for all those times you didn't offer his smaller cousins any crumbs. Close-up foot here, with, helpfully, a pigeon for scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the Bottle: Pursuit Spirits siphons inspiration from chardonnay and a beloved “dusty”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861284</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/inside-the-bottle-pursuit-spirits-siphons-inspiration-from-chardonnay-and-a-beloved-dusty/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T17:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pursuit Spirits Double-Oaked Bourbon Whiskey // Photo by Mike Dahlor Pursuit Spirits’ latest whiskey is special, but to fully appreciate the depth of this offering, I’m going to guide you on a trip through time. Time to fire up the Flux Capacitor. This trip is focused on what, in the whiskey world, is known as a “Dusty.” A dusty whiskey...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Dahlor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Outrageous talent makes for a bodacious bloodbath in KCRep’s Little Shop of Horrors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859887</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-outrageous-talent-makes-for-a-bodacious-bloodbath-in-kcreps-little-shop-of-horrors/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T17:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chioma Anyanwu, Alyssa Byers, Chloe Castro-Santos, and Amari Lewis in KCRep’s 2024 production of LITTLE SHOP OF HORRORS. // Photo by Don Ipock Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can’t Sell Tua Tagovailoa’s Story]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173006</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/you-cant-sell-tua-tagovailoas-story"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T16:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before Monday night's game between the Miami Dolphins and Los Angeles Rams, ESPN reporter Jeff Darlington and Dolphins quarterback Tua Tagovailoa teamed up to produce one of the year's strangest pieces of NFL-related media.
Tagovailoa is exactly the sort of young, talented, charismatic quarterback that the league and its broadcasters crave in order to sell fans on a Monday night game between two mediocre teams, so it makes sense that he would be the centerpiece of ESPN's pregame coverage. Tagovailoa's marketability is complicated, however, by the fact that he recently completed yet another stint on the IR after being concussed in Week 2. Tagovailoa's career, from college to the pros, has been riddled with brain injuries, at such an alarming rate that many pundits were urging him to retire following the hit he took in September. Tagovailoa didn't retire, though, and now he's trying to salvage the Dolphins' season. It's a story worth telling, surely, but how exactly does a network sell the story to fans?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Can’t Stop Drinking This Fucked-Up Protein Shake]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172921</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-cant-stop-drinking-this-fucked-up-protein-shake"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T15:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every morning, I make for myself a protein shake. It is my impression that this is good behavior, healthy and so forth. I do not consider it my business to engage in any even half-serious interrogation of this impression. The body requires protein, probably, and though I do enjoy gnawing on animal parts, it's a lot simpler to fire down a daily hit of protein out of a shaker bottle (or three) than it is to make sure I have handfuls of meat available in the fridge at all times. Every morning, I open the pantry and hunt around for the tub of protein powder. Very often on these hunts, I encounter other, different tubs, tubs and bags of things that look like protein powder but possibly are not, or tubs or bags of things that definitely are not protein powder, but look and smell like they are meant to be dissolved in water and then consumed, for health. Health being good, I find it wise simply to throw a scoop or two of these things into the shaker bottle, to make the resulting sludge maximally healthful.
Here are some things that are going into my current "protein" shake, in order of application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Weather weirdness alert (TUE-11/12)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3726047</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-weather-weirdness-alert-tue-11-12/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T15:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got to say, watching the model data for next week is a walk on the wild side right now, and fascinating as well. This happens when the models are trying to figure something out, something that may be highly unusual, and as a result, they sort of freak out. Most models have some fascinating solutions, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Somebody Somewhere’ Is A Dream Without A Deadline]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173001</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/somebody-somewhere-is-a-dream-without-a-deadline"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T14:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bridget Everett is 52. She was 48 when HBO took on her show, Somebody Somewhere, now in its third and final season. The show, in which she plays the lead character, Sam, loosely depicts Everett’s own life, or at least the one she would have lived if she had stayed in Kansas instead of moving to New York, where she eventually became a downtown alt-cabaret star. If you consider her start getting her equity card around the age of 26, that’s a good two decades to get to the position she is in now, where her show is a Peabody Award winner and she no longer has to wait tables as a fallback. Depending on your perspective, that’s incredibly cool or incredibly nuts.
“Dreams don’t have deadlines.” The first time I saw Everett say that was in 2017, during an interview for the indie film Patti Cake$, in which she plays the alcoholic mother of a bartender (Danielle Macdonald) who aspires to become a rap star. “There’s a quote from LL Cool J,” Everett tells the young interviewer, laughing, “it’s DDHD—Dreams don’t have deadlines—and I live by that and I think everybody should live by it because it doesn’t matter if you’re 15, you’re 23, or you’re collecting retirement checks, just keep going for what makes you feel happy and follow and live your dream.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: The Rabbit hOle digs deeper into their own private Narnia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859878</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-the-rabbit-hole-digs-deeper-into-their-own-private-narnia/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T14:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of The Rabbit hOle Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Receive PPI Pick For Witt’s Top-Three MVP Finish]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=830531</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/royals-receive-ppi-pick-for-witts-top-three-mvp-finish.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T05:20:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Baseball Writers Association of America announced the finalists for the 2024 awards this evening. Bobby Witt Jr. was among the finalists for American League MVP, indicating he finished in the top three in the balloting. As Matt Eddy of Baseball America points out (on X), that’ll earn the Royals an extra pick after the first…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daisy Ridley’s mean little neo-noir Magpie forgets to give its characters any character]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=860529</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/daisy-ridleys-mean-little-neo-noir-magpie-forgets-to-give-its-characters-any-character/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T22:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Shout! Studios There are few genres we’re more on board for than the tiny cat-and-mouse thriller—especially those that feel like a stage play captured on film… those intimate games with twists, turns, and a chance for a small set of actors to just go hard in the paint. Last month’s Hitchcockian thriller The Wasp turned a muder-for-hire thriller into...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Current swipe first match of 2024 NWSL Playoffs against North Carolina Courage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=860755</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-current-swipe-first-match-of-2024-nwsl-playoffs-against-north-carolina-courage/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T22:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KC Current versus North Carolina Courage on Saturday, Nov. 9, 2024. // Photo by Tarik Sykes KC Current took on North Carolina Courage in their first match of the 2024 NWSL Playoffs on Saturday, Nov. 9. Coming into the playoffs as the four-seed, the Current were matched up against five-seed North Carolina. Temwa Chawinga—the team’s savior—quickly did what she knows...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarik Sykes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premier League Ref Admits Video Of Him Talking Wild Shit About Liverpool Not Actually A Deepfake]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172913</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-really-is-david-coote-shitting-on-klopp"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T21:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Monday morning, English soccer's referee association (PGMOL) announced that it had suspended Premier League ref David Coote after an odd video of him leaked online. In the video, Coote, who appears to be absolutely smacked off of some kind of intoxicating substance, chats some generationally compromising shit. Despite his earlier assertion that someone put a ton of effort into producing a bizarre fake video of a relatively obscure referee talking generationally compromising shit, Coote's since admitted it was indeed him.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WQtnWER3TEU]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boots Ennis Learns That Being Boring Can Be Worse Than Losing]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172920</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/boots-ennis-learns-that-being-boring-can-be-worse-than-losing"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T19:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jaron "Boots" Ennis put himself in a KO-or-lose situation. So even while keeping his belt in what was a romp on the scorecards in Saturday’s IBF welterweight title fight against Karen Chukhadzhian in front of a hometown Philadelphia crowd, in the big picture Ennis hardly came away a winner. 
Over the summer, Ennis and his team booked what looked like a paid workout when he signed to face the Ukrainian, whom he’d already beaten by decision in January 2023 on the undercard of a Tank Davis fight. Boots had the title, the perfect record (32-0 with 29 knockouts), and a one-two combo of out-of-the-ring charm and on-the-job ferocity that put him in any conversation about boxing’s Next Big Thing. The 27-year old Philly native was maybe just one highlight-reel KO away from breathing the rare air that Tank breathes popularity-wise, hitting pay-per-view headliner status and getting what all boxers suddenly covet: An invite to Saudi Arabia. This was the fight that was supposed to get Ennis all that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester City Is Stuck In The Mud]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172861</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/manchester-city-is-stuck-in-the-mud"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T19:15:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester City loves to give rivals hope right before snatching it away. The four-peating Premier League champions started each of those consecutive title-winning campaigns with whimpers, relatively speaking, dropping at least eight points in Premier League play in each of them by about mid-November. Each of those stretches of (relatively) subpar play gave hope to everyone who supports a fellow title contender or simply (and justifiably) hates City's whole deal. But, as the saying goes, it's the hope that kills you, and City eventually crushed those hopes in each of those four seasons.
Right on time, the present day Citizens have entered the late-fall point of the schedule mired in a funk. Right now City sits in second place on the league table, having dropped 10 points in its first 11 matches. After a strong start to the campaign, the Mancs have hit the skids hard recently, currently stuck in a four-match losing streak across all competitions. The latest blow came in a come-from-ahead 2-1 loss to Brighton on Saturday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analog Adventures: Ray Charles, The Creature Comforts, The Fleshtones, and more new vinyl releases for October 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859853</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/analog-adventures-ray-charles-the-creature-comforts-the-fleshtones-and-more-new-vinyl-releases-for-october-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T19:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Analog Adventures, where we run down the latest stacks of wax to hit our mailbox. Reissues, new releases, and more are all on the turntable as we spin these records. Ray Charles Modern Sounds in Country and Western Music Modern Sounds in Country and Western Music Volume Two Country and Western Meets Rhythm and Blues Crying Time Best...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Jayhawks take down #17 Cyclones in high-scoring affair]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=860752</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-jayhawks-take-down-17-cyclones-in-high-scoring-affair/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T17:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas Jayhawks versus Iowa State Cyclones on Saturday, Nov. 9, 2024. // Photo by Tarik Sykes College football was on display again this past weekend at Arrowhead Stadium at GEHA Field, as the Kansas Jayhawks took on the #17 ranked Iowa State Cyclones on Saturday, Nov. 9. Saturday was an action-packed, high-scoring display of talent between the two Big 12...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarik Sykes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Blood on the big screen as Wichita-shot Western pistol-whips the genre]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859868</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-blood-on-the-big-screen-as-wichita-shot-western-pistol-whips-the-genre/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T17:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Matthew Lloyd Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be publishing these...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NBA Friendship Wobbled By Ill-Timed Fake Handshake]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172844</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nba-friendship-wobbled-by-ill-timed-fake-handshake"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T16:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early in the second quarter of Sunday's game between the excellent but joyless Boston Celtics and the talented but butt Milwaukee Bucks, Giannis Antetokounmpo kerpowed Jaylen Brown with a high elbow. Giannis had the ball on the block, drove to the defense's middle, and then attempted to pivot over his left shoulder, throwing out a cartoonishly long and pointy chicken wing to clear some shooting space; Brown, the primary defender, took the blow to the shoulder and head, and went down with a shout. The referees signaled an offensive foul and awarded the ball to the Celtics. Giannis offered Brown a conciliatory handshake and then cruelly yoinked it away, executing the rude "too slow" hair-smoothing maneuver and leaving Brown grasping at air.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d6crt19V_mU]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Nov. 11: Paintball]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172864</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-nov-11-paintball"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a picture perfect Monday crossword for you. This week's puzzle was constructed by Will Nediger and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Will is a crossword constructor from London, Ontario who uses the nom de plume Bewilderingly (an anagram of "by Will Nediger").
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NBA Is Turning Into One Big Hospital Ward]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172880</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-nba-is-turning-into-one-big-hospital-ward"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T15:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our NBA Injury Of The Day is brought to you by the G League. Eventually, All You'll Have Left Is Us.
Today's IOTD is Chet Holmgren's fractured pelvis, which given that he just played in his 100th career NBA game Friday night almost sounds like he is using his grandfather's bones to carry his skin. He contested an Andrew Wiggins shot less than six minutes into Sunday's early season marquee stealer between Golden State and Oklahoma City and fell hard to the floor, limped off, and won't even be evaluated again before mid-January at the earliest. Now that we're all more seasoned in the way of evaluating injury evaluations, that means he won't be back until early February.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Could winter weather arrive in 10 days? (MON-11/11)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3725031</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-could-winter-weather-arrive-in-10-days-mon-11-11/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T15:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our mild November will continue for the next week or so in the region as we're running 5.5° above average so far this month and with more days in the next 7 in the 60s for highs...it won't be all that bad around these parts. As a matter of fact since meteorological fall began on [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jerry Jones Does Not Have Sufficient Respect For The Sun]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172837</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jerry-jones-does-not-have-sufficient-respect-for-the-sun"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T15:07:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A big, dense ball of gas that has fascinated mankind since the dawn of time, Jerry Jones is constantly innovating in the field of sabotaging his own team. Not content with letting paying customers watch Cowboys players poop, Jones has perfected a unique method of neutralizing players: blinding them with the awesome power of the Sun itself. Supervillain shit.
A wide-open CeeDee Lamb tried and failed to catch a second-quarter touchdown pass in Sunday's 34-6 loss to the Eagles, and it's not really his fault, since he had no idea there was a pass at all. The Sun, low in the standard-time skies and blasting through the huge glass windows at the opposite end of Cowboys Stadium, made sure of that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: KC Current’s cultural currency as classy competitors earns their crowns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859858</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-kc-currents-cultural-currency-as-classy-competitors-earns-their-crowns/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T14:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Tarik Sykes Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be publishing these...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jared Goff Threw Five Interceptions And None Of Them Mattered]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172832</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jared-goff-threw-five-interceptions-and-none-of-them-mattered"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T14:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If an accurate quarterback is a comfortable quarterback, then the Texans' pass rush made Jared Goff play like he was wearing cleats filled with Christmas tree needles for most of Sunday's night contest against the Lions. A one-loss signal-caller who entered Houston on a record pace for completion percentage, who hadn't thrown a ball to the wrong-colored jerseys since Week 3, looked without warning like a Lions QB from the old days, completing a season-low 50 percent of his 30 passes while tossing an increasingly confounding five interceptions as his boys trailed by as much as 23-7 in the second half. Still, all was forgiven in the end, as some Texan mistakes, a refocused offense, and a couple of clutch kicks all combined to deliver Detroit an inspiring comeback—26-23, with a walk-off field goal for the win. 
Most of what you need to know about Detroit's offense is this: In their one loss this season, Week 2 vs. Tampa Bay, Goff threw the ball 55 times. In all other games leading into their primetime clash against Houston, he'd maxed out at 28. The two prongs that allow this offense to plug into a power source are running backs David Montgomery and Jahmyr Gibbs, and their punishing runs behind a fearsome offensive line are what open up opportunities for Goff to find his receivers on play-action pass plays. But the Texans' pressure in the early going both suffocated the run and forced Goff into uncharacteristic errors. On the game's opening drive, an energetic deflection by Jalen Pitre created a Jimmie Ward interception, and with the Lions down 13-7 in the second, Denico Autry got his hand on Goff while he threw and sparked a tip frenzy that eventually led to another Texans field goal. Detroit proceeded to go three-and-out on each of the next two drives, as Houston's aggression disrupted Goff's rhythm and refused to give him clear looks at his targets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Creed took us higher at T-Mobile Center]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=860551</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-creed-took-us-higher-at-t-mobile-center/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T13:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creed. // photo by Isabella Galvan Creed with 3 Doors Down and Mammoth WVH T-Mobile Center Wednesday, November 6 On Wednesday, it was a soaring evening of big ol’ rock ‘n’ roll vibes when Creed brought their Are You Ready? tour to T-Mobile Center with fellow brothers in big guitars 3 Doors Down and Mammoth WVH. Our photographer Isabella Galvan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isabella Galvan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Lost Dog Street Band brought raw authenticity to Liberty Hall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=860555</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-lost-dog-street-band-brought-raw-authenticity-to-liberty-hall/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T13:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lost Dog Street Band. // photo by Allison Scavo Lost Dog Street Band with Nolan Taylor Liberty Hall Friday, November 8 One of the original traveling street bands, these Lost Dogs have built a loyal following over the years who scream, cry, and laugh with them. Lost Dog Street Band is a dark country-folk band whose music cuts right to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Scavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Was Too Warm This Week]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172810</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/it-was-too-warm-this-week"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T20:24:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FLATBUSH, BROOKLYN – It was 74 degrees on Election Day; I wore bike shorts on the two block walk to my polling site. The iced coffee in my hand proved unwieldy as I scanned my ballot, the poll worker’s hands fluttering nervously nearby. By the time I completed my civic duty, I still had most of my coffee left, along with a mostly free afternoon. When I messaged my editor to get a vibe check for the day, she told me “For election coverage, I think nobody has a sense of what to write right now but then it will get either pretty easy or pretty hard.” It was as true then as it is now. 
But I had that strangely beautiful afternoon ahead of me. It was the kind of day that tricks everyone into believing they like summer in New York, except it was early November. My face and legs began to prick with heat as I settled onto a park bench and lit a joint. A pickup basketball game unfolded before me. A group of teens gossiped at a table nearby, shedding their black puffer jackets as the sun's warmth intensified. I remembered a wish I’d made earlier that year, that this fall would be the most beautiful I’d ever witnessed. I wondered if it was a curse. In a group chat with my best friends, one of them, a culture editor at the New Yorker, said, “I hate to say this and I want to be wrong but I kind of think he’s going to win.” My legs began to burn; I pulled a book out of my bag, my jacket over my knees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[College Football Is In A Golden Age Of Throwing Garbage]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172813</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/college-football-is-in-a-golden-age-of-throwing-garbage"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T19:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone in the stadium at Texas Tech's loss to Colorado on Saturday would have understood why Tech head coach Joey McGuire took it upon himself to seize a microphone and begin yelling at the home fans near the beginning of the fourth quarter. They would have seen what people watching at home did not, which was those fans throwing a bunch of garbage from the seats and onto the field while officials reviewed a Colorado sack that involved both a facemask penalty that was not called and a targeting infraction that first was, and then was overturned. While Dean Blandino explained to the TV audience what was happening, his traditional more-in-sorrow-than-in-anger tone was overtaken by something that sounded more like a Muppet that had been stuffed into a dryer against its will. That was McGuire, and he wanted everyone to knock it off.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mTAMqZDCh1Y]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Belief]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172704</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/beyond-belief"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T18:33:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the absence of any actual recourse or meaningful agency where the material terms of your existence are concerned, you are permitted to create a reality of your own. You can't fully live there because there's nowhere to cook or sleep, but you can decorate it however you like. This space is not and cannot really ever be home, and also it is not even really safe—there are always sketchy guys letting themselves in and going through your stuff, grabbing at your wallet, constantly issuing what are very clearly threats in the form of insulting advice. There is a screen you can watch, but it mostly just shows commercials in a little box surrounded by tickers and betting lines and blaring chyrons lousy with incomprehensible AI babble, things that are shaped like words but are not. When the news …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auburn Beat Each Other Up Before They Beat Houston]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172805</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/auburn-beat-each-other-up-before-they-beat-houston"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T17:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is early enough in the college basketball season that nothing really feels consequential yet. Most of the programs that will matter in March are still tuning up teams that won't, to the point where the scoreboard has kind of a pleasant abstraction to it. For every early match-up between North Carolina and Kansas—it really happened, on Friday night; Kansas won, it was a fun game—there are two that mostly serve to remind you what a vast and varied country this is. Kentucky and Bucknell? Arizona and Old Dominion? Auburn, but also Vermont? Provided you don't look at the scores in those games, which were decided by a combined margin of 137 points in favor of the programs you'd expect, it's kind of nice to think about. But it's conceptual, in the ways that basketball games played before Thanksgiving tend to be.
So much of the season hasn't happened yet that the broader stakes are not yet set, but it seems safe to say that Auburn's convincing 74-69 road win over Houston on Saturday night will matter. Houston, which came into the game ranked fourth in the country, is very good; Auburn, which was ranked 11th, won by getting second-half buckets with striking efficiency against one of the best defensive teams in the country. What was abstract and unrepresentative about Auburn's season-opening thrashing of Vermont—and they won that game 94-43, so that's basically everything—looked sharper and more significant on Saturday. The performance vaulted the Tigers to the top spot on the KenPom rankings, just ahead of Houston; the inherently unstable admixture of transfer portal ronin and multi-star recruits, which could always become anything, looked like a (very good) basketball team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday Notes: Dispatches From the GM Meetings in San Antonio]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=450554</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/sunday-notes-dispatches-from-the-gm-meetings-in-san-antonio/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T13:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus Will Pennyfeather, Roki Sasaki, a Classic Baseball Era Committee ballot poll, facts and stats galore, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Laurila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AL Central Notes: Royals Pitching, Rodriguez, Manning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=830315</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/al-central-notes-royals-pitching-rodriguez-manning.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T23:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Michael Wacha retained on a three-year deal worth at least $51MM, “we don’t expect to be in the market for a starter moving forward.  We’re going to focus on some other things,” Royals general manager J.J. Picollo told MLB.com’s Maria Guardado and other reporters during the GM Meetings.  Picollo cited the projected top five…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here are Kansas City's best restaurants for Southern comfort cooking and soul food]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2024-11-09/kansas-city-southern-food-restaurants-soul-cooking</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2024-11-09/kansas-city-southern-food-restaurants-soul-cooking"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smack in the middle of the country, Kansas City is a melting pot of different cultures and cuisines — especially soul food. At this restaurants, there's plenty to enjoy with the big flavor, and portions, of Southern comfort cooking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shannon Carpenter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>