<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-11-24T14:13:28.169Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump tells US Senate Republicans they ‘must kill’ journalism shield law]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862780</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/donald-trump-tells-us-senate-republicans-they-must-kill-journalism-shield-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T16:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President-elect Donald Trump ordered congressional Republicans on Wednesday to block a broadly popular bill to protect press freedoms, likely ending any chance of the U.S. Senate clearing the legislation. The measure would limit federal law enforcement surveillance of journalists and the government’s ability to force disclosure of journalists’ sources, codifying regulations the Department of Justice has put in place under President...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Fischler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reds, Royals Agree To Trade Involving Brady Singer, Jonathan India]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=831820</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/reds-royals-agree-to-trade-involving-brady-singer-jonathan-india.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T00:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals are acquiring second baseman Jonathan India and outfielder Joey Wiemer from the Reds for starter Brady Singer, the teams announced. Robert Murray of FanSided first reported (on X) that Wiemer was being traded to Kansas City. Ken Rosenthal and C. Trent Rosecrans of the Athletic reported last week that the teams were discussing an India-Singer framework.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[American League Non-Tenders: 11/22/24]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=831767</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/american-league-non-tenders-11-22-24.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T00:10:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The deadline to tender a contract to arbitration-eligible players is tonight at 7pm CT. Here’s a rundown of the players on American League teams that have been non-tendered today. This post will be updated as more decisions are revealed. MLBTR contributor Matt Swartz projected salaries for all players eligible for arbitration last month. All players who are…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Wards rewarded as state staple Hembree finally achieves rockstar dreams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861721</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-wards-rewarded-as-state-staple-hembree-finally-achieves-rockstar-dreams/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T22:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hembree // Photo by Nick Spacek Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Beard Award-nominated bar operator Jay Sanders dishes on the unique approach for his next bar in this Pitch Questionnaire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862238</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/james-beard-award-nominated-bar-operator-jay-sanders-dishes-on-the-unique-approach-for-his-next-bar-in-this-pitch-questionnaire/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T19:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jay Sanders and Shelley Shackelford behind the bar at Wild Child for Almost Monday // Photo by Sarah Sipple Jay Sanders is an undeniable force in Kansas City’s bar scene. Next on his vision board: affordability. As owner/operator of Shawnee’s Wild Child Libations and Drastic Measures, he has helped usher in a new era of notoriety for the suburb’s historic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rudy Gobert Found A New Guy To Annoy]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174229</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rudy-gobert-found-a-new-guy-to-annoy"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T18:26:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's fun to speculate about bad team chemistry. Sometimes the sideline body language is revealing enough. Sometimes you get an uncharacteristically detailed and cogent Shams Charania report, like the one the Sixers suffered last week. Sometimes you can figure it out in the circuitous sentences of beat reporters, who are too polite or compromised to say it outright. And sometimes it can be deduced from the mere presence of Rudy Gobert, a man so unpopular among his colleagues that ESPN tried to learn why at feature length. Even as the team around him has changed, Gobert is still Gobert, with charisma about as strong as his low-post repertoire.
This offseason's trade between the Knicks and Wolves was, in some ways, trading like for like. One offensively gifted, sporadically infuriating big man was swapped for another, Julius Randle to Minnesota and Karl-Anthony Towns to New York. All things considered, the Towns-Gobert pairing was a pretty successful experiment, schematically and interpersonally. But Randle is a bit more dour than the man he was replacing. Gobert-Randle had tremendous grump-on-grump potential, and we're starting to see it, eight wins and seven losses into a Wolves campaign against a very soft slate of opponents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sure, Go Ahead And Try To Fix The NBA All-Star Game]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174239</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/sure-go-ahead-and-try-to-fix-the-nba-all-star-game"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T18:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like Adam Silver is out there again, tinkering away and trying to fix that rusted out old heap in the driveway that hasn't run right in years and has a wasp hive nestled against the drivetrain after years of inactivity. In other words, he's messing around with the All-Star Game.
Credit to him for trying, anyway. Silver is nothing if not persistent, and at his pay grade as commissioner of your National Basketball Association, he'd damned well better be. He is already being given credit for the largely illusory benefits of the in-season tournament, which is mostly just a tribute to schedule manipulation (good games between good teams are always that, Emirates branding be damned), some gym floor murals by 12-year-olds with an unlimited supply of spray paint, and a trophy nobody has any particular attachment to. But Silver does understand that customers will buy anything they can be fooled into thinking is worth the attention span. The challenge, where the All-Star Game is concerned, is that no one is fooled.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Triumphant trek to top-tier tastes at Triune]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861562</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-triumphant-trek-to-top-tier-tastes-at-triune/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T17:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Triune // Photo by Zach Bauman Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deadlock Pro-Wrestling Is As Fun As It Is Fragile]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173921</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/deadlock-pro-wrestling-is-as-fun-as-it-is-fragile"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T16:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JERSEY CITY, N.J. — You're probably going to have a good time at the independent wrestling show.
Just a few small things need to go your way: It shouldn't be longer than three hours; the matches should have a decent pace to them; the venue should have air conditioning; and the largest, sweatiest, most obnoxious men should avoid standing directly in front of you. Nail all these parts, and I can almost guarantee you that something will click. Maybe the entrances will remind you of a drag show. Maybe the flips will take your breath away. Maybe you'll love trying to decipher the inner workings of the performance. Maybe you'll really like gawking at shirtless men from so close.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Clouds Have Gathered Over The World Chess Championship]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174216</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-clouds-have-gathered-over-the-world-chess-championship"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T15:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chess world championship title goes on the line once again starting this Monday, where the incumbent Ding Liren will face off against the challenger Gukesh D for the highest title in chess! Playing 14 head-to-head games in Singapore over two and a half weeks, Ding is looking to correct his post-title form slump, while Gukesh could become the 18th world chess champion at just 18 years of age.
The chess is back! Let’s go!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Tippett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: So you say (or don't) you want snow (FRI-11/22)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3737101</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-so-you-say-or-dont-you-want-snow-fri-11-22/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T15:23:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we set up for the winter forecast on Monday, blog on Tuesday about it...I thought I'd share with you some winter weather stats regarding snow. I did a presentation for emergency managers and NWS people back in October and I wanted to show you what I did. Just a bunch of interesting snow stats, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even A Little Khvicha Kvaratskhelia Goes A Long Way]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173818</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/even-a-little-khvicha-kvaratskhelia-goes-a-long-way"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T15:07:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As fans in America, it's important to remain grateful for the ease with which we can indulge a truly gluttonous appetite for elite soccer, our consumption unshackled from the regional restrictions, splintered broadcast rights, and timezone issues that make it much more difficult for everyone else to watch as much of the best teams and leagues as we can. That being said, I do regret the fact that it's recently become a lot harder to keep up with the international game stateside.
For a couple years now I've spent most midseason international breaks spotting tasty UEFA Nations League matchups and CONMEBOL World Cup Qualifiers on the schedule, only to learn that watching them would require expanding my already bloated streaming service subscriptions to divorce-threatening levels. I'm about as motivated a soccer fan as there is, and yet even I refuse to stump up for the Fubos and Vixes and Fox Soccer Pluses of the world, especially when you can't even rely on those services to air every match in the competitions they have the rights to. It's gotten to the point where I've now all but given up even thinking about catching non-tournament national team games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making spirits bright: Our exhaustingly festive list of holiday pop-up bars in Kansas City]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862594</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/making-spirits-bright-our-exhaustingly-festive-list-of-holiday-pop-up-bars-in-kansas-city/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T15:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miracle // Photo by Sarah Sipple We’re not sure how this list continues to grow each year. Nevertheless, Kansas Citians are clearly clamoring for the merriment, and we’re here for it. From Olathe to North KC, food and drink-focused festivities abound in the KC metro. Here, The Pitch has gathered the important details, done a vibe check, and included some...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steelers-Browns Was A Miserable And Majestic Classic Of Bad-Weather Football]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174162</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/steelers-browns-was-a-miserable-and-majestic-classic-of-bad-weather-football"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T14:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People who we hate—this is as opposed to people, comma, who we hate—like to criticize Al Michaels for not seeming properly effusive about some idiotic false start penalty in a nothing vs. nothing game, played on a Thursday night and aired on Jeff Bezos's principal home surveillance tool. This is all fair, although to be frank, Michaels has seen everything a thousand times during his long career; it would be not just weird but worrying if he was hooting and hollering over the ordinary nonsense like some unhinged post-Ritalin Kevin Harlan. It’s just the Jaguars on a weeknight, and also the man just turned 80.
But Thursday night's Steelers-Browns game, a blizzard that happened to feature yard lines and penalty flags, turned Michaels absolutely giddy. The ultimate broadcasting lifer became your 7-year-old on Christmas morning, full of wonder and delight and processed sugar, tucking into his gig as if every play was a hunk of prime rib with a double-baked tater the size of your spaniel's head and a Balvenie on the side, neat—all fed to him forkful by straining forkful by Jane Fonda circa Barbarella.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Fetch signs up to be KC’s unapologetic mouthpiece]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861596</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-fetch-signs-up-to-be-kcs-unapologetic-mouthpiece/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T14:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Fetch Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be publishing these...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gladiators, Ranked]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173890</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/gladiators-ranked"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T13:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In honor of today's release of the major motion picture and guaranteed box office smash Wicked, here is my non-exhaustive ranking of the types of gladiator.
I. Murmillones
The kings of the arena. Armed with a short sword, protected by a shield and a bracer on his sword arm, and decked out in an extravagant, often fish-themed helmet, there's a reason you think of the murmillo when you think of gladiators: They look fucking awesome. Because of the combined weight of the upper-body gear, murmillones were usually the tallest, strongest gladiators, and they were rock stars—some may even have done product endorsements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City has the meats: How the city's butcher shops prepare for Thanksgiving]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2024-11-22/kansas-city-has-the-meats-how-the-metros-top-butcher-shops-prepare-for-thanksgiving</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2024-11-22/kansas-city-has-the-meats-how-the-metros-top-butcher-shops-prepare-for-thanksgiving"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanksgiving is the busiest time of year for Kansas City butchers. If you're looking for the right meat to go on your table this holiday season, the city's locally-owned butcher shops can be your guide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kraske, Josh Marvine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Have Shown Interest In Juan Soto]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=831677</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/royals-have-shown-interest-in-juan-soto.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T04:56:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have reached out to Juan Soto this offseason, writes Jon Heyman of the New York Post. It doesn’t appear talks got far, as Heyman unsurprisingly adds that Soto’s asking price is out of Kansas City’s comfort zone. At the start of the offseason, Heyman reported that a pair of small-market teams were among…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Judge Wins AL MVP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=831646</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/aaron-judge-wins-al-mvp-2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T23:31:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Judge is the MVP once again. The Baseball Writers Association of America announced this evening that the Yankee captain was the unanimous choice for the American League’s top player this year. Bobby Witt Jr. of the Royals was the unanimous runner-up, getting all of the second-place votes. Judge’s teammate Juan Soto finished third in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Green Dirt Farm delivers gastro-revolutionary goat cheese]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861714</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-green-dirt-farm-delivers-gastro-revolutionary-goat-cheese/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T22:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smiling ewe at Green Dirt Farm // Photo courtesy Green Dirt Farm Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Motet delivered a tight, exploratory set at recordBar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862629</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/the-motet-delivered-a-tight-exploratory-set-at-recordbar/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T21:07:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Motet. // photo by Allison Scavo The Motet with ETHNO recordBar Tuesday, November 19 The Motet took the stage in a way only they could Tuesday—on their own terms and ahead of schedule. Surprisingly, they walked on stage one minute early, which set the tone that they wanted to be here, play, and that it wasn’t a job to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Allison Scavo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Will The ‘Wicked’ Press Campaign End?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174070</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/when-will-the-wicked-press-campaign-end"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T20:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since it was first announced in December 2012, the feature film adaptation of the wildly popular musical Wicked, itself an adaptation of the incredibly strange Gregory Maguire novel, has been beset by delays. First, there were eight years in development hell, easily enough to kill most films. Then there was a pandemic. Nearly a decade had passed since the initial announcement by the time Jon M. Chu took over as director in 2021, fresh off In The Heights and Crazy Rich Asians. By the end of the year, Cynthia Erivo and Ariana Grande were cast as the green and pink protagonists, respectively. In April 2022, Chu posted a note sent from his “OzPhone” on Twitter that read, in part, “As we prepared the production over the last year, it became impossible to wrestle the story of 'Wicked' into a single film without doing some real damage to it":
As we tried to cut songs or trim characters, those decisions began to feel like fatal compromises to the source material that has entertained us all for so many years. We decided to give ourselves a bigger canvas and make not just one 'Wicked' movie but two! With more space, we can tell the story of 'Wicked' as it was meant to be told while bringing even more depth and surprise to the journeys for these beloved characters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Nightmare in the Ozarks’ film fest turned Eureka Springs into a goth Mardi Gras]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861472</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/nightmare-in-the-ozarks-film-fest-turned-eureka-springs-into-a-goth-mardi-gras/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T20:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typically, film festival planners start preparing for their event at least a year out from opening. If you’re starting a festival from scratch and want it to be successful, you’ll probably want even more time to plan. You’re thinking about venues, bookings, sponsors, ticket sales, merch design, marketing…it’s a lot. It’s certainly not the kind of thing that comes together...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: Two juicy new canned KC bevs, Thanksgiving for one, and The Black Pantry party]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862573</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-two-juicy-new-canned-kc-bevs-thanksgiving-for-one-and-the-black-pantry-party/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T20:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Life in KC is pretty delicious. In fact, there is often so much going on that it can be hard to decide where to go and what to try. That’s where I come in.  I’ve curated this weekly list of events, openings, deals, and celebrations to keep you in-the-know. Cheers! Something New Mean Mule: The Crossroads...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The American Nightmare Is A Rerun]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174107</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-american-nightmare-is-a-rerun"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T19:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The week before the election, for two nights in a row, I dreamt about the moon. The dreams were in sequence: two parts of a single story that were braided together. A single day of my life became the intermission. Everyone thinks their dreams are interesting. We are self-involved creatures, infatuated with the shiny pictures our subconscious makes for us and presents like a movie in the mere seconds before our brains return to the living. But the week before the election, my subconscious gave me something special. 
In the dream, the moon was shrinking. I was staring up at the sky while it swirled around and around, becoming smaller and smaller, orbiting around nothing, counterclockwise in an oval like it was going around a race track. And just when it became too small to really see, it became larger and larger and larger and larger. It was coming toward us, falling, plummeting into the Earth's atmosphere. And then I woke up. The whole next day, I read about the moon. I researched what would happen if the moon fell (we would all die). I tried to understand how big the moon actually is (very big). Of course, it returned to my dreams the next night. In the sequel, the moon was lost. The moon had plummeted into the Pacific Ocean, and we could not find it. In the dream, I watched videos on my phone, desperate to try and understand what had happened here: videos from the ISS, of the news, or of crews searching the Pacific.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emergency Christmas Protocols And Underwater Hotels, With Sabrina Imbler]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174072</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/emergency-christmas-protocols-and-underwater-hotels-with-sabrina-imbler"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T19:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are certain hard and fast facts to deal with. Christmas simply is when and where it is; Christmas season surrounds it in some more subjective but necessarily limited ways. Christmas season may begin for some people after Halloween, and for others after Thanksgiving, but it ends before the new year begins for everyone and cannot just begin whenever a person needs or wants it to. Anyway, this is what I would have told you before we had Defector's own Sabrina Imbler on the podcast this week. Now I am not so sure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creature Feature: Meet the darling Draco who is looking for a forever home]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862595</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/creature-feature-meet-the-darling-draco-who-is-looking-for-a-forever-home/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T18:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Scott Poore Meet Draco, the current longest resident at the Olathe Animal Shelter, here for nearly 200 days. This three-year-old pitbull has a heart full of love to give, but he needs to be the only pet in his new home. Gentle with people of all ages and a huge fan of snacks, Drako is ready to find...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Poore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ridley Scott’s Gladiator II returns to a colosseum where spectacle decapitates substance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862606</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/ridley-scotts-gladiator-ii-returns-to-a-colosseum-where-spectacle-decaptiates-substance/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T18:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[copyright Paramount Pictures If nothing else, Gladiator II is a testament to the fact that if you put enough charmers and dang-ass freaks in your movie, and a historical epic-obsessed director like Ridley Scott behind the camera, you’re going to end up with something that’s at least fun.  The legacy-quel to Scott’s 2000 swords-and-sandals action drama Gladiator has a script...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Hockey’s new home begins to break through the ice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861584</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-hockeys-new-home-begins-to-break-through-the-ice/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T17:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Eli Ralls Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be publishing these...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Am The Passenger Now]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173989</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-am-the-passenger-now"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T16:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
There are childhood memories that linger in your soul for no discernible reason, and here is one of mine. I was six years old. I was living in Chicago, and playing on a Mites-level youth hockey team. I have no memory of whether or not I was a good hockey player. This was the level of youth sports where you’re essentially dressing up as an athlete without being one yet. You put on your equipment, you skate onto the ice, you do what the coach tells you until you don’t feel like doing it anymore, and then you dick around like the kid you are. A slightly more organized playdate. I remember my skates being super tight, I remember being taught how to loosely stick handle the puck, and I remember my pads smelling like a cadaver after I’d taken them off. The rest is a haze.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Premiere: Digester’s Grandmother is a doom-laden rage against the dying of the light]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862420</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/premiere-digesters-grandmother-is-a-doom-laden-rage-against-the-dying-of-the-light/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T16:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digester. // photo courtesy the artist Lawrence “prairie sludge” band Digester has been playing for over a decade now, but aside from a single, “The Old Order,” in December of last year, the band’s last release was their self-titled release over eight years ago. Thankfully, that all changes when Digester releases Grandmother, their new full-length this Friday, November 22, with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Colder air to finish the month (THU-11/21)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3735711</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-colder-air-to-finish-the-month-thu-11-21/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T15:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reminder that the winter forecast is coming on Monday the 25th. We may have some snow chances next week in the forecast as well as we head into early December depending on how things play out with another intrusion of cold air sliding down through the upper Midwest into the Plains. Right now the [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best And The Worst Of Christian Pulisic]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173960</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-best-and-the-worst-of-christian-pulisic"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T14:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At every stage of his career, Christian Pulisic has always relished playing for the USMNT. When he was a boy wonder at Borussia Dortmund, it was by scoring a ton of goals in the U.S.'s failed efforts to qualify for the 2018 World Cup that he introduced himself to the country and legitimized himself as more than just the next Julian Green. When he was alternating between sitting on the Chelsea bench due to injuries and sitting on the Chelsea bench because he'd slipped down the pecking order, getting to come and bang in CONCACAF was a way to rebuild his confidence. And now that he's in the form of his life for AC Milan, rounding into his prime by playing a huge role for a team competing for domestic and continental honors, his play with the USMNT feels equally expansive and ambitious. This is the best Christian Pulisic we've ever seen, a prospect that is equal parts encouraging and annoying.
The headlining event came in Monday night's huge win against Jamaica—where Captain America grabbed two goals in a thrilling 4-2 victory—though Pulisic built the foundation for that big performance by killing it for Milan all season. With Rafael Leão holding down Pulisic's preferred left wing position, the American has split his time in Italy this season between setting things up as a central attacking midfielder and ripping down the right wing. And rip he has: Pulisic leads Milan in Serie A goals and assists, and he's scored against Liverpool and gotten an assist against Real Madrid in the Champion's League. Milan has been slightly off the pace in Serie A this year, mostly because their backline has been somewhat wobbly and the new coach wasn't getting along with Leão, the club's best player. Throughout it all, though, Pulisic has been flying.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rafael Nadal Found Process In Pain]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173888</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/rafael-nadal-found-process-in-pain"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T14:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nadal was the destroyer of context, the man who played every point in vacuum, through comebacks and blowouts with the same equanimous mind and full effort.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: ADHDIY Craft Cafe democratizes the hobby hubbub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861574</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-adhdiy-craft-cafe-democratizes-the-hobby-hubbub/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T14:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASHDIY Craft Cafe supply shelf // Photo by Sarah Sipple Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tarik Skubal Wins American League Cy Young Award]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=831554</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/tarik-skubal-wins-american-league-cy-young-award.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T00:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tarik Skubal has his first Cy Young award. The Baseball Writers Association of America announced that the Tigers ace won the AL Cy Young by a unanimous margin. He received all 30 first-place votes. Kansas City’s Seth Lugo placed runner-up, while Cleveland closer Emmanuel Clase rounded out the top three. Whether Skubal would win the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Missouri Princess Chappell Roan’s rise and fall (and rise)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861707</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-missouri-princess-chappell-roans-rise-and-fall-and-rise/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T22:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chappell Roan // Photo by Zoe Strohm Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Someone Please Write Normally About This Fascinating Woman?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173964</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/can-someone-please-write-normally-about-this-fascinating-woman"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T20:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Augusta Britt has had, by any reasonable accounting, an extraordinarily rich and interesting life, and seems like a vivid and fascinating person. By her mid-teens in the mid-1970s, she was a pistol-packing Arizona refugee from her own abusive family and any number of atrocious foster homes. She met the novelist Cormac McCarthy by a motel pool in 1976 when she was 16 (and he 42) and became, for the next few years, his secret lover as well as, for the next four decades, the pretty direct inspiration for many of his stories and characters.
When she was 17—and McCarthy, Britt would find out later, was still married to Annie DeLisle—the two ran off to Mexico believing (or fantasizing) that the FBI was after McCarthy on statutory rape and human trafficking charges; they returned to the U.S. shortly after her 18th birthday. In 1981, when she would have been 21 or thereabouts, she left McCarthy in Tennessee and returned to Arizona. They saw each other many times over the following decades and kept up a deep correspondence for the rest of his life, but never lived together again; he asked her to marry him two separate times but backed out of both proposals. Britt has spent time as a patient in a mental hospital; she has worked as a trauma nurse; she is richly thoughtful about her unique life; now, at 64, she still trains horses and shoots guns, and evidently taught McCarthy much of what he learned about both hobbies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Albert Burneko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Helping hands craft a new kind of hero at Happy Bottoms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861696</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-helping-hands-craft-a-new-kind-of-hero-at-happy-bottoms/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HappyBottoms volunteers hand out diapers at a mass distribution site. // Photo Curtesy of Happy Bottoms Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For The Sake Of The Jets, Woody Johnson Must Take Another Overseas Diplomatic Post]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173998</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/for-the-sake-of-the-jets-woody-johnson-must-take-another-overseas-diplomatic-post"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T19:37:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Due to reporting from The Athletic's resident football pot-stirrer Dianna Russini and co-conspirator Zack Rosenblatt, we now realize that Aaron Rodgers is only partly to blame for the New York Jets being the latest iteration of the New York Jets—and yes, everyone knows what that means. Their recent reporting reveals that superannuated yet still overmatched owner Woody Johnson has also stamped his footprint right in the middle of the mudslide which led yesterday to the firing of general manager Joe Douglas, only six weeks after he fired head coach Robert Saleh. What was already a typically Jetsy situation has only continued to get more Jetsy.
Now, the report could just be an act of reputational sanitation on Rodgers’ behalf, although that scale of clean-up job would require more than a double byline, plus we have no evidence that either author is particularly keen on Rodgers one way or another. According to Rosenblatt and Russini (we're switching billboard credits because we don't know who did more heavy lifting on this), Woody broached the subject of benching Rodgers for backup quarterback Tyrod Taylor earlier this season, only to be talked off that particular comedic ledge by everyone else in the room. You may now talk among yourselves on the subject of whether Johnson might not be a genius, or just someone who has watched Rodgers closely this year. But frankly, everyone is ignoring the central fact, which is that no matter what the cast of characters shows, the Jets were the Jets and are the Jets, and because of Items 1 and 2, they shall always be the Jets. A benching or a firing or another firing or some future firing will not and cannot change that. The only thing for Jets employees to do at this point is to become ex-employees as quickly as possible. I mean, who on that payroll has got it better than Smilin' Bobby Saleh right now?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make It A Ham Bag This Holiday Season]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173968</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/make-it-a-ham-bag-this-holiday-season"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T18:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In theory, you can’t step into the same river twice. Ideally you do a lot of growing and changing when you flounce off to college. That is especially true when you cross an ocean to go off to school. But sooner or later, the siren song of home becomes harder and harder to ignore. This is not without a number of risks: your parents, your old friends and confronting your old self. 
But when you run into your hometown crush and they look sexier than ever, all the usual psychochemical accouterments of said crush—paralysis, bewitchment, intoxication—sure make a strong case that you are awash in the same old waters after all. Good luck.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MJ Unpacked St. Louis stages glamorous cannabis expo for hashing out Missouri’s future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862466</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/mj-unpacked-st-louis-stages-glamorous-cannabis-expo-for-hashing-out-missouris-future/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T18:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Jennifer Korman Photography From Tuesday, Nov. 5 to Thursday, Nov. 7, St. Louis’ Union Station transformed into a glossy, gaudy gallery of cannabis ornamentation, chocked-full of big wigs within the industry as MJ Unpacked—an exclusive conference for experts within the cannabis industry to network, collaborate, and ultimately spread cannabis knowledge and awareness—was underway. The three-day event consisted of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Ellett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mortality Always Wins By Knockout]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173688</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mortality-always-wins-by-knockout"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T17:33:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People hate Jake Paul. He is the walking personification of a Reddit board: a cocky, belligerent white boy who loves to troll as much as he loves to use mental health issues as marketing. His transition from YouTube provocateur to "serious" "boxer" has been built on the calculated decision to fight washed-up black athletes. It’s smart; boxing has always thrived when catering to the public imagination around race war. The desire to see Paul get knocked out by one of the faded avatars of black masculinity he sets himself against explains much of the draw of his fights. His savvy protection of that appeal explains why he only fights people he can comfortably beat with his young legs and just-about-competent skills.
When it was first announced that Paul planned to fight a 58-year-old Mike Tyson, the initial response was one of widespread incredulousness. Over time, people seemed to convince themselves that somehow a geriatric Tyson could be the one to finally put Jake Paul “in his place,” whatever that might mean. It always made sense why Paul would want to fight an old Mike Tyson. But what exactly was in it for Tyson? Money, surely, but that can’t be the only reason. This is a man in his late 50s, who’d been mostly retired since the early 2000s. The people who got suckered into caring about this fight didn't want to see that reality, transposing instead an image of the Mike Tyson of yore, maybe older and slower in some vague way, but still in possession of the exhilarating, terrifying power and violence that made him a legend. On some level, maybe Tyson wanted to see that too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘YeeHaw!’ benefit from KC Tenants Union finds joy within the work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862460</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/yeehaw-benefit-from-kc-tenants-union-finds-joy-within-the-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T17:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now in its third year, YeeHaw!, a variety show benefiting the KC Tenants Union, has grown by leaps and bounds. Its first year took place at the Ship, last year was at the Truman, and this year moves to the Midland. The lineup is rather stellar for the Saturday, November 23, event as well, with comedian Beth Stelling (fresh off...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sarah Brightman brings A Christmas Symphony to the Midland on November 30]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862486</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/sarah-brightman-brings-a-christmas-symphony-to-the-midland-on-november-30/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T17:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sarah Brightman. // photo courtesy the artist With the holidays fast approaching, Sarah Brightman brings her now annual A Christmas Symphony to Kansas City at the Midland Theater on Saturday, November 30. Brightman will be joined by an orchestra and choir for the seasonal event that will take her to several cities across the U.S. as well as Mexico. During...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Botelho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Saber-Toothed Kitten Mummy Is So Stinking Cute That I’m Gonna Cry!]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173847</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-saber-toothed-kitten-mummy-is-so-stinking-cute-that-im-gonna-cry"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T17:10:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ice patches surrounding the Indigirka River and its tributaries in northeastern Russia serve as a graveyard for the Ice Age: mammoths, woolly rhinoceros, saiga, and bison that lived and died in the Last Glacial Period. Mammoth tusk collectors trawl the ice for tusks and other bones poking out from the melting permafrost, but occasionally they stumble on bodies that have been frozen for tens of thousands of years. In 2017 and 2018, tusk collectors found two mummified cave lion cubs, a species that has been extinct for thousands of years and likely resembled modern lions. In 2020, a tusk collector unearthed another, even rarer ancient kitten: a frozen saber-toothed cat cub, as Asher Elbein reported in The New York Times.
Despite their presence in our prehistorical imaginings—such as a starring role in the Ice Age franchise—the actual soft-tissue appearance of saber-toothed cats remained a mystery to scientists. So this new cub offers the first-ever glimpse at how the cats appeared in real life, about 35,000 to 37,000 years ago. The term saber-toothed cat refers to a plethora of cat-like species with elongated teeth, and the most famous—and perhaps most extravagantly toothed—belonged to the genus Smilodon. Scientists identified the new cub as Homotherium latidens, a species in another genus that contained the "scimitar-toothed cats," as these cats had curved canines that were smaller than Smilodon's. The researchers' paper describing the new kitten was recently published in Scientific Reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Voters overwhelmingly reject naked cashgrab for downtown stadium]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861567</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-voters-overwhelmingly-reject-naked-cashgrab-for-downtown-stadium/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T17:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illustration by Bob Unell Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be publishing these...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off Gets Stuck In The 1970s]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173749</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-not-so-great-defector-bake-off-gets-stuck-in-the-1970s"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T16:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off, where Kelsey and Chris attempt to complete the technical challenges from the newest season of The Great British Bake Off in their own home kitchens, with the same time parameters as the professional-grade bakers competing on the show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLBTR Podcast: The Rays’ Stadium Plans, Diamond Sports, And Some Offseason Rumors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=831441</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/mlbtr-podcast-the-rays-stadium-plans-diamond-sports-and-some-offseason-rumors.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T15:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest episode of the MLB Trade Rumors Podcast is now live on Spotify, Apple Podcasts, and wherever you get your podcasts! Make sure you subscribe as well! You can also use the player at this link to listen, if you don’t use Spotify or Apple for podcasts. This week, host Darragh McDonald is joined by Anthony Franco of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: The La Nina that isn't (so far) (WED-11/20)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3734283</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-the-la-nina-that-isnt-so-far-wed-11-20/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T15:28:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Winter Weather Forecast is coming up this coming MONDAY the 25th on FOX 4. We'll reveal all our individual thoughts during the course of the day and evening then I'll have the team average for you and that will be our official forecast for this coming winter. It's really just an exercise in some [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Not Accept An Unscientific American]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173619</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/do-not-accept-an-unscientific-american"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T14:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laura Helmuth was named editor-in-chief of Scientific American in March 2020, shortly before the magazine was set to celebrate its 175th year in print. Helmuth, who had previously directed health and science coverage at The Washington Post, told Poynter it was her dream job: "I love this magazine. It’s been around forever ... and I want to make it even more influential.”
Last week, after four-and-a-half years at the helm of the oldest continuously published magazine in the United States, Helmuth resigned. She made this decision shortly after a series of posts on Bluesky in which she called Trump voters "fucking fascists." Helmuth later deleted the posts, but screenshots wound their way to Twitter, where Elon Musk weighed in, leading to a wave of online harassment. It's unclear what exactly prompted Helmuth's resignation, but it's hard not to connect the dots. Helmuth did not respond to a request for comment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Family dinner at Pho Tuoi and a sense of belonging at Gaels Public House & Sports]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862361</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-family-dinner-at-pho-tuoi-and-a-sense-of-belonging-at-gaels-public-house-sports/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T14:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pho Tuoi // Photo By Tiffany Watts Pho Tuoi  Every once in a while, cooking at home can just feel like too much. So, my family and I decided to ditch our kitchen at home and get some comfort food at Pho Tuoi, where they’re not just serving soup, they’re serving a slice of Vietnamese tradition. With recipes passed down...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shovel fighting stand-up comic Matt Braunger brings his big dumb animal vibes to KC this week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862385</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/shovel-fighting-stand-up-comic-matt-braunger-brings-his-big-dumb-animal-vibes-to-kc-run-of-shows/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T07:17:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Provided by Matt Braunger This weekend, stand-up comic Matt Braunger will be returning to Kansas City to perform five live shows in three nights at the Comedy Club of Kansas City from Nov. 21 to Nov. 23.  Braunger’s comedy career kicked off 20 years ago in Portland, Oregon, though he spent a majority of his early career as an actor....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>