<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-11-27T16:20:42.840Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creature Feature: Meet Apollo, an incredibly persistent pup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863616</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/creature-feature-meet-apollo-an-incredibly-persistent-pup/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Krystle-Lee You may remember Apollo—a senior pup who was adopted from Great Plains SPCA six years ago. The team at Great Plains removed a benign mass from his hind leg and reunited him with his owner. In late October, Apollo was rushed back to our shelter in the midst of a medical emergency—an infection in his front leg,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Poore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLBTR Podcast: Yusei Kikuchi, The Aggressive Angels, And The Singer/India Trade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=832223</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/mlbtr-podcast-yusei-kikuchi-the-aggressive-angels-and-the-singer-india-trade.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T15:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest episode of the MLB Trade Rumors Podcast is now live on Spotify, Apple Podcasts, and wherever you get your podcasts! Make sure you subscribe as well! You can also use the player at this link to listen, if you don’t use Spotify or Apple for podcasts. This week, host Darragh McDonald is joined by Tim Dierkes of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off Must Alas Die, Die For Pâtisserie Week]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174465</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-not-so-great-defector-bake-off-must-alas-die-die-for-patisserie-week"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T15:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off, where Kelsey and Chris attempt to complete the technical challenges from the newest season of The Great British Bake Off in their own home kitchens, with the same time parameters as the professional-grade bakers competing on the show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Watching for snow on Saturday (WED-11/27)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3741713</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-watching-for-snow-on-saturday-wed-11-27/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T15:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With this colder pattern, two disturbances will be moving towards the region. One rainmaker and one snowmaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Is Everyone’s Problem, Even In Germany]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174545</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/donald-trump-is-everyones-problem-even-in-germany"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T15:19:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BERLIN — When Germans woke up on the morning of Nov. 6th, it felt like déjà vu: Once again the country had been on the edge of its seat following the U.S. presidential elections, with a qualified left-leaning female candidate losing to an erstwhile reality star turned right-wing political icon. And once again, there was the question: What now?
Germany's relationship with the U.S. is based on decades of economic ties, shared democratic values, and strategic cooperation on multilateral issues, particularly global security concerns. While a certain anti-Americanism has always persisted in Germany, especially since the U.S. invasion of Iraq in 2003, and German public opinion on the United States fluctuates significantly with whoever is president at the time, the majority of Germans consider the U.S. to be a key partner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luisa Rollenhagen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Your Questions Will Be Answered In This 2024-25 PWHL Season Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173228</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/all-your-questions-will-be-answered-in-this-2024-25-pwhl-season-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T14:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was no big Defector-style Professional Women’s Hockey League season preview last year, because I was (shameless plug) a little busy reporting this feature on the league’s formation. But it’s also tough to preview an inaugural season. Ideally the preview writer is offering special wisdom, honed over many years, manifested in cute and knowing references. How could I do that with a brand-new league? It would have been the blind previewing for the blind—an insult, frankly, to your intelligence. Only now, after one whole year of PWHL fandom, do I feel comfortable sharing a preview with you, valued reader. Let’s see what the league’s second season might have in store. The games start Saturday.
The six teams are listed below in draft order, each entry highlighting a cool veteran and a rookie. If you’re new to watching the PWHL, welcome! At the very end of this preview, there’s an FAQ section with some extra notes, tips, and reminders of the rules. As noted in that FAQ section, the PWHL point system distinguishes between wins in regulation and overtime or shootout wins, so each team’s record is formatted in the following order: regulation win-overtime win-overtime loss-regulation loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Soulful flavors at Lutfi’s Fried Fish and happy hour at Beer Kitchen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863575</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-soulful-flavors-at-lutfis-fried-fish-and-happy-hour-at-beer-kitchen/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T14:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lutfi’s // Photo By Tiffany Watts Lutfi’s When the craving for fried fish hits, there’s only one logical move: follow the scent of golden batter to the best spot in town. This time, my taste buds led me to Lutfi’s Fried Fish in the Northland—a local treasure that Kansas City swears by. With their reputation for crispy comfort food that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disney’s Moana 2 stitches fragments of a cancelled TV show into a lackluster unit-of-entertainment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863558</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/disneys-moana-2-stitches-fragments-of-a-cancelled-tv-show-into-a-lackluster-unit-of-entertainment/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T23:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Disney Let’s start here: Moana 2 was initially meant to be a Disney+ series. This is helpful context to have in mind as you watch the sequel to the 2016 original, if only to temper your expectations. The follow up to Moana has nowhere near the same musical, dramatic and thematic richness of its predecessor, but it’s fine as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Royals throwback to 2015]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861763</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-royals-throwback-to-2015/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T22:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City Royals versus Arizona Diamondbacks on July 22, 2024 // Photo by Tarik Sykes Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Inaugural Black Feast Week rallies for Willa’s Books & Vinyl and launches new tradition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861604</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-inaugural-black-feast-week-rallies-for-willas-books-vinyl-and-launches-new-tradition/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T21:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Kansas City Defender Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Akins PC Repair’s Cody Akins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862184</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-akins-pc-repairs-cody-akins/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T20:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Cody Akins Just when IT guru Cody Akins thinks he’s seen it all, along comes an even more insane computer issue to deal with. From cyber-hacking to waterlogged servers, Akins says no two days are even remotely similar at Akins PC Repair. “For some reason, computers have always come naturally to me,” he says. “When it comes to troubleshooting, very rarely is it ever...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Kendrick’s Party, You Can Cry If You Want To]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174436</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-kendricks-party-you-can-cry-if-you-want-to"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T19:48:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe this is my fault. For years, I've been begging Kendrick Lamar to lighten up a little. To stop with the hip-hop savior complex and the often incoherent political grandstanding. To stop treating music like a college level African-American history course and just enjoy himself. Well, that more or less arrived in 2024: the year of Kendrick Lamar. We've seen him battle and ultimately defeat Drake, put on for the West Coast, and work his way into being this season's Super Bowl halftime performer. To commemorate all this success, he has released a new album, GNX, in a surprise drop over the weekend that appropriately sent the internet into hysterics.
In a bit of irony that I'm sure is not lost on Kendrick, GNX is a party record full of earworms and radio-friendly pop records that, on the surface, more closely resembles something Drake would release than the sweeping artistic statements Kendrick has become known for. It is a victory lap in album form, ostensibly a showcase of Kendrick relaxing and having a good time. But there is something a little too empty about it for comfort. To paraphrase his words in "TV Off," there's a few solid jams on this record but it's not enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scandal-Ridden High School Football Powerhouse Removed From Virginia Playoffs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174574</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/scandal-ridden-high-school-football-powerhouse-removed-from-virginia-playoffs"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T18:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hayfield High's season from hell is done. The Alexandria, Va., school's leaders tried adopting the winningest football program in the state from a school in another county and damn near got away with it. But Hayfield's messy 2024 campaign ended last night, just one day after intrepid local reporters published text messages from the school's athletic director indicating that Hayfield administrators had considered using "homeless" designations for out-of-district players in order to get around athletic eligibility rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Reads A Book Is Leaping Toward The Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174593</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-reads-a-book-is-leaping-towards-the-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T18:21:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As longtime readers of this website would tell you, wildfires hold a certain morbid fascination for the Defector staff. As observers of the ice caps and fans of "going outside" would tell you, the medium and long-term future will both be infernal ones. The more I learn about the theory and practice of wildfire combat, forest management, and the history of megafires, the more fascinated I become. A phenomenon that seems inexorable and fundamentally uncontainable emerges, through the smoke, as a far more subjective problem. This month's DRAB selection is a famed nonfiction look at one of the most infamous wildfire disasters in United States history.
Norman Maclean published Young Men and Fire in 1992, 43 years after the Mann Gulch fire killed 13 wildland firefighters. From what I gather, the book begins with the disaster and radiates outward from it in pulses, getting into deeper philosophical territory yet holding true to the hub at its center. The New York Times review both refers to Maclean as a great artist and contains the phrase "cornball pastoral," which makes the book seem like turf worth mining. It is raining all along the West Coast as I write this and somehow we have avoided a catastrophic fire season for the third year running, which would seem to make a book about a summer occurrence an odd choice for an early winter DRAB selection. Great news there, though: The book also seems to be about the phenomenology of death. "There's a lot of tragedy in the universe that has missing parts and comes to no conclusion, including probably the tragedy that awaits you and me," Maclean, who would die two years before the publication of Young Men and Fire, writes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matheus Cunha Is A Wolf In Wolves Clothing]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174286</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/matheus-cunha-is-a-wolf-in-wolves-clothing"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T17:40:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wolverhampton Wanderers are a soccer club in sort of the same way that Silvio Dante's Bada Bing was an adult entertainment concern; technically it is indeed part of that industry, but the real business all takes place in the offices in the back.
In Wolves' case, superagent Jorge Mendes is to the club what Tony Soprano was to the Bada Bing. Since Chinese investment group Fosun International bought the club in 2016, the Old Gold has seemed to operate principally as a clearing house for Gestifute, Mendes's talent agency. This hasn't been the worst fate in the world. After spending about a decade and a half bobbing up and down England's top three divisions, with only brief spells in the promised land, the Mendes-puppeted Wolves quickly returned to the Premier League and have established themselves as midtable stalwarts for going on seven seasons now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JAWS and the 2025 Hall of Fame Ballot: Carlos Beltrán]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=451626</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/jaws-and-the-2025-hall-of-fame-ballot-carlos-beltran/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T17:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The center fielder with the great power-speed combination has Hall of Fame numbers, but his legacy is clouded by his role in the Astros’ sign-stealing saga.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Jaffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[City Market Coffee takes on turnover with upcoming Murmuration Eatery and Cocktail Bar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861323</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/city-market-coffee-takes-on-turnover-with-upcoming-murmuration-eatery-and-cocktail-bar/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T17:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Murmuration Eatery & Cocktail Bar signage at City Market // Photo courtesy of Nikole Ammer The marbled teal and salmon floor of the upcoming Murmuration Eatery & Cocktail Bar in City Market emerged completely by accident.  Owner Nikole Ammer found the pattern beneath layers and layers of paint left by previous tenants. Realizing it fit the new concept’s copper patina...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dayten Rose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Easy Sweet Potato Brûlée Recipe For You, The Brûlée Lover]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174431</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-easy-sweet-potato-brulee-recipe-for-you-the-brulee-lover"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T16:52:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about flossing at your desk, Aaron Rodgers, college football QBs, and more.
Happy Thanksgiving, everyone! Before we get to all the fun stuff, I have a quick recipe if you need ideas for sides on Thursday. For medical reasons, my wife is on a low-histamine, zero-gluten diet (if you ever wanna lose weight, try being allergic to 70 percent of the nation’s food supply), which means that she eats a lot of sweet potatoes. This means that the rest of us in the family eat a lot of sweet potatoes, too. To liven up the proceedings one night, I decided to mash them up and bake them, with some (OK, a lot of) brown sugar sprinkled on top.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Be Sure You Are Reading Some Dumb Bullshit]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174368</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-to-be-sure-you-are-reading-some-dumb-bullshit"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T15:16:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever found yourself reading an article, and needing to stop halfway through in order to ask yourself an important question: "Wait a minute, am I reading some dumb bullshit?" The question is not always easy to answer. If the author of the piece is a particularly gifted stylist, or adept at persuasive writing, you might find yourself needing to spend some time unpacking their arguments and deconstructing their sentences before you can figure out if you are indeed reading some dumb bullshit. Other times, the question is very easy to answer.
Here's a tip that will allow you to immediately suss out dumb bullshit whenever and wherever you encounter it: If the phrase "to be sure" appears at the beginning of a sentence anywhere in the text, then it is likely that you have encountered some of the dumbest bullshit ever written.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: The 2024-25 Winter Forecast]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3740452</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-the-2024-25-winter-forecast/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T15:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOX4 Weather team Joe Lauria, Karli Ritter, Michelle Bogowith, Alex Countee, Jacob Lanier share snow predictions for upcoming winter season]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Watches A Christmas Movie: ‘Christmas in the Spotlight’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174234</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-watches-a-christmas-movie-christmas-in-the-spotlight"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T14:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the time of year when the best, biggest, and most ambitious movies come out. Not Oscar season, but rather that stretch when the halls of streaming services are decked with the brightly lit, thinly disguised advertisements that are the year's new Christmas movies. There are more than 100 new Christmas films to watch this holiday season, and whether that number horrifies or excites you depends upon how much of a freak you are for the festive. Sabrina is proud to say they are a real Christmas freak, and this year they asked some of their colleagues to watch some of the most, uh, available new holiday movies. The second movie in our lineup is Christmas in the Spotlight, Lifetime's adaptation of Taylor Swift and Travis Kelce's real-life romance.
Sabrina Imbler: Thank you so much for joining me in watching what might be the celebrity singer-celebrity athlete Christmas rom-com movie of the season. I came into this movie knowing a lot about Christmas, but relatively little about the real-life stars that inspired this movie. I would love to know how each of you started this journey. What are your relationships to Travis and Taylor and their love connection?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Ryan Reynolds flick IF features Simple Mischief Studio’s savoir-faire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861748</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-ryan-reynolds-flick-if-features-simple-mischief-studios-savoir-faire/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T14:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Justin J Wee Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be publishing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri judge upholds state ban on transgender health care for minors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863481</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missouri-judge-upholds-state-ban-on-transgender-health-care-for-minors/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T23:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Craig Carter, a Wright County judge serving in Cole County for Missouri’s gender-affirming care trial, listens to testimony. “There were so many binders of evidence that were piled so high on the bench that the court’s vision was at times obscured,” he noted in his ruling Monday (Annelise Hanshaw/Missouri Independent) Missouri’s restrictions on puberty blockers and hormone treatment for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Spoerre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Yeehaw!’ variety show raises $36k for the ongoing work of Kansas City Tenants Union]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862823</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/yeehaw-variety-show-raises-36k-for-the-ongoing-work-of-kansas-city-tenants-union/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T22:34:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saturday night at the Midland, Yeehaw!: A Benefit for Kansas City, raised over 36k for The Kansas City Tenants Union. The benefit show brought in 17,000 people for a night of comedy, music and support for their community. Each performer donated their time, and all proceeds from the event go directly to KC Tenants. Missouri native Caleb Hearon returned to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zoe Strohm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Chiefs on pace for the triple crown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861736</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-chiefs-on-pace-for-the-triple-crown/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T22:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A red-clad crowd packs Arrowhead Stadium to watch the Kansas City Chiefs play. // Photo by Eric Thomas/Kansas Reflector Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NWSL Commissioner Jessica Berman Keeps Talking Around The San Diego Wave Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174444</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nwsl-commissioner-jessica-berman-keeps-talking-around-the-san-diego-wave-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T21:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NWSL Championship could not have worked out better for the league. The best team in the league, the Orlando Pride, beat the Washington Spirit, 1-0, in front of a sell-out crowd. Marta, the best women’s player in history, won her first NWSL title while her mother was in attendance for the first time. Rookie sensation and MVP candidate Barbra Banda scored the game’s decisive goal. It was a good day for the NWSL, and women’s soccer, but it did not remove the season’s blemishes. None are bigger than the pending lawsuit against the San Diego Wave and the league itself, which alleges multiple forms of discrimination and negligence.
On July 3, a former Wave employee named Brittany Alvarado went public with a statement on Twitter. She accused team president Jill Ellis and the Wave of fostering an abusive environment, and the NWSL of improperly addressing the abusive leadership under Ellis. The Wave went on the attack, denying wrongdoing and threatening legal action. A week later, Ellis made good on the threat, and sued Alvarado for defamation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lesley Ryder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything Is Working For Saquon Barkley]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174314</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/everything-is-working-for-saquon-barkley"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T20:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For everything astonishing about the average Saquon Barkley touchdown run, the most uncanny is how natural it all looks. It is not, of course; on the merits, and even by the absurd standards for this kind of thing that apply in the NFL and basically nowhere else on earth, it just does not really compute to see someone Barkley's size moving through space with the speed and precision with which he does those things. But if the particulars don't really make sense on their own, the little narrative of Barkley's long runs is entirely coherent, just in the sense that they just sort of seem like what would happen when you hand a football to someone who can do all that stuff. They are dazzling to the point of being implausible, but they make sense.
There is a lot of meaningful context on both sides of the ball on all of these runs, and some broader and less meaningful historical context trailing Barkley into the huddle on every play. The Los Angeles Rams talked about bad gap discipline on the 70- and 72-yard rushing touchdowns that Barkley had against them in the second half of Philadelphia's 37-20 win on Sunday night, and Coach Sean McVay was forced out into the more literary extremes of coaching syntax—crediting Barkley with "erasing angles" and the like—in giving credit where it was due. But even bearing in mind that none of it is as simple as it looks, it is astonishing how simple this looks:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Shutterbug Tarik Sykes brought sports photography to life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861731</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-shutterbug-tarik-sykes-brought-sports-photography-to-life/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T20:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Tarik Sykes Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be publishing these...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secret Lives Of Squirting Cucumbers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174312</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-secret-lives-of-squirting-cucumbers"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The squirting cucumber Ecballium—not to be confused with the exploding cucumber Cyclanthera—is not a showy plant. It meanders on a vine on the ground, sprouting craggly green leaves and demure yellow flowers. Neither are Ecballium's fruits memorable to look at; the pale, bristly green pods are around the size of erasers and dangle glumly off their stems. But once ripe, the fruits will burst at a single touch, jettisoning a gloppy stream of seeds that can reach speeds of nearly 45 miles per hour and land 30 feet away from the plant. Today, a new paper in Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences explains the mechanisms behind the squirting cucumber's fine-tuned ballistics.
The seeds of the paper were sown in the summer of 2022, when Chris Thorogood, the head of science at the Oxford Botanic Garden and an author on the paper, brought three mathematicians and one physicist to an unassuming patch of cucumbers. "Cucumbers aren’t normally very interesting," Derek Moulton, an applied mathematician at the University of Oxford and an author on the paper, wrote in an email. When Thorogood bent down to squeeze a fruit, "you could hear a tiny little squirt," Moulton said. But no one actually saw anything, leading Moulton to assume the squeezed cucumber was a dud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Can He Slap?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174340</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-can-he-slap"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T19:26:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Due to a feat of collective willpower this website is not a 24/7 Nikola Jokic propaganda outlet. The Denver Nuggets center is averaging 30 points, 14 rebounds, and 11 assists on 67 percent true shooting; he's on track for his fourth MVP in five seasons; he performs so many spectacular feats on a nightly basis that he's raised the standard for his own newsworthiness. It may then seem strange that we've opted to show you, of all things, a Jokic missed field goal attempt from Saturday night's 127-102 win over the Lakers. However!
With just 0.3 seconds on the clock in the third quarter, Jokic asked his teammate Peyton Watson to "put it up," pointing his finger. Watson obliged, inbounded the ball at head height, and Jokic nearly volleyball-served it the length of the court and into the hoop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunrise Movement KC expands rallies against incoming bus budget cuts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862793</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/sunrise-movement-kc-expands-rallies-against-incoming-bus-budget-cuts/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T19:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Raymond Forstater Over 60 people attended Sunrise Movement Kansas City’s mass meeting this past week to go over their long-term plan to organize, strike, and disrupt business as usual over the next four years of Trump’s presidency. The Sunrise Movement is an organization of young individuals fighting to stop the climate crisis and win a Green New Deal....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paige Eichkorn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Orlando Magic Are Just That]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174236</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-orlando-magic-are-just-that"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T18:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, after a grindhouse 94-90 win against the Pacers, second-year Orlando guard Anthony Black was asked about his team's defensive performance, and he provided a succinct thesis statement on what makes the team special. "It feels good, feeling their frustration with each other," Black said. "Just seeing the looks on their faces is definitely something we talk about. Pressure, relentless pressure. I think that's what we brought tonight, and I think throughout the game that breaks teams down, and when they get to that breaking point, they break." In other words, to play the Magic is to feel pain, to squirm against a force that is trying to constrict you until you turn purple and croak.
And thus far through the young season, opponents have croaked. Orlando is 11-7, third in both the Eastern Conference standings and defensive rating in the NBA. In a conference otherwise populated by mounds of butt, the Magic are the one cool young team breaking out. While would-be contenders in Milwaukee and New York are slowly righting the ship, the young wingspan freaks in Orlando are playing the conference's best defense by a whopping five points per possession and consolidating last season's breakout campaign, developing into an ambitious team with a clear identity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case For Thanksgiving II]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174330</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-case-for-thanksgiving-ii"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T18:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Perfectly Fine Dinner Party Club, a cooking and hosting column from Libby Watson, who likes to throw dinner parties but is normal about it.
A quick thank-you to people who emailed me about bo ssam! I would especially like to shout out Jerry, who said the post inspired him to invite new neighbors over for dinner, which is just the most lovely thing I've ever heard. He also shared a really great recipe for a cucumber kimchi, which his Korean mom calls "quick kimchi," that I will be making myself. I'll share it at the bottom of this post. I also received a great email from Samuel, telling me to do as the Times recipe suggested and serve the pork with raw oysters. I am unfortunately a little chicken-nuggies-and-chips baby who doesn't like seafood, but I will share his suggestion with you all so that it wasn't in vain. He correctly advises that "if you want to impress people, sit them down in front of a big table of all the bo ssam fixins and then start shucking oysters next to them like you run an ice bar on the bayou." Do the voice too. Say stuff about gators. It'll be fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Libby Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cody Wyoming’s Holly Holy Night brings the music of Neil Diamond to life Thanksgiving weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862776</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/cody-wyomings-holly-holy-night-brings-the-music-of-neil-diamond-to-life-thanksgiving-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T18:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just so you know, the upcoming Holly Holy Night: The Music of Neil Diamond will feature many of Neil Diamond’s finest songs as presented by musician Cody Wyoming and friends, but “Sweet Caroline” will not be one of them. “We have a very carefully maintained setlist and ‘Sweet Caroline’ has grown its own identity that has nothing to do with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reds Trade Jonathan India for a Song Singer]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=451508</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/reds-trade-jonathan-india-for-a-song-singer/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T18:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Better late than never: The Reds dealt from their surplus of infielders to add some much-needed pitching.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Clemens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Giants On New York Giants: “That’s Ass”]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174348</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/new-york-giants-on-new-york-giants-thats-ass"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T18:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Football (So To Speak) Giants still have that dawg in them, trust us. They've just moved on from the mundane world of victory and defeat to the loftier pursuit of indiscriminate shame-flinging. Nobody can rip them better or faster than they can do it themselves, and they added the magic ingredient of unbroadcastable profanity to make it stick. Having that dawg doesn’t necessarily mean it is housebroken.
After their weekly pantsing, a 30-7 loss to Tampa Bay that featured Tommy DeVito looking like the winner of a North Jersey Daniel Jones play-alike contest and the defense retreating early and often as is the Giants' traditional wont, several team employees lined up to gently debate the intensely personal art of observational quitting. That is, they started pointing fingers everywhere and nowhere simultaneously, with the attached benefit of piquant naughty words for added authenticity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Commanders Really Blew That One]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174310</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-commanders-really-blew-that-one"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T17:50:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Commanders had what looked like a choice match-up at home against Cooper Rush and the three-win Cowboys on Sunday—a gift of the schedule that could have been a get-right game after two straight tough losses to very good opponents. But rather than reassert themselves as the upstart team that impressed so much in the early part of the season, Washington spent a long time doing nothing much at all. As the Dallas pressure injured running back Brian Robinson and contained QB Jayden Daniels, inhibiting his ability to either look downfield or scramble, the score was a meager 3-3 at halftime, and with 11 minutes to go in the fourth, fans had just witnessed five straight punts while the Cowboys held a 10-9 lead. That's when the game suddenly turned into chaos.
With a Dallas field goal off some good field position, a Washington fumble, and a Rush pass to a completely uncovered Luke Schoonmaker in the end zone, the 'boys seemingly took control. Under pressure to score, the 'mmanders found their tempo and took bite after bite out of the field until they were rewarded with eight points. On the ensuing kickoff, KaVontae Turpin muffed the catch, picked the ball up, and used a vicious spin move to open a lane that stretched the remaining length of the field. Washington hurried a field goal to cut it to it 27-20 with under two minutes to play, the Cowboys took the clock down to 40 seconds with a three-and-out, and so the Commanders had about half a minute and 86 yards to go for a miracle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-porn lawyers ready to profit from a Kansas age-gating law that may violate the First Amendment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862702</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/anti-porn-lawyers-ready-to-profit-from-a-kansas-age-gating-law-that-may-violate-the-first-amendment/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T17:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The legal industry isn’t immune to quackery. Think about this recent example in central Kansas. Kansas state lawmakers adopted mandatory age verification for porn websites last legislative session. Knowing that her veto might not stand, Democratic Gov. Laura Kelly refused to kill the law, indicating that her administration felt it was in conflict with the First Amendment. Despite the sentiment,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael McGrady Jr.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Kansas Jayhawks dominate #16 Colorado at Arrowhead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862888</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-kansas-jayhawks-dominate-16-colorado-at-arrowhead/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T17:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas Jayhawks versus Colorado Buffaloes on Saturday, Nov. 23, 2024. // Photo by Tarik Sykes Arrowhead was painted red and blue for another Big 12 Saturday on Nov. 23, as the Kansas Jayhawks took on the #16 Colorado Buffaloes. While many were under the assumption that the Deion Sanders led Colorado team would roll over KU, the Jayhawks had other...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarik Sykes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Food Editor’s KC gifting picks for the foodies on your list]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=860540</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/our-food-editors-kc-gifting-picks-for-the-foodies-on-your-list/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T17:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Sarah Sipple Gifting is an art, and I’ve been known to excel at this medium. This specific list is comprised of things I have used, tested, and thoroughly enjoyed. They also happen to be local, consumable, and relatively practical gift ideas.  If you’re not shopping directly from someone’s wishlist, I’m a firm believer that a consumable gift is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Nov. 25: Party Hat (Themeless)]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174319</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-nov-25-party-hat-themeless"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aren’t you thankful that it's time to to wrap up the month with a challenging themeless? Keep an eye out for tricky clues and fun wordplay. This week’s puzzle was constructed by Brandon Koppy and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Brandon lives in Dripping Springs, Texas, just outside Austin, with his wife and two little girls. You can also find his puzzles in The New York Times or on his blog, see17across.com.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Colder and colder again (MON-11/25)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3739396</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-colder-and-colder-again-mon-11-25/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T15:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After an unseasonably warm November, cold, winter weather is entering the Kansas City metro region for Thanksgiving into early December]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Colder and colder again (MON-11/25)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3739396</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-colder-and-colder-again-mon-11-25/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T15:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reminder that TODAY the Winter Weather Forecast is coming in various chunks. I'll add my thoughts on the air tonight at 5/6/9/10 and then get all the teams thoughts together in a blog tomorrow morning for you. Lots of folks enjoy this little exercise. It's also being done way earlier than I would prefer, [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lapse Of Judgment]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174308</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/lapse-of-judgment"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T15:18:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter, examining the apocalyptic politics, coverage, and consequences of Campaign 2024.
The Federalist Society convention the week before last opened with a joke from a federal judge. Here was the joke, as reported by Bloomberg:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Is As Dangerous As Anyone, When It Wants To Be]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174296</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tottenham-is-as-dangerous-as-anyone-when-it-wants-to-be"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T14:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who is the real Tottenham Hotspur? Is it the team that's picked up five early-season losses in the Premier League, most recently and most ignominiously a 2-1 home defeat to Ipswich Town, the newly promoted Tractor Boys' only win? Maybe, but Tottenham is also, and perhaps first and foremost, a giant thorn in Manchester City's side, and Saturday's 4-0 drubbing of the reigning champions, at those reigning champions' home stadium, might be more representative of Tottenham's potential and peak, if not their consistent form.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ltPzF_P7M5o]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Mid-America LGBT Chamber of Commerce’s Tracey DeMarea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862165</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-mid-america-lgbt-chamber-of-commerces-tracey-demarea/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T14:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Morgan Miller Photography Mere mortals don’t stand a chance if they venture into Tracey DeMarea’s orbit. Before they know it, they’re immediately pulled into her Chatty Cathy vortex. Her ability to talk to anyone about anything for any length of time has served her well as the Mid-America LGBT Chamber of Commerce executive director. When asked for her...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orlando Runs Away With The NWSL, And The Rest Will Have To Catch Up]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174289</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/orlando-runs-away-with-the-nwsl-and-the-rest-will-have-to-catch-up"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T22:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before Saturday’s NWSL championship-deciding match between the Orlando Pride and the Washington Spirit, Brazilian legend Marta reflected on her journey with Orlando, where she’s played since 2017, the club’s second-ever season in existence. As the only remaining player from that squad, she told Sandra Herrera that she’s asked herself, “Why? Why am I still looking to do something special here?”
The journey hasn’t been an easy one. The Pride had only made the playoffs once before this year, back in Marta’s first season in 2017. Despite star-laden squads led by the likes of Alex Morgan, Ali Krieger, Sydney Leroux, Ali Riley, and Marta herself, Orlando never could quite form a team greater than the sum of its most impressive parts. Until this season, that is, when Marta, Orlando, and maybe even the NWSL as a whole all found the success they’d long been working for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abigail Segel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Max Verstappen Is Champion Once Again]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174277</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/max-verstappen-is-champion-once-again"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T16:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Max Verstappen claimed his fourth consecutive championship Saturday night, at the conclusion of the Las Vegas Grand Prix. Verstappen came into the race 62 points clear of Lando Norris with three races to go; some truly improbable stuff would've needed to happen over the season's remaining few weeks for Norris to complete the overtake, but at a minimum the McLaren driver needed to finish ahead of Verstappen in Vegas. He could not. Verstappen cruised home in sixth place, half a minute ahead of seventh-place Norris, who surrendered late and took an extra pit stop in order to pursue the point for fastest lap on fresh soft tires, his McLaren team having shifted its attention to holding off Ferrari in the constructor standings.
It was a somewhat anticlimactic conclusion to a championship chase that juiced up the middle third of a Formula 1 season that in its early stages looked like another dreary Red Bull cakewalk. Even as the McLaren plot-line fizzled and it became clear into autumn that Norris's title hopes rested upon Verstappen's car kerploding at some point and then continuing to kerplode on an almost weekly basis, there was still fun to be had in Red Bull's mounting frustration and increasingly visible dysfunction. Then Verstappen had one of the most impressive races of his career in a soaked and chaotic São Paolo Grand Prix, releasing a lot of pressurized angst and giving his inevitable fourth championship its signature moment. São Paolo at least delivered the thrills, even if it all but ended the underdog charge that gave the season its flavor. A Norris win in Las Vegas would've prolonged the chase, but not for very long.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zion Williamson Is Back In The Shop]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174271</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/zion-williamson-is-back-in-the-shop"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T14:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some human bodies are not meant to endure a full 82-game NBA regular season. It's not necessarily the marker of doom it may seem. Bill Walton never could, and he won an MVP award, a Finals MVP award, two titles, and made the Hall of Fame. Tracy McGrady, a fellow Hall-of-Famer, never suited up for 82 games in any of his 16 NBA seasons. Joel Embiid, with two scoring titles and an MVP under his belt at age 30, hasn't yet managed it, and almost certainly never will. You can be a great player without ever exactly being an every-night player. Zion Williamson can still be great.
That's the thing I keep repeating to myself, in the manner of one who recites comforting air-travel safety statistics immediately after having watched both of his plane's wings shear off at 39,000 feet, when I read that Williamson's latest leg injury has not responded as hoped to "multiple treatments" and that he is "not close to a return to action." Williamson started the season with a sore left leg, and then on Nov. 6 he tweaked his hamstring. He returned on Nov. 9 and played well in a loss. Williamson says he "felt fine" after this game, but during treatment the next day he felt "more sore here than usual," and was told after a checkup that he'd suffered a strain and would be ruled out indefinitely. It's been two weeks, and now someone wants Shams to spread the word that fans should not expect Zion to return to the court anytime soon, despite several different attempts having been made at healing that hamstring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump tells US Senate Republicans they ‘must kill’ journalism shield law]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862780</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/donald-trump-tells-us-senate-republicans-they-must-kill-journalism-shield-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T16:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President-elect Donald Trump ordered congressional Republicans on Wednesday to block a broadly popular bill to protect press freedoms, likely ending any chance of the U.S. Senate clearing the legislation. The measure would limit federal law enforcement surveillance of journalists and the government’s ability to force disclosure of journalists’ sources, codifying regulations the Department of Justice has put in place under President...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Fischler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reds, Royals Finalize Trade Involving Brady Singer, Jonathan India]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=831820</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/reds-royals-agree-to-trade-involving-brady-singer-jonathan-india.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T05:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals and Reds made the biggest move of the non-tender deadline. Kansas City acquired infielder Jonathan India and outfielder Joey Wiemer from Cincinnati for starting pitcher Brady Singer. The Royals had space on their 40-man roster, so no corresponding moves were necessary. It’s a swap of big league veterans between teams that expect to compete…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>