<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-02-01T02:45:47.740Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Made Three-Year Offer To Santander Before Jays Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840062</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/01/royals-made-three-year-offer-to-santander-before-jays-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-01T02:24:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have been searching for a middle-of-the-order bat throughout the offseason. Anthony Santander was evidently one such target. Ken Rosenthal of The Athletic reports that Kansas City made Santander a three-year, $66MM offer that included unspecified deferrals and would’ve allowed him to opt out after the second season. Of course, Santander declined that proposal in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Designate Braden Shewmake For Assignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840046</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/01/royals-designate-braden-shewmake-for-assignment.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-01T00:43:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that they’ve designated infielder Braden Shewmake for assignment. That opens a 40-man roster spot for reliever Carlos Estévez, who inked a two-year free agent deal. Shewmake was claimed off waivers from the White Sox a few weeks ago. He’d spent one season with Chicago, who acquired him from the Braves as part of the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xfce4-taskmanager – monitor system resources]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141577</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/xfce4-taskmanager-monitor-system-resources/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T23:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xfce4-taskmanager is an easy to use task manager.
The post xfce4-taskmanager – monitor system resources appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Look For The Helpers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180188</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/look-for-the-helpers"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T23:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter, examining the apocalyptic politics, coverage, and consequences of Campaign 2024.
Everyone knows what Donald Trump is and what his administration is doing. Before he got up in front of the cameras and blamed the deadly midair collision between an Army helicopter and a passenger jet on diversity hiring, and before his vice president got up in front of those cameras and specifically argued that if a white person had contributed to the crash, it was because they were under the strain of working with unqualified minorities, there was his opening salvo of Jan. 6 pardons paired with the executive order denying the 14th Amendment's guarantee of birthright citizenship. And then the executive order calling trans identity a "falsehood" and saying it "is not consistent with the humility and selflessness" required for military service. And the executive order mandating "patriotic education" for primary and secondary schools built around the "celebration of America’s greatness and history." And the memo ordering the Department of Transportation to "give preference to communities with marriage and birth rates higher than the national average." And the unlawful and unconstitutional cutoff of federal grant spending, and the mass firing of the inspectors general, and the mass firing of the prosecutors who'd investigated Trump's previous apparent crimes, and—there was much more than that, and they've tacked on still more of it since the press conference, and anyone who claims to see anything in it other than intentional, comprehensive misrule by sadists and criminals and bigots is someone who is helping to bring it about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laura Stacey Has No Rust To Shake Off]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180137</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/laura-stacey-has-no-rust-to-shake-off"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T20:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the cooler things an athlete can do is return from injury with an “I’ve still got it” game. What a relief, a pleasant surprise. Fans kindly set the bar low—maybe she'll need a few days to get to full speed, no pressure—and then she clears it by a mile, reminding those fans just how much they’ve missed her. In the case of Laura Stacey, who hadn’t dressed for first-place Montreal’s past three games because of a lower-body injury, Victoire fans weren’t the only ones setting the bar low. When the team posted lines before Thursday night's home game against struggling rival Toronto, Stacey was listed on a line by herself, as a 13th forward. Surely, she was still working her way back.  
But Laura Stacey isn't one for seeing how it goes. The tireless power forward always plays like she’s making up for lost time. After last night, consider those missed games made up for. In the Victoire’s 4-3 shootout win, Stacey set up every Montreal goal herself and finished with three points in a decidedly un-13th forward-like 20 minutes of ice time. The win kept Montreal at the top of the PWHL standings as the league heads into next week's international break.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cruelty, Hype, And The American Way In Harry Stein’s Baseball Novel ‘Hoopla’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179932</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cruelty-hype-and-the-american-way-in-harry-steins-baseball-novel-hoopla"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T16:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A line about the experience of reading, possibly first spoken by the young actor Zoe Colletti in the 2019 film adaptation of Scary Stories to Tell in the Dark, is that you don’t read a book, the book reads you. Applied to something other than haunted books, which was Colletti’s usage, the statement suggests that because each reader brings their unique point of view to a work of art, our experience of that book reveals something not just about the work but about ourselves. We find our own preoccupations loose in the pages of works that couldn’t possibly have taken notice of them. This is what makes reading fun.
In this way, it is entirely reasonable that Hoopla, Harry Stein’s 1983 baseball novel about demagoguery framed around the Black Sox conspiracy to throw the 1919 World Series in service to gamblers, seems very much like a work about the present moment. It’s a book that says very little of importance about baseball, but which does a great job of explaining how a country might come to find itself spending the better part of a decade as (mostly) unwilling participants in the Donald Trump Extended Universe. Hoopla depicts an America in which news and entertainment have become so thoroughly muddled and cynical that stories derived from human pleasure and pain, fortune and misfortune, have value only insofar as they can be torqued so as to serve one agenda or another. Truth still exists in this world, but it doesn’t really matter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Goldman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ohkami – intuitive and declarative web framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141600</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ohkami-intuitive-and-declarative-web-framework/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T15:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ohkami is an intuitive and declarative web framework for Rust.
The post Ohkami – intuitive and declarative web framework appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Have Strong Feelings About The Use Of Limp Bizkit’s “Rollin’ (Air Raid Vehicle)” In The Opening Credits To This Netflix Video Game Anime]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180127</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-have-strong-feelings-about-the-use-of-limp-bizkits-rollin-air-raid-vehicle-in-the-opening-credits-to-this-netflix-video-game-anime"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T15:42:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hate to give Netflix credit for anything, anything at all, but I will power through: The streaming service has carved out a pretty decent niche for itself as the home of passable-to-good video game anime adaptations. Starting with 2017's Castlevania, a great show completely ruined by horrific allegations against its creator, and continuing with Arcane: League of Legends, Cyberpunk: Edgerunners, and Castlevania: Nocturne—now with less horrible creators, I hope—the network has a solid enough pedigree to get me to check out shows based on games that I don't particularly care about.
Enter Devil May Cry, a game series I almost entirely missed save for its fourth installment in 2008, which serves as the basis for a new anime coming out on April 3. The network teased the opening credit sequence for the adaptation on Thursday, and for a game series that started in 2001, the show leans into the era by picking a recognizable nu metal song as the backing track. Unfortunately, the song is Limp Bizkit's "Rollin' (Air Raid Vehicle)".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A Different Man’ Has Sebastian Stan At His Most Alluring]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180040</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-different-man-has-sebastian-stan-at-his-most-alluring"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T15:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever you think of Sebastian Stan, it’s hard not to look at him and immediately think: Well, I mean, he’s beautiful. Because, conventional or not—with his square jaw and Rossetti lips and little nose and cleft chin and blue eyes and thick straight hair and straight white teeth—Sebastian Stan is beautiful. What must it be like to walk through the world looking like that? It must do something to the way you move, the way you talk, the way you make decisions. Maybe there’s nothing to think about when it’s all you’ve known. But Stan has talked enough about struggling with his identity as a Romanian immigrant for the thought not to have occurred to him: the strangeness of everyone welcoming you in even when you are uncertain who you even are.
Considering his bold looks in films like I, Tonya…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Battle of the air masses into February (FRI-1/31)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3809834</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-battle-of-the-air-masses-into-february-fri-1-31/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T15:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're going to start February on a mild note with plenty of 50s on the way into early next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Battle of the air masses into February (FRI-1/31)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3809834</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-battle-of-the-air-masses-into-february-fri-1-31/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T15:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're going to finish the month about 5° below average (give or take) a bit as temperatures for today will be into the mid to upper 40s during the afternoon. At one point this month we were down to about 8° below average so we've made up a big of ground in the last 10 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“It Changes Everything”: What Canada’s New Women’s Soccer League Means To Two Of Its Players]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180114</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/it-changes-everything-what-canadas-new-womens-soccer-league-means-to-two-of-its-players"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T14:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just over two years ago, Diana Matheson announced formal plans to create a professional women's soccer league in Canada. Matheson, who racked up 206 caps for the Canadian national team in her career of nearly two decades, was the first to pursue what is usually a given in countries with successful national teams: a domestic incubator for top talent. But the Canadian national team, which won Olympic gold in 2021, has almost exclusively relied on foreign leagues to develop elite players. 
In the months since Matheson's efforts went public the Northern Super League, as it's now known, has released a final list of its six participating cities and committed to an April 2025 kickoff; it also, in October 2024, announced a standard player agreement which looks a lot like the NWSL's hard-fought 2024 collective bargaining agreement. It precludes a player draft, prohibits trades without player consent, and grants automatic free-agency at the end of contracts. It also guarantees a minimum salary of 50,000 CAD—about 36,500 U.S. dollars in 2024. Teams across the NSL have announced some splashy signings: CANXNT standout Quinn, newly un-retired Desiree Scott, and veteran goalkeeper Erin McLeod.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abigail Segel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nick Silvio carries the flames from serving on KCFD to the Hawg Jaw Que & Brew smoker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=868431</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/nick-silvio-carries-the-flames-from-serving-on-kcfd-to-the-hawg-jaw-que-brew-smoker/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T14:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Irish Hawg. // Photo Courtesy of Hawg Jaw Que & Brew Creating delicious barbecue requires a lot of different skills outside of a deft hand at flavor: Patience, endurance, experience, and decisiveness are all part of the special sauce to make tender brisket or mouthwatering pulled pork. Who better to call in than a firefighter? Nick Silvio has served on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Baranowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[agg – asciinema gif generator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141602</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/agg-asciinema-gif-generator/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T12:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[agg is a command-line tool for generating animated GIF files from terminal session recordings.
The post agg – asciinema gif generator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Best Free and Open Source Terminal-Based Matrix Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141678</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-terminal-based-matrix-clients/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T11:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This roundup features the finest terminal-based Matrix clients. Only free and open source software is eligible for inclusion.
The post 5 Best Free and Open Source Terminal-Based Matrix Clients appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City welcomed Baba's Pantry with open arms. A bakery now shows off Palestinian treats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-01-31/babas-pantry-bakery-kansas-city-palestinian-food</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-01-31/babas-pantry-bakery-kansas-city-palestinian-food"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After their cafe was named one of 2022's best new restaurants by Bon Appetit magazine, the Kamal family is expanding its dessert and pastry offerings next door, at Baba's Bakery. It's now open on Saturdays, and there are plans to expand hours by March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Celisa Calacal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gisto – code snippet manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141663</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gisto-code-snippet-manager/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T10:07:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gisto is a code snippet manager that runs on GitHub Gists and adds additional features such as searching, tagging and sharing gists 
The post Gisto – code snippet manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City's new Palestinian bakery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/podcast/kansas-city-today/2025-01-31/kansas-citys-new-palestinian-bakery</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/podcast/kansas-city-today/2025-01-31/kansas-citys-new-palestinian-bakery"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fans of the desserts at Baba’s Pantry will get to try even more sweet treats in a new, dedicated space right next door. After Kansas City embraced their Palestinian deli, the Kamal family is expanding with Baba's Bakery, which they call a "labor of love."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nomin Ujiyediin, Byron J. Love</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Best Free and Open Source Text-Based Git Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=84829</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-text-based-git-clients/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T08:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our recommended text-based Git clients, captured in a legendary LinuxLinks chart. We only feature free and open source software here.
The post 8 Best Free and Open Source Text-Based Git Clients appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Taffy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/black-taffy</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/black-taffy"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T08:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Friday so we’re listening to something slightly more upbeat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Damn Small Linux – Linux distro for older hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141583</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/damn-small-linux-linux-distro-older-hardware/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T07:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New DSL is a compact Linux distribution tailored for low-spec x86 computers. It packs a lot of applications into a small package. 
The post Damn Small Linux – Linux distro for older hardware appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21 Best Free and Open Source Linux Graphical Calculators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=2932</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/calculators/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T06:04:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the basic utilities supplied with any operating system is a desktop calculator. We cover the best graphical tools.
The post 21 Best Free and Open Source Linux Graphical Calculators appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlphaMove]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3045/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3045/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ement.el – Matrix client for Emacs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141504</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ement-el-matrix-client-emacs/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T23:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ement.el is a Matrix client for Emacs. It aims to be simple, fast, featureful, and reliable, while integrating naturally with Emacs.
The post Ement.el – Matrix client for Emacs appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Movie Studio At The End Of The World, With Will Tavlin]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179939</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-movie-studio-at-the-end-of-the-world-with-will-tavlin"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T21:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I will not bore or depress you with an explanation of how online media is doing, so you'll have to take me at my word when I say that it's unusual and significant when an 8,500-word essay from n+1 goes as wildly viral as Will Tavlin's essay, about the damage Netflix has done to the concept of "the movies." The story rocks, and is a comprehensive and convincing explanation of both the crisis Netflix represents and the various other crises that created it. Drew and I, who have very different relationships with Netflix, both thought it was excellent, so we were excited to bring Will onto the podcast this week to talk about that story, Netflix's contested history and queasy present, and where all this might be going.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Six Massage Therapists Accuse Justin Tucker Of Sexual Misconduct During Massages]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180072</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/report-six-massage-therapists-accuse-justin-tucker-of-sexual-misconduct-during-massages"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T21:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six massage therapist said longtime Ravens kicker Justin Tucker "engaged in inappropriate behavior" while visiting spas where they worked in the Baltimore area, The Baltimore Banner reported Thursday. The examples given by the therapists included Tucker wiggling so sheets would fall away to expose his penis during massages, Tucker brushing two therapists with his penis, and in three cases Tucker leaving what appeared to be ejaculate on the massage table. Management at two spas also confirmed to The Banner that they banned Tucker from returning after getting reports of inappropriate behavior from their massage therapists.
The massage therapists all said these incidents happened between 2012 and 2016; all spoke anonymously for fear of retaliation from the Ravens organization as well as fans. Most of the women did not know each other beforehand, The Banner reported, but they all provided similar details about what happened.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terry Rozier Is The Latest Player Implicated In Illegal Sports Betting Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180070</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/terry-rozier-is-the-latest-player-implicated-in-illegal-sports-betting-scheme"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T21:03:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After discovering Jontay Porter's connection with an illegal sports-betting ring last year, federal prosecutors are now investigating whether Terry Rozier similarly manipulated his performance as part of a gambling scheme.
According to a report Thursday in the Wall Street Journal, on March 23, 2023, U.S. Integrity, a group that monitors betting markets for sports entities, gambling operators and government agencies, noticed a suspicious wave of bets centered on the performance of Rozier, then a Charlotte Hornet. The Hornets played the New Orleans Pelicans that night, and though Rozier started the game, he played only about 10 minutes before being substituted out with what was later said to be a foot injury. He did not return to the game, and subsequently missed the remaining eight games of the season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Isaiah Stewart Beefs Incessantly]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180063</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/isaiah-stewart-beefs-incessantly"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T20:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this point, it seems like opposing players know that Stewart's easily provoked and do it for sport. He never lets them down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[halp – CLI tool to get help with CLI tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141571</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/halp-cli-tool-help/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T20:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[halp aims to help find the correct arguments for command-line tools by checking the predefined list of commonly used options/flags. 
The post halp – CLI tool to get help with CLI tools appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Shore up Bullpen With Carlos Estévez]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=455868</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/royals-shore-up-bullpen-with-carlos-estevez/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T19:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fly ball pitchers and Kauffman Stadium - name a more iconic duo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Clemens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Poor, Mostly Dead 76ers Are Once Again Groaning Back To Life]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180025</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-poor-mostly-dead-76ers-are-once-again-groaning-back-to-life"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T18:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If I were a fan of the Philadelphia 76ers, I know that I would've already checked out on this season. No one needs this shit! People have lives to live, real priorities, existential matters for the pondering, perfectly blank expanses of painted drywall to stare into while sobbing. Then again, my hoops fandom is weak from decades of malnourishment. Perhaps true 76ers fans—people who've tasted success and grown accustomed to their team's general relevance—are meaningfully better built for enduring such a preposterous first half of the season. Already these people have seen their team lose 14 of its first 17 games, and then win 10 of its next 13 games, and then immediately lose 10 of 12. Not too long ago this team had credible championship aspirations, and now they are this sputtering, lurchi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evisum –  Enlightenment system monitor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141523</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/evisum-enlightenment-system-monitor/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T18:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evisum is a system monitor using Enlightenment Foundation Libraries (EFL).
The post Evisum –  Enlightenment system monitor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phone Too Big]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179809</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/phone-too-big"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T17:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the final months of 2023, I made one of my most controversial decisions.
More than four years had elapsed since I'd last upgraded my phone; the battery life had already begun its slow descent into either planned or technologically inevitable obsolescence. I'd reached the point in life where purchasing a new phone was more of a chore than anything else. And besides, I loved my then-current phone, the iPhone 12 mini. I'd seen enough of the newer iPhones to know that they'd all pose challenges not just for my pockets, but for my hands. I'd recently discovered that contrary to popular belief, I'm not what anyone would describe as tall. My hands are proportional to my 64-inch frame; the webbed skin between my forefinger and thumb stretched, unfamiliar and unpleasant, whenever I had the misfortune of using someone else's Big Phone. With my iPhone 12 mini I could text one-handed, at a speed only previously achieved in the days of T9.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[mlterm – multi lingual terminal emulator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141544</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/mlterm-multi-lingual-terminal-emulator/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T17:17:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mlterm is a multilingual terminal emulator on X11. It's written in C.
The post mlterm – multi lingual terminal emulator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best Free and Open Source Linux Speed Reading Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=39108</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-linux-speed-reading-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T16:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The software featured in here is based on spritzing. Read text without moving your eyes, and therefore rapidly increase your reading speed.
The post 10 Best Free and Open Source Linux Speed Reading Tools appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entertaining VCU-Saint Louis Game Leads To—Fine, Let’s Talk About This Huge Fan Brawl]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179998</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/entertaining-vcu-saint-louis-game-leads-to-fine-lets-talk-about-this-huge-fan-brawl"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T16:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saint Louis was looking to complete the biggest win of its season. The Billikens men’s basketball team has been playing brilliant defense since starting Atlantic 10 conference play, and their 78-69 win over VCU on Tuesday night continued that trend. The Rams have been the best team in the conference this year; their offensive philosophy involves banging inside and making layups. The Billikens didn't really let them do either, as VCU shot just 32.8 percent on Tuesday; they ended up taking 31 threes and made just five.
The Billikens have been solid on defense all year, and a brick wall in conference play. Opponents are shooting just 21.3 percent from distance against them. The Billikens are coming around offensively, too, and there's reason to believe they could get even better; first-year coach Josh Schertz had the best-shooting offense in the country at Indiana State last year. But it’s on the other end where things are getting really interesting. Isaiah Swope and Robbie Avila, who followed Schertz from Indiana State to St. Louis, have stepped up their contribution on the defensive end.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Normalize Eating Poop]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178432</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/normalize-eating-poop"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T15:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elaine Powers first became interested in studying coprophagy—the practice of eating feces—when she was teaching high school biology. Powers often told her students about rabbits, which excrete a special form of poop called a cecotrope that is meant to be eaten, as the rabbits cannot absorb all the nutrients in their food in the first go-around. Her students, perhaps unsurprisingly, demonstrated a distinct enthusiasm for hearing more about poop-eating.
After Powers retired from teaching, she wondered just how many animals ate their own poop. She had started an internship at the Smithsonian's National Zoo and Conservation Biology Institute, where she discovered just how frequently the zoo fields visitors' questions about animals eating poop. In one particular multi-species exhibit, a South American rodent routinely ate the food for and excrement of their monkey roommates. The monkey's food, and by extension, their poop, was high in vitamin D. The rodents quickly developed vitamin D toxicity, which mineralized their muscle tissues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s No High School Basketball Like D.C. High School Basketball]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179955</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/theres-no-high-school-basketball-like-d-c-high-school-basketball"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T15:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s so much to despise about high school sports in 2025: crass commercialization, win-at-all-cost woefulness, etc. 
Counterpoint: Paul VI vs. Gonzaga! On Tuesday night I attended this matchup of the top two basketball programs in what is historically the strongest hoops conference in the strongest hoops city in the country, played in front of an overflow crowd in a tiny gym on a historic campus in the shadow of the U.S. Capitol Building.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Rainy times with colder changes (THU-1/30)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3808159</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-rainy-times-with-colder-changes-thu-1-30/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T14:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thursday will be cloudy with fog, periods of rain and drizzle increasing later. There may even be a thunderstorm around somewhere tonight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ScriptHaus – organize scripts and bash one-liners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141566</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/scripthaus-organize-scripts-bash-one-liners/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T14:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ScriptHaus lets you run bash, Python, and JS snippets from your Markdown files directly from the command-line. 
The post ScriptHaus – organize scripts and bash one-liners appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All The Trains I Rode In China]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179453</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/all-the-trains-i-rode-in-china"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T14:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VARIOUS EASTERN LOCALES, China — Relative velocity's a hell of a thing. It's impossible to conceptualize how fast 300 kilometers per hour is until you're on a train that fast. Even then, it's primarily visual: Until you look at the window and briefly shock the brain with parallax, a G-class high-speed rail train runs so smoothly that you may as well be held still in space. Then, another train runs in the opposite direction on the adjacent track, and in those few seconds that they pass one another, you can feel it: the brief moment when you go from 300 kilometers per hour in one reference frame to over 500 kilometers per hour in another.
The math is, at least, a little easier. To drive from Beijing to Rizhao would take roughly seven hours without traffic, over 400 or so miles. The G-class train we took a day after arriving in Beijing, a Fuxing train produced by state-owned rolling stock manufacturer CRRC, made the trip in about four very comfortable hours, much of which I spent on Wikipedia. (The new CR450 rolling stock, designed for operating speeds of 400 kilometers an hour, is expected to enter service this year. CRRC also has a subsidiary based in Massachusetts, with a rather unfortunate record when it comes to delivering on its contracts with various American urban metro systems, like the MBTA and SEPTA.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carapace  – multi-shell multi-command argument completer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141563</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/carapace-multi-shell-multi-command-argument-completer/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T12:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carapace is a shell completion library (carapace-sh/carapace) as well as a binary containing a collection of shell completers.
The post Carapace  – multi-shell multi-command argument completer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acronym Decoder – explains acronyms and abbreviations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141517</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/acronym-decoder-explains-acronyms-abbreviations/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T09:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acronym Decoder is a simple tool for quick searching of meaning for various acronyms and abbreviations. It's written in Pascal.
The post Acronym Decoder – explains acronyms and abbreviations appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Picocrypt – small and secure encryption tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141627</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/picocrypt-small-secure-encryption-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T08:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Picocrypt is billed as a very small (hence Pico), very simple, yet very secure encryption tool that you can use to protect your files.
The post Picocrypt – small and secure encryption tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rafael Toral]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/rafael-toral</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/rafael-toral"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T08:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Rafael Toral, a Portuguese electronic musician and guitarist from Lisbon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Armbian – Linux for ARM development boards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141551</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/armbian-linux-arm-development-boards/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T07:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Armbian is a highly optimized base operating system specialized for single board computers.
The post Armbian – Linux for ARM development boards appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals To Sign Carlos Estévez]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=839760</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/01/royals-to-sign-carlos-estevez.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T00:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals and right-hander Carlos Estévez are in agreement on a contract, reports Jon Heyman of The New York Post. It’s a two-year deal with a club option, reports Ken Rosenthal of The Athletic. Per Mark Feinsand of MLB.com, the Premier Talent Sports and Entertainment client is expected to make $22MM over two years, which…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[mnotify – simple Matrix CLI client]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141501</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/mnotify-simple-matrix-cli-client/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T23:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[mnotify is a simple CLI for the Matrix chat system. It's written in the Rust programming language.
The post mnotify – simple Matrix CLI client appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sun And Mercury Join The WNBA Trade Fun]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179920</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-sun-and-mercury-join-the-wnba-trade-fun"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T22:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An earlier blog called blockbuster trades “rare in the WNBA.” In fact, they happen twice a week now. We regret the error.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LXTask – lightweight task manager for LXDE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141574</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/lxtask-lightweight-task-manager-lxde/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T21:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LXTask is a lightweight and desktop-independent task manager derived from xfce4-taskmanager with all dependencies on xfce removed
The post LXTask – lightweight task manager for LXDE appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CmdCompass – collect, learn, recall terminal commands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141528</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/cmdcompass-collect-learn-recall-terminal-commands/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T18:19:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[cmdCompass is a command manager/notebook, enabling users to organize commands into collections, apply tags, define templates 
The post CmdCompass – collect, learn, recall terminal commands appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Wrong With War Tourism?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179899</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ukraine-war-tourism"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T16:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KHARKIV, Ukraine — On a cold and cloudy morning in Ukraine’s second city, our tour guide Kirill met us at our hotel. Twenty-seven, with dark, combed-back hair and a neatly trimmed beard, he spoke excellent English. He welcomed us warmly and led us to his dusty blue Honda. His father drove and, as we headed northeast, I was reminded of the first lesson from a hostile-environment training course I once took: Wear your seatbelt. He drove like a man who had grown used to being the only person on the road.
Thirty minutes later, we stepped out onto damp earth slicked with iced-over puddles. Towering above us were the shells of Soviet-era residential apartment blocks. This was the Saltivka district, in the city’s northeast, and it’s where Russia’s 2022 invasion first reached Kharkiv. Two years later, the invasion has stalled but it’s unquestionably still a war zone. Concrete buildings pockmarked by bullets and shrapnel, scorched by fires, and bearing gaping holes from missile strikes. A pair of anti-tank obstacles called hedgehogs blocked the door at one entrance. This is the kind of devastation most of us will only ever see on TV, and to be up close is to be transported—the cold silence in a place designed to be brimming with life, the broken glass crunching underfoot, the doors standing open to dark hallways. This is where people once lived.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jen Golbeck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YASnippet – template system for Emacs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141495</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/yasnippet-template-system-emacs/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T16:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[YASnippet is a template system for Emacs. It allows you to type an abbreviation and automatically expand it into function templates.
The post YASnippet – template system for Emacs appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Naomi Girma’s Move To Chelsea Is Ambition Incarnate]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179852</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/naomi-girmas-move-to-chelsea-is-ambition-incarnate"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T15:38:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coming into last Sunday's match against Arsenal in the Women's Super League, the Chelsea starting lineup was missing some of its, and therefore the world's, best players. Some of these superstar absences were injury related—the recently recovered Lauren James was only fit enough for the substitute's bench, while Sam Kerr remains at least a few weeks away from her long-awaited comeback from last January's ACL tear. Thankfully, the one big-name omission from Chelsea's lineup that had the stadium and the sport as a whole abuzz was the opposite of depressing. Earlier that day the club had officially announced the signing of USWNT legend-in-the-making Naomi Girma, who came from the San Diego Wave via a record-breaking transfer fee. Girma, who obviously couldn't play on Sunday having only just signed her contract with the team hours before, was on hand at Stamford Bridge before the match began, smiling at and waving to the attending fans, who surely feel like they've won a jackpot some orders of magnitude larger than the $1.1 million it cost to bring Girma across the pond.
But amidst all the excitement about the biggest defensive talent in world soccer moving for the largest fee in women's soccer history, there was a game to play, and an important one at that. Chelsea vs. Arsenal is probably the WSL's preeminent rivalry match, pitting the two best-supported and, along with Manchester City, most serious clubs in England against one another in a crosstown match that always has significant title implications. This edition was no different. Chelsea came in looking to extend its lead atop the table, while Arsenal sought to claw its way back into the title race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Weather whiplash time (WED-1/29)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3806182</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-weather-whiplash-time-wed-1-29/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T15:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The good news, as the title of the blog says, is the whiplash part of the pattern is here. So, we're flipping to "warm" and above-average days for a while. Today is a test. Let's see if we can get into the mid-50s, because I think on Sunday we may be pushing 60° heading into early February!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Weather whiplash time (WED-1/29)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3806182</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-weather-whiplash-time-wed-1-29/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T15:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The month is almost over and it's been a cold month as I've highlighted for you recently. We're running about 6.5° below average this month, and we'll chew on that a bit over the next couple of days before we switch over to February. As a matter of fact this is the coldest January, through [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What To Know About The Newest Asteroid That Probably Won’t Obliterate You]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179872</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-to-know-about-the-newest-asteroid-that-probably-wont-obliterate-you"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T15:04:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a website that might tell you how you're going to die. It's constantly updated with various potential causes of your death, and their odds. I don't visit this website regularly, which might sound surprising at first—wouldn't you think I'd want to know this?—but the website is superfluous. If one if the items on the list causes your death, it's likely to cause the deaths of many, most, or all other humans on Earth. Once we get to that point, I figure it'll be on the news or something.
The site is Sentry, an automated prediction system run by NASA's JPL. It lists near-Earth asteroids, and their chances of hitting us, and projects the damage they would do. It offers a helpful 10-point scale to tell us how worried we should be. As of this week, there's a new asteroid atop the leaderboard, rated a 3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need To Get Off The Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179775</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/we-need-to-get-off-the-internet"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T14:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I will admit, there was a point at the start of New York magazine's profile of the jubilant young Trumper right when I started to get nervous. The article opens on Inauguration Day, depicting a party scene in D.C. full of young people enjoying the night, the atmosphere, and each other, the kind of celebrations that have felt all too rare in the COVID-19 pandemic's aftermath. I found myself thinking, Could it really be that the right has stolen partying and nightlife from under our nose? Is their scene truly, viscerally alive in a way the fractured and depressed left no longer seems to be? Could they actually be the cool ones now? These fears emerged quickly and were doused ever quicker as I kept reading:
Conservatism — as a cultural force, not just a political condition — is back in a real way for the first time since the 1980s. But here in D.C., among the tourists from Tampa, the donors, and the last politicians Trump whipped into submission, one can also witness the emerging influence of a newer type of conservative. They are not disenfranchised or working class or anti-elite or many of the other adjectives used to describe Trump supporters since 2016. Rather, they are young, imposingly well connected, urban, and very online. They are rebels once again storming Capitol Hill, though without the pathetic scariness of the January 6 rioters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happens In Prison When You Can’t Pee On Command]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179786</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-happens-in-prison-when-you-cant-pee-on-command"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T14:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prison is always about being less-than. Segregation is prison inside of prison: where you are less than less-than. The very little you have is stripped from you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Hawes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Satisfaction for less than $15 at Los Hornos and China Wok]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=868547</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-satisfaction-for-less-than-15-at-los-hornos-and-china-wok/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T14:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Los Hornos // Photo By Tiffany Watts Los Hornos Argentinian Flavors When you’re a food writer constantly exploring Kansas City’s diverse dining scene, sometimes all you need is a light bite and something refreshing to sip on. That’s exactly what I found at Los Hornos, an Argentinian restaurant tucked away in North Kansas City—a spot that quickly became the perfect...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Microsoft Windows Clock]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141537</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-microsoft-windows-clock/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T13:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Clock is a time management app offering alarms, world clocks, timers, a stopwatch, and focus sessions.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Microsoft Windows Clock appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ehh – CLI tool to help remember commands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141489</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ehh-cli-tool-help-remember-commands/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T11:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ehh is a command-line tool for  remembering Linux / terminal commands. Store and run any command inside ehh.
The post ehh – CLI tool to help remember commands appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City's Asian communities are welcoming in the Lunar New Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2025-01-29/kansas-citys-asian-communities-are-welcoming-in-the-lunar-new-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/podcast/up-to-date/2025-01-29/kansas-citys-asian-communities-are-welcoming-in-the-lunar-new-year"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Year of the Snake begins on Wednesday, Jan. 29. Up To Date heard how Asian communities around Kansas City celebrate, and how to take part.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kraske, Josh Marvine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[openKylin – Chinese desktop Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141509</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/openkylin-chinese-desktop-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T08:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[openKylin is a Chinese desktop distribution which runs the Kylin and UKUI desktop environments. Both Wayland and X11 sessions are available.
The post openKylin – Chinese desktop Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rubey Hu (Guest rec from Jake Newby)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/rubey-hu-guest-rec-from-jake-newby</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/rubey-hu-guest-rec-from-jake-newby"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T08:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we have a guest recommendation from Jake Newby, whose newsletter Concrete Avalanche covers music from China.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KAlgebra – graphing calculator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141559</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/kalgebra-graphing-calculator/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T06:26:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KAlgebra is an application that can replace your graphing calculator. 
The post KAlgebra – graphing calculator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iamb – Matrix client for Vim addicts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141498</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/iamb-matrix-client-vim-addicts/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T06:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iamb is a terminal-based client for Matrix for the Vim addict.You can edit messages, navigate windows and manage tabs.
The post iamb – Matrix client for Vim addicts appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Humidifier Review]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3044/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3044/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[nap – code snippets in your terminal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141457</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/nap-code-snippets-terminal/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T23:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Create and access new snippets quickly with the command-line interface or browse, manage, and organize them with the text-user interface.
The post nap – code snippets in your terminal appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nazism & Hitler: The Defector Explainer]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179767</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nazism-hitler-the-defector-explainer"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T19:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about second booth legends, Chris Farley, the search for decent Italian food in North Carolina, and more.
Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eg – provides examples of common uses of command line tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141454</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/eg-examples-common-uses-command-line-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T19:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[eg will give you useful examples right at the command line. Think of it as a companion tool for man.
The post eg – provides examples of common uses of command line tools appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Artist’s Way’ Week 3: Synchronicities And Faith]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179715</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-artists-way-week-3-synchronicities-and-faith"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T18:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When things just happen to work out for you, do you chalk that up to coincidence, or is it something more? Julia Cameron would call that a synchronicity, and in Week 3 of The Artist's Way, she had us keeping an eye out for them. According to Cameron, synchronicities are more than just happy accidents; they're indications that the universe (or god, or whatever) is responding positively to active changes you're making in your life. 
This part of Cameron's philosophy veers a bit dangerously into Power of Positive Thinking territory for many of our tastes. But in the spirit of doing the process in good faith, we continued to show up for our morning pages and artist dates. (By the way, if you're just catching this now, a few of us at Defector are blogging our way through Julia Cameron's The Artist's Way this winter.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Celtics Can Afford To Wait For Math To Come Back Around]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179740</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-celtics-can-afford-to-wait-for-math-to-come-back-around"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T18:12:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Boston Celtics are by no means in any trouble. They lost Monday night at home to the ascending Houston Rockets, and yes, the Celtics are now more than five games back of the Cleveland Cavaliers at the top of the Eastern Conference; also yes, they've been playing approximately .500 ball since the middle of December. Yes, too, fine: The New York Knicks are breathing midtown hot dog breath down their necks. Still: The Celtics are in no real danger of sliding out of contention. They've had some bad luck in the clutch, going 11–10 over a stretch of games where they've posted the fourth best net rating in the league. This is a tough part of their schedule, they're not entirely healthy, and a competent team can only slide so far in the soft East. They'll be fine.
If you imagined Joe Mazzulla's perfected ActuariBall made the Celtics immune from hard times—and whether that thought filled you with comfort or dread—I suppose this recent slump has disabused you of the notion. It is precisely on the side of the ball where Boston leans furthest into math mode that they are presently struggling: Per Cleaning The Glass, over the last two weeks Boston's offense, which on the season scores the third most points per possession in the NBA, has dropped to 16th in efficiency, just above the ridiculous Charlotte Hornets and just below the somehow even more ridiculous Philadelphia 76ers. They've been hucking just as many threes as ever, but where the Celtics were above average by proficiency across the first two months of the season, since their unexpected home loss to the Chicago Bulls on Dec. 19 they have fallen to eighth worst. It's not entirely that simple, but also, the Celtics are to a certain extent dying by the sword. Mazzulla's offense seeks to remove some of the variance of distance shooting by maximizing volume, but it is still, by God, a make-or-miss league. Monday night it was the dreaded Dillon Brooks doing the making, to the deep and audible exasperation of the Boston faithful:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Mite’s Leap Of Electric Faith Into A Hummingbird Nostril]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179601</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-mites-leap-of-electric-faith-into-a-hummingbird-nostril"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T17:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The milky specks known as hummingbird mites are among the most skilled hitchhikers in the world. They live their lives inside flowers and inflorescences, where they feed on nectar and pollen, mate, and produce their young. But all flowers eventually wither and die, and a mite, approximately the size of a grain of sugar, is far too tiny to set out into the world in search of a new flower. Instead, it awaits the beak of a hungry hummingbird to dip into the chute of their flower. When one arrives, the mite leaps from petal to beak, where it crawls inside the bird's nostrils to hitch a ride and hop off whenever the bird visits another flower of the same species.
These mites, however, lack wings, as well as the ability to jump. So how do they manage to leap from beak to flower and back? A new paper reveals the arachnids actually harness the power of electrostatic attraction to make the leap. Once the mites detect the signature electrical charge of a hummingbird—an ability known as electroreception—they whoosh through the air, their itty-bitty bodies riding the charged air. The new paper is published in Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eat This Now: Crab Rangoon at Sayachi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=867799</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/eat-this-now-crab-rangoon-at-sayachi/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T17:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crab rangoons at Sayachi. // Photo by Emily Wheeler As a self-proclaimed crab rangoon connoisseur, I have spent my time in Kansas City scouring for the best in the city. Brookside sushi restaurant Sayachi offers some of the most flavorful crab rangoons I’ve tried around the metro. I’ve returned to Sayachi many times over the past couple of years, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Wheeler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dma – DragonFly Mail Agent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141443</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/dma-dragonfly-mail-agent/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T16:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[dma is a small Mail Transport Agent (MTA), designed for home and office use.
The post dma – DragonFly Mail Agent appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Wizards Are Going All The Way Down]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179744</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-washington-wizards-are-going-all-the-way-down"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T16:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing much of note happened to the Washington Wizards last night, which is to say the same thing that usually happens to them happened again. They lost their 14th game in succession, a routine 130-108 loss to the truncated Dallas Mavericks, and in so doing became the 98th team in NBA history to compile a losing streak that long. We mention that only because the 97th team to do it was the Wizards back in November, when they lost 16 straight before the holiday sales had time to gather steam. They are 6-39 this morning, the 15th-worst record after 45 games in history, and only one game better than last year's Pistons, who lost games 4 through 31.
That Pistons team was thought to be among the worst of all time, and for two months they were. But whatever passes as desire for a team that finished 14-68 flashed as often as not after their losing streak; by a stretchy definition, those Pistons played hard, or at least as hard as a doomed team can be expected to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Detroit Auto Show Used To Be The Future]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179751</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-detroit-auto-show-used-to-be-the-future"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T15:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DETROIT — There was a brief moment where I, as a child growing up in Michigan, thought heaven might look something like the North American International Auto Show. Inside a vast convention center hall, impossibly shiny cars stretched out before me in a vast maze that seemed to hold surprises around each corner. There were driving simulators to play and collectible cards to hoard. I could sit in the front seat of a car, and did, racing from vehicle to vehicle on the showroom floor. Everything was sleek and perfect. Maybe not when my friends and I got yelled at for touching the cars at the Porsche display. But everything else was perfect. 
When you’re a kid in the Mitten State, there are a lot of car-related field trips. You can go to the Ford Rouge Factory Tour, where you watch F-150s get assembled. At the historical Greenfield Village, one highlight is being able to ride around in a refurbished Model T. Many Michigan museums have some form of an auto manufacturing exhibit. Still, the auto show always stood out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heather Wei-Xi Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let Us Compare These Two Men In Tan Suits]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179645</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/let-us-compare-these-two-men-in-tan-suits"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T15:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In two weeks, the Philadelphia Eagles will play the Kansas City Chiefs in the Super Bowl. Every single day until then a bunch of people will use "data" and "history" to try to predict who will win. But sports are about vibes (which can also be called "luck") as much as they are about talent. And so we must measure the vibes of these teams. Luckily, it is easy to do this because we have an useful comparison point: Chief's tight end Travis Kelce and Eagles quarterback Jalen Hurts both wore tan suits this past Sunday.
Let's see how they compare!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: So close to another blizzard (TUE-1/28)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3804865</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-so-close-to-another-blizzard-tue-1-28/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T14:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the 14th coldest January through yesterday and what is somewhat remarkable is that we all remember LAST January, and how cold it was, with the extreme cold on some mornings, well believe it or not, this January, through yesterday is EVEN COLDER!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FastFlix – GUI for encoding videos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141480</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/fastflix-gui-encoding-videos/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T14:26:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FastFlix is a GUI for H.264, HEVC and AV1 hardware and software encoding.
The post FastFlix – GUI for encoding videos appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future Is Too Easy]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=178446</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-future-is-too-easy"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LAS VEGAS — There is something unstable at the most basic level about any space with too much capitalism happening in it. The air is all wrong, there's simultaneously too much in it and not enough of it. Everyone I spoke to about the Consumer Electronics Show before I went to it earlier this month kept describing it in terms that involved wetness in some way. I took this as a warning, which I believe was the spirit in which it was intended, but I felt prepared for it. Your classically damp commercial experiences have a sort of terroir to them, a signature that marks a confluence of circumstances and time- and place-specific appetites; I have carried with me for decades the peculiar smell, less that of cigarette smoke than cigarette smoke in hair, that I remember from a baseball card show at a Ramada Inn that I attended as a kid. Only that particular strain of that particular kind of commerce, at that moment, gave off that specific distress signal. It was the smell of a living thing, and the dampness in the (again, quite damp) room was in part because that thing was breathing, heavily.
CES, which this year claimed 141,000 attendees and 4,500 exhibitors, could on the other hand have been anywhere, or everywhere. That it was held across several vast convention spaces in Las Vegas certainly helped with that placelessness, or everyplacefulness, but the overwhelming volume and scale of the thing ensured it. The air in every space was charged with all that commerce, somehow shortened by the competition for it, but it wasn't close in the ways that I had prepared myself for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HyperHDR – ambient lighting implementation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141474</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/hyperhdr-ambient-lighting-implementation/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T11:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HyperHDR is an ambient lighting implementation for television and music sets based on the video and audio streams analysis
The post HyperHDR – ambient lighting implementation appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flowkeeper – Pomodoro Technique desktop timer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141446</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/flowkeeper-pomodoro-technique-desktop-timer/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T10:23:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flowkeeper is a Pomodoro Technique desktop timer for power users. It is a simple tool, which focuses on doing one thing well.
The post Flowkeeper – Pomodoro Technique desktop timer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Best Free and Open Source Software KVM Switches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141344</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-software-kvm-switches/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T09:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The main function of a KVM switch is to control, switch between, and manage multiple PCs or servers via a single keyboard, monitor and mouse
The post 6 Best Free and Open Source Software KVM Switches appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Great-OS – Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141461</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/great-os-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T09:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great-OS is an independent Linux distribution made in France. It provides a variety of different desktop environments.
The post Great-OS – Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flow State Episode 262 (Vinyl Special)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-episode-262-vinyl-special</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-episode-262-vinyl-special"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T08:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s mix is all vinyl and available to everyone, in support of dublab’s record sale for fire relief this Sunday at Sound & Vision in Los Angeles (more info here).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[asciit – compact ASCII table]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141407</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/asciit-compact-ascii-table/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T23:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[asciit is a more compact and intuitive ASCII table highlighting digits and letters.
The post asciit – compact ASCII table appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Got A Real WNBA Trade, With Stars And Everything]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179599</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/we-got-a-real-wnba-trade-with-stars-and-everything"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T22:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was a trade—a big splashy one, which is rare in the WNBA!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jimmy Butler Suspended Again, If You Even Care]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179690</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jimmy-butler-suspended-again-if-you-even-care"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T22:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The protracted standoff between the Miami Heat and Jimmy Butler, which has always been more of a mid-off given the relative states of the parties involved, has taken yet another turn. ESPN's Shams Charania reports that Butler has now been suspended indefinitely, following an incident at today's shootaround in which he walked off the court after being informed that he would not be starting Monday night's game against the Orlando Magic.
It has been several weeks since Butler first made an explicit demand to be traded, and if I am being honest, I have not really kept track of all the developments since. Headlines and BREAKING NEWS reports have passed along the edge of my awareness, heralding various suspensions and returns from suspensions, and meetings with ownership, and agent back-channeling, and so on and so on. At some point, I am pretty sure I read something about Butler renting his own house in Boulder during the 2023 Finals. It's been difficult to keep track of all this, only because it is difficult to raise much concern about a player vs. front office battle as juiceless as this one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[spigot – command-line exact real calculator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141390</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/spigot-command-line-exact-real-calculator/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T21:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[spigot is a command-line streaming exact real calculator. It's written in the C++ programming language.
The post spigot – command-line exact real calculator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Madison Keys Won Her First Major By Changing Her Racquet And Mind]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179565</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/madison-keys-won-her-first-major-by-changing-her-racquet-and-mind"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T21:15:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People had been telling Madison Keys she had the game to win majors since she was a kid. "Probably 11, 12," she said on Saturday. "It obviously was meant to be confidence-building and all of that." One look at the sheer power in her game, and it's easy to see what made them think that way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eagles Fans Are Happiest At The Brink Of Agony]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179656</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/eagles-fans-are-happiest-at-the-brink-of-agony"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T20:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I knew it was over when Tress Way’s pass was in the air. Jeremiah Trotter Jr. was too far behind whichever Washington player was running free downfield. I didn’t yet know the name of the guy who was going to end the Eagles’ season was, but I learned. A third-string tight end named Ben Sinnott caught that 23-yard pass on a fake punt, and this was absolutely the turning point. The Commanders were down 14-3 at that moment, but I knew what was going to happen next. I was already thinking about how Way and Sinnott were going to become part of DC sports lore, famous for the play that turned around a game that seemed to be getting away from them. The Commanders were going to win the NFC Championship.
I like to think I’m a reasonable person, but I am not. There were still two minutes left in the first quarter when my brain decided that the Eagles, up two scores and moving the ball with ease, were going to lose. Anyway, that Commanders’ drive ended with a field goal and not a touchdown, and I relaxed a little. Some time later, the Eagles won the game by the score of 55-23.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[snip – CLI snippets manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141434</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/snip-cli-snippets-manager/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T18:53:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[snip is a simple snippet manager for bash, to save useful and important bash code snippets directly from the bash prompt.
The post snip – CLI snippets manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tottenham Inches Towards Implosion]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179608</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/tottenham-inches-towards-implosion"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T18:43:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Nov. 23, Tottenham Hotspur notched what would be most teams' season-defining victory, smacking the ever-loving crap out of Manchester City 4-0 on the road. Even in light of the well-documented tailspin City was in the midst of at the time, Tottenham's performance that day was a perfect exhibition of manager Ange Postecoglou's whirlwind of chaos. It was also a much-needed salve after the opening months of the season, which had seen Spurs' offense, once the best in the Premier League, routinely let down by a shorthanded defense that continuously conceded ill-timed goals, leading to a procession of narrow defeats.
That salve was short-lasting, as Tottenham's season went from mildly frustrating to complete shambles soon after the win over City. In the two months since, Tottenham has won exactly one Premier League match—a 5-0 thrashing of bottom-dwelling Southampton on Dec. 15—to go with two draws and a gobsmacking eight losses. The run has dropped Spurs from the table's sixth spot to its 15th, much closer to the relegation zone (eight points) than the top seven (16 points). While the schedule has not done the side any favors—in that span, Tottenham has played games ranging from tricky, like Fulham and Bournemouth, to exceedingly tough, like Liverpool, Arsenal, and the mighty Nottingham Forest—the biggest culprit for the collapse has been the team's nightmarish injury situation, and Postecoglou has not had the answers for how to deal with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Australian Open Is Happy And Hot]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179629</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-australian-open-is-happy-and-hot"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T17:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MELBOURNE – Envy sabotaged my plans for watching the first day of the 2025 Australian Open. I was going to take in Day One on a projector at Federation Square, a public area surrounded by angular buildings that look like they've been shattered and pieced back together for effect. There would be other people to help simulate a crowd, the city serves as a pretty backdrop, and I could save my money for later in the tournament. Unfortunately, Fed Square is between the city center and the Australian Open, and the endless stream of people walking past me on their way to the tournament obliterated my resistance. A quick tussle with Ticketmaster, a grounds pass purchase, and I was in. 
The walkways were choked with fans. The air smelled like sunscreen and sweat and perfectly matched the temperature of my skin. Then, as I observed last year's finalist Qinwen Zheng hit devastating backhands on the big screen, raindrops splattered on my skin. Blinks of lightning disrupted the pleasant equilibrium. The band playing quietly in the background fired off an errant thrum of bass that rattled the ground. The rain paced itself at a reasonable patter at first, so I sought refuge in a crowd under some stilted, overhanging structures resembling giant lily pads, which I knew were for shade but hoped would block light rain. Then God's gentle weeping turned into crocodile tears, soaking those of us underneath as if we were standing out in the open. I made for inside, laughing, and others were laughing too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Owen Lewis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[rkvm – virtual KVM switch for Linux machines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141336</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/rkvm-virtual-kvm-switch-linux-machines/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T16:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[rkvm is a tool for sharing keyboard and mouse across multiple Linux machines. It is based on a client/server architecture
The post rkvm – virtual KVM switch for Linux machines appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Jan. 27: Bursting With Pride (Themeless)]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179582</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-jan-27-bursting-with-pride-themeless"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T15:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time to wrap up the month with a challenging themeless. Keep an eye out for tricky clues and fun wordplay. This week’s puzzle was constructed by Rebecca Goldstein and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Rebecca is a scientist and crossword constructor in the Bay Area. 
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick Mahomes Will Always Make You Pay]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179579</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/patrick-mahomes-will-always-make-you-pay"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T14:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can’t win against Patrick Mahomes and the Chiefs. I know you THINK you can. I know you saw all those graphics about the Chiefs stringing together one-score win after one-score win and said to yourself, Well, that’s not analytically sustainable, right before they made your team their next victim. I know that the Bills, who spent the entirety of last night’s AFC title game playing like the proverbial dog on the porch who’s tired of getting kicked, could have won that game had just one thing gone differently. Slide a door and there isn’t a game-breaking disagreement between opposing side judges on Josh Allen’s failed fourth-down attempt. Slide another and Xavier Worthy doesn’t Fail Mary his way to the 3-yard line toward the close of the first half. Slide another and the Bills don’t call a piddly shit bubble screen on third-and-10 on their final drive. To lose to the Chiefs is to be trapped in a room of nothing but sliding doors, all of them bolted shut.
It’s enough to drive you mad, and that madness will be on full display today and forever. It will manifest itself on sports talk radio, and on television, and on the internet. The Bills were just an inch away from beating the Chiefs, you swear. It’s a lie that’s equal parts comforting and enraging. Buffalo should have won that game, you’ll tell everyone. But nefarious external forces—the refs, the league office, Big Government—deliberately fixed the outcome in Kansas City’s favor. It’s not just. It’s not even real. Fetch me my bag of asterisks. All my life, this has been the preferred defense mechanism for all sports fans in the face of greatness. This is because it feels better to deny greatness—to believe what can’t be defeated can be—than to accept that you and your team’s powerlessness against it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>