<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-11-30T12:30:06.335Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enjoy The Lily Yohannes Victory Lap]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174490</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/enjoy-the-lily-yohannes-victory-lap"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T21:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States Women's National Team is currently in Europe to play a pair of friendlies that will thoroughly stretch the meaning of that designation.
First up is a date with England at Wembley, both a homecoming for USWNT coach Emma Hayes and a fascinating opportunity to consider the dynamics of the transatlantic soccer exchange on both the Olympic champions and the European champions. Hayes, of course, made her name managing Chelsea for over a decade, though she got her start coaching in New York, a bit north of where Three Lionesses manager Sarina Wiegman played college soccer. USWNT vets have enjoyed short stints in England, and so many England players have tussled in the NWSL that The Athletic ran a long story with quotes from each payer about how physical and demanding the standard of play was stateside. The game is not exactly a referendum on whose development environment is better, though it does provide an occasion to think seriously about at the state of the best women's club league and the second-best as it closes the gap. It's also a serious test for both teams with close to their full rosters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Last Pitcher]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174670</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-last-pitcher"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T17:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defector has partnered with Baseball Prospectus to bring you a taste of their work. They write good shit that we think you’ll like. If you do like it, we encourage you to check out their site and subscribe.
This story was originally published at Baseball Prospectus on November 22.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Dubuque</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Fast moving snows Saturday (FRI-11/29)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3743490</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-fast-moving-snows-saturday-fri-11-29/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T16:50:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we head toward the last day of November tomorrow, Mother Nature may give us a last day of November snow, and perhaps, it may be more than just a casual amount for parts of the area]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Does Hotel Art Look Like That?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174198</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/why-does-hotel-art-look-like-that"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T14:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently stayed at a blandly business-oriented hotel in San Jose in order to celebrate my birthday, drink a tall boy, and watch the Sharks lose. You know this type of hotel. There were white duvet covers, white sheets, beige walls, dark wood for the closet and bathroom doors. There was a nice light under a wall bench to help you find your way to the bathroom in the middle of the night. The soundproofing was good.
There was also, of course, a picture on the wall. There is always a picture on the wall in hotel rooms. It was a photograph and it showed a cement wall and floor belonging to what seemed to be a warehouse building.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felix Kent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Staying Up Late And Being Stupid]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174669</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/staying-up-late-and-being-stupid"/>
        <updated>2024-11-28T17:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is not important how late I stayed up watching Rutgers defeat Notre Dame on Tuesday night, in one of the many Thanksgiving-season college basketball tournaments happening right now. It is sufficient to say that it was late enough that I felt both tired and stupid the next morning, and arrived at my parents' house the next evening to help with Thanksgiving prep both a little droopy and decently primed for the cascading excesses of this season. Staying up to watch tournaments sponsored by the manufacturers of the orange-shaped chocolate thing my in-laws like, or the early rounds of the Bad Boy Mowers Battle 4 Atlantis, is a kind of gluttony in itself. It's less literal than the kind that generally defines Thanksgiving, but it comes from the same place—the instinct, when presented with an abundance of something/anything, to let yourself have a little treat, and then maybe another after that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pass The Salt]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174547</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/pass-the-salt"/>
        <updated>2024-11-28T15:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, through here.
It’s Thanksgiving today, and I have only one message for you, the Holiday-American: please pass the salt. Do not hog the salt. Do not set the table without salt and pepper, as if the food you’ve cooked has already been flawlessly seasoned. And do NOT, under any circumstances, give me any guff when I ask for more salt on my food.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pitch’s 2024 Holiday Self-Gift Guide for spoiling yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861402</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/the-pitchs-2024-holiday-self-gift-guide-for-spoiling-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-28T14:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Keegan Hudspeth   Bryan Busby KMBC 9 Meteorologist  The book, You are a badass, by Jen Sincero. It is a self-help book like no other, using very directed, frank wording. With a title like that, you can only imagine the language she uses to motivate you. I have given friends and my protégés this book as a holiday...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City Wing Tour: Six must-try spots for chicken wing lovers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861989</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kansas-city-wing-tour-six-must-try-spots-for-chicken-wing-lovers/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T22:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Q39 // Photo By Tiffany Watts If you’re on the hunt for the best chicken wings in Kansas City, you’re in luck. From smoky BBQ to bold international flavors, these local gems are redefining what it means to serve unforgettable wings. Here’s your ultimate guide to KC’s wing scene—grab your wet wipes and prepare for a flavor-packed journey. Mr. Wingz...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with A Christmas Carol’s Nedra Dixon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863493</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-a-christmas-carols-nedra-dixon/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T20:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Don Ipock Not unlike the arrival of Mariah Carey, the holidays aren’t the holidays without KCRep’s annual performance of the beloved holiday classic, Charles Dickens’s A Christmas Carol. Over the decades, the play—which runs through Dec. 28 at Spencer Theatre—has become an iconic KC tradition.  If you’ve been living under a rock, the show tells the tale of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They Put Trent Green In This Hallmark Christmas Movie]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174698</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/they-put-trent-green-in-this-hallmark-christmas-movie"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T18:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trent Green does not have a long acting career. His IMDb page is basically his football career. For example, it lists him as appearing in 11 episodes of NFL On Fox as “Self,” while quarterbacking Washington, St. Louis, and Kansas City. Now Green has a real credit to his name, though he’s still playing himself—Trent Green is in a Hallmark Christmas movie.
Earlier this week, Alex, Kelsey, Sabrina and I discussed Christmas in the Spotlight. That was a Lifetime Christmas movie featuring not-so-thinly veiled versions of Taylor Swift and Travis Kelce. It was like any other football movie that existed in a world outside the NFL, in that the teams were fake—the Kelce character, Gonzo, played for the Bay Springs Bombers—and the extra-large end zones in the football scenes were proof that the film was made in Canada. But Trent Green’s movie debut features the real Kansas City Chiefs. Holiday Touchdown: A Chiefs Love Story, which premieres Saturday, is an actual honest-to-God NFL-licensed Hallmark Christmas movie. Score one for Hallmark in the annual contest for made-for-TV Christmas supremacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Does A Recipe Become Your Own?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174752</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/when-does-a-recipe-become-your-own"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growing up my grandma lived in a small green house that sat under a towering cottonwood tree on the southside of Minneapolis. She had many old things, or at least things that felt old to my young brain: a cast iron fire place that looked like it could forge steel, a massive wooden cabinet TV that hummed and seemed almost radioactive, a whole rainbow's worth of colorful mixing bowls that were sturdy enough to survive in the oven.
The bowls are what I remember the most, because I remember the kitchen more vividly than anything else. On holidays like Thanksgiving, Christmas and Easter, work would start in the narrow galley of a kitchen very early and it would go late, until family arrived, until the very minute everyone sat at the table, through the comabtive games of Uno to decide who would do dishes after no one was foolish enough to eat more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri AG lays out abortion restrictions he argues remain in place despite Amendment 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863643</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missouri-ag-lays-out-abortion-restrictions-he-argues-remain-in-place-despite-amendment-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T18:17:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An opinion issued by Missouri Attorney General Andrew Bailey states that while any statutes prohibiting abortion prior to fetal viability will no longer be enforceable in their entirety, the state can still enforce some laws (photo submitted). Missouri Attorney General Andrew Bailey believes the state can still enforce some abortion restrictions even after voters lifted the state’s ban earlier this...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Spoerre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KBI seeks $114.4 million for new headquarters and exit from ‘horrible’ neighborhood in Topeka]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863644</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kbi-seeks-114-4-million-for-new-headquarters-and-exit-from-horrible-neighborhood-in-topeka/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T18:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Mattivi, director of the Kansas Bureau of Investigation, urged the 2025 Legislature to approve plans for a new $114.4 million headquarters building in Topeka. He said the existing facilities posed fire-safety risks, lacked a suitable perimeter and were otherwise inadequate to complete the agency’s law enforcement mission. (Tim Carpenter/Kansas Reflector) TOPEKA — The director of the Kansas Bureau of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Carpenter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Purpose Of A Bathroom Law]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174525</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-purpose-of-a-bathroom-law"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T18:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Current Delaware state senator Sarah McBride was elected to the U.S. House of Representatives as a Democrat earlier this month, replacing Lisa Blunt Rochester, who moved to the Senate to replace the retiring Tom Carper. McBride is the first known trans person to serve in the U.S. Congress.
The left wing of the trans community was not that enthused by McBride's victory, in part because the representative-elect positioned herself during the campaign as a staunch Israel hawk even as its military continues to inflict apocalyptic conditions on Palestinians in Gaza (including, obviously, our siblings in the queer community). Given her ties to Joe Biden and the aggressively centrist Human Rights Campaign, plenty of trans people (myself included) resisted any framing of McBride's election as groundbreaking. In nearly every respect, she is an extremely typical middle-of-the-road politician.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consider The Fruit Tea Dilemma]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174697</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/consider-the-fruit-tea-dilemma"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T17:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even though you knew about the great rice/wheat cultivation divide, the extent to which you missed rice after one-and-a-half weeks in China surprised you. But now—after countless delicious but rice-less meals with millet porridge, mantou, and/or dumplings as the primary carb delivery vessels—you and your older sister are finally let loose upon the city of Qingdao to pick a meal for yourself.
It is 4:30 p.m. on a weekday. You ate so much at the hotel breakfast that lunch was patched up with a snack, but now you are very hungry. It is time for something spicy and ricey. You are armed with Chinese fluency and a working Alipay. But no creature is perfect, and so you are also functionally illiterate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dodgers Should Cut To The Chase]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174710</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-dodgers-should-cut-to-the-chase"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T17:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Be amazed all you like by the Los Angeles Dodgers firing out another $182 million for the next five years of Blake Snell’s services. Wonder how much deferred money they will have to pay Snell, the offseason's finest domestic pitching prize, after the club’s current management team is either retired or dead. Speculate in rage about how the Dodgers will invariably get Juan Soto before Christmas and then pick up Roki Sasaki while they're standing in the checkout line like he was a damned Almond Joy. Complain to your spleen's content about how, if the Dodgers ever keep everyone healthy, they will win 146 games and be awarded the World Series by acclamation after the American League champion declares "screw it" and goes on vacation early. They're still doing this world domination thing wrong.
What they should be doing, simply put, is eliminating the middleman. The Dodgers should simply buy Scott Boras.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our December 2024 Events Calendar showcases Justin Timberlake, The Allman Betts Band, and holiday season happenings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861391</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/our-december-2024-events-calendar-showcases-justin-timberlake-the-allman-betts-band-and-holiday-season-happenings/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T17:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Chris Ortiz. // Art by Cassondra Jones ONGOING Dec 6 & 7 Sam Jay, Comedy Club KC Dec 6-8 Kansas City Symphony Presents Handel’s Messiah, Kauffman Center for the Performing Arts Dec 6-24 Kansas City Ballet Presents The Nutcracker, Kauffman Center for the Performing Arts Dec 19-22 Kansas City Symphony Presents Christmas Festival, Kauffman Center for the Performing Arts...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitter Fruit From The Fig Of Deceit]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174709</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bitter-fruit-from-the-fig-of-deceit"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T16:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speaking from experience, buying into symbolism will drive you mad. I cannot tell you how many times I’ve been absolutely certain that a certain gesture definitively means a person is now my enemy. My long-suffering therapist always tries to remind me that there are other potential explanations for most things. But why shouldn’t I believe my own interpretations, especially if my enemies are making themselves known?
I’m convinced my therapist would be eaten alive if they stepped in the neighborhood where today’s episode takes place. We’ve got divorce lore, hot young lawn boys, cryptic Instagram posts, and garden parties. Everyone’s favorite vehicle for flexing on each other is a gigantic bronze sculpture of a fig. Love the fig, hate the fig, pretend indifference to the fig—it’s up to you. But one thing is certain and unavoidable: On this street, there is no such thing as neutrality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creature Feature: Meet Apollo, an incredibly persistent pup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863616</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/creature-feature-meet-apollo-an-incredibly-persistent-pup/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Krystle-Lee You may remember Apollo—a senior pup who was adopted from Great Plains SPCA six years ago. The team at Great Plains removed a benign mass from his hind leg and reunited him with his owner. In late October, Apollo was rushed back to our shelter in the midst of a medical emergency—an infection in his front leg,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Poore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLBTR Podcast: Yusei Kikuchi, The Aggressive Angels, And The Singer/India Trade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=832223</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/mlbtr-podcast-yusei-kikuchi-the-aggressive-angels-and-the-singer-india-trade.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T15:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest episode of the MLB Trade Rumors Podcast is now live on Spotify, Apple Podcasts, and wherever you get your podcasts! Make sure you subscribe as well! You can also use the player at this link to listen, if you don’t use Spotify or Apple for podcasts. This week, host Darragh McDonald is joined by Tim Dierkes of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off Must Alas Die, Die For Pâtisserie Week]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174465</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-not-so-great-defector-bake-off-must-alas-die-die-for-patisserie-week"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T15:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off, where Kelsey and Chris attempt to complete the technical challenges from the newest season of The Great British Bake Off in their own home kitchens, with the same time parameters as the professional-grade bakers competing on the show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Watching for snow on Saturday (WED-11/27)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3741713</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-watching-for-snow-on-saturday-wed-11-27/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T15:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With this colder pattern, two disturbances will be moving towards the region. One rainmaker and one snowmaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Is Everyone’s Problem, Even In Germany]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174545</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/donald-trump-is-everyones-problem-even-in-germany"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T15:19:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BERLIN — When Germans woke up on the morning of Nov. 6th, it felt like déjà vu: Once again the country had been on the edge of its seat following the U.S. presidential elections, with a qualified left-leaning female candidate losing to an erstwhile reality star turned right-wing political icon. And once again, there was the question: What now?
Germany's relationship with the U.S. is based on decades of economic ties, shared democratic values, and strategic cooperation on multilateral issues, particularly global security concerns. While a certain anti-Americanism has always persisted in Germany, especially since the U.S. invasion of Iraq in 2003, and German public opinion on the United States fluctuates significantly with whoever is president at the time, the majority of Germans consider the U.S. to be a key partner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luisa Rollenhagen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Your Questions Will Be Answered In This 2024-25 PWHL Season Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=173228</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/all-your-questions-will-be-answered-in-this-2024-25-pwhl-season-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T14:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was no big Defector-style Professional Women’s Hockey League season preview last year, because I was (shameless plug) a little busy reporting this feature on the league’s formation. But it’s also tough to preview an inaugural season. Ideally the preview writer is offering special wisdom, honed over many years, manifested in cute and knowing references. How could I do that with a brand-new league? It would have been the blind previewing for the blind—an insult, frankly, to your intelligence. Only now, after one whole year of PWHL fandom, do I feel comfortable sharing a preview with you, valued reader. Let’s see what the league’s second season might have in store. The games start Saturday.
The six teams are listed below in draft order, each entry highlighting a cool veteran and a rookie. If you’re new to watching the PWHL, welcome! At the very end of this preview, there’s an FAQ section with some extra notes, tips, and reminders of the rules. As noted in that FAQ section, the PWHL point system distinguishes between wins in regulation and overtime or shootout wins, so each team’s record is formatted in the following order: regulation win-overtime win-overtime loss-regulation loss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Soulful flavors at Lutfi’s Fried Fish and happy hour at Beer Kitchen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863575</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-soulful-flavors-at-lutfis-fried-fish-and-happy-hour-at-beer-kitchen/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T14:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lutfi’s // Photo By Tiffany Watts Lutfi’s When the craving for fried fish hits, there’s only one logical move: follow the scent of golden batter to the best spot in town. This time, my taste buds led me to Lutfi’s Fried Fish in the Northland—a local treasure that Kansas City swears by. With their reputation for crispy comfort food that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disney’s Moana 2 stitches fragments of a cancelled TV show into a lackluster unit-of-entertainment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=863558</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/disneys-moana-2-stitches-fragments-of-a-cancelled-tv-show-into-a-lackluster-unit-of-entertainment/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T23:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Disney Let’s start here: Moana 2 was initially meant to be a Disney+ series. This is helpful context to have in mind as you watch the sequel to the 2016 original, if only to temper your expectations. The follow up to Moana has nowhere near the same musical, dramatic and thematic richness of its predecessor, but it’s fine as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Royals throwback to 2015]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861763</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-royals-throwback-to-2015/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T22:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City Royals versus Arizona Diamondbacks on July 22, 2024 // Photo by Tarik Sykes Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Inaugural Black Feast Week rallies for Willa’s Books & Vinyl and launches new tradition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861604</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-inaugural-black-feast-week-rallies-for-willas-books-vinyl-and-launches-new-tradition/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T21:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Kansas City Defender Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Akins PC Repair’s Cody Akins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=862184</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-akins-pc-repairs-cody-akins/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T20:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Cody Akins Just when IT guru Cody Akins thinks he’s seen it all, along comes an even more insane computer issue to deal with. From cyber-hacking to waterlogged servers, Akins says no two days are even remotely similar at Akins PC Repair. “For some reason, computers have always come naturally to me,” he says. “When it comes to troubleshooting, very rarely is it ever...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Kendrick’s Party, You Can Cry If You Want To]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174436</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/its-kendricks-party-you-can-cry-if-you-want-to"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T19:48:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe this is my fault. For years, I've been begging Kendrick Lamar to lighten up a little. To stop with the hip-hop savior complex and the often incoherent political grandstanding. To stop treating music like a college level African-American history course and just enjoy himself. Well, that more or less arrived in 2024: the year of Kendrick Lamar. We've seen him battle and ultimately defeat Drake, put on for the West Coast, and work his way into being this season's Super Bowl halftime performer. To commemorate all this success, he has released a new album, GNX, in a surprise drop over the weekend that appropriately sent the internet into hysterics.
In a bit of irony that I'm sure is not lost on Kendrick, GNX is a party record full of earworms and radio-friendly pop records that, on the surface, more closely resembles something Drake would release than the sweeping artistic statements Kendrick has become known for. It is a victory lap in album form, ostensibly a showcase of Kendrick relaxing and having a good time. But there is something a little too empty about it for comfort. To paraphrase his words in "TV Off," there's a few solid jams on this record but it's not enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scandal-Ridden High School Football Powerhouse Removed From Virginia Playoffs]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174574</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/scandal-ridden-high-school-football-powerhouse-removed-from-virginia-playoffs"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T18:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hayfield High's season from hell is done. The Alexandria, Va., school's leaders tried adopting the winningest football program in the state from a school in another county and damn near got away with it. But Hayfield's messy 2024 campaign ended last night, just one day after intrepid local reporters published text messages from the school's athletic director indicating that Hayfield administrators had considered using "homeless" designations for out-of-district players in order to get around athletic eligibility rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Reads A Book Is Leaping Toward The Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174593</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-reads-a-book-is-leaping-towards-the-fire"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T18:21:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As longtime readers of this website would tell you, wildfires hold a certain morbid fascination for the Defector staff. As observers of the ice caps and fans of "going outside" would tell you, the medium and long-term future will both be infernal ones. The more I learn about the theory and practice of wildfire combat, forest management, and the history of megafires, the more fascinated I become. A phenomenon that seems inexorable and fundamentally uncontainable emerges, through the smoke, as a far more subjective problem. This month's DRAB selection is a famed nonfiction look at one of the most infamous wildfire disasters in United States history.
Norman Maclean published Young Men and Fire in 1992, 43 years after the Mann Gulch fire killed 13 wildland firefighters. From what I gather, the book begins with the disaster and radiates outward from it in pulses, getting into deeper philosophical territory yet holding true to the hub at its center. The New York Times review both refers to Maclean as a great artist and contains the phrase "cornball pastoral," which makes the book seem like turf worth mining. It is raining all along the West Coast as I write this and somehow we have avoided a catastrophic fire season for the third year running, which would seem to make a book about a summer occurrence an odd choice for an early winter DRAB selection. Great news there, though: The book also seems to be about the phenomenology of death. "There's a lot of tragedy in the universe that has missing parts and comes to no conclusion, including probably the tragedy that awaits you and me," Maclean, who would die two years before the publication of Young Men and Fire, writes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matheus Cunha Is A Wolf In Wolves Clothing]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174286</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/matheus-cunha-is-a-wolf-in-wolves-clothing"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T17:40:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wolverhampton Wanderers are a soccer club in sort of the same way that Silvio Dante's Bada Bing was an adult entertainment concern; technically it is indeed part of that industry, but the real business all takes place in the offices in the back.
In Wolves' case, superagent Jorge Mendes is to the club what Tony Soprano was to the Bada Bing. Since Chinese investment group Fosun International bought the club in 2016, the Old Gold has seemed to operate principally as a clearing house for Gestifute, Mendes's talent agency. This hasn't been the worst fate in the world. After spending about a decade and a half bobbing up and down England's top three divisions, with only brief spells in the promised land, the Mendes-puppeted Wolves quickly returned to the Premier League and have established themselves as midtable stalwarts for going on seven seasons now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JAWS and the 2025 Hall of Fame Ballot: Carlos Beltrán]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=451626</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/jaws-and-the-2025-hall-of-fame-ballot-carlos-beltran/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T17:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The center fielder with the great power-speed combination has Hall of Fame numbers, but his legacy is clouded by his role in the Astros’ sign-stealing saga.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Jaffe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[City Market Coffee takes on turnover with upcoming Murmuration Eatery and Cocktail Bar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861323</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/city-market-coffee-takes-on-turnover-with-upcoming-murmuration-eatery-and-cocktail-bar/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T17:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Murmuration Eatery & Cocktail Bar signage at City Market // Photo courtesy of Nikole Ammer The marbled teal and salmon floor of the upcoming Murmuration Eatery & Cocktail Bar in City Market emerged completely by accident.  Owner Nikole Ammer found the pattern beneath layers and layers of paint left by previous tenants. Realizing it fit the new concept’s copper patina...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dayten Rose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Easy Sweet Potato Brûlée Recipe For You, The Brûlée Lover]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174431</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/an-easy-sweet-potato-brulee-recipe-for-you-the-brulee-lover"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T16:52:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about flossing at your desk, Aaron Rodgers, college football QBs, and more.
Happy Thanksgiving, everyone! Before we get to all the fun stuff, I have a quick recipe if you need ideas for sides on Thursday. For medical reasons, my wife is on a low-histamine, zero-gluten diet (if you ever wanna lose weight, try being allergic to 70 percent of the nation’s food supply), which means that she eats a lot of sweet potatoes. This means that the rest of us in the family eat a lot of sweet potatoes, too. To liven up the proceedings one night, I decided to mash them up and bake them, with some (OK, a lot of) brown sugar sprinkled on top.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Be Sure You Are Reading Some Dumb Bullshit]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174368</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-to-be-sure-you-are-reading-some-dumb-bullshit"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T15:16:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever found yourself reading an article, and needing to stop halfway through in order to ask yourself an important question: "Wait a minute, am I reading some dumb bullshit?" The question is not always easy to answer. If the author of the piece is a particularly gifted stylist, or adept at persuasive writing, you might find yourself needing to spend some time unpacking their arguments and deconstructing their sentences before you can figure out if you are indeed reading some dumb bullshit. Other times, the question is very easy to answer.
Here's a tip that will allow you to immediately suss out dumb bullshit whenever and wherever you encounter it: If the phrase "to be sure" appears at the beginning of a sentence anywhere in the text, then it is likely that you have encountered some of the dumbest bullshit ever written.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Ley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: The 2024-25 Winter Forecast]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3740452</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-the-2024-25-winter-forecast/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T15:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOX4 Weather team Joe Lauria, Karli Ritter, Michelle Bogowith, Alex Countee, Jacob Lanier share snow predictions for upcoming winter season]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defector Watches A Christmas Movie: ‘Christmas in the Spotlight’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=174234</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/defector-watches-a-christmas-movie-christmas-in-the-spotlight"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T14:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the time of year when the best, biggest, and most ambitious movies come out. Not Oscar season, but rather that stretch when the halls of streaming services are decked with the brightly lit, thinly disguised advertisements that are the year's new Christmas movies. There are more than 100 new Christmas films to watch this holiday season, and whether that number horrifies or excites you depends upon how much of a freak you are for the festive. Sabrina is proud to say they are a real Christmas freak, and this year they asked some of their colleagues to watch some of the most, uh, available new holiday movies. The second movie in our lineup is Christmas in the Spotlight, Lifetime's adaptation of Taylor Swift and Travis Kelce's real-life romance.
Sabrina Imbler: Thank you so much for joining me in watching what might be the celebrity singer-celebrity athlete Christmas rom-com movie of the season. I came into this movie knowing a lot about Christmas, but relatively little about the real-life stars that inspired this movie. I would love to know how each of you started this journey. What are your relationships to Travis and Taylor and their love connection?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best of KC 2024: Ryan Reynolds flick IF features Simple Mischief Studio’s savoir-faire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=861748</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/best-of-kc-2024-ryan-reynolds-flick-if-features-simple-mischief-studios-savoir-faire/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T14:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Justin J Wee Earlier this month, we published The Pitch’s annual Best of Kansas City issue. You can take a peek at the results of the readers’ poll here. The issue also included a list, compiled and written by our editorial staff, of some local people, places, and things that we thought clearly won 2024. We’ll be publishing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>