<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2024-11-08T14:14:10.396Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End MLB Pride Nights]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172599</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/end-mlb-pride-nights"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T14:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than Freddie Freeman or Francisco Lindor or those Yankee jamokes who tried to rip off Mookie Betts's hand, I will remember the 2024 MLB postseason for the commercials. Specifically, it was impossible to sit through any game across the entire month of October without being forced to watch multiple Donald Trump campaign ads that fear- and hate-mongered about trans people. Here's an example, if you somehow missed them:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3xzybGKwIGk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Season three of Somebody, Somewhere embraces laughter, tears, and all things Manhattan, Kansas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858553</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/season-three-of-somebody-somewhere-embraces-laughter-tears-and-all-things-manhattan-kansas/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T14:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Sandy Morris/HBO For a low-key comedy actress, Bridget Everett sure does a lot of crying in the third season of HBO’s award-winning series Somebody, Somewhere. The show—set in Manhattan, Kansas—has seen Everett’s alter-ish ego character, Sam, tackle plenty of personal highs and lows over the past two seasons. Now, in its final season, Sam’s emotional arcs quietly peak… crater… and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 11.08.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077171</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/morning-docket-11-08-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T13:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Diddy's team unhappy that grand jury witnesses are talking, worrying that the publicity hurts his chances to Finna Get Loose. [NewsNation]
* Trump judge blocks immigration rule because the law allowing the government to choose to allow immigrants with citizen spouses to "into the United States" legally on parole while their status is processed couldn't support letting those people serve parole while their status is processed if they were already in the United States when the decision was made. It's like Textualism, but a game of Balderdash. [Law360]
* OpenAI wins copyright suit over using material to train the model on the English language. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Judge says his jurisdiction is just more sweary. [Roll on Friday]
* Trump was never going to get jail time -- if the judge didn't put him in a cell for contempt for his behavior during the trial, he was never going to -- but now it's pretty much certain that this will be an all cash sentencing. [New York Law Journal]
* It's a good time to be a partner who does deals that would otherwise violate the Sherman Act! [American Lawyer]
* Firm leaders still convinced that generative AI will have a big impact on the profession. [Thomson Reuters]
The post Morning Docket: 11.08.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC renters in tenant union enter a second month of strike against landlords]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=860317</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-renters-in-tenant-union-enter-a-second-month-of-strike-against-landlords/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T04:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Paige Eichkorn “NOT ONE CENT FOR THE SLUM LORDS!” “DON’T PAY RENT!” Tenants at Independence and Quality Hill Towers led chants and marched outside their buildings on Friday in protest of the Federal Housing Finance Agency’s redaction of their offer for a bargaining meeting with Director Sandra Thompson in Washington, DC. This came after leaders of the Tenant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paige Eichkorn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photos: Invicta FC 58: Ducote vs. Ostroverkhova from Memorial Hall]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859941</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/photos-invicta-fc-58-ducote-vs-ostroverkhova-from-memorial-hall/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T01:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Tarik Sykes On Wednesday, Nov. 6, Invicta Fighting Championships hosted Invicta FC 58: Ducote vs. Ostroverkhova from Memorial Hall. In the night’s main event, former strawweight champion Emily Ducote re-established herself as a contender with a submission win over Russia’s Yulia Ostroverkhova. Our photographer Tarik Sykes was there to capture the entire event: Categories: Sports Tags: Emily Ducote,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarik Sykes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Partner In Neighborly Dispute Drops Slur Using His Work Email — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077157</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/biglaw-partner-in-neighborly-dispute-drops-slur-using-his-work-email-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T00:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty Harsh Language There, Partner: Not a good look for Goodwin Procter.
Now That's A Smart Investment!: Billionaires dropped millions to get their chosen judges elected in Texas.
You Know We Can Hear You, Right?: Giuliani doesn't seem too torn up about his defaming.
There's A Lot Of Phish Out There: Watch out for this phishing scam!
Here's How To Manage The Career Bumps: Being an in-house lawyer isn't always easy, but at least there's help.
The post Biglaw Partner In Neighborly Dispute Drops Slur Using His Work Email — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Big Thanks To Our Advertisers]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077125</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/a-big-thanks-to-our-advertisers-21/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T00:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We love working with you.
The post A Big Thanks To Our Advertisers appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[<em>Survivor</em> Alum Makes Legal History]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077146</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/survivor-alum-makes-legal-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T23:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He's been pretty busy since his reality TV debut 23 years ago.
The post <em>Survivor</em> Alum Makes Legal History appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rudy Giuliani Is Exactly That Fool Of A Client]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077144</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/rudy-giuliani-is-exactly-that-fool-of-a-client/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T22:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Putting a microphone in front of 2024 Rudy? What could possibly go wrong?
The post Rudy Giuliani Is Exactly That Fool Of A Client appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Will Be Looking For ‘More Bold, More Fearless’ Judges In His Second Term]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077128</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/trump-will-be-looking-for-more-bold-more-fearless-judges-in-his-second-term/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T21:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moderate Republican judges are being urged to step aside to allow a wave of even more conservative, younger judges to be appointed to the federal courts.
The post Trump Will Be Looking For ‘More Bold, More Fearless’ Judges In His Second Term appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ECHL’s Adirondack Thunder Launch Special Jerseys for Military Appreciation Night]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83255</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/07/echls-adirondack-thunder-launch-special-jerseys-for-military-appreciation-night/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ECHL team based in Glens Falls, New York, goes with grey digital camouflage pattern for base of jersey; Viking in primary logo swaps out blade of hockey stick for American flag]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Beck and Bryan Woods’ holy terror Heretic casts Hugh Grant as a nightmare nihilist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=860356</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/scott-beck-and-bryan-woods-holy-terror-heretic-cast-hugh-grant-as-nightmare-nihilist/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T21:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When cataclysmic events happen — the kind that take time to recover from, if you recover at all — the first thing we reach for is explanation. What could we have done differently? Were we destined to end up where we did? If you’re a person of faith, you may wonder where God is in all this. What do your...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abby Olcese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creature Drops: A Big Baby From Patagonia]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172666</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/creature-drops-a-big-baby-from-patagonia"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Newsletterer's Note: Each weekday, I send out a newsletter called The Cipher to Defector Pal-level subscribers, which has a recap of the blog day, links to other sites, and extra takes and bits from staffers. (You can change your newsletter preferences or upgrade your subscription at the My Account page.) Today, we are inexplicably locked out of Sendgrid, so everyone gets a bonus bit from Sabs.
Also, an announcement: Defector Trivia is happening on Twitch today at 5 p.m. ET. I would have put that in the newsletter, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Money Changed The Texas Judiciary]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077148</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/billionaire-money-changed-the-texas-judiciary/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T21:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who needs justice for all when you could have corporate interests?
The post Billionaire Money Changed The Texas Judiciary appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Partner Drops Slur In Dustup With Neighbors]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077132</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/biglaw-partner-drops-slur-in-dustup-with-neighbors/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T20:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not a good look for the partner.
The post Biglaw Partner Drops Slur In Dustup With Neighbors appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Taste Of That Football-Shaped Bread, With Ray Ratto]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172582</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-taste-of-that-football-shaped-bread-with-ray-ratto"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T20:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are times when the lag between when we record The Distraction (on Tuesday mornings) and when it goes up (the first minutes of Thursday) is not to our advantage. But there are also instances, like this week, where it is absolutely essential. 
As frustrating as this can be, I think the very fact that this week's episode is a pretty straightforward football-and-Funbag installment of the pod, and not a morose reckoning with the horror and unknowability of this country and this moment, is a good thing. You'll get one of those soon enough, but for the time being perhaps I could interest you in something more along the lines of "Three guys trying to figure out what's wrong with various lousy NFL teams, as if they had no other care in the world." Also I got kind of upset about my co-hosts' bagel orders of choice, which is maybe small or ungenerous of me, but which I also stand by.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Case Management Platform Clarra Unveils Suite Of New Features, Including Gen AI, Analytics, And Tracking Of Client Communications]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077103</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/11/case-management-platform-clarra-unveils-suite-of-new-features-including-gen-ai-analytics-and-tracking-of-client-communications.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T19:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tech-forward approach makes Clarra particularly attractive for law firms looking to migrate away from older systems or avoid the pitfalls of merging incompatible tech stacks.
The post Case Management Platform Clarra Unveils Suite Of New Features, Including Gen AI, Analytics, And Tracking Of Client Communications appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week In Skeletons]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172577</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-week-in-skeletons"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T19:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are looking for some wonder and whimsy from the animal kingdom to lift your spirits this week—some uplifting tale of a shrew that is so small that it sails on gusts of wind, or a fossil of an ancient crab that had an exquisitely defined buttcrack—you have not come to the right place. Instead, I have two tales about dead people and the bones they left behind. Is it the news we want? No. It is the news we have.
Skeleton No. 1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Sipps: A new emo bar, Sido’s third location opens, and kudos to Kata Nori]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859838</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-sipps-a-new-emo-bar-sidos-third-location-opens-and-kudos-to-kata-nori/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T19:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art by Cassondra Jones Life in KC is pretty delicious. In fact, there is often so much going on that it can be hard to decide where to go and what to try. That’s where I come in.  I’ve curated this weekly list of events, openings, deals, and celebrations to keep you in-the-know. Cheers! Today’s Tip Have you ever wondered...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Sipple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back To Law (Practice) School: The Essential Skills You Didn’t Learn In Law School [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077015</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/back-to-law-practice-school-the-essential-skills-you-didnt-learn-in-law-school/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T18:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve got new answers to the ongoing test of law firm management strategy!
The post Back To Law (Practice) School: The Essential Skills You Didn’t Learn In Law School appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JARED CORREIA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Big Boy Sam Darnold Is Big Fun]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172590</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/my-big-boy-sam-darnold-is-big-fun"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T18:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew Magary’s Thursday Afternoon NFL Dick Joke Jamboroo runs every Thursday at Defector during the NFL season. Got something you wanna contribute? Email the Roo. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out,”through here.
Here are some Dad Facts for you. Sam Darnold is 27 years old, three years older than Falcons rookie Michael Penix. He became the youngest starting quarterback in post-merger NFL history after the Jets drafted him. He played for three different franchises in his first six seasons. His first head coach was Todd Bowles, who was fired at the end of his rookie season. His second head coach was Adam Gase, who is Adam Gase. His third head coach was Matt Rhule, who was fired early into Darnold’s second season in Carolina. And his fourth head coach (if you don’t count Steve Wilks, who took over the Panthers as interim coach after Rhule oozed back down to the college ranks) was Kyle Shanahan, who used him exclusively as a backup. His career was Ryan Fitzpatrick’s in miniature, with the proportionately diminished reputation to accompany it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embrace The Future: How In-House Legal Professionals Can Thrive By Partnering With AI]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1072595</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/embrace-the-future-how-in-house-legal-professionals-can-thrive-by-partnering-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T18:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For in-house legal professionals, AI isn’t just a buzzword.
The post Embrace The Future: How In-House Legal Professionals Can Thrive By Partnering With AI appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olga V. Mack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Champions League Format Actually Rocks]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172595</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-new-champions-league-format-actually-rocks"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T17:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As loyal readers of Defector know, I am never wrong. I've certainly never written an article that was eventually proven to be overly optimistic, overly pessimistic, or overly incorrect. Given my general infallibility, I come today to apologize for my first incorrect thought in at least three years: The new Champions League format kind of whips ass.
I didn't think it would, and I wasn't alone in that thought. When it was announced, my first reaction was that this would just make the group stage—now called the league stage—even more tilted in favor of the big clubs on the continent. Whereas before, these clubs could be thrown in together in a group of death—like last season's Dortmund-PSG-Milan-Newcastle meat grinder—now, my theory went, they would just be able to mop up on a diet of weak clubs to secure a spot in the knockout rounds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baltimore Ravens To Debut “Purple Rising” Alternate Helmets On Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83247</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/07/baltimore-ravens-to-debut-purple-rising-alternate-helmets-on-thursday/football/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T17:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Baltimore Ravens will debut their new "Purple Rising" alternate helmets during Thursday night's game against the Cincinnati Bengals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Has Come To This: A Derrick White Appreciation Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172593</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/it-has-come-to-this-a-derrick-white-appreciation-blog"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T17:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Derrick White, unglamorous secondary ball-handler for the defending champion Boston Celtics, does many things well. He's a knock-down shooter who in his eighth professional season is attempting a career-high 9.6 threes per game, or about 68 percent of his total shot output. He's a Tony Allen-level perimeter defender, a Danny Green-level transition defender, and among the greatest shot-blocking guards in NBA history. You might lazily describe him as a 3-and-D specialist, except that he is also a competent and quick-thinking passer, a slick and reliable pick-and-roll operator, and an artist from floater range. Through nine games this season he is giving the Celtics 20 points a night on 64 percent true shooting, and is averaging better than three assists per turnover, and is using just a shad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Thompson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Of Times, The Worst Of Times: Navigating The Emotional Roller Coaster As An In-House Lawyer]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076908</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-best-of-times-the-worst-of-times-navigating-the-emotional-roller-coaster-as-an-in-house-lawyer/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T17:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’re not just the company lawyer; you’re also a trusted confidant.
The post The Best Of Times, The Worst Of Times: Navigating The Emotional Roller Coaster As An In-House Lawyer appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lisa Lang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Warriors Are Still Doing It The Warriors Way]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172609</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-warriors-are-still-doing-it-the-warriors-way"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T16:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Golden State Warriors are evidently the dynasty that won't die. It is a dynasty that will age and eventually expire, of course, because they all do, and maybe this will all collapse in a heap of spent tendons and uncontrolled rage. But dynasties can sometimes linger beyond their rational shelf life; San Antonio's fifth championship came seven years after its fourth. And every time the Warriors seem to flatline—the 2024 season, for one example—they rise up and remember themselves. What they remember, specifically, is not really that complicated. When the Warriors defend, they are truly dynastic. It’s not as easy as they make it look, but it is almost as simple as that.
Their 118-112 win over Boston last night was a fresh reinforcement of that essential truth. Yes, many folks will be distracted by Steve Kerr having the carte blanche to yell at Stephen Curry after Curry passed the mythical 3,000 career turnover mark, but all that has been true forever; Curry turnovers, Kerr getting cranky about it, Curry not making a thing out of getting yelled at, and so endlessly on. Same as it ever was, same as it ever was.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is AI The Key To Efficient Contract Reviews? [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077088</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/is-ai-the-key-to-efficient-contract-reviews/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T16:32:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our friends at LegalOn Technologies share real world use cases on how legal professionals are transforming their contract review process. 
The post Is AI The Key To Efficient Contract Reviews? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LegalOn Technologies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri AG Andrew Bailey’s electoral victory foreshadows a civil liberties nightmare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859836</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missouri-ag-andrew-baileys-electoral-victory-foreshadows-a-civil-liberties-nightmare/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T16:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri Attorney General Andrew Bailey delivers a victory speech to supporters in Columbia after winning the primary election against Republican attorney general hopeful Will Scharf on Tuesday (Anna Spoerre/Missouri Independent) Andrew Bailey, the incumbent Republican Attorney General of Missouri, won his first election in a landslide over Democratic rival Elad Gross. This was expected, given the remarkable success of now-President-elect...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael McGrady Jr.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quincy Jones Was Greater Than Any One Era]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172447</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/quincy-jones-was-greater-than-any-one-era"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T15:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Quincy, the 2018 documentary meant to capture the totality of Quincy Jones's contributions to the last 70-plus years of music, film, and television, he spoke about his time living in Paris in the late 1950s and working under acclaimed composer Nadia Boulanger. "There are only 12 notes, and you should investigate what everyone did with those 12 notes," she said to him, as he explains in the doc. It was the lesson of not just the outward simplicity of music, but the lineage and vast worlds contained within its grand history. It was a call to be a student of the art, just as much as a player.
Jones, who died on Sunday at the age of 91, leaves behind an enormous absence in entertainment. He was the ultimate connective tissue in making the greatest media of the last few eras of entertainment. He orchestrated Count Basie's band when they played for Frank Sinatra. He composed the theme for Sanford and Son, and scored films like In The Heat of the Night, The Italian Job, and The Color Purple. He produced The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air, co-founded Vibe magazine, brought jazz and hip-hop together for his Back On The Block album. Off The Wall, Thriller, Bad—there is not one medium, genre, or business within entertainment that did not have Jones's hand in it. He was just as eager to teach the intricacies of making good music and art as he was to tell those ribald stories about Sinatra, Michael Jackson, or Prince. His death is not a surprise, but it is upsetting all the same, less because of what he's done and more because of how little the modern entertainment industry resembles the kind of place that fosters that kind of artistic talent and allowed him to thrive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert For Lawyers: Don’t Fall For This Federal Courts Phishing Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077129</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/alert-for-lawyers-dont-fall-for-this-federal-courts-phishing-scam/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T15:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Be very careful, lawyers, because your personal or client data could be at risk.
The post Alert For Lawyers: Don’t Fall For This Federal Courts Phishing Scam appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PWHL Unveils Jerseys for All 6 Teams Ahead of 2024-25 Season Start]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83205</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/07/pwhl-unveils-jerseys-for-all-6-teams-ahead-of-2024-25-season-start/hockey-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T15:42:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After team names and logos were revealed in September, jerseys hit shelves with just over three weeks until the puck drops on the 2024-25 PWHL regular season]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Admin Will Bring ‘Uncertainty,’ Opportunities For Defense Industry: Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077102</id>
        <link href="https://breakingdefense.com/2024/11/trump-admin-will-bring-uncertainty-opportunities-for-defense-industry-analysts/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T15:03:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘The makeup of Congress, and specifically the makeup of the House, I think will actually matter much more to the future of the defense budget than whoever the president is,’ said Todd Harrison of AEI.
The post Trump Admin Will Bring ‘Uncertainty,’ Opportunities For Defense Industry: Analysts appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VALERIE INSINNA - BREAKING DEFENSE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trying To Catch Up With Lael Wilcox As She Biked Around The World In 108 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172248</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/trying-to-catch-up-with-lael-wilcox-as-she-biked-around-the-world-in-108-days"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WHITEHORSE, Canada — I stood on an empty stretch of the Alaska Highway and squinted north as the sky darkened. I had parked a couple of miles away, at a relatively busy intersection on the edge of the Yukon’s small capital city, and pedaled north up a long hill onto this quieter stretch of road. It was just after 9:30 on a Saturday night. I waited on the southbound shoulder, helmeted and hi-vis-vested, watching for a cyclist.
When a black dot crested the next hill, my heart started beating a little faster. I turned, threw a leg over my own bicycle, and stood on my toes, checking over my shoulder as the dot coalesced into a woman pedaling steadily toward me. As she came closer, I pushed off and started riding, trying to get up to speed so she wouldn’t just blow right by.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eva Holland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 11.07.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077131</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/morning-docket-11-07-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T13:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Biglaw thinks Trump's next administration will be good for business. I guess they missed the part where his economic czar Elon pledged to crash the economy as part of the plan. [National Law Journal]
* We're already talking about Supreme Court shortlists as though it's not just the loudest mouths from the Fifth Circuit. [Law360]
* Remember polio? That was fun, right? [Bloomberg Law News]
* Jack Smith preparing to drop criminal cases against Trump before the new president has to pardon himself and potentially put a controversial constitutional question to the test. [ABA Journal]
* American lawyers in London report working 13-hour days. Which... is that not how all of Biglaw works anymore? [Fortune]
* Good news for the heroin trade, as Trump seems likely to turn the SEC over to the crypto industry. [Cointelegraph]
* What happens with Trump's state law issues now? [Courthouse News Service]
The post Morning Docket: 11.07.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spinning Tree Theatre’s musical adaptation of Bubble Boy makes for oddly prescient cultural commentary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859286</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/spinning-tree-theatres-musical-adaptation-of-bubble-boy-makes-for-oddly-prescient-cultural-commentary/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T13:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joshua Johnson as Jimmy Livingston (the Bubble Boy) and Jordan Rosenwald as Chloe Molinski. // Photo by Micah Thompson/Spinning Tree Theatre If you caught the 2001 Jake Gyllenhaal film Bubble Boy, there’s a better than non-zero chance you haven’t thought about it since. The cartoonishly over-the-top story about a boy allergic to the air is probably more closely associated with the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brock Wilbur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partner? More Like Buddy Of The Firm — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077100</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/partner-more-like-buddy-of-the-firm-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T00:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Is A Title Worth?: Nonequity partners cover liability without sharing profits.
UK Firm Is Closing Foreign Doors: Eversheds Sutherland is shutting its Beijing office.
No Thanks to DeSantis!: Monique Worrell is back in the big seat.
Utah Is Considering Its Options: A bar exam alternative may be underway!
Last Call!: Send in your final submissions for Above the Law's 15th annual Legally Themed Halloween Costume Contest!
The post Partner? More Like Buddy Of The Firm — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Impact Of Trump’s Second Term On The Federal Judiciary]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077087</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-impact-of-trumps-second-term-on-the-federal-judiciary/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T23:18:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Senate has confirmed 213 of Joe Biden's nominees.
The post The Impact Of Trump’s Second Term On The Federal Judiciary appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw’s Betting On Trump’s Presidency Being Good For Business]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077039</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/biglaws-betting-on-trumps-presidency-being-good-for-business/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T22:27:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’ll certainly be good for specific Biglaw practice groups, that is.
The post Biglaw’s Betting On Trump’s Presidency Being Good For Business appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Utah May Add A New Path To Practicing Law]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077086</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/utah-may-add-a-new-path-to-practicing-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who doesn't love options?
The post Utah May Add A New Path To Practicing Law appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sir Sam Alito Decides No Pesky ‘Constitution’ Governs Him]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077079</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/sir-sam-alito-decides-no-pesky-constitution-governs-him/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T21:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That Governing Document Can't Stop Me Because I Can't Read!
The post Sir Sam Alito Decides No Pesky ‘Constitution’ Governs Him appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Football League’s Adelaide Crows Flying High With Launch of New Logo]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83199</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/06/australian-football-leagues-adelaide-crows-flying-high-with-launch-of-new-logo/other/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T20:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New logo depicts full body of swooping crow — in stark contrast to previous version, which only depicted crow's head — with red and gold streaks in wings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VP Harris concedes presidential race in phone call to Donald Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859828</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/vp-harris-concedes-presidential-race-in-phone-call-to-donald-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T20:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vice President Kamala Harris delivers remarks Nov. 6, 2024, at Howard University in Washington, D.C., after conceding the presidential race to Donald Trump. (Grace Hills/Kansas Reflector) WASHINGTON — Vice President Kamala Harris Wednesday afternoon called Donald Trump to concede the 2024 presidential race, according to a senior Harris aide. During the call, the Democratic presidential nominee “discussed the importance of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ariana Figueroa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whether Your Candidate Won Or Lost, Don’t Blame The Election Results For Whatever The Stock Market Is Doing]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077019</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/whether-your-candidate-won-or-lost-dont-blame-the-election-results-for-whatever-the-stock-market-is-doing/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T20:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most stock prices do not react instantaneously to election results.
The post Whether Your Candidate Won Or Lost, Don’t Blame The Election Results For Whatever The Stock Market Is Doing appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Wolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Last Time Was Lucky]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172572</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/last-time-was-lucky"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:54:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter, examining the apocalyptic politics and coverage of Campaign 2024.
On the last day of vamping about opinions before the election became a fact, in a roundtable discussion among New York Times pundits, the respectable conservative David Brooks tried to turn to history to understand what might be coming. "Mostly I just worry about Trump's general incompetence," Brooks wrote. "We got lucky during his term, because there were no existential or complicated threats, until the pandemic."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Non-Equity Partners Are ‘Partners’ For Covering Firm Costs But Not Partners For Pay]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077082</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/non-equity-partners-are-partners-for-covering-firm-costs-but-not-partners-for-pay/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['Partner' isn't the deal it used to be.
The post Non-Equity Partners Are ‘Partners’ For Covering Firm Costs But Not Partners For Pay appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ultimate Fakebook and friends celebrated 25 years of This Will Be Laughing Week Saturday night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859497</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/ultimate-fakebook-and-friends-celebrated-25-years-of-this-will-be-laughing-week-saturday-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ultimate Fakebook. // photo by Whitney Young Ultimate Fakebook with Schatzi, Jon Snodgrass, and the Touchdowns The Bottleneck Saturday, November 1 Going to a show the night after Halloween when you and your wife went bar-hopping means you’re gonna be tired. But it’s Ultimate Fakebook, doing their penultimate show after playing their 1999 album, This Will Be Laughing Week, in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Surprising Insights That Will Change Your Mind About BI [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076989</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/5-surprising-insights-that-will-change-your-mind-about-bi/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:43:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on November 20th for this CLE-eligible webinar and learn how BI can revolutionize your law firm's approach to data, driving efficiency and informed decision-making. 
The post 5 Surprising Insights That Will Change Your Mind About BI appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Litera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Might As Well Believe In The Winnipeg Jets]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172565</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/might-as-well-believe-in-the-winnipeg-jets"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We open today's reading with Susie Dent's Word Of The Day. That word is “recrudescence,” and it means “the return of something terrible after a time of reprieve.” It originates in the 17th century, and lives in the 21st.
With that as our guiding rubric—always trust a brilliant lexicographer from another land to contextualize America's decision to put itself on Santa's Seriously Pissed Off List—let us now turn our attention instead to the best team in the National Hockey League, the profoundly Who The Hell Are They And Why Are They Doing This Winnipeg Jets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final Call For Submissions: ATL’s 15th Annual Legally Themed Halloween Costume Contest]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077081</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/10/atls-15th-annual-legally-themed-halloween-costume-contest/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you got what it takes to top the winners of years past?
The post Final Call For Submissions: ATL’s 15th Annual Legally Themed Halloween Costume Contest appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progressive State Attorney Thumbs Her Nose At Ron DeSantis]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077072</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/progressive-state-attorney-thumbs-her-nose-at-ron-desantis/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T17:12:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voters disagreed with DeSantis on this one.
The post Progressive State Attorney Thumbs Her Nose At Ron DeSantis appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to providing care, time is obsolete for The Pitch’s 2024 Best Budtender Damone Garrison]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859745</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/when-it-comes-to-providing-care-time-is-obsolete-for-the-pitchs-2024-best-budtender-damone-garrison/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T17:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Joe Ellett The votes are in, and the stage is set as The Pitch’s Best Of Kansas City picks have been announced. Across the community, there are countless individuals and institutions who have been crowned ‘Best Of’ in their respective areas. “Best Bartender” has been a popular category in the city for years on end. This year, its...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Ellett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is How My Brownies Turned Out]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172534</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/here-is-how-my-brownies-turned-out"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T16:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A frugal baker can also be an adventurous baker, in the sense that leftover ingredients from one recipe can be used as an excuse to try something new. I still had a bunch of marshmallows from the fudgy frosting I made for these decadent peanut butter brownies that use approximately one tanker truck full of sugar (they tasted spectacular; I will go to the hospital if I eat one more before at least 18 months have passed). I can use marshmallows in hot chocolate, but it is 75 degrees right now, so instead I thought of the one other use I know for marshmallows. I did a search for "smores brownies" and hit this extremely basic and simple recipe, which I thought would occupy my mind without providing any extra stress on Tuesday night.
Basically, all you're doing in this recipe is baking brownies from a mix and putting a bunch of s'mores toppings on it midway through. I'd actually never in my life used a pre-packaged mix before, but I appreciated the shortcut on this occasion. I baked it for 15 minutes, took it out of the oven, and added a very appealing collage of chocolate, marshmallow, and graham cracker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tackling Deposition Anxiety: How AI Is Changing The Way Lawyers Do Depositions [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076656</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/tackling-deposition-anxiety-how-ai-is-changing-the-way-lawyers-do-depositions/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T16:33:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Depo CoPilot is a cutting-edge technology laser-focused on helping you perform your very best at every deposition.
The post Tackling Deposition Anxiety: How AI Is Changing The Way Lawyers Do Depositions appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FILEVINE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bromance Languages 101]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172545</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/bromance-languages-101"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T16:28:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some college students plunge into parties, hookups and dates without hesitation, while some of us linger on the diving board, paralyzed by such questions as Sex: how? What is attraction anyway? And the classic Am I worthy of love?
But how are matters of the heart mediated through the sometimes delicate, sometimes volatile state of brohood? Could you leap without looking into a new romance if subtly pushed, or, perhaps, hit by a flying tackle from your most supportive bro? Can two college-aged bros survive a bond of mutual support without serious injury?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jae Towle Vieira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172537</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/after-tuesday"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T16:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I went for a run on Election Day. The streets near my neighborhood, normally clogged with cars dropping off children at an elementary school down the road, were mostly empty. Public schools were closed, and the same yard signs I’d been walking and driving past for the last several months—Trump/Vance, Harris/Walz—seemed, ironically, beside the point. In a country where the lead-up to a presidential election is excruciatingly drawn out, where, in this specific case, an incumbent head of state more closely resembling a corpse threatened to run for office again before bowing out at the last second, throwing the entire race into disarray, the eventual arrival of the day itself was lackluster. I drove to work, where I overheard murmurs from customers about how they voted, the increased police pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The First U.K.-Based Biglaw Firm To Shutter An Office In Mainland China]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077049</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-first-u-k-based-biglaw-firm-to-shutter-an-office-in-mainland-china/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another Biglaw firm closes the door on a Chinese office.
The post The First U.K.-Based Biglaw Firm To Shutter An Office In Mainland China appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Where's the cold air (WED-11/6)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3720601</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-wheres-the-cold-air-wed-11-6/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:29:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's feeling like fall for sure, but in the big picture of things, there really isn't much in the way of unusual cold coming towards the region anytime soon. Some transient cool air masses that will slip in and through rather quickly to be replaced with above average temperatures on the bigger picture of things. [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off Contemplates The Melting Method For Autumn Week]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172444</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-not-so-great-defector-bake-off-contemplates-the-melting-method-for-autumn-week"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to The Not-So-Great Defector Bake Off, where Kelsey and Chris attempt to complete the technical challenges from the newest season of The Great British Bake Off in their own home kitchens, with the same time parameters as the professional-grade bakers competing on the show.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsey McKinney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSC Napoli Brings A Little Bit of Japan to Italy With New Third Kit]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83192</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/06/ssc-napoli-brings-a-little-bit-of-japan-to-italy-with-new-third-kit/soccer/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:25:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shirt celebrates Naples' sister city of Kagoshima with blend of Italian and Japanese art styles and characters representing seven Bushido virtues down the right side]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why AI Governance Is The Number 1 Issue On This Health System Exec’s Mind]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077067</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/11/ai-healthcare-technology/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Hill, Ochsner Health’s innovation officer, said he goes to sleep most nights and wakes up most mornings worried about one thing: the state of generative AI governance in healthcare. To him, providers and other healthcare organizations are in dire need of frameworks to ensure their AI tools are safe and perform well over time.
The post Why AI Governance Is The Number 1 Issue On This Health System Exec’s Mind appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KATIE ADAMS - MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Saying goodbye to a legend, plus a visit to Thou Mayest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859691</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-saying-goodbye-to-a-legend-plus-a-visit-to-thou-mayest/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T14:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courtesy Of Anita’s Famous Rolls On my recent visit to Anita’s Famous Rolls, I was met with the cozy, nostalgic scent of cinnamon and freshly baked rolls wafting through the air—instantly transporting me back to childhood Christmas mornings. More than just a bakery, Anita’s is a heartwarming spot where tradition and a genuine love for baking take center stage. It’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Place Is All Fucked Up]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172500</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/this-place-is-all-fucked-up"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T13:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It doesn't appear to have been close. Georgia flipped for Trump. Pennsylvania and Wisconsin, too. The Blue Wall crumbled like Jericho's. Just about everywhere voted redder than in 2020. Young people went right. New York City went right. The polls said what they said, but then Americans went to the voting booth and said what they said, which is that they want four more years of Donald Trump. This feels worse than 2016. That was a squeaker, and you could convince yourself it was a fluke. The Comey letter. No Midwest Dem ground game. A uniquely unpopular candidate. Belief that maybe Trump wasn't being totally serious about the things he said, or might surround himself with smarter, better people. Maybe it was possible people were voting for Trump just to seize on an intrusive thought, a call of the void. You can't tell yourself these stories this time. Trump is a known quantity. We know what he would do as President, and we know all the things he'd promised to do as President a second time, and millions of Americans took all that into consideration and said, Yes, I want that.
What do you do in a place like this, with an electorate like that? You survive it, mostly, unless you don't. You will try to figure out how it got there, got so angry and stupid and cruel, so that you can nudge it somewhere else next time. You do this by seeing what went wrong this time. This seems like an impossible task this morning, because everything went wrong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 11.06.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077066</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/morning-docket-11-06-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T13:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* To all you public defenders trying to get criminal clients off... have you considered just winning the electoral college? [Guardian]
* If you're the worst student at your law school, but belong to FedSoc and want a federal judgeship, STAY IN LINE. [Yale Daily News]
* Law firms ask judge to dismiss "incoherent" lawsuit. [ABA Journal]
* Tug of war continues as voters reinstall prosecutor that DeSantis removed. [Bloomberg Law News]
* The firms poised to benefit from hitching their brand to the convicted felon rapist guy. [Law360]
* A fake money business isn't the height of professionalism? Shocking. [The Recorder]
* Cute! States seek to enshrine reproductive rights in their constitutions like that will matter. [NPR]
The post Morning Docket: 11.06.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missourians vote to increase minimum wage, require paid sick leave]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859794</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missourians-vote-to-increase-minimum-wage-require-paid-sick-leave/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T05:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Tucker, a leader with the Missouri Workers Center, teaches chants customized to an initiative petition to raise the minimum wage and mandate paid sick leave outside of the Secretary of State’s office building in Jefferson City in May (Annelise Hanshaw/Missouri Independent) An effort to hike the state’s minimum wage to $15 an hour and guarantee paid sick leave won...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clara Bates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Could Listen On Kris Bubic, Alec Marsh In Search For Offense]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=829962</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/royals-could-listen-on-kris-bubic-alec-marsh-in-search-for-offense.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T05:17:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals already knocked out one key bit of offseason business, re-signing Michael Wacha to a $51MM deal just before the veteran starter could discuss contracts with other teams. It seems they’ll now turn their attention to deepening a top-heavy lineup. Will Sammon and Katie Woo of the Athletic write that the Royals are looking for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri voters approve Amendment 3, overturn state’s abortion ban]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859766</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missouri-voters-overturn-states-near-total-abortion-ban/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T04:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maggie Olivia, a senior policy manager with Abortion Action Missouri, embraces abortion-rights supporters after the race is called in favor of Amendment 3 on Tuesday in St. Louis (Anna Spoerre/Missouri Independent). Abortion rights will be enshrined in the Missouri Constitution after voters on Tuesday overturned the state’s near-total ban. The Associated Press called the race at 10:30 p.m. with Amendment...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anna Spoerre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Josh Hawley defeats Lucas Kunce in Missouri U.S. Senate race]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859747</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/josh-hawley-defeats-lucas-kunce-in-missouri-u-s-senate-race/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T03:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senator Josh Hawley speaks to reporters at the governor’s ham breakfast at the Missouri State Fair in Sedalia on Aug. 15 (Annelise Hanshaw/Missouri Independent) OZARK — U.S. Sen. Josh Hawley won a second term on Tuesday, overcoming a well-financed rival in a state that hasn’t elected a Democrat to statewide office since 2018. Hawley led Marine veteran Lucas Kunce 51%...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Hancock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republican Mike Kehoe wins Missouri governor’s race over Democrat Crystal Quade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859734</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/republican-mike-kehoe-wins-missouri-governors-race-over-democrat-crystal-quade/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T03:25:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Kehoe, the Republican candidate for Missouri governor, thanks supporters as he steps onstage for his victory speech the night of the primary election in August (Annelise Hanshaw/Missouri Independent). Missouri’s next governor will be Mike Kehoe, a Republican who cruised to victory Tuesday night over Democrat Crystal Quade. The Associated Press called the race at 8:30 p.m. with 22% of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Rivas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They Let You Say Anything When You’re A Law Professor! — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077046</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/they-let-you-say-anything-when-youre-a-law-professor-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T00:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Professor Echoes Donald Trump's Message Of Peace: It rings almost as hollow as his skull.
Do It On Your Own Time: Fewer firms are giving paid time off to vote this time around.
That's Thinking Like A Lawyer!: See if you recognize any of the names on Kamala's transition team.
Not Worth Losing Your License Over: Learn from the ones who lost their licenses over MAGA.
Was The Fight Worth It?: Lawyer hit with ethics complaint after escalating their $550 typo.
The post They Let You Say Anything When You’re A Law Professor! — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gold Star Standard For Election Day]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077023</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-gold-star-standard-for-election-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T00:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don't be like Oklahoma.
The post The Gold Star Standard For Election Day appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supreme Courts Of Delaware And Georgia Act To Regulate Use Of Generative AI In The Courts]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076986</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawnext.com/2024/11/supreme-courts-of-delaware-and-georgia-act-to-regulate-use-of-generative-ai-in-the-courts.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T23:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courts continue to make rules about the use of artificial intelligence within the practice of law.
The post Supreme Courts Of Delaware And Georgia Act To Regulate Use Of Generative AI In The Courts appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Ambrogi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers, Take Note: Microsoft Offers Current Advice On Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076988</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/lawyers-take-note-microsoft-offers-current-advice-on-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T23:18:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These simple steps can be quickly implemented by lawyers at no or little additional cost.
The post Lawyers, Take Note: Microsoft Offers Current Advice On Cybersecurity appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharon D. Nelson, John W. Simek, and Michael C. Maschke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RNC Face Plants In Suit To Toss Out Georgia Ballots]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077030</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/rnc-face-plants-in-suit-to-toss-out-georgia-ballots/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T22:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it good when the judge says you failed in your duty of candor? 
The post RNC Face Plants In Suit To Toss Out Georgia Ballots appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Books You Can Read Tonight To Distract Yourself From Whatever Is To Come]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172483</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/books-you-can-read-tonight-to-distract-yourself-from-whatever-is-to-come"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T22:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one knows anything. Everyone claiming to know something is lying. The odds are 50-50, always, even if they say the odds are different. And though it can be a delicious hell to watch cable news and scroll on your phone all night, it does not make actually the election get decided any faster. In all likelihood, there will be nothing to know until well past midnight, if not several days from now. It is perhaps unreasonable to expect anyone who cares about this country to truly log off in any real way, but perhaps you can make your evening less miserable as the polls close. What if you could go to the bookstore and pick up something that would be gripping enough to stop you from watching Steve Kornacki zoom in on some random county that is behaving slightly differently than it did four or eight years ago? What if you could escape this mortal level of hell by entering your imagination guided by a sure hand? 
Well, you could try! The key to choosing a good book for election night is that it must be engaging, plot-heavy, and more desirable than your phone. You must be so mesmerized by what is happening that you are more invested in the next page than you are in the results out of Fulton County, which, remember, you cannot affect with your television-watching. This is both a high bar and a low bar for fiction to clear. Also: The book should not explicitly contain material that reminds you of the election, and it should not be so highbrow that if you check your phone every 10 minutes (you are allowed to cheat, and will) you will lose the plot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hundreds Of Biglaw Attorneys Staffing Election Protection Hotline To Help Voters]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077002</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/hundreds-of-biglaw-attorneys-staffing-election-protection-hotline-to-help-voters/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T21:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These lawyers understand how important it is to protect voter access on Election Day. Thank you!
The post Hundreds Of Biglaw Attorneys Staffing Election Protection Hotline To Help Voters appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attorney’s Response To A Zelle Typo Could Be A Stain On Her Career]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077027</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/attorneys-response-to-a-zelle-typo-could-be-a-stain-on-her-career/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T21:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would have never happened on Cash App.
The post Attorney’s Response To A Zelle Typo Could Be A Stain On Her Career appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Will Rageful Democrats Embrace Trump’s Message Of Peace, Wonders Dumbest Law Professor Alive]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077009</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/democrats-rage-trump-peace-jonathan-turley/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T20:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Turley explains how Democrats are REALLY responsible for heated political rhetoric.
The post When Will Rageful Democrats Embrace Trump’s Message Of Peace, Wonders Dumbest Law Professor Alive appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rudy Giuliani Wows Judge In Collections Case By Stripping The Apartment He No Longer Owns]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077017</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/rudy-giuliani-wows-judge-in-collections-case-by-stripping-the-apartment-he-no-longer-owns/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T19:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's distract ourselves from today's shitshow election with detritus from the last one.
The post Rudy Giuliani Wows Judge In Collections Case By Stripping The Apartment He No Longer Owns appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Influencer Guy Disqualified And Banned From NYC Marathon For Bringing Bikes Onto Course]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172443</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/influencer-guy-disqualified-and-banned-from-nyc-marathon-for-bringing-bikes-onto-course"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T19:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you are running the New York City Marathon, trying like hell to hold onto the group setting a sub–three hour pace.
You are ingesting disgusting energy slurry from gel packs, listening to Crazy Frog on your wireless headphones for motivation, and longing for your foam roller. You can feel sweat emerging from the soles of your feet. As you run north up First Avenue, you feel the ache set in, and you grit your teeth. You are off the pace, slowing, but you know you only have to endure 30 more minutes of pain. All of a sudden an electric Citi Bike, ridden by a guileless jackass in a yellow hi-vis vest, catches up to you, then a second electric Citi Bike, also piloted by a jolly dipshit in a yellow hi-vis vest, catches up to you. Through the throng of miserable souls, they are filming a hot shirtless man in tactical sunglasses, who is trying not to look at the phones filming him as he runs at 6:44 pace. You look around at your fellow runners to see if they are also seeing this trio when you drift ever so slightly into one of the electric Citi Bike cameramen, who sends you careening into the barriers and onto the deck. As you seize into a full-body cramp, you wonder what final product could be worth such debasement, and then you smile as you realize that because of the social media video content that ended your marathon, people will discover running and lead better, healthier lives. Your sacrifice was worth it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s The Big Day]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172411</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/todays-the-big-day"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T18:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It all comes back to the missed opportunity of 2016.
That year, of course, marked the biggest disappointment in the history of the San Jose Sharks—a loss in the Stanley Cup Final to the Pittsburgh Penguins. What could have been the culmination of nearly two decades as one of the NHL's most consistent franchises instead left Sharks fans hanging yet again. While that generation of stars still managed to string together one last push in 2019, which ended in Game 6 of the Western Conference Final, it's that failure eight years ago that continues to define San Jose's identity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Leans Heavily On Biglaw Attorneys To Staff Her Presidential Transition Team]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077012</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/kamala-harris-leans-heavily-on-biglaw-attorneys-to-staff-her-presidential-transition-team/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T18:43:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This lawyer knows that she needs attorneys to help her forge ahead should she win the presidential election.
The post Kamala Harris Leans Heavily On Biglaw Attorneys To Staff Her Presidential Transition Team appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missouri Election Day FAQ: What you need to know to make sure your vote counts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859598</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/missouri-election-day-faq-what-you-need-to-know-to-make-sure-your-vote-counts-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T18:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Months of campaigning and TV ad wars will come to a close Tuesday, as Missouri voters head to the polls to pick their next member of Congress, the state legislature and nearly every statewide office. The Independent tried to answer some of the questions you may have about voting in Missouri. What time do polls open? Polls across the state...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pitch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Officials say Missouri elections take time, but remain secure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859563</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/officials-say-missouri-elections-take-time-but-remain-secure/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T18:09:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A polling location in Jefferson City (Annelise Hanshaw/Missouri Independent) If the 2020 presidential election is an indicator, determining who the next president will be may not be clear on election night. Local election officials as well as Secretary of State Jay Ashcroft said that voters should be assured that elections in Missouri are secure even if vote counting takes time....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sterling Sewell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Bar Association Leaders Give Blunt Warning To MAGA Lawyers]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077011</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/former-bar-association-leaders-give-blunt-warning-to-maga-lawyers/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T18:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But will anyone listen?
The post Former Bar Association Leaders Give Blunt Warning To MAGA Lawyers appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Few Sends His Son To Slaughter]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172414</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mark-few-sends-his-son-to-slaughter"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T17:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Few, son of Gonzaga men's basketball coach Mark Few, has fond memories of hanging out courtside as a kid and asking his dad to put the walk-ons into the game. "Don't ever do that again," he recalled his dad replying in one instance involving a crowd chant for Rem Bakamus. Now Joe himself is one such walk-on. The redshirt junior has appeared in 29 games and averaged under three minutes per. With the Bulldogs up 36 points on Baylor in Monday's season opener, Mark Few reasonably concluded that it was Son Time.
"It might blow the roof off this place if Joe Few scores," said the ESPN commentator as Gonzaga set up its offense. Instead, Dusty Stromer's lazy pass was picked off, Joe hustled back on defense to get in front of Baylor guard V.J. Edgecombe, and the two of them collaborated in the clearest possible visual representation of "five-star recruit vs. coach's son."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giri Nathan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Sauce My Fried Chicken If You Suck At It]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172401</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/dont-sauce-my-fried-chicken-if-you-suck-at-it"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T17:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time for your weekly edition of the Defector Funbag. Got something on your mind? Email the Funbag. And buy Drew’s book, The Night The Lights Went Out, while you’re at it. Today, we're talking about Ozempic, sex with Muppets, Matchbox cars, chips and dip, and more.
Happy Election Day, everyone. Get out there and take care of business. And if you need something to tide you over as the returns come in, I’ve got just the thing. Your letters:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew Magary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fewer Biglaw Firms Are Offering Paid Time Off To Encourage Voting, Volunteering During Election 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077005</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/fewer-biglaw-firms-are-offering-paid-time-off-to-encourage-voting-volunteering-during-election-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T17:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter what your firm is doing, please do your civic duty and vote in today's election. Your vote matters!
The post Fewer Biglaw Firms Are Offering Paid Time Off To Encourage Voting, Volunteering During Election 2024 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A historic presidential race ends with Election Day: How did we get here?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859756</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/a-historic-presidential-race-ends-with-election-day-how-did-we-get-here/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T16:40:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vice President and Democratic presidential nominee Kamala Harris speaks at a rally on the Ellipse in Washington, D.C., on Tuesday, Oct. 29, 2024. (Photo by Ashley Murray/States Newsroom) A series of shocking events have rocked this presidential race as Vice President Kamala Harris and former President Donald Trump sprint to the finish line in the hopes of securing the nation’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shauneen Miranda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Employment Lawyers: See How Thomson Reuters Practical Law Can Bolster Your Practice [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076990</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/employment-lawyers-see-how-thomson-reuters-practical-law-can-bolster-your-practice/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T16:36:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A sampling of resources that will help you get up to speed quickly so you can practice with confidence.
The post Employment Lawyers: See How Thomson Reuters Practical Law Can Bolster Your Practice appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>THOMSON REUTERS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Eastern Conference Is 87 Percent Butt]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172404</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-eastern-conference-is-87-percent-butt"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T15:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We want to get this out of the way now so that we won't have to revisit it when everyone else weighs in with their turgid and superficial analyses of what is wrong with the new NBA season. Put simply, and to borrow a phrase from our Bakery Division, the Eastern Conference is made up almost entirely of warm, flaky ass. And it's going to stay that way all year. Now that's turgidity you can taste.
Now, we realize there have only been 108 games played so far over 11 days, which measures out to less than nine percent of the season. We know, too, that early projections do not necessarily indicate final results, as the gathering cadres of electoral fraud lawyers will make rancidly clear over the next several days. But the East has two teams, Cleveland and Boston, who are 15-1 and well worth your attention. The third best team at this moment by record is Brooklyn, which had to grind its gears audibly to hold off Memphis last night to get to 4-4. Memphis is also 4-4, a record that has more reasonably placed them in 10th place in the West.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Have To Change How You Think About Free Speech]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077007</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/you-have-to-change-how-you-think-about-free-speech/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T15:46:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's important now, more than ever.
The post You Have To Change How You Think About Free Speech appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Next storm in the line (TUE-11/5)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3718504</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-next-storm-in-the-line-tue-11-5/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T15:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a wet start to the week, additional rains potentially develop on Friday, but more than likely later Friday night into Saturday morning]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PBGH CEO: Transparency Is ‘Table Stakes’ And An ‘Expectation’]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076984</id>
        <link href="https://medcitynews.com/2024/11/employers-data-transparency/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T15:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview, Elizabeth Mitchell, president and CEO of the Purchaser Business Group on Health, discussed employers' challenges in accessing medical data, emphasizing the need for transparency and potential strategies to enhance their fiduciary responsibilities.
The post PBGH CEO: Transparency Is ‘Table Stakes’ And An ‘Expectation’ appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MARISSA PLESCIA - MEDCITY NEWS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Might Want To Know About Peanut, The Squirrel Star Turned MAGA Martyr]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172268</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/everything-you-might-want-to-know-about-peanut-the-squirrel-star-turned-maga-martyr"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T14:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just days before the presidential election, the death of a gray squirrel named Peanut has become a somewhat inexplicable rallying cry for some of the worst people in the country. JD Vance claimed at a rally that Donald Trump was "fired up" about Peanut's death. Elon Musk tweeted an unsettling AI rendering of a red squirrel (a different species) cloaked in Jedi garb with a quote attributed to "Obi PNut Kenobi." On Nov. 2, the House Judiciary GOP tweeted "Justice for Peanut." $PNUT is trending, and I refuse to learn what that means.
If you are a normal person, you might have not heard of Peanut and have no interest in learning who he is, in which case I wish you a peaceful and evolved day. But you are open to a light bit of brain poisoning in the name of knowledge, step inside, and let me explain how the saga of Peanut the Squirrel took over the internet and may or may not influence the 2024 presidential election.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Culinary Class Wars’ Is A Tribute To Getting Your Reps In]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172107</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/culinary-class-wars-is-a-tribute-to-getting-your-reps-in"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T14:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since their inception, food competition shows have seen very little real innovation. Most entries into the genre are variations on a theme, the stakes artificially raised through less time allotted, increasingly sadistic ingredient choices or semi-regular trauma dumps. There's something deliberately anesthetizing in this; in the same way that I know a Starbucks sous vide egg bite will taste the same whether I buy it in New Jersey or Texas, I know what I'm in for when I turn on Chopped or Great British Bake-Off or Top Chef.
At first glance Culinary Class Wars, Netflix’s newest entrant into this gastronomical pantheon, looks to be yet another of these variations. There are familiar elements at play here; two celebrity judges, mystery ingredients and seemingly rigged team challenges make frequent appearances. But by the end of the first episode, it’s abundantly clear that the creative minds behind Physical: 100 and The Influencer have managed yet again to create a reality show with an elusive secret ingredient: novelty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachelle Hampton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 11.05.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1077006</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/morning-docket-11-05-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T14:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* "Several Big Law firms treat nonequity lawyers as full partners for tax purposes" without giving them the share of profits the actual partners in the firm receive. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Texas loses bid to bar DOJ from sending monitors to ensure the state abides by voting laws. AG Ken Paxton -- who settled outstanding felony charges against him earlier this year -- argued that Texas was fully capable of keeping things legal. [Lawyer Monthly]
* Biglaw firms not as eager to give time off to vote as they were four years ago. [American Lawyer]
* Latham & Watkins sanctioned. [ABA Journal]
* New solicitor disciplined for making up emails... and without the help of generative AI. [LegalCheek]
* Supreme Court takes up challenge to Louisiana congressional maps or "the existence of the Voting Rights Act" depending on how much you want to keep it real. [Law360]
* The election may end, but uncertainty about Lina Khan's work at FTC will remain. [Corporate Counsel]
The post Morning Docket: 11.05.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KC Cares: The Learning Club tutors future teacher talent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=855150</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kc-cares-the-learning-club-tutors-future-teacher-talent/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T14:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volunteer tutors and students interact at sites all around Kansas City, Kan., as part of The Learning Club. // Courtesy Photo With teacher shortages looming nationwide, The Learning Club is doing its part to provide extra help for students and develop some homegrown teaching talent. The program focuses on helping children in the Kansas City, Kansas schools grow to meet...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beth Lipoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chicago Bulls Unveil United Center-Inspired City Edition Uniforms]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83183</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/05/chicago-bulls-unveil-united-center-inspired-city-edition-uniforms/basketball/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T07:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although the rest of the league isn’t set to officially reveal their City Edition uniforms until Nov. 14, the Chicago Bulls unveiled their new United Center-inspired design over the weekend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Lind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Independence’s historic Twin Drive-In movie theater to close after 60 years of screenings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859482</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/independences-twin-drive-in-movie-theater-to-close-after-60-years-of-screenings/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T04:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This morning, the historic B&B Theatres Twin Drive-In announced in a Facebook post that it will be turning its lights off permanently on Nov. 17.  For 60 years, the cinema has provided a variety of movies to the Kansas City area as one of the only drive-in theaters in Missouri.  The company took to Facebook to share the news, saying...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lane Rozin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Luck Trying To Get A Remote Biglaw Job — See Also]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076991</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/good-luck-trying-to-get-a-remote-biglaw-job-see-also/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T00:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want To Work Remotely? Well, you probably can't.
Biglaw Gets Fuzzy On The Lessons From Dewey's Collapse: Lateral partner guarantees are back, baby!
The Supreme Court Is Scary! But make it Halloween.
The Latest In The GOP's Election Nonsense: From Georgia.
Don't Speculate About Your Lawyer's Pregnancy (Or Anyone's): They'll tell you when they're ready, *IF* you need to know.
The post Good Luck Trying To Get A Remote Biglaw Job — See Also appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris vows to end war in Gaza during final Michigan rally]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859717</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/kamala-harris-vows-to-end-war-in-gaza-during-final-michigan-rally/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T00:19:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vice President Kamala Harris speaks at a rally in East Lansing, Mich., on Nov. 3 (Andrew Roth/Michigan Advance) Vice President Kamala Harris vowed during a rally of thousands at Michigan State University on Sunday that she would do “everything in her power” to end the war in Gaza if she is elected president. Harris said that “leaders of the Arab-American...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Roth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Department Of Justice Is Going To Be Real Busy On Election Day]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076985</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/the-department-of-justice-is-going-to-be-real-busy-on-election-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T00:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DOJ's election day schedule is intense.
The post The Department Of Justice Is Going To Be Real Busy On Election Day appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk’s Henchmen Testify There Was No Illegal Lottery, Just Good Old Fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076979</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/musks-henchmen-testify-there-was-no-illegal-lottery-just-good-old-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T23:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peanut the squirrel would be so disappointed. 
The post Musk’s Henchmen Testify There Was No Illegal Lottery, Just Good Old Fraud appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reminder: Stop Gossiping About Your Coworkers’ Fertility]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076987</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/reminder-stop-gossiping-about-your-coworkers-fertility/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T22:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not a good look.
The post Reminder: Stop Gossiping About Your Coworkers’ Fertility appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giants Loss Marked By Anti-Irish Playcalling]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172343</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/giants-loss-marked-by-anti-irish-playcalling"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T22:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why does Brian Daboll hate the Irish? 
Among the many failed decisions the soon-to-be-former Giants head coach made on what was a bloody awful Sunday for his home side, none were more noticed than Daboll’s bypassing extra-point kicks in favor of two-point conversions in the fourth quarter—not once, but twice. Daboll kept kicker Jude McAtamney on the sidelines, only to watch poor and poorly supported quarterback Daniel Jones muck things up both times, and see his team lose precious points in a 27-22 loss to the Commanders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, Trump Supporters! Just Who Thinks You’re Deplorable?]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076965</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/hey-trump-supporters-just-who-thinks-youre-deplorable/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T21:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How does Trump view your intellect as it relates to tomorrow's election?
The post Hey, Trump Supporters! Just Who Thinks You’re Deplorable? appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Herrmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOP Demands Judge Throw Out Legitimate Ballots In Georgia Because Of Poll Workers’ Error (There Was No Error)]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076973</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/gop-demands-judge-throw-out-legitimate-ballots-in-georgia-because-of-poll-workers-error-there-was-no-error/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T21:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They lost in state court. But what if you make the same argument in federal court while shouting EQUAL PROTECTION?
The post GOP Demands Judge Throw Out Legitimate Ballots In Georgia Because Of Poll Workers’ Error (There Was No Error) appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Dye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biglaw Lateral Partner Compensation Guarantees Are All The Rage Again]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076972</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/biglaw-lateral-partner-compensation-guarantees-are-all-the-rage-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T20:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dewey Know What's The (Old) New Hotness In Partner Compensation?
The post Biglaw Lateral Partner Compensation Guarantees Are All The Rage Again appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Rubino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The São Paulo Grand Prix Was A Wet And Wild Max Verstappen Masterclass]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172262</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-sao-paulo-grand-prix-was-a-wet-and-wild-max-verstappen-masterclass"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T19:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many reasons, the São Paulo Grand Prix is my favorite weekend of any in Formula 1. The track is the best, or at least my favorite, on the ever-more-bloated calendar, and its traditional position towards the end of the season makes it appointment viewing any time there is a semblance of a title race. Throw in the possibility for rain, given that the race almost always takes place in São Paulo's wet season, and the stage is often set for chaos, drama, and all-timer performances. The 2024 edition at the Autódromo de Interlagos might end up the most memorable weekend of all, if not for the pure quality on display, then for the sheer chaos that altered the schedule, upended the grid both before and during the race, and left the only man who could have won this race at the top of the podium, and within millimeters of another world title.
Let's start with that man, Max Verstappen. While last weekend in Mexico brought out some of Verstappen's worst impulses en route to a penalty-aided sixth-place finish that kicked Lando Norris' title charge and its corresponding narrative into overdrive, Sunday's race was Verstappen at his absolute best. That's not to say he had a great Sunday altogether; thanks to heavy rain on Saturday, qualifying was postponed to Sunday morning, under still wet conditions. Thanks to poorly timed red flag in the second part of qualifying, Verstappen was mired in 12th place for the start of the race, and a five-grid penalty, due to adding in a new internal combustion engine, pushed him further back to 17th. To make matters worse, Norris nabbed pole position, giving the McLaren driver hope of a not just a big points finish but also the possibility that Verstappen wouldn't get many points of his own, shrinking the drivers' championship gap further.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Athletics Officially Change Name, Introduce Logos for Sacramento]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83173</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/04/athletics-officially-change-name-introduce-logos-for-sacramento/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T19:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Oakland Athletics are no longer. The club officially announced today that they are now known simply as Athletics. The new location-less name will stick for as long as the team plays in Sacramento, which looks like it will be for the next three seasons before they move to Las]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Creamer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Elite Litigation Boutique Where Associates Gain Early Trial Experience And Learn By Doing]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076958</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/holwell-shuster-goldberg-elite-litigation-boutique-where-associates-gain-early-trial-experience-and-learn-by-doing/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T19:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Holwell Shuster & Goldberg is committed to developing the finest associates by putting complete trust in them at the earliest opportunity, allowing them to grow exponentially as litigators.
The post An Elite Litigation Boutique Where Associates Gain Early Trial Experience And Learn By Doing appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Political scientists lay out how abortion views could impact the vote]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859450</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/political-scientists-lay-out-how-abortion-views-could-impact-the-vote/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T19:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday, Nov. 5, is Election Day — the last day for Americans to cast their ballots. In 10 states, voters could reinstate or expand abortion rights, or add further protections. (John Partipilo/Tennessee Lookout) Political scientists and pollsters who have been studying attitudes on abortion since Roe v. Wade was overturned in June 2022 told States Newsroom that abortion has become...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sofia Resnick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of the classical cover song with the Vitamin String Quartet ahead of their Kauffman gig]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859433</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/the-art-of-the-classical-cover-song-with-the-vitamin-string-quartet-ahead-of-their-kauffman-gig/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T18:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vitamin String Quartet. // image courtesy the artist Instrumental interpreters of popular music Vitamin String Quartet have been making music for 25 years. Their classical versions of pop hits have not only sold a million copies, but also found their way onto the soundtracks of shows like Bridgerton, Gossip Girl, and Westworld. VSQ’s versions of songs feel timeless and, given...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Spacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working Remotely As A Biglaw Associate Is Sadly A Thing Of The Past]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076976</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/working-remotely-as-a-biglaw-associate-is-sadly-a-thing-of-the-past/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T18:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Associates were very successful when they worked remotely during the pandemic, but in-person requirements are the newest normal.
The post Working Remotely As A Biglaw Associate Is Sadly A Thing Of The Past appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women’s Pro Baseball League Set to Launch in Summer 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://news.sportslogos.net/?p=83168</id>
        <link href="https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/11/04/womens-pro-baseball-league-set-to-launch-in-summer-2026/baseball/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T18:27:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[League co-founded by Justine Siegal — first woman to coach a pro men's team and to throw batting practice in MLB — aims to ride wave of women's sports by throwing out first pitch in summer 2026 with six teams primarily in northeast United States]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Cook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raiders Fire Three Coaches For Lack Of Anything Else To Do]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172307</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/raiders-fire-three-coaches-for-lack-of-anything-else-to-do"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T18:23:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NFL is becoming weirder with every week. If you doubt that, let us present Saquon Barkley's airborne rear end as the first thing you see when he and it sail over your head. It's becoming too hard to keep up with all of the concussion-infused nonsense in this league, especially in a week in which two teams with one win on the season triumphed on the same day.
But then, just as your disorientation is threatening to swallow you whole, there are the Las Vegas Raiders. To call them a pillar of stability would be inaccurate, but damn if they aren’t reliable. Their gift for ass-backwardness (hello again, Saquon) is overwhelming, and after a loss on Sunday they defenestrated three of their most prominent offensive coaches—nine months after those coaches were hired, and nine games into the current season.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recent safeguards should quash efforts to overturn election results, experts say]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859442</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/recent-safeguards-should-quash-efforts-to-overturn-election-results-experts-say/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T18:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two election observers watch election workers at the Milwaukee Election Commission’s warehouse south of downtown during the August primary. The post-election period in swing states, including Wisconsin, will be closely watched as local officials certify results (Matt Vasilogambros/Stateline) Recent sweeping changes to how the nation handles election results should prevent a repeat of the near-constitutional crisis four years ago. For...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Vasilogambros</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How The Newest Supreme Court Justices Compare: A Look At Each Of Their Respective First Two Years On The Court]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076971</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/how-the-newest-supreme-court-justices-compare-a-look-at-each-of-their-respective-first-two-years-on-the-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T18:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overall, these justices reflect the ideological spectrum of the Supreme Court.
The post How The Newest Supreme Court Justices Compare: A Look At Each Of Their Respective First Two Years On The Court appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Adam Feldman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Keeps Voters Interested With Surprise Cameo Appearance On SNL]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076891</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/kamala-harris-keeps-voters-interested-with-surprise-cameo-appearance-on-snl/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T17:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[End the drama-la and vote for Kamala!
The post Kamala Harris Keeps Voters Interested With Surprise Cameo Appearance On SNL appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Staci Zaretsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Inane Questions with Grief Cards’ Madison Clark]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=858541</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/four-inane-questions-with-grief-cards-madison-clark/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T17:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of Madison Clark When Madison Clark quietly launched her specialized brand of sympathy cards late last year, she was hopeful they’d find an audience. Born and raised in Kansas City, Clark experienced a tremendous loss at 15 years old when her big brother Garrett was killed in a car accident at only 18 in 2008. Clark went on to travel the world, teaching in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mackie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Tech-Savvy GCs Can Overcome Governance And Productivity Challenges [Sponsored]]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076710</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/how-tech-savvy-gcs-can-overcome-governance-and-productivity-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T16:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA['The Modern CLO & Legal Ops Toolkit' provides a road map to excel in an evolving landscape. 
The post How Tech-Savvy GCs Can Overcome Governance And Productivity Challenges appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LITERA AND ABOVE THE LAW</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eagles Take One Giant Leap Backwards In Win Over Jaguars]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172245</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/eagles-take-one-giant-leap-backwards-in-win-over-jaguars"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T16:23:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hurdle only gained the Eagles five more yards, on a drive that ended with a field goal. But it was one of the weirder things you could ever see on a football field; until it happened, it wouldn't have even seemed to be on the menu. It will be in Eagles highlight packages forever. Early in the second quarter on Sunday, Saquon Barkley took a pass from Jalen Hurts in the flat. He juked one defender to pick up a first down, then spun away from another. Now with his back to the end zone, Barkley jumped into the air and over Jacksonville Jaguars cornerback Jarrian Jones and landed on his feet. It was a play that had Eagles color commentator Mike Quick screaming. “It was the best play I’ve ever seen,” head coach Nick Sirianni said.
Eagles beat reporter Zach Berman wrote that down the line, this is the play you will first remember from this game. That makes sense, and not just because the play was unique and incredible. When the Eagles honored LeSean McCoy at halftime yesterday, they showed some of his runs in the Blizzard Bowl. Nobody remembered that the Eagles trailed 14-0 in that game, or that they gave up punt and kickoff return touchdowns. They only cared that the Eagles came back to win 34-20, with McCoy rushing for a franchise-record 217 yards. (People tailgating yesterday will probably also remember that Robert De Niro and John Kerry were there.) The Eagles beat the Jaguars on Sunday, although what was once a laugher came down to the wire. Barkley's hurdle will be remembered a lot longer than that, and deservingly so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wacha Won’t Walk: Michael Wacha Signs Three-Year Deal To Stay in Kansas City]]></title>
        <id>https://blogs.fangraphs.com/?p=450260</id>
        <link href="https://blogs.fangraphs.com/wacha-wont-walk-michael-wacha-signs-three-year-deal-to-stay-in-kansas-city/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T16:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After arguably the best season of his career, Wacha will return to the Royals for at least three years are $51 million. A better writer would have figured out how to wedge a Fozzie Bear joke into the headline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davy Andrews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Nov. 4: Rock Group]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172254</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-nov-4-rock-group"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T16:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ll have a blast doing our Monday crossword. This week's puzzle was constructed by Adam Simpson, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Adam is a game designer living in San Francisco's colorful Castro neighborhood. When he's not making crosswords, Adam enjoys watching horror movies, playing Metroidvanias, and cuddling with his black cat named Rook.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Halloween House Of Horrors Channels Supreme Court]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076968</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/halloween-house-of-horrors-channels-supreme-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T15:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The true Courthouse of Horrors.
The post Halloween House Of Horrors Channels Supreme Court appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Patrice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Favorite Influencer Is In Her 60s]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=171965</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/my-favorite-influencer-is-in-her-60s"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T15:22:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heidi Clements jolted me out of a glaze-eyed scrolling spiral one night a few months ago. A typical video of hers starts with her bending over toward her camera and then stepping back to reveal her starting point, a bra and pants. Then she builds an outfit while a voiceover shares a funny or heartbreaking or inspiring nugget of wisdom, like "If you don't ask for what you want, you probably won't get it," and "You may say you have nothing to wear, I say: just get dressed. Even if you have nowhere to go, just get dressed. Even if you don't like how your body feels right now, just get dressed."
Clements has amazing style. It's androgynous and playful, a little punk, a little Stevie, California-easy with a heavy silver chain or a black leather bag. Her arms are covered in tattoos and she has a shaggy haircut I've been trying to learn to cut via internet videos. Her nose is pierced with a silver hoop and she loves a red lip. She's an influencer; she has more than 600,000 followers on both TikTok and Instagram and her manager's information is in her bio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Election Day Looms, What Trump And Harris Presidencies Will (And Won’t) Mean For Defense]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076950</id>
        <link href="http://breakingdefense.com/2024/11/as-election-day-looms-what-trump-and-harris-presidencies-will-and-wont-mean-for-defense/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T15:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While analysts told Breaking Defense a Trump administration would likely be a more unpredictable one, they also said that equally, if not more important, will be whichever party controls the houses of Congress where the defense budget is crafted.
The post As Election Day Looms, What Trump And Harris Presidencies Will (And Won’t) Mean For Defense appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VALERIE INSINNA - BREAKING DEFENSE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jaguars Junction: Week 9]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172261</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jaguars-junction-week-9"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T14:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you get to the stadium for the NFL game and suddenly soul singer Ronald Isley walks out to midfield. The lights go down and someone hands him a microphone. He strikes a pose and begins to sing: 
Hey Moo Dang, 
Sit and speak to me brother
You're moving too fast
Life is more than eating grass]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamilton Nolan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: More rain today and later this week (MON-11/4)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3717284</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-more-rain-today-and-later-this-week-mon-11-4/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T14:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drought breaking rains are still coming for the region over the coming days, including today as our system(s) output continues to create needed rains for the region. Many areas have had 1-2 1/2" worth, perhaps more a bit farther south of KC since everything started and today's rain will add to that as it moves [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Docket: 11.04.24]]></title>
        <id>https://abovethelaw.com/?p=1076959</id>
        <link href="https://abovethelaw.com/2024/11/morning-docket-11-04-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T14:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* Car crashed into law firm office Halloween night. Too bad it wasn't a DWI firm. [KOAT]
* Second Circuit affirms that "Thinking Out Loud" is not "Let's Get It On." You could say they didn't even see any Blurred Lines when considering their similarities. [Law360]
* Considering potential Harris and Trump judicial nominations. [ABA Journal]
* Another Biglaw salary bump... in London. [Bloomberg Law News]
* Law firm converting a bar into their new office. One stop shopping! [KTAR]
* Class action targets company charging big transaction fees for school lunch payments. CFPB already found that the company has charged parents $100 million in "junk fees." [NJ Law Journal]
* Eric Adams trial set for April. [Courthouse News Service]
The post Morning Docket: 11.04.24 appeared first on Above the Law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Above the Law</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cowboys Are In The Pain Zone]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=172233</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-cowboys-are-in-the-pain-zone"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T14:01:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the second quarter of their game against the Cowboys, the Atlanta Falcons faced fourth-and-3 from the Dallas 36-yard line. What played out once Kirk Cousins got the ball snapped to him was a pristine example of two interrelated statistical probabilities coming true at the same time. The Cowboys' pass defense allows the most yards per attempt in the NFL, and had given up the second-highest number of plays of 40 yards or more even before Trevon Diggs tore a muscle in his calf. Falcons wide receiver Darnell Mooney, meanwhile, leads the NFL in receptions of 20 or more yards. As three Cowboys defenders bumbled into each other, with Diggs raising his hands in disbelief, Mooney ran into a pasture of space and sauntered in for an easy touchdown.
That play was one of the many embarrassments suffered by the Cowboys as they lost, 27-21, and fell to 3-5. Their year is less than halfway over and they already have as many losses as they had in each of the past three seasons. The football Mike McCarthy's team is playing has him smashing tablets on the sideline, Ezekiel Elliott is only nominally on the team, and they have to play through a brutal schedule without several key players, including possibly Dak Prescott. The NFL's highest-paid player hurt his hamstring on a run in the third quarter and was quickly taken out of the game, leaving Cooper Rush to see out the loss. After three losses in a row, things are suddenly looking dire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smoke This Now: STIIIZY vape cartridges are now available to the Missouri cannabis market]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859247</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/smoke-this-now-stiiizy-vape-cartridges-are-now-available-to-the-missouri-cannabis-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T14:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Courtesy of STIIIZY STIIIZY—a cannabis brand that originated in Los Angeles—has recently expanded to the Missouri market. Popular for its vape cartridges, 12 different strains of cartridges are now in your local dispensaries.  Among the 12 strains are indicas Watermelon Z, OG Kush, Skywalker OG, and King Louis XIII, sativas Blue Dream, Super Lemon Haze, Sour Diesel, and Strawberry...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Ellett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOP outrage sparked Missouri decision to make it harder to change gender on licenses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=859462</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/gop-outrage-sparked-missouri-decision-to-make-it-harder-to-change-gender-on-licenses/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T13:24:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wayne Wallingford, the director of the Missouri Department of Revenue, speaks to reporters in December 2021 (photo: Missouri Governor’s Office) The emails started showing up on Aug. 1 into the inboxes of Missouri Department of Revenue officials, signaling growing outrage from GOP officials over what they were seeing on social media. A transgender woman in Ellisville was using the women’s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Annelise Hanshaw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Michael Wacha To Three-Year Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=829045</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/11/royals-sign-michael-wacha-to-three-year-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T05:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced this afternoon that they’ve signed right-hander Michael Wacha to a three-year contract with a club option for the 2028 season. Wacha will earn $18MM in each of the 2025 and 2026 seasons and then at least $14MM in 2027, with another $4MM available in incentive bonuses. The $14MM club option for 2028…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Deeds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>