<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-01-02T06:22:11.974Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do You Win When You Compete With Yourself?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176544</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/how-do-you-win-when-you-compete-with-yourself"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T18:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The good thing about hinging some degree of your mental health on working out is that you can almost always exercise; the bad thing about hinging some degree of your mental health on working out is that you can almost always exercise. 
This story of hubris starts in January, when I was climbing in the gym and my finger—and this is not a medical term, but it is the most accurate way I can describe the process—exploded. Perched near the top of the wall, my left hand curled around a sloping hunk of white plastic and my right pulling hand on a wallet-thick crimp oriented sideways, I unmoored my left to swing it over to a larger white hold, bearing all my body weight for a long second or two on my tensed right hand. The tension violently and suddenly resolved itself; by which I mean a tendon in my right ring finger snapped.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Major winter storm potential increases (WED-2025)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3776402</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-major-winter-storm-potential-increases-wed-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T18:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year! 2024 will go down as the 16th warmest year in KC weather record history...records go back about 135 years...and the 58th driest year with 34.63" of moisture. It was memorable in some ways too...including the increase in severe weather and tornadoes in the region, some of the big ups and downs, and [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Was Wrong About Diet Coke]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176331</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-was-wrong-about-diet-coke"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T16:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was in college, I declared Diet Coke my enemy. My reason was the only good reason to declare anything an enemy: someone wrote a bad blog about it. 
Some girl I didn’t know published an op-ed in the school newspaper counting all the reasons she was truly, deeply devoted to Diet Coke. It wasn’t serious, but it pissed me off so much I started fights with girls in my sorority kitchen over it. Couldn’t they see that she was making all of us look like idiots by publishing something like this?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dish & Drink KC: Northland coziness at BC Bistro and Renegade Coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866069</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/dish-drink-kc-northland-coziness-at-bc-bistro-and-renegade-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T14:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BC Bistro BC Bistro was the perfect spot for a casual lunch with my mom and daughter. The ambiance felt effortlessly festive, with a cozy, holiday-inspired touch that made the space warm and inviting without going overboard. The service was just as welcoming—attentive and efficient, with hot, fresh food arriving at our table right on time. We started with the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Horrible Things Did We Do To Our Penises Last Year?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=175085</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/what-horrible-things-did-we-do-to-our-penises-last-year-5"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T14:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy new year to one and all. Make a resolution never to do any of these things.
All descriptions are taken verbatim from the U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission’s database of emergency room visits:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barry Petchesky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNS3 – network simulator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140312</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gns3-network-simulator/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T09:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Graphical Network Simulator-3 (GNS3) is software that allows users to emulate, configure, test, and troubleshoot virtual and real networks.
The post GNS3 – network simulator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skew-T Log-P]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3032/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3032/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managers & Top Front Office Executives On Expiring Contracts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=836143</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2024/12/managers-top-front-office-executives-on-expiring-contracts-6.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T18:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several teams don’t publicize contract details for their top front office executives or even for their managers, so this list of skipper and execs (any head of a baseball operations department, whether titled as a president of baseball ops, general manager, chief baseball officer, etc.) entering the final year of their deals may not be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oh Hey, Agave!: Erica Schulte of Rose Productions puts on a spirited event in Crossroads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=866031</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/oh-hey-agave-erica-schulte-of-rose-productions-puts-on-a-spirited-event-in-crossroads/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T17:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh Hey, Agave! // Courtesy of Vanessa Rao Earlier this month, I slipped away to an agave oasis in the heart of Kansas City at Oh Hey, Agave!, a unique event hosted by Rose Productions. Held at No Vacancy Guesthouse and Gathering Place, this intimate soirée was all about tequila, mezcal, and community. The event offered a chance to taste...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiffany Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Software: November and December 2024 Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=139880</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-software-november-december-2024-updates/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November and December 2024 updates to the largest compilation of recommended free and open source software available for Linux.
The post Best Free and Open Source Software: November and December 2024 Updates appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Best Free and Open Source Text-Based Spotify Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=95478</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-text-based-spotify-clients/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T15:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These text-based Spotify clients lets you enjoy Spotify streaming without using the semi-official bloated app.
The post 7 Best Free and Open Source Text-Based Spotify Clients appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jimmy Carter Was The Iron Man Of Hospice]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177446</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/jimmy-carter-was-the-iron-man-of-hospice"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T15:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jimmy Carter was a good dude.
Back to me: In the summer of 2023, I pitched a story about Jimmy Carter outliving his hospice welcome. Carter, the former president who died Sunday at 100 years old, had been in hospice for about six months when I made my pitch, and somehow seemed to be getting stronger in palliative care. I’d lived long enough and had enough personal experience with hospice to know that dying is the most stressful situation you’ll ever inflict on those around you. I hadn’t personally known any hospice enrollee to live anywhere near that long after going in; the lengthiest hospice stay I knew about was my buddy’s dad who lasted just under two weeks, and even that left the family feeling so beaten down they’d have all volunteered to put a pillow over his head to get it over with. Carter’s six-month run seemed downright cruel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[faint – extensible TUI fuzzy file explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140301</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/faint-extensible-tui-fuzzy-file-explorer/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T15:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[faint is a fuzzy file explorer for the CLI that supports various extensible features.
The post faint – extensible TUI fuzzy file explorer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Rumors of a snowstorm (12/31)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3775649</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-rumors-of-a-snowstorm-12-31/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T15:22:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It started yesterday...big bad graphics from some sources on the internet, on social media, and elsewhere...big maps with big snow accumulations over the weekend. All because of a storm some 4000 miles away, if not more, moving through the northern Pacific Ocean that potentially could impact us at some point over the weekend. I got [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Miriway – Mir based Wayland compositor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140299</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/miriway-mir-based-wayland-compositor/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T15:15:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miriway is a starting point for creating a Wayland based desktop environment using Mir.
The post Miriway – Mir based Wayland compositor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware The Vacation Fedora]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176648</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/beware-the-vacation-fedora"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T15:14:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hats are a relatively indiscriminate fashion choice. For starters, you can buy them at gas stations, when we all know the only things you buy at gas stations are gas and Tic-Tacs to combat the taste of the gas. There is no real standard for owning or wearing a hat as long as the owner has a head, just as long as it isn't a visor. Visors are the most pointless of affectations, as George Carlin pointed out decades ago and Steve Spurrier ran into the ground. Visors aren't hats. Visors are a board with a strap on the back. The only way a visor could be a worse idea is if the wearer were actually bald.
Everything else from toques to berets to the nattiest or rattiest ballcap are on fashion scholarship, as they work as both a utilitarian and fashion choice depending on the logo on the front—except the Yankees and Red Sox. As Comrade Xu pointed out, those are enforced choices based on lack of selection. The wearer can rise or fall based on the logo involved (extra credit for old, defunct teams like the Montreal Expos or Fort Wayne Kekiongas), but the base line is "fine, whatever."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[rxfetch – minimal but geeky fetch utility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140296</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/rxfetch-minimal-geeky-fetch-utility/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T14:57:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[rxfetch is a custom system fetching tool written in a Bash script. 
The post rxfetch – minimal but geeky fetch utility appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotifatius – simple Spotify CLI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140281</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/spotifatius-simple-spotify-cli/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T14:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spotify + status + some Latin = Spotifatius
The post Spotifatius – simple Spotify CLI appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible-Coconut – Linux distro dedicated to accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140288</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/accessible-coconut-linux-distro-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T11:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible-Coconut (AC) is a community driven Linux distribution which is completely accessible for persons with visual impairments.
The post Accessible-Coconut – Linux distro dedicated to accessibility appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[transgender – minimalistic terminal file explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140268</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/transgender-minimalistic-terminal-file-explorer/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T08:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[transgender is a minimalistic TUI file explorer with minimal dependencies, written by a Ranger hater.
The post transgender – minimalistic terminal file explorer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[zpotify – CLI for controlling Spotify playback]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140275</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/zpotify-cli-spotify/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T06:41:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[zpotify is a CLI for controlling Spotify playback and much more.
The post zpotify – CLI for controlling Spotify playback appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SrTemplate – string template system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140264</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/srtemplate-string-template-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T05:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mr. strings template (SrTemplate) is a library that allows you to render just text templates. It's written in Rust.
The post SrTemplate – string template system appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Things We Ate In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177408</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-best-things-we-ate-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T18:36:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is what the Defector staff enjoyed eating in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Defector Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Defector Pals Attempt ‘The Artist’s Way’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=176828</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/your-defector-pals-attempt-the-artists-way"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T18:10:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you harbor secret creative dreams for the new year? Do you miss the way it felt to make things just for the sake of it, without any care for how good or commercially viable it was? Maybe you’ve never considered yourself an artist, but there’s a tinge of discontent you can’t escape in your daily life.
I have great news for you: Some Defector staffers are going to do The Artist’s Way together, and we’d love for you to join us.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Sujong Laughlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Microsoft Disk Cleanup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140137</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-microsoft-disk-cleanup/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T18:06:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Disk Cleanup is a computer maintenance utility designed to free up disk space. We recommend the best free and open source alternatives.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Microsoft Disk Cleanup appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Wrestling Matches I Liked In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=175972</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/some-wrestling-matches-i-liked-in-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T17:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a concerning year. WWE continued to enlarge and enrich itself even as it failed to honestly reckon with the legacy of Vince McMahon. AEW—once an avatar of hope and change—took a creative and cultural nosedive. The Japanese scene is economically hamstrung and can't keep its top talents from moving to the States. It all combined for perhaps the worst non-COVID year for a wrestling fan since the widespread adoption of internet streaming. I look around and I crave a spark—an inspiring rivalry like Kobashi-Misawa, Punk-Joe, or Omega-Okada that lights a better path forward.
With that pessimism in mind, I picked 10 matches from 10 promotions this year, instead of the 15 I struggled to narrow down in 2022 and 2023. But I liked them, and I think you should check them out, because I got out of them what I still get out of great wrestling: excitement, astonishment, joy. Here they are, in chronological order:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Theisen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Dec. 30: Out Of Office (Themeless)]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177258</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-dec-30-out-of-office-themeless"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T16:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time to to wrap up the month with a challenging themeless. Keep an eye out for tricky clues and fun wordplay. This puzzle was constructed by Evan Mulvihill, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Evan is a cruciverbalist living in San Francisco. His crosswords have been published by the Wall Street Journal and Los Angeles Times, and will be appearing in the New York Times sometime in the next year or two. When he's not working as a pharmacist at Zuckerberg San Francisco General Hospital, he enjoys attending gay ski weeks, "doing it live," and creating Spotify playlists with titles like "Extra Chill Vibes ✨ONLY✨." He puts out crosswords that attempt to slap, chew, tear, and eat, on his blog FlossWords. Collab? 
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Fancy Little Mocktail Was Missing More Than Booze]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=175821</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/my-fancy-little-mocktail-was-missing-more-than-booze"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T15:19:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I stopped drinking alcohol in June 2023, a decision that was long overdue and has since improved my life unconditionally—congratulations to me! And yet stopping drinking did in no way quench my urge to drink, because that's not how addiction works. In fact, I felt thirstier than ever and fiending for something to glug at a bar or a house party and pretend I was still a younger, more foolish version of myself. So I turned to mocktails, because that's what was increasingly advertised on the menus and on the subways and in a slew of articles and books. People were paying $14 for a Phony Negroni® at the shadowy pizza place down the street, so why shouldn't I?
My first foray in mocktails happened in 2016, during a six-month dry spell when I was on a course of the acne drug Accutane. The dive bars I went to with friends didn't yet have a trendy fleet of non-alcoholic drinks, and I was mostly too scared to make a bartender feel put upon by asking for an off-the-menu mocktail. (I did try this once in an attempt to flirt with the bartender and promptly received a Shirley Temple, which I didn't not enjoy but also made me feel like a child with no game.) Sodas were a no-go because of the caffeine, and plain seltzer made me wonder if bubbles were worth paying up to $3 for water. After some trial and error, I settled on a DIY mocktail I called spicy drink: I'd order seltzer with pineapple juice and douse it with hot sauce that I carried in my bag. The resulting concoction was sweet and sizzly, vaguely reminiscent of some of my favorite tequila drinks, although I would never serve it to anyone else. I made it work with spicy drink because I knew in a few months I'd be back in the saddle, reunited with my beloved tequila soda.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabrina Imbler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Cold...colder...coldest (MON-12/30)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3774971</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-cold-colder-coldest-mon-12-30/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T15:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today will likely be the last mildish day for the next couple of weeks at least (although Thursday may not be too bad) as a significant pattern shift will be starting and ushering in likely the cold air we've seen around these parts since last January. With the cold, chances of snow with be showing [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Best Free and Open Source JavaScript-Based Web Content Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=91754</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-javascript-web-content-management-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T06:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are our favorite JavaScript-based web content management systems. They are all free and open source software.
The post 6 Best Free and Open Source JavaScript-Based Web Content Management Systems appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gg – TUI for small offline games]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140252</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gg-tui-small-offline-games/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T06:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[gg is a small collection of games that you can play in your terminal.
The post gg – TUI for small offline games appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Capsule Instructions]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3031/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3031/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Rodgers Incapable Of Throwing Even One Touchdown Pass]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177374</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/aaron-rodgers-incapable-of-throwing-even-one-touchdown-pass"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T23:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been said many times before, across many different eras, but that doesn't make it any less true: The New York Jets always find new ways to humiliate themselves. Regardless of the circumstances, they really can take any setup and provide it with a proper punchline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Gumbel Kept It All In Perspective]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177365</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/greg-gumbel-kept-it-all-in-perspective"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T23:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Greg Gumbel was named host of the CBS NFL pregame show in 1990, he was viewed as a departure for the network. Brent Musberger had been host of The NFL Today for the past 15 years, and a lot of people were tired of his shtick. He dominated the show, and much of the network's sports coverage. Reporters wondered whether Gumbel, who had previously called NFL games and hosted NCAA men’s basketball tournament coverage for CBS, would be another preempting pregame personality.
He wasn’t, instead guiding the show in a lower key. Gumbel hosted in the studio with Terry Bradshaw, while Lesley Visser and Pat O’Brien handled features. The new host wanted to be the conductor, not the star. “If Terry stars on that show,” Gumbel told the AP right before starting, “then I’ll have done my job.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL Schedule Creep Is Getting Out Of Control]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177346</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/nfl-schedule-creep-is-getting-out-of-control"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T20:02:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Christmas showcase, the Black Friday game, the doubled-up Monday Night Football experience, the possibility of RedZone introducing commercials—the NFL realized that it didn't have to stick to three days per week, and it could be as ubiquitous and greedy as it wants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[screenFetch – Bash information tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140247</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/screenfetch-bash-information-tool/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T19:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[screenFetch is a handy Bash script that can be used to generate one of those nifty terminal theme information and ASCII distribution logos.
The post screenFetch – Bash information tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PakOS – Debian-based Linux distribution from Pakistan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140222</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pakos-debian-based-linux-distribution-pakistan/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T18:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PakOS is a Debian-based Linux distribution which bills itself as reasonably secure. It's designed to be light on resources. 
The post PakOS – Debian-based Linux distribution from Pakistan appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to popular CLI tools: tar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=105947</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alternatives-popular-cli-tools-tar/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T17:56:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We showcase free and open source alternatives to tar, the most widely used archiving utility in Linux systems.
The post Alternatives to popular CLI tools: tar appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magnus Carlsen Quits Chess Tournament Over Jeans Violation]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177351</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/magnus-carlsen-quits-chess-tournament-over-jeans-violation"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T17:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This past Friday, Magnus Carlsen left his lunch meeting and headed to the second day of the World Rapid Chess Championship. He said he changed beforehand, putting on a blazer over a button-front shirt. He changed his shoes, too. Crucially, he didn’t change out of the jeans he was wearing.
Carlsen told the Chess YouTube show Take Take Take that he was in a rush to make it to the tournament. He got there in time, but his pants got him into trouble: Jeans are not allowed, per the International Chess Federation's dress code. FIDE said in a statement later that jeans are “explicitly prohibited under long-standing regulations for this event,” adding that the rules are “designed to ensure professionalism and fairness for all participants.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cam Ward Tarnishes The Sanctity Of Bowl Game Sponsored By Toaster Pastry]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=177334</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cam-ward-tarnishes-the-sanctity-of-bowl-game-sponsored-by-toaster-pastry"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T14:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Select portions of the college football world were outraged—big shock there—by Miami quarterback Cam Ward's decision to play only the first half of Saturday's bowl game sponsored by a toaster pastry. In this exhibition, the Hurricanes ended up losing to Iowa State, 42-41.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samer Kalaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[fex – command-line file explorer prioritizing quick navigation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140108</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/fex-command-line-file-explorer-prioritizing-quick-navigation/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T10:22:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[fex is a command-line file explorer inspired by Vim, exa and fzf, built with quick exploration and navigation in mind.
The post fex – command-line file explorer prioritizing quick navigation appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[18 Best Free and Open Source Personal Finance Software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=83790</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-personal-finance-software/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T08:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We focus on the best personal finance software for Linux. We only feature open source goodness.
The post 18 Best Free and Open Source Personal Finance Software appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[stagen – wlroots-based wayland compositor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140193</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/stagen-wlroots-based-wayland-compositor/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T08:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[stagen is a simple experimental wlroots-based wayland compositor.
The post stagen – wlroots-based wayland compositor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Best Free and Open Source non-GTK non-Qt File Managers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=127276</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-non-gtk-non-qt-file-managers/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T06:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many graphical non-Qt and non-Gtk file managers available. This article examines 11 such file managers.
The post 11 Best Free and Open Source non-GTK non-Qt File Managers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[tere – terminal file explorer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140106</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tere-terminal-file-explorer/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T23:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tere is a terminal file explorer. It is a faster alternative to using cd and ls to browse folders in your terminal.
The post tere – terminal file explorer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>