<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html</id>
    <title>Fake News Site</title>
    <updated>2025-02-04T12:31:17.324Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://jacquesfunk.github.io/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gum – tool for glamorous shell scripts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141845</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gum-tool-glamorous-shell-scripts/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T10:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gum lets you leverage the power of Bubbles and Lip Gloss in your scripts and aliases without writing any Go code.
The post Gum – tool for glamorous shell scripts appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EasyOS – experimental Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141801</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/easyos-experimental-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T09:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EasyOS is an experimental Linux distribution made in Australia. While using Easy, everything happens in RAM. 
The post EasyOS – experimental Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QIV – Quick Image Viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=129</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/qiv/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T08:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Image Viewer (QIV) is a very small and pretty fast open source gdk/imlib image viewer.
The post QIV – Quick Image Viewer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flow State Ep. 263: Ghostly Label Edit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-ep-263-ghostly-label-edit</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/flow-state-ep-263-ghostly-label-edit"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T08:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s mix is all music from Ghostly International in honor of their recent reissue of Studio’s 2006 record, West Coast. Thanks to Sam Valenti IV for the assistance (check out his newsletter, Herb Sundays]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minisign – sign files and verify signatures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141772</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/minisign-sign-files-verify-signatures/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T23:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minisign is a very simple tool to sign files and verify digital signatures.
The post Minisign – sign files and verify signatures appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emails Show How Saints Leadership Offered To Help Local Clergy With Damage Control Amid Sexual Abuse Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180355</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/saints-pelicans-clergy-abuse-emails-released"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T22:04:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just how much help did the leadership of the Saints and Pelicans provide to the archdiocese of New Orleans as it was forced to acknowledge its own role covering up sexual abuse for decades amid in the global Catholic church sex abuse crisis? Four news outlets—WWL Louisiana, The Guardian, the Associated Press, and The New York Times—fought for the release of emails between local Catholic leadership and the Saints. The emails were first obtained through a clergy abuse lawsuit brought against the archdiocese, but the Saints and the church wanted them kept private. The Saints and the church lost their court battle, and recently the four news outlets were finally given copies of the emails.
All four outlets wrote about what they discovered and published stories Monday; each report is worth your time. If one thing is made clear from the emails that were released, it is how easy it is for one powerful organization, when in crisis, to turn to another for help, and receive it with few questions asked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Moskovitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beef-Ending Trade Of J.T. Miller Leaves Vancouver Sports Media With Nothing To Talk About]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180323</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/j-t-miller-elias-pettersson-canucks-beef-update"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T21:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The only way forward seemed to be for the Canucks to get rid of either Miller or Pettersson, and indeed that's what happened: Miller was traded to the Rangers on Friday evening. Let’s see how they got there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No But Seriously, Why Did The Mavericks Trade Luka?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180324</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/no-but-seriously-why-did-the-mavericks-trade-luka-doncic"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T20:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty much right away, late on Saturday night when the Luka Doncic trade was first announced, I was convinced there had to be something wrong. Not just that I thought Shams was hacked—which I did—but even after we found out it was legit. Not to get all conspiracy-brained, but none of it passed the smell test, and it didn't help that various commentators seemed to have the same talking points explaining the trade, all of it revolving around Luka Doncic being so fat that when he sits down, he swallows the whole arena, or something. There is just no way to convince me that "conditioning" is why the Mavericks had to trade a 25-year-old superstar that just took them to the Finals last season. To that end, I would like to dissect some of the talking points.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Israel Daramola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Times Call For More Trade Chaos]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180334</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/these-times-call-for-more-trade-chaos"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T18:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can say it with some certainty now: whoever thought that the NBA trade deadline would work best when fit into Superb Owl Week is a genius. Assuming politics in the league office work as they do in every other corporate structure, with credit flowing upward towards the Monopoly Guy reclining in the fattest chair, that would make Adam Silver a super-genius.
And credit where it’s due: it worked. Nothing else could have kept us from our preordained position—face down in the gutter, licking up the two main themes of this championship week, the referees taking a knee for the Chiefs, and Patrick Mahomes Legacy Talk. Nothing else would have elevated our attention beyond the please-just-play-the-stinking-game-now mantra that hits like clockwork on Big Game Thursday. Nothing else would have spared us from the ceaseless bleating of the Owl Nobody Wanted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Ratto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[17 Best Free and Open Source GUI Matrix Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=75460</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-matrix-clients/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T18:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matrix is an open standard for interoperable, decentralised, real-time communication over IP.  Here's our recommended free and open source GUI Matrix clients.
The post 17 Best Free and Open Source GUI Matrix Clients appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mirage – fast and simple GTK+ image viewer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141908</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/mirage-fast-simple-gtk-image-viewer/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T18:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mirage is a fast and simple GTK+ image viewer which only depends on PyGTK.
The post Mirage – fast and simple GTK+ image viewer appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Jhon Durán Ever Be Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180043</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/will-jhon-duran-ever-be-back"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T16:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friday afternoon saw the official announcement of the latest coup Saudi Arabia has struck against the traditional soccer establishment. Jhon Durán, Aston Villa's impossibly cool backup striker, is headed to Saudi Pro League club Al-Nassr, which has acquired the Colombian's services for a reported transfer fee of €77 million. The move is just the latest escalation of an ongoing trend that has seen dozens of legitimately top-level talents eschew Europe's big leagues in favor of Saudi Arabia's big bucks. Like all those other moves, this one sucks ass.
The word "unprecedented" has already been attached to several previous transfers into the SPL, but it needs to be trotted out once again to describe the Durán move. This one's a lot like the Gabri Veiga transfer, only much, much more significant. Veiga was (and I guess still is?) a young prospect with genuine potential to one day reach the elite of the elite, but was not yet of serious interest to the top clubs as anything other than a flier. Durán, in contrast, has already gotten the big boys' tongues wagging. He's proven his scoring prowess in the best league in the world. He's played, and played well, in the Champions League. He's probably the single best U23 striker prospect in the world. West Ham and Chelsea both came close to signing him last summer, and his star has only risen since then. Aston Villa didn't hesitate to slap down the £57 million bid West Ham sent for Durán about a week ago, no doubt expecting that in a mere matter of months even bigger clubs—the likes of Chelsea, Paris Saint-Germain, and Barcelona have all reportedly been keeping a close eye on him—would come offering even bigger money. Anyone who pays attention to this stuff would've predicted that, by this time next year, Durán would have been either the face of Aston Villa's attack or the splashy new signing of one of Europe's perennial contenders. Veiga could've maybe, eventually gotten to where Durán is now, right on the doorstep of the soccer elite. And yet Durán, like Veiga, turned away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Haisley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cade Cunningham Will Beat You Up]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180232</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cade-cunningham-will-beat-you-up"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T16:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luka Doncic spent his final game as a Dallas Maverick on the bench watching a coronation and a tribute act. Days after Cade Cunningham was named an all-star for the first time, Adam Silver came to Detroit to chat about the possibility of WNBA expansion, toast Cunningham, and join the besweatpantsed Laker-to-be in watching the newly minted all-star throw down a Doncic-esque 40-pointer. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BQ1b-ZVQaNE]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Redford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crossword, Feb. 3: Space Jam]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180315</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-crossword-feb-3-space-jam"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the crossword. This week's puzzle was constructed by Shannon Rapp and Will Eisenberg, and edited by Hoang-Kim Vu. Shannon is a research administrator at Washington University in St. Louis. Will is a French horn player and music teacher in the Twin Cities. As a constructing duo, they've collaborated for every branch of AVCX and many other venues. They enjoy visiting new places, dining well, and solving and making crosswords together.
Defector crosswords, launched in partnership with our friends at AVCX, run every Monday. If you’re interested in submitting a puzzle to us, you can read our guidelines HERE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Apple Universal Control]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141833</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-alternatives-apple-universal-control/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T15:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Universal Control is software which lets you use the keyboard and mouse to control up to two other nearby Mac or iPad devices.
The post Best Free and Open Source Alternatives to Apple Universal Control appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drawing – simple image editor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141902</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/drawing-simple-image-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T15:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drawing is a basic raster image editor is similar to Microsoft Paint, but aiming at the GNOME desktop. 
The post Drawing – simple image editor appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s A Supercut Of Groundhog Day In Punxsutawney]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180291</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/heres-a-supercut-of-groundhog-day-in-punxsutawney"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T14:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday was Groundhog Day, the annual weirdo holiday where weather-prediction rodents and other animals come out of hibernation and pretend to tell us what the weather will be like over the next few weeks; people stand around and cheer while this happens. I do not understand any of this and I am sure I never will. But that does not mean I don't like it.
Two years ago, Quebec meteorologist/rodent Fred la Marmotte was found dead on the morning of Groundhog Day; he had likely died the previous year. But organizers in Val-d’Espoir went along with the ceremony anyway, announcing “la mor du Fred” to the crowd right before he was to make his prediction. A new Fred made it to Feb. 2 this year and said we’d get six more weeks of winter, though the CBC reports that Canada's weather oracles were at odds: Lucy the Lobster, Shubenacadie Sam, and Fred agreed, but Wiarton Willie said we’d get an early spring. Soon, these predictions will cost 25 percent more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan McQuade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Winters ugly return (MON-2/3)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3812565</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-winters-ugly-return-mon-2-3/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T14:27:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, our January to February thaw is almost done. One more day from KC of nice and mild temperatures before the step down to colder wintry weather commences. Yesterday was phenomenal with highs in the lower 60s, and today will follow suit -- maybe even cracking 70° farther south of the Metro. A cold front [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arsenal Did To Manchester City What Manchester City Used To Do To Everyone Else]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180233</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/arsenal-did-to-manchester-city-what-manchester-city-used-to-do-to-everyone-else"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T14:02:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This version of Manchester City must hate the entirety of North London. After losing 4-0 to Tottenham back in November, and the subsequent run of bad form that followed, City went into Arsenal's home ground on Sunday riding a bit of a high, relatively speaking. Though it had choked away a 2-0 lead to Paris Saint-Germain in the second-to-last Champions League league phase match, City has actually been on a bit of an upswing recently, winning six of its last eight matches across all competitions. In its most-recent match, a must-win against Club Brugge, City gave up the opener but ended up winning convincingly 3-1, thanks to a steady and ruthless second half. While I wouldn't have said that City is all the way back to its world-conquering ways, I wouldn't have been shocked if it went into North London and beat Arsenal, something it had done 12 times in a row in Premier League play between 2017 and 2023.
That being said, I am also not shocked at how the match actually went, as Arsenal played the most brutal of hosts—eat your heart out, Walder Frey—and stomped on City's slowly reanimating corpse to the tune of 5-1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[grype – vulnerability scanner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141818</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/grype-vulnerability-scanner/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T12:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[grype is a vulnerability scanner for container images and filesystems. 
The post grype – vulnerability scanner appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clear Linux OS – Linux distribution optimized for performance and security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141795</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/clear-linux-os-linux-distribution-optimized-performance-security/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T09:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clear Linux OS is an open source, rolling release Linux distribution optimized for performance and security.
The post Clear Linux OS – Linux distribution optimized for performance and security appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternatives to popular CLI tools: grep]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=105280</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/alternatives-popular-cli-tools-grep/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T08:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article spotlights alternative tools to grep, a utility that searches for patterns in each file.
The post Alternatives to popular CLI tools: grep appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chick Corea & Béla Fleck]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/chick-corea-and-bela-fleck</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/chick-corea-and-bela-fleck"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T08:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re listening to Chick Corea & Béla Fleck, an American pianist and American banjoist, respectively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[bower – curses frontend for the Notmuch email system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141809</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/bower-curses-frontend-notmuch-email/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T07:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[bower is a curses frontend for the Notmuch email system. There are two main views: the index, and the combined thread/pager.
The post bower – curses frontend for the Notmuch email system appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stromatolites]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3046/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3046/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Other Competitive Balance Round Draft Picks Could Be Traded This Winter?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840183</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/02/what-other-competitive-balance-round-draft-picks-could-be-traded-this-winter.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T04:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Competitive Balance Rounds are a pair of bonus rounds within the MLB draft, designed to give an extra pick to the game’s smaller-market teams.  Teams that fall within either the bottom 10 in revenues and market size are eligible, and since 2017, the league determined the eligible teams based on a formula involving market…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Polishuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Witch Hunt]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180125</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/the-witch-hunt"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T01:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of January the president sat impatient on a Zoom call from his garish, gilded estate in Florida, slumped and flustered as his lawyer idled next to him. Even his makeup reflected the mood, with his face daubed to a dull flaxen hue instead of his typical defiant goldenrod. Whatever it was that Judge Juan Merchan was saying from his courtroom in New York during Donald Trump's sentencing that day faded into a dull whistling sound. When the time finally came for him to speak, Trump strung together the same phrases he has uttered every time the subject of his criminal history comes into question. He had suffered an "injustice," been through a "very terrible experience," before landing on one of his favorites: "It's been a political witch hunt." Persecuted and yet unbound, 10 days later the convicted felon was re-inaugurated to the most powerful political office on earth.
I've been thinking of this moment a lot in the last two weeks as Trump, or his cadres of sycophants and sympathetic oligarchs and associated corps of sunlight-deprived grifters, have set about dismantling the American project with the speed and enthusiasm of a contestant on Supermarket Sweep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Way – code snippets manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141720</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/the-way-code-snippets-manager/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T23:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[the-way is a terminal-based code snippets manager.Record and retrieve snippets you use every day, or occasionally, without starting a browser.
The post The Way – code snippets manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland Moves Toward Historic Rugby Three-peat While Humiliating Failed Imperialist Nation Where Rugby Was Invented]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180247</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/ireland-defeats-england-rugby-six-nations-2025"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T22:32:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody has ever won three consecutive outright titles in the Six Nations Championship. That’s a rather stupendous stat, considering that this annual round-robin affair for Europe’s top national rugby teams, which kicked off this weekend, dates all the way back to the nineteenth century. But maybe this is the year: Ireland, the reigning two-time defending champs, took a step toward history on Saturday night in Dublin by pounding England, 27-22, in the opening round of the 2025 tournament. Don’t be fooled by the final score: A pair of garbage-time tries from England covered up Ireland’s actual dominance. 
Heading into the matchup against its most despised rival on and off the pitch, Ireland is currently ranked second in the world (behind only South Africa) and has the highest-rated squad in this year’s all-Euro Six Nations field.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pygments – generic syntax highlighter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141756</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/pygments-generic-syntax-highlighter/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T21:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pygments is a generic syntax highlighter suitable for use in code hosting, forums, wikis or other applications.
The post Pygments – generic syntax highlighter appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can’t Be Headbutting Dudes On The Basketball Court]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180236</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/you-cant-be-headbutting-dudes-on-the-basketball-court"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T20:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With just under three minutes left, Arizona pulled away from Arizona State to win the Grand Canyon-adjacent rivalry game, 81-72, on Saturday. It had been a sleepy start to the game, with both teams combining to hit a mere 23 shots and commit 19 fouls in the first half. Basheer Jihad kicked some life into the Sun Devils at the beginning of the second half with a pair of dunks and a three-pointer to grab a five-point lead. Alas, it was not meant to be. Caleb Love, last seen hitting a ridiculous half court three to force overtime on way to a win against Iowa State Monday night, led the comeback hitting multiple threes as the Wildcats went on a run.
Things were almost wrapped up with about 30 seconds left on the clock when Love was jawing with Arizona State's BJ Freeman under the hoop during an out of bounds play and, well, Freeman replied ... headfirst. Both were ejected, and Arizona State Coach Bobby Hurley yanked his team from the floor as the final buzzer sounded, bypassing the handshake line and customary pleasantries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kryptor – simple, modern, and secure file encryption and signing tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141727</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/kryptor-file-encryption-signing-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T19:27:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kryptor lets you encrypt multiple files/directories with a passphrase, symmetric key, or asymmetric keys.
The post Kryptor – simple, modern, and secure file encryption and signing tool appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docfd – TUI multiline fuzzy document finder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141732</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/docfd-tui-multiline-fuzzy-document-finder/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T17:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docfd is a text user interface  multiline fuzzy document finder written in OCaml.
The post Docfd – TUI multiline fuzzy document finder appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black – Python code formatter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141747</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/black-python-code-formatter/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T17:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Black is an uncompromising PEP 8 compliant opinionated formatter.
The post Black – Python code formatter appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mavericks Send Luka Doncic To The Lakers In Trade Best Described With Unhinged Obscenities]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180199</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/mavericks-lakers-doncic-trade"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T17:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nah, April Fools' Day didn’t come two months early. It’s all true: The Dallas Mavericks really are trading Markieff Morris to the Los Angeles Lakers. The deal reportedly also includes Maxi Kleber and, um, Luka Doncic?
Luka Doncic? Future-of-the-sport Luka Doncic? Once-in-a-lifetime-talent, face-of-the-franchise Luka Doncic? Dallas dumped that guy? Get the hell outta here!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[18 Best Free and Open Source Linux Astronomy Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=4452</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/astronomy/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T16:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article focuses on selecting the best free astronomy software available for Linux.
The post 18 Best Free and Open Source Linux Astronomy Apps appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uruk Linux – full free, simple and lightweight distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141701</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/uruk-linux-full-free-simple-lightweight-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T09:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uruk Linux is billed as a fully free, simple, and lightweight operating system for home users, small enterprises and educational centers.
The post Uruk Linux – full free, simple and lightweight distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[massCode – code snippets manager for developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141668</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/masscode-code-snippets-manager-developers/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-02T06:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[massCode is a code snippets manager.  It helps you create and organize your own personal snippet collection and have quick access to it.
The post massCode – code snippets manager for developers appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bats – Bash Automated Testing System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141770</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/bats-bash-automated-testing-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-01T17:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bats is a TAP-compliant testing framework. It provides a simple way to verify that the UNIX programs you write behave as expected.
The post Bats – Bash Automated Testing System appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[22 Best Free and Open Source Terminal-Based Linux Calculators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=108117</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-terminal-based-linux-calculators/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-01T16:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the basic utilities supplied with any operating system is the calculator.  We recommend the finest terminal-based calculators.
The post 22 Best Free and Open Source Terminal-Based Linux Calculators appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prism – lightweight, extensible syntax highlighter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141753</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/prism-lightweight-extensible-syntax-highlighter/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-01T16:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prism is a lightweight, extensible syntax highlighter, built with modern web standards in mind. It’s used in millions of websites
The post Prism – lightweight, extensible syntax highlighter appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eilidih Parris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Free and Open Source Software: January 2025 Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=140724</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-software-january-2025-updates/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-01T11:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 2025 updates to the largest compilation of recommended free and open source software available for Linux.
The post Best Free and Open Source Software: January 2025 Updates appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[wat – instant, central, community-built docs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141654</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/wat-instant-central-community-built-docs/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-01T09:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wat is an interactive app built to drastically reduce time spent searching for syntax and code usage questions. 
The post wat – instant, central, community-built docs appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tiny Desktop Linux – mini desktop oriented Linux distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141695</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/tiny-desktop-linux-mini-desktop-oriented-linux-distribution/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-01T08:47:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tiny Desktop Linux (TDL) tries to revive the legendary and original DSL. This one is based on Tiny Core 15
The post Tiny Desktop Linux – mini desktop oriented Linux distribution appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kleopatra – KDE tool for managing X.509 and OpenPGP certificates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141673</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/kleopatra-kde-tool-managing-x509-openpgp-certificates/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-01T07:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kleopatra is the KDE tool for managing X.509 and OpenPGP certificates in the GpgSM and GPG keyboxes and for retrieving certificates.
The post Kleopatra – KDE tool for managing X.509 and OpenPGP certificates appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Made Three-Year Offer To Santander Before Jays Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840062</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/01/royals-made-three-year-offer-to-santander-before-jays-deal.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-01T02:24:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals have been searching for a middle-of-the-order bat throughout the offseason. Anthony Santander was evidently one such target. Ken Rosenthal of The Athletic reports that Kansas City made Santander a three-year, $66MM offer that included unspecified deferrals and would’ve allowed him to opt out after the second season. Of course, Santander declined that proposal in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Designate Braden Shewmake For Assignment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=840046</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/01/royals-designate-braden-shewmake-for-assignment.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-01T00:43:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals announced that they’ve designated infielder Braden Shewmake for assignment. That opens a 40-man roster spot for reliever Carlos Estévez, who inked a two-year free agent deal. Shewmake was claimed off waivers from the White Sox a few weeks ago. He’d spent one season with Chicago, who acquired him from the Braves as part of the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Franco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Royals Sign Carlos Estévez]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/?p=839760</id>
        <link href="https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2025/01/royals-to-sign-carlos-estevez.html"/>
        <updated>2025-02-01T00:24:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Royals and right-hander Carlos Estévez are in agreement on a two-year deal that comes with a club option for 2027. It’s reportedly a $22MM guarantee for the Premier Talent Sports and Entertainment client, which includes a $2MM buyout on the option valued at $13MM. If the Royals exercise the option, the deal would reach…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darragh McDonald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[xfce4-taskmanager – monitor system resources]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141577</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/xfce4-taskmanager-monitor-system-resources/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T23:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xfce4-taskmanager is an easy to use task manager.
The post xfce4-taskmanager – monitor system resources appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Look For The Helpers]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180188</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/look-for-the-helpers"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T23:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Margin of Error, a politics column from Tom Scocca, editor of the Indignity newsletter, examining the apocalyptic politics, coverage, and consequences of Campaign 2024.
Everyone knows what Donald Trump is and what his administration is doing. Before he got up in front of the cameras and blamed the deadly midair collision between an Army helicopter and a passenger jet on diversity hiring, and before his vice president got up in front of those cameras and specifically argued that if a white person had contributed to the crash, it was because they were under the strain of working with unqualified minorities, there was his opening salvo of Jan. 6 pardons paired with the executive order denying the 14th Amendment's guarantee of birthright citizenship. And then the executive order calling trans identity a "falsehood" and saying it "is not consistent with the humility and selflessness" required for military service. And the executive order mandating "patriotic education" for primary and secondary schools built around the "celebration of America’s greatness and history." And the memo ordering the Department of Transportation to "give preference to communities with marriage and birth rates higher than the national average." And the unlawful and unconstitutional cutoff of federal grant spending, and the mass firing of the inspectors general, and the mass firing of the prosecutors who'd investigated Trump's previous apparent crimes, and—there was much more than that, and they've tacked on still more of it since the press conference, and anyone who claims to see anything in it other than intentional, comprehensive misrule by sadists and criminals and bigots is someone who is helping to bring it about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Scocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laura Stacey Has No Rust To Shake Off]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180137</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/laura-stacey-has-no-rust-to-shake-off"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T20:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the cooler things an athlete can do is return from injury with an “I’ve still got it” game. What a relief, a pleasant surprise. Fans kindly set the bar low—maybe she'll need a few days to get to full speed, no pressure—and then she clears it by a mile, reminding those fans just how much they’ve missed her. In the case of Laura Stacey, who hadn’t dressed for first-place Montreal’s past three games because of a lower-body injury, Victoire fans weren’t the only ones setting the bar low. When the team posted lines before Thursday night's home game against struggling rival Toronto, Stacey was listed on a line by herself, as a 13th forward. Surely, she was still working her way back.  
But Laura Stacey isn't one for seeing how it goes. The tireless power forward always plays like she’s making up for lost time. After last night, consider those missed games made up for. In the Victoire’s 4-3 shootout win, Stacey set up every Montreal goal herself and finished with three points in a decidedly un-13th forward-like 20 minutes of ice time. The win kept Montreal at the top of the PWHL standings as the league heads into next week's international break.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maitreyi Anantharaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cruelty, Hype, And The American Way In Harry Stein’s Baseball Novel ‘Hoopla’]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=179932</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/cruelty-hype-and-the-american-way-in-harry-steins-baseball-novel-hoopla"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T16:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A line about the experience of reading, possibly first spoken by the young actor Zoe Colletti in the 2019 film adaptation of Scary Stories to Tell in the Dark, is that you don’t read a book, the book reads you. Applied to something other than haunted books, which was Colletti’s usage, the statement suggests that because each reader brings their unique point of view to a work of art, our experience of that book reveals something not just about the work but about ourselves. We find our own preoccupations loose in the pages of works that couldn’t possibly have taken notice of them. This is what makes reading fun.
In this way, it is entirely reasonable that Hoopla, Harry Stein’s 1983 baseball novel about demagoguery framed around the Black Sox conspiracy to throw the 1919 World Series in service to gamblers, seems very much like a work about the present moment. It’s a book that says very little of importance about baseball, but which does a great job of explaining how a country might come to find itself spending the better part of a decade as (mostly) unwilling participants in the Donald Trump Extended Universe. Hoopla depicts an America in which news and entertainment have become so thoroughly muddled and cynical that stories derived from human pleasure and pain, fortune and misfortune, have value only insofar as they can be torqued so as to serve one agenda or another. Truth still exists in this world, but it doesn’t really matter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Goldman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ohkami – intuitive and declarative web framework]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141600</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/ohkami-intuitive-and-declarative-web-framework/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T15:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ohkami is an intuitive and declarative web framework for Rust.
The post Ohkami – intuitive and declarative web framework appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Have Strong Feelings About The Use Of Limp Bizkit’s “Rollin’ (Air Raid Vehicle)” In The Opening Credits To This Netflix Video Game Anime]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180127</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/i-have-strong-feelings-about-the-use-of-limp-bizkits-rollin-air-raid-vehicle-in-the-opening-credits-to-this-netflix-video-game-anime"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T15:42:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hate to give Netflix credit for anything, anything at all, but I will power through: The streaming service has carved out a pretty decent niche for itself as the home of passable-to-good video game anime adaptations. Starting with 2017's Castlevania, a great show completely ruined by horrific allegations against its creator, and continuing with Arcane: League of Legends, Cyberpunk: Edgerunners, and Castlevania: Nocturne—now with less horrible creators, I hope—the network has a solid enough pedigree to get me to check out shows based on games that I don't particularly care about.
Enter Devil May Cry, a game series I almost entirely missed save for its fourth installment in 2008, which serves as the basis for a new anime coming out on April 3. The network teased the opening credit sequence for the adaptation on Thursday, and for a game series that started in 2001, the show leans into the era by picking a recognizable nu metal song as the backing track. Unfortunately, the song is Limp Bizkit's "Rollin' (Air Raid Vehicle)".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Paez-Pumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘A Different Man’ Has Sebastian Stan At His Most Alluring]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180040</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/a-different-man-has-sebastian-stan-at-his-most-alluring"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T15:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever you think of Sebastian Stan, it’s hard not to look at him and immediately think: Well, I mean, he’s beautiful. Because, conventional or not—with his square jaw and Rossetti lips and little nose and cleft chin and blue eyes and thick straight hair and straight white teeth—Sebastian Stan is beautiful. What must it be like to walk through the world looking like that? It must do something to the way you move, the way you talk, the way you make decisions. Maybe there’s nothing to think about when it’s all you’ve known. But Stan has talked enough about struggling with his identity as a Romanian immigrant for the thought not to have occurred to him: the strangeness of everyone welcoming you in even when you are uncertain who you even are.
Considering his bold looks in films like I, Tonya…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soraya Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Battle of the air masses into February (FRI-1/31)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3809834</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/weather/weather-blog/joes-blog-battle-of-the-air-masses-into-february-fri-1-31/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T15:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're going to start February on a mild note with plenty of 50s on the way into early next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe's Blog: Battle of the air masses into February (FRI-1/31)]]></title>
        <id>https://fox4kc.com/?p=3809834</id>
        <link href="https://fox4kc.com/email-alerts/joes-weather-blog-email-alerts/joes-blog-battle-of-the-air-masses-into-february-fri-1-31/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T15:10:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're going to finish the month about 5° below average (give or take) a bit as temperatures for today will be into the mid to upper 40s during the afternoon. At one point this month we were down to about 8° below average so we've made up a big of ground in the last 10 [...]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Lauria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“It Changes Everything”: What Canada’s New Women’s Soccer League Means To Two Of Its Players]]></title>
        <id>https://defector.com/?p=180114</id>
        <link href="https://defector.com/it-changes-everything-what-canadas-new-womens-soccer-league-means-to-two-of-its-players"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T14:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just over two years ago, Diana Matheson announced formal plans to create a professional women's soccer league in Canada. Matheson, who racked up 206 caps for the Canadian national team in her career of nearly two decades, was the first to pursue what is usually a given in countries with successful national teams: a domestic incubator for top talent. But the Canadian national team, which won Olympic gold in 2021, has almost exclusively relied on foreign leagues to develop elite players. 
In the months since Matheson's efforts went public the Northern Super League, as it's now known, has released a final list of its six participating cities and committed to an April 2025 kickoff; it also, in October 2024, announced a standard player agreement which looks a lot like the NWSL's hard-fought 2024 collective bargaining agreement. It precludes a player draft, prohibits trades without player consent, and grants automatic free-agency at the end of contracts. It also guarantees a minimum salary of 50,000 CAD—about 36,500 U.S. dollars in 2024. Teams across the NSL have announced some splashy signings: CANXNT standout Quinn, newly un-retired Desiree Scott, and veteran goalkeeper Erin McLeod.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abigail Segel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nick Silvio carries the flames from serving on KCFD to the Hawg Jaw Que & Brew smoker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thepitchkc.com/?p=868431</id>
        <link href="https://www.thepitchkc.com/nick-silvio-carries-the-flames-from-serving-on-kcfd-to-the-hawg-jaw-que-brew-smoker/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T14:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Irish Hawg. // Photo Courtesy of Hawg Jaw Que & Brew Creating delicious barbecue requires a lot of different skills outside of a deft hand at flavor: Patience, endurance, experience, and decisiveness are all part of the special sauce to make tender brisket or mouthwatering pulled pork. Who better to call in than a firefighter? Nick Silvio has served on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan Baranowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[agg – asciinema gif generator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141602</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/agg-asciinema-gif-generator/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T12:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[agg is a command-line tool for generating animated GIF files from terminal session recordings.
The post agg – asciinema gif generator appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Best Free and Open Source Terminal-Based Matrix Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141678</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-terminal-based-matrix-clients/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T11:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This roundup features the finest terminal-based Matrix clients. Only free and open source software is eligible for inclusion.
The post 5 Best Free and Open Source Terminal-Based Matrix Clients appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City welcomed Baba's Pantry with open arms. A bakery now shows off Palestinian treats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-01-31/babas-pantry-bakery-kansas-city-palestinian-food</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/arts-life/2025-01-31/babas-pantry-bakery-kansas-city-palestinian-food"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After their cafe was named one of 2022's best new restaurants by Bon Appetit magazine, the Kamal family is expanding its dessert and pastry offerings next door, at Baba's Bakery. It's now open on Saturdays, and there are plans to expand hours by March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Celisa Calacal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gisto – code snippet manager]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141663</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/gisto-code-snippet-manager/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T10:07:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gisto is a code snippet manager that runs on GitHub Gists and adds additional features such as searching, tagging and sharing gists 
The post Gisto – code snippet manager appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kansas City's new Palestinian bakery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.kcur.org/podcast/kansas-city-today/2025-01-31/kansas-citys-new-palestinian-bakery</id>
        <link href="https://www.kcur.org/podcast/kansas-city-today/2025-01-31/kansas-citys-new-palestinian-bakery"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fans of the desserts at Baba’s Pantry will get to try even more sweet treats in a new, dedicated space right next door. After Kansas City embraced their Palestinian deli, the Kamal family is expanding with Baba's Bakery, which they call a "labor of love."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nomin Ujiyediin, Byron J. Love</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Best Free and Open Source Text-Based Git Clients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=84829</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/best-free-open-source-text-based-git-clients/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T08:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our recommended text-based Git clients, captured in a legendary LinuxLinks chart. We only feature free and open source software here.
The post 8 Best Free and Open Source Text-Based Git Clients appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Taffy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.flowstate.fm/p/black-taffy</id>
        <link href="https://www.flowstate.fm/p/black-taffy"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T08:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Friday so we’re listening to something slightly more upbeat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flow State</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Damn Small Linux – Linux distro for older hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?p=141583</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/damn-small-linux-linux-distro-older-hardware/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T07:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New DSL is a compact Linux distribution tailored for low-spec x86 computers. It packs a lot of applications into a small package. 
The post Damn Small Linux – Linux distro for older hardware appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Karlsson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21 Best Free and Open Source Linux Graphical Calculators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.linuxlinks.com/?page_id=2932</id>
        <link href="https://www.linuxlinks.com/calculators/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T06:04:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the basic utilities supplied with any operating system is a desktop calculator. We cover the best graphical tools.
The post 21 Best Free and Open Source Linux Graphical Calculators appeared first on LinuxLinks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Emms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlphaMove]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/3045/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/3045/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>